<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	
	xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
	xmlns:geo="http://www.w3.org/2003/01/geo/wgs84_pos#"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Memes Archives - Blockonomi</title>
	<atom:link href="https://blockonomi.com/memes/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://blockonomi.com/memes/</link>
	<description>Cryptocurrency News &#38; Your Guide to the Blockchain Economy</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 11:14:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.7.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/fav-50x50.png</url>
	<title>Memes Archives - Blockonomi</title>
	<link>https://blockonomi.com/memes/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
<site xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">134176212</site>	<item>
		<title>POPCAT ($POP) Price: Shows Rising Momentum as Bulls Defend Critical $1 Level</title>
		<link>https://blockonomi.com/popcat-pop-price-shows-rising-momentum-as-bulls-defend-critical-1-level/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Oliver Dale]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 11:14:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blockonomi.com/?p=108032</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>TLDR POPCAT has found strong buyer support at the $1 level, showing resilience after a recent pullback The 4-hour RSI indicates increasing buyer momentum as it moves out of oversold territory toward 50% 1-day RSI shows selling pressure decreasing with a reversal trend from 40% level Key resistance levels to watch are the 100-day SMA [...]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/popcat-pop-price-shows-rising-momentum-as-bulls-defend-critical-1-level/">POPCAT ($POP) Price: Shows Rising Momentum as Bulls Defend Critical $1 Level</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>TLDR</h2>
<ul>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">POPCAT has found strong buyer support at the $1 level, showing resilience after a recent pullback</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">The 4-hour RSI indicates increasing buyer momentum as it moves out of oversold territory toward 50%</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">1-day RSI shows selling pressure decreasing with a reversal trend from 40% level</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Key resistance levels to watch are the 100-day SMA and $1.50 mark</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Current trading price is $1.20 with next support at $0.80 if bullish momentum fades</li>
</ul>
<hr />
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words"><a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/popcat-holds-firm-at-1-support/">POPCAT&#8217;s price has established firm support at the $1 level, marking a potential turning point for the token after its recent market pullback.</a> Trading data from the past 24 hours shows increased buying activity as the price stabilizes and begins showing signs of upward momentum.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The digital asset, currently trading at $1.20, has attracted renewed buyer interest after testing the crucial dollar support level. Market data indicates a steady increase in trading volume, with buyers stepping in to defend the price floor established at $1.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Technical analysis of the 4-hour chart reveals improving market conditions for POPCAT. The Relative Strength Index (RSI), a key momentum indicator, has moved out of oversold territory and is approaching the 50% level. This movement suggests growing buyer confidence and could signal the start of a new upward trend.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Looking at the daily timeframe, the RSI shows a notable reversal from the 40% level, indicating that selling pressure may be easing. This technical indicator&#8217;s recovery provides additional evidence that market sentiment could be shifting in favor of buyers.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The token&#8217;s price action around the $1 support level has caught the attention of traders and market participants. Data from multiple exchanges shows increasing bid orders near this price point, suggesting strong buyer interest in accumulating POPCAT at current levels.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Trading volumes have seen an uptick during this period of price stabilization. Exchange data reveals a 24-hour trading volume of over $10 million, showing active market participation as traders position themselves for potential future price movements.</p>
<figure id="attachment_108034" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-108034" style="width: 847px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-108034" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-12-at-11-13-05-Popcat-Price-POPCAT-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko.png" alt="Popcat Price on CoinGecko" width="847" height="631" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-12-at-11-13-05-Popcat-Price-POPCAT-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko.png 847w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-12-at-11-13-05-Popcat-Price-POPCAT-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko-300x223.png 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-12-at-11-13-05-Popcat-Price-POPCAT-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko-768x572.png 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-12-at-11-13-05-Popcat-Price-POPCAT-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko-50x37.png 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-12-at-11-13-05-Popcat-Price-POPCAT-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko-150x112.png 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-12-at-11-13-05-Popcat-Price-POPCAT-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko-450x335.png 450w" sizes="(max-width: 847px) 100vw, 847px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-108034" class="wp-caption-text">Popcat Price on <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/popcat">CoinGecko</a></figcaption></figure>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The current market structure shows several resistance levels that POPCAT needs to overcome for continued upward movement. The first major hurdle lies at the 100-day Simple Moving Average, which has historically served as a key technical reference point for the token&#8217;s price action.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Beyond the moving average, the $1.50 price level represents the next major resistance zone. This level previously acted as support during earlier trading periods and now serves as a target for bulls looking to push the price higher.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Market order books show concentrated seller interest around these resistance levels. However, the gradual accumulation of buy orders at current prices suggests traders are preparing for potential upward price movements.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The token&#8217;s price behavior has maintained a pattern of higher lows since finding support, indicating growing buyer conviction. This technical pattern often precedes larger price moves, though market conditions can change rapidly.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">If POPCAT fails to maintain its current price levels, the next support zone lies at $0.80. This level aligns with previous trading ranges and could serve as a secondary support if market sentiment weakens.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Short-term price action shows consolidation above the $1 mark, with decreasing volatility as the market establishes a new base. Trading ranges have tightened in recent hours, often a predecessor to larger price movements.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Exchange data reveals an increase in wallet addresses holding POPCAT, suggesting growing distributed ownership of the token. This metric often indicates longer-term holder conviction, though it doesn&#8217;t guarantee future price appreciation.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Recent trading patterns show declining sell-side pressure compared to previous weeks. Order flow data indicates more balanced trading activity, with buy and sell orders reaching closer to equilibrium.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The most recent market data shows POPCAT trading at $1.20, maintaining its position above the crucial $1 support level as traders watch for further signs of price direction.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/popcat-pop-price-shows-rising-momentum-as-bulls-defend-critical-1-level/">POPCAT ($POP) Price: Shows Rising Momentum as Bulls Defend Critical $1 Level</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">108032</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dogecoin (DOGE) Price: Maintains $0.40 Support Level Despite $86M Liquidation Event</title>
		<link>https://blockonomi.com/dogecoin-doge-price-maintains-0-40-support-level-despite-86m-liquidation-event/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Oliver Dale]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2024 11:38:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blockonomi.com/?p=107942</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>TLDR Dogecoin maintained crucial support levels during recent market downturn $86.29 million in DOGE long positions were liquidated on December 9 Price held strong at $0.40 despite market-wide leverage flush Funding rates reset to lower levels, potentially encouraging new buying Strong spot market activity suggests underlying bullish sentiment The cryptocurrency market experienced its largest leverage [...]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/dogecoin-doge-price-maintains-0-40-support-level-despite-86m-liquidation-event/">Dogecoin (DOGE) Price: Maintains $0.40 Support Level Despite $86M Liquidation Event</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>TLDR</h2>
<ul>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Dogecoin maintained crucial support levels during recent market downturn</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">$86.29 million in DOGE long positions were liquidated on December 9</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Price held strong at $0.40 despite market-wide leverage flush</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Funding rates reset to lower levels, potentially encouraging new buying</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Strong spot market activity suggests underlying bullish sentiment</li>
</ul>
<hr />
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The cryptocurrency market experienced its largest leverage flush out since April 2021 on December 9, but Dogecoin has shown remarkable stability. While many cryptocurrencies faced steep declines, <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/dogecoin/dogecoin-crypto-crash-looks-incredible/">DOGE maintained its position around the $0.40 price level, demonstrating unusual market resilience.</a></p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Data from Coinglass reveals that $86.29 million in DOGE long positions were liquidated during the market event. This represents the highest single-day liquidation volume for Dogecoin since the 2021 bull market peak, indicating the scale of the market movement.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Technical analysis of the DOGE/USDT trading pair shows that Dogecoin has maintained a crucial uptrend line on the 4-hour chart. This trend line has served as dynamic support, with the price touching but not breaking below it on three separate occasions since mid-November.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Market data indicates strong buyer interest at current levels. Each time the price has approached the trend line, it has bounced back, suggesting sustained confidence among investors during price dips. This pattern has repeated consistently through the recent market volatility.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr"><a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24DOGE&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">$DOGE</a> looks incredible </p>
<p>Whole market shat itself but it barely flinched + didn&#39;t break structure</p>
<p>Now funding has completely reset and a ton of OI has been washed out</p>
<p>Won&#39;t be long until this is trending hard again IMO <a href="https://t.co/EAaecaFu36">pic.twitter.com/EAaecaFu36</a></p>
<p>&mdash; CRG (@MacroCRG) <a href="https://twitter.com/MacroCRG/status/1866430082094411964?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">December 10, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The $0.47 price point has emerged as a key resistance level for <a href="https://moneycheck.com/best-doge-casinos/">Dogecoin</a>. Multiple tests of this level have occurred, with each attempt meeting selling pressure. These repeated tests without breakthrough suggest a consolidation phase may be underway.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Looking at market structure, the reduction in open interest in stablecoin-margined contracts presents a clearer picture of the current market dynamics. This decrease suggests a clearing out of leveraged positions and speculative traders from the market.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Funding rates have reset to lower levels following the recent market movement. This development reduces the cost associated with maintaining long positions in Dogecoin, potentially creating more favorable conditions for new market participants.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The Cumulative Volume Delta (CVD) shows an interesting divergence between futures and spot markets. The futures CVD has dropped below spot market levels, indicating different sentiment between these two market segments.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Spot market activity has remained notably strong, suggesting sustained interest from longer-term holders and investors. This contrasts with the more volatile futures market, where traders often take shorter-term positions.</p>
<figure id="attachment_107943" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-107943" style="width: 847px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-107943" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-11-at-11-34-25-Dogecoin-Price-DOGE-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko.png" alt="Dogecoin Price on CoinGecko" width="847" height="637" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-11-at-11-34-25-Dogecoin-Price-DOGE-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko.png 847w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-11-at-11-34-25-Dogecoin-Price-DOGE-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko-300x226.png 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-11-at-11-34-25-Dogecoin-Price-DOGE-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko-768x578.png 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-11-at-11-34-25-Dogecoin-Price-DOGE-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko-50x38.png 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-11-at-11-34-25-Dogecoin-Price-DOGE-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko-150x113.png 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-11-at-11-34-25-Dogecoin-Price-DOGE-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko-450x338.png 450w" sizes="(max-width: 847px) 100vw, 847px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-107943" class="wp-caption-text">Dogecoin Price on <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/dogecoin">CoinGecko</a></figcaption></figure>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Trading volume analysis reveals consistent activity at the current price levels, with spot market volumes maintaining steady levels despite the broader market volatility. This suggests ongoing interest from buyers at current price points.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The price action around the $0.40 level has formed a clear support zone, with multiple tests of this level showing strong buying pressure. This price point has become increasingly important as a reference for market participants.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Market data shows that while leveraged positions were cleared out during the recent movement, spot market holdings have remained relatively stable. This suggests that long-term holders have maintained their positions through the market volatility.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Order book analysis reveals substantial buying interest below current price levels, with notable support clusters forming around key technical levels. This suggests potential price stability even if further market pressure emerges.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Recent trading patterns show decreased volatility following the liquidation event, with price action consolidating around current levels. This stabilization period often precedes new market movements.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The current market structure shows Dogecoin trading within a defined range, with clear support and resistance levels established. At press time, DOGE trades at $0.40, maintaining its position above key technical support levels.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/dogecoin-doge-price-maintains-0-40-support-level-despite-86m-liquidation-event/">Dogecoin (DOGE) Price: Maintains $0.40 Support Level Despite $86M Liquidation Event</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">107942</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shiba Inu (SHIB) Price: Network Activity Surges with Shibarium Growth</title>
		<link>https://blockonomi.com/shiba-inu-shib-price-network-activity-surges-with-shibarium-growth/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Oliver Dale]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2024 11:21:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blockonomi.com/?p=107935</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>TLDR Shibarium Layer-2 surpassed 600 million transactions and reached 2 million total addresses Total Value Locked (TVL) hit new all-time high of $6 million Daily active addresses peaked at 12,000 on December 8th before declining below 2,000 SHIB price rose from $0.000017 in June to $0.000027 in early December Technical indicators show SHIB in uptrend [...]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/shiba-inu-shib-price-network-activity-surges-with-shibarium-growth/">Shiba Inu (SHIB) Price: Network Activity Surges with Shibarium Growth</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>TLDR</h2>
<ul>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Shibarium Layer-2 surpassed 600 million transactions and reached 2 million total addresses</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Total Value Locked (TVL) hit new all-time high of $6 million</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Daily active addresses peaked at 12,000 on December 8th before declining below 2,000</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">SHIB price rose from $0.000017 in June to $0.000027 in early December</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Technical indicators show SHIB in uptrend with support at $0.00002357</li>
</ul>
<hr />
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Shiba Inu&#8217;s Layer-2 scaling solution,<a href="https://ambcrypto.com/shiba-inu-milestone-shibarium-transactions-reach-600-mln/"> Shibarium, has reached a major milestone by exceeding 600 million total transactions,</a> marking rapid growth for the network&#8217;s infrastructure. The achievement comes alongside other key metrics showing expanded adoption of the platform.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Data from network monitoring tools confirms that Shibarium has also surpassed 2 million total addresses, indicating growing user adoption. The network saw peak activity on December 8th, when daily active addresses touched 12,000, though this metric has since declined to below 2,000 addresses.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words"><a href="https://www.shibariumscan.io/stats">The Total Value Locked (TVL) in Shibarium</a> protocols has reached a new all-time high of $6 million. This metric represents the total value of crypto assets deposited in the network&#8217;s smart contracts and serves as a key indicator of user confidence and platform utilization.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Transaction volume growth has maintained steady momentum throughout the final quarter of 2024. The network passed the 500 million transaction mark last week before quickly advancing beyond 600 million, demonstrating accelerated adoption rates.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Technical analysis of <a href="https://moneycheck.com/best-shib-casinos/">SHIB</a> price action shows correlation with Shibarium&#8217;s expanding metrics. The token price has moved from June lows of $0.000017 to December highs above $0.000027, though recent days have seen some retracement from these levels.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Current price indicators show SHIB maintaining an upward trend on daily timeframes. The 50-day moving average provides technical support at the $0.00002357 level, while the Relative Strength Index (RSI) reads 50.60, suggesting neutral momentum.</p>
<figure id="attachment_107936" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-107936" style="width: 847px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-107936" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-11-at-11-19-23-Shiba-Inu-Price-SHIB-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko.png" alt="Shiba Inu Price on CoinGecko" width="847" height="632" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-11-at-11-19-23-Shiba-Inu-Price-SHIB-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko.png 847w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-11-at-11-19-23-Shiba-Inu-Price-SHIB-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko-300x224.png 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-11-at-11-19-23-Shiba-Inu-Price-SHIB-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko-768x573.png 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-11-at-11-19-23-Shiba-Inu-Price-SHIB-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko-50x37.png 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-11-at-11-19-23-Shiba-Inu-Price-SHIB-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko-150x112.png 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-11-at-11-19-23-Shiba-Inu-Price-SHIB-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko-450x336.png 450w" sizes="(max-width: 847px) 100vw, 847px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-107936" class="wp-caption-text">Shiba Inu Price on <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/shiba-inu">CoinGecko</a></figcaption></figure>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Trading volume has seen modest decline in recent sessions, with market participants appearing to await clear direction before establishing new positions. The $0.000030 price level remains a key resistance point watched by traders.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Looking at network development, Shibarium&#8217;s growth comes from its role as a scaling solution designed to reduce transaction costs and increase processing speed. The platform enables faster and cheaper transactions compared to the main Ethereum network.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The recent surge in TVL suggests growing comfort among users in deploying assets within the Shibarium ecosystem. This metric has shown particularly strong growth in the fourth quarter, rising steadily to its current $6 million level.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Daily transaction counts have maintained consistency even as total transaction milestones are reached. This indicates sustainable user activity rather than temporary spikes driven by specific events or promotions.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Address growth metrics show both new and returning users engaging with the network. The rise to 2 million total addresses represents organic expansion of the user base over time.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Network data indicates balanced distribution between new address creation and activity from existing addresses. This pattern typically suggests healthy ecosystem development rather than concentrated usage by a small number of participants.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Technical infrastructure has demonstrated stability during the growth phase, with network uptime remaining robust as transaction volumes expanded. This performance metric supports confidence in the platform&#8217;s ability to scale.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The correlation between Shibarium&#8217;s expanding metrics and SHIB price movement has drawn market attention. Price support levels have generally held during recent consolidation phases.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Most recent data shows continued steady growth in network metrics, with transaction counts maintaining their upward trajectory as of the latest monitoring period.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/shiba-inu-shib-price-network-activity-surges-with-shibarium-growth/">Shiba Inu (SHIB) Price: Network Activity Surges with Shibarium Growth</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">107935</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dogwifhat (WIF) Price: Whale Moves 1.2M Tokens Worth $3.47M</title>
		<link>https://blockonomi.com/dogwifhat-wif-price-whale-moves-1-2m-tokens-worth-3-47m/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Oliver Dale]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2024 09:21:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blockonomi.com/?p=107878</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>TLDR Dogwifhat (WIF) whale transferred 1.2M tokens ($3.47M) to Coinbase after turning $393K into $3M profit Move comes during broader crypto market turbulence with $1.76B in recent liquidations WIF price dropped 3.5% to $2.87 after the whale&#8217;s transfer Token currently trading 41% below its all-time high of $4.85 Technical analysis suggests potential $10 price target [...]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/dogwifhat-wif-price-whale-moves-1-2m-tokens-worth-3-47m/">Dogwifhat (WIF) Price: Whale Moves 1.2M Tokens Worth $3.47M</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>TLDR</h2>
<ul>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Dogwifhat (WIF) whale transferred 1.2M tokens ($3.47M) to Coinbase after turning $393K into $3M profit</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Move comes during broader crypto market turbulence with $1.76B in recent liquidations</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">WIF price dropped 3.5% to $2.87 after the whale&#8217;s transfer</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Token currently trading 41% below its all-time high of $4.85</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Technical analysis suggests potential $10 price target by end of 2025 if key resistance levels are broken</li>
</ul>
<hr />
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">A major holder of the <a href="https://coingape.com/dogwifhat-whale-moves-3m-tokens-to-coinbase-whats-next-for-wif/">Dogwifhat cryptocurrency has moved tokens worth $3.47 million to Coinbase, triggering price movements and market reactions.</a> The transfer occurred during a period of heightened volatility in the broader cryptocurrency market.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Blockchain analytics platform Lookonchain identified the whale&#8217;s movement of 1.2 million WIF tokens to the popular cryptocurrency exchange. The wallet address, identified as 72X13Krh1nCM on Solscan, originally acquired these tokens through an initial investment of $393,000 approximately eleven months ago.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The timing of this transfer coincides with recent market-wide turbulence. Cryptocurrency markets have experienced substantial liquidations, with the total value reaching $1.76 billion across various digital assets. Dogwifhat itself saw $22 million in liquidations during December 9 and 10, according to data from Coinglass.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Following the whale&#8217;s transfer to Coinbase, the WIF token price experienced a decline of approximately 3.5 percent, settling at $2.87. The token&#8217;s trading range for the 24-hour period showed a low of $2.66 and a high of $3.01.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Market data indicates that WIF is currently trading 41 percent below its all-time high price of $4.85. The recent price movement reflects the immediate market reaction to the whale&#8217;s decision to move their holdings to an exchange.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The whale&#8217;s original investment strategy proved highly profitable, turning $393,000 into approximately $3.47 million. This represents a return on investment that showcases the potential volatility and opportunity within the cryptocurrency market.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Trading volumes for WIF have shown increased activity following the whale&#8217;s movement. This uptick in volume indicates heightened market interest and participation from traders responding to the price action.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Technical analysts watching the WIF price charts have identified $4.00 as a key resistance level. Breaking through this price point could potentially lead to testing the previous all-time high of $4.85.</p>
<figure id="attachment_107879" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-107879" style="width: 847px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-107879" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-11-at-09-18-40-dogwifhat-Price-WIF-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko.png" alt="Dogwifhat Price on CoinGecko" width="847" height="689" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-11-at-09-18-40-dogwifhat-Price-WIF-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko.png 847w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-11-at-09-18-40-dogwifhat-Price-WIF-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko-300x244.png 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-11-at-09-18-40-dogwifhat-Price-WIF-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko-768x625.png 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-11-at-09-18-40-dogwifhat-Price-WIF-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko-50x41.png 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-11-at-09-18-40-dogwifhat-Price-WIF-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko-150x122.png 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-11-at-09-18-40-dogwifhat-Price-WIF-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko-450x366.png 450w" sizes="(max-width: 847px) 100vw, 847px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-107879" class="wp-caption-text">Dogwifhat Price on <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/dogwifhat">CoinGecko</a></figcaption></figure>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Market participants are closely monitoring exchange inflows and outflows for WIF, as these metrics often provide insights into potential selling or buying pressure. The movement of large quantities of tokens to exchanges sometimes precedes increased selling activity.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The broader cryptocurrency market context plays an important role in WIF&#8217;s price action. Recent market-wide volatility has affected various digital assets, with altcoins particularly impacted by the turbulent conditions.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Data from cryptocurrency exchanges shows varying levels of liquidity for WIF across different trading pairs. This liquidity distribution can influence price stability and trading efficiency during periods of high market activity.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Short-term price movements for WIF have demonstrated increased volatility following the whale&#8217;s transfer. Trading patterns show reactions from both buyers and sellers as the market adjusts to the new supply dynamics.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Historical data for WIF indicates previous instances of price recovery following similar large token movements. However, each market situation presents unique circumstances that affect price development.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Current market metrics for WIF show trading activity across multiple exchanges, with Coinbase receiving increased attention due to the recent whale transfer. Trading pairs with both stablecoins and major cryptocurrencies continue to show active market participation.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Price charts for WIF display the token&#8217;s reaction to various support and resistance levels during recent trading sessions. These technical indicators help traders understand potential price movement ranges.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The blockchain data for WIF reveals continued network activity and token movements across various addresses. This on-chain activity provides transparency into market participant behavior and token distribution patterns.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/dogwifhat-wif-price-whale-moves-1-2m-tokens-worth-3-47m/">Dogwifhat (WIF) Price: Whale Moves 1.2M Tokens Worth $3.47M</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">107878</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>LUIGI Token Market Cap Hits $60M Following Murder Suspect&#8217;s Arrest</title>
		<link>https://blockonomi.com/luigi-token-market-cap-hits-60m-following-murder-suspects-arrest/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Oliver Dale]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2024 10:37:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Memes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blockonomi.com/?p=107807</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>TLDR Luigi Inu (LUIGI) memecoin reached $60M market cap after Luigi Mangione&#8217;s arrest for murder of UnitedHealthcare CEO Mangione was arrested in Pennsylvania for allegedly killing Brian Thompson in a &#8220;premeditated attack&#8221; Token gained popularity after arrest and Mangione&#8217;s anti-corporate manifesto went viral Competing token $BRIAN launched in support of victim Brian Thompson Trading activity [...]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/luigi-token-market-cap-hits-60m-following-murder-suspects-arrest/">LUIGI Token Market Cap Hits $60M Following Murder Suspect&#8217;s Arrest</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>TLDR</h2>
<ul>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Luigi Inu (LUIGI) memecoin reached $60M market cap after Luigi Mangione&#8217;s arrest for murder of UnitedHealthcare CEO</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Mangione was arrested in Pennsylvania for allegedly killing Brian Thompson in a &#8220;premeditated attack&#8221;</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Token gained popularity after arrest and Mangione&#8217;s anti-corporate manifesto went viral</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Competing token $BRIAN launched in support of victim Brian Thompson</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Trading activity concentrated on Solana&#8217;s Raydium platform with high volatility</li>
</ul>
<hr />
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">A new memecoin called <a href="https://crypto.news/after-murder-arrest-luigis-market-cap-climbs-to-60m/">Luigi Inu (LUIGI) has reached a $60 million market capitalization following the arrest of its namesake, Luigi Mangione, for the alleged murder of UnitedHealthcare CEO Brian Thompson in Manhattan.</a></p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The token, which trades on <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/dexscan/solana/AWcXGpmBGvhyZgWE4rEfSTFoDgHHrHa12fhyjqBvqeUL/">Solana&#8217;s Raydium platform</a>, first gained attention after Mangione&#8217;s arrest in Altoona, Pennsylvania on December 9. The market cap initially touched $29 million before doubling to $60 million as news of the arrest spread across social media platforms.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Anonymous crypto traders launched the LUIGI token shortly after Mangione&#8217;s arrest made headlines. The token&#8217;s rapid price increase occurred alongside growing public interest in the case, with trading volume spiking on Raydium&#8217;s automated market maker system.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Pennsylvania police took Mangione into custody in connection with what they described as a &#8220;premeditated and pre-planned attack&#8221; on Thompson. Surveillance footage showed Mangione leaving the area shortly after gunshots were reported in Manhattan.</p>
<p><iframe class="youtube-player" width="814" height="458" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/ryk76suVGPY?version=3&#038;rel=1&#038;showsearch=0&#038;showinfo=1&#038;iv_load_policy=1&#038;fs=1&#038;hl=en-US&#038;autohide=2&#038;wmode=transparent" allowfullscreen="true" style="border:0;" sandbox="allow-scripts allow-same-origin allow-popups allow-presentation allow-popups-to-escape-sandbox"></iframe></p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The case gained additional attention when authorities revealed Mangione had published a manifesto containing critical statements about corporate America. This document&#8217;s circulation online helped fuel trading activity in the LUIGI token.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The price of LUIGI/SOL has shown extreme volatility, reaching 0.0003198 in recent trading. The token&#8217;s value fluctuations reflect the fast-moving nature of memecoin markets and their sensitivity to news events.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">In response to the LUIGI token&#8217;s rise, another cryptocurrency called $BRIAN emerged. This competing token, created to show support for the victim, has seen its own trading activity with a market cap of $68,000 and 24-hour volume of $691,000.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The $BRIAN token maintains about $33,000 in liquidity and has experienced a 25.23% decrease in market value during recent trading sessions. Its creators framed the project around &#8220;Justice for Brian Thompson&#8221; as its central theme.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Trading activity has split between supporters and critics of the situation. While some traders have embraced LUIGI&#8217;s anti-establishment narrative, others in the crypto community have expressed strong opposition to profiting from the tragic events.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">I am not against memes, but meme coins are getting &quot;a little&quot; weird now.</p>
<p>Let&#39;s build real applications using blockchain.</p>
<p>&mdash; CZ <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/15.0.3/72x72/1f536.png" alt="ðŸ”¶" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> BNB (@cz_binance) <a href="https://twitter.com/cz_binance/status/1861306581758976434?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">November 26, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The emergence of these tokens occurs during a period of uncertainty for memecoins. Many new tokens have struggled to maintain momentum or reach new price highs, challenging the concept of a &#8220;memecoin supercycle&#8221; discussed at the Token2049 conference.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Market observer Alex Beene points out that such tokens often leverage fear of missing out through viral narratives about wealth creation. He compares their appeal to sports betting while noting their lack of fundamental value.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The LUIGI token&#8217;s trading patterns show concentrated activity on Solana&#8217;s Raydium platform, where automated market makers facilitate quick trades and price discovery for new tokens.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Current data shows the token maintaining active trading volume, though price volatility continues as market participants react to ongoing developments in the criminal case.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Police investigations remain active, with authorities gathering additional evidence about the events leading up to Thompson&#8217;s death in Manhattan.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The most recent trading data shows LUIGI&#8217;s market cap holding at $60 million, with ongoing price swings as traders continue to enter and exit positions on various decentralized exchanges.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/luigi-token-market-cap-hits-60m-following-murder-suspects-arrest/">LUIGI Token Market Cap Hits $60M Following Murder Suspect&#8217;s Arrest</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">107807</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dogecoin (DOGE) Price: Whales Accumulate 550M Tokens Amid Technical Breakout Setup</title>
		<link>https://blockonomi.com/dogecoin-doge-price-whales-accumulate-550m-tokens-amid-technical-breakout-setup/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Oliver Dale]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2024 09:39:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blockonomi.com/?p=107779</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>TLDR Dogecoin shows strong price momentum with technical indicators suggesting potential breakout Historic wallet containing 870,000 DOGE activated after 11 years with 64,249% ROI Whales accumulated over 550 million DOGE in past month Price targets of $8-10 projected based on technical analysis Currently trading at $0.4088, down 7.15% daily and 1.39% weekly A combination of [...]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/dogecoin-doge-price-whales-accumulate-550m-tokens-amid-technical-breakout-setup/">Dogecoin (DOGE) Price: Whales Accumulate 550M Tokens Amid Technical Breakout Setup</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>TLDR</h2>
<ul>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Dogecoin shows strong price momentum with technical indicators suggesting potential breakout</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Historic wallet containing 870,000 DOGE activated after 11 years with 64,249% ROI</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Whales accumulated over 550 million DOGE in past month</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Price targets of $8-10 projected based on technical analysis</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Currently trading at $0.4088, down 7.15% daily and 1.39% weekly</li>
</ul>
<hr />
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">A combination of technical indicators and increased whale activity suggests <a href="https://www.crypto-news-flash.com/doge-on-track-for-10-as-dogecoin-momentum-and-investor-interest-grow/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=doge-on-track-for-10-as-dogecoin-momentum-and-investor-interest-grow">Dogecoin (DOGE) could be positioning for a notable price movement.</a> The popular cryptocurrency, which began as a meme coin in 2013, has attracted renewed attention from large investors and long-term holders.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Recent market data shows Dogecoin moving out of oversold territory on technical charts, indicating a possible shift in market sentiment. This transition comes as trading volumes have steadily increased over the past week, with daily volumes averaging above $500 million.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The reactivation of a dormant wallet containing 870,000 DOGE after 11 years of inactivity has caught the attention of market observers. This wallet&#8217;s movement resulted in a remarkable 64,249% return on investment, highlighting the potential long-term value appreciation of early DOGE holdings.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Whale activity has seen a marked increase, with large investors accumulating over 550 million DOGE throughout the past month. Data from blockchain analytics platform Whale Alert confirms this trend, showing multiple large-scale transactions moving between wallets and exchanges.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr"><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/15.0.3/72x72/1f4a4.png" alt="ðŸ’¤" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />  A dormant address containing 870,019 <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/DOGE?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#DOGE</a> (391,889 USD) has just been activated after 11.0 years!<a href="https://t.co/lNKHA7fzfx">https://t.co/lNKHA7fzfx</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Whale Alert (@whale_alert) <a href="https://twitter.com/whale_alert/status/1865361260222509367?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">December 7, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Price action around the $0.60 level has formed a consolidation pattern, which technical analysts interpret as a potential launching pad for future price movement. Historical patterns suggest similar consolidation periods have preceded previous rallies.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Trading indicators point to decreasing selling pressure, with the Relative Strength Index (RSI) showing recovery from oversold conditions. Volume profiles indicate growing buyer interest at current price levels, particularly during Asian trading hours.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Market makers have increased their position sizes, according to order book data from major exchanges. This development typically precedes periods of enhanced price discovery and could signal institutional interest in building larger positions.</p>
<figure id="attachment_107780" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-107780" style="width: 847px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-107780" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-10-at-09-29-22-Dogecoin-Price-DOGE-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko.png" alt="Dogecoin Price on CoinGecko" width="847" height="628" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-10-at-09-29-22-Dogecoin-Price-DOGE-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko.png 847w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-10-at-09-29-22-Dogecoin-Price-DOGE-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko-300x222.png 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-10-at-09-29-22-Dogecoin-Price-DOGE-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko-768x569.png 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-10-at-09-29-22-Dogecoin-Price-DOGE-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko-50x37.png 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-10-at-09-29-22-Dogecoin-Price-DOGE-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko-150x111.png 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-10-at-09-29-22-Dogecoin-Price-DOGE-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko-450x334.png 450w" sizes="(max-width: 847px) 100vw, 847px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-107780" class="wp-caption-text">Dogecoin Price on <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/dogecoin">CoinGecko</a></figcaption></figure>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">On-chain metrics reveal an uptick in active addresses, suggesting broader participation in the<a href="https://moneycheck.com/best-doge-casinos/"> Dogecoin</a> network. The number of daily active addresses has grown by 15% compared to the previous month&#8217;s average.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Transaction counts have also risen, with the network processing an average of 50,000 daily transactions over the past week. This represents a 25% increase from the monthly average and indicates growing usage of the network.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The technical setup shows formation of a potential bull flag pattern on daily timeframes. This pattern, combined with increasing volume, has led some analysts to project price targets in the $8-10 range, though such projections remain speculative.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Hash rate data shows mining activity remains stable, with network security maintaining consistent levels. This stability in fundamental metrics provides a foundation for potential price appreciation.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Social media mentions and sentiment analysis indicate growing retail interest in Dogecoin. Twitter mentions have increased by 30% week-over-week, while Reddit discussions show similar growth patterns.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Exchange inflow and outflow data reveals a net outflow of DOGE from centralized platforms, suggesting holders are moving coins to private wallets for longer-term storage. This behavior often precedes periods of reduced selling pressure.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Currently, Dogecoin trades at $0.4088, representing a 7.15% decrease over the past 24 hours and a 1.39% decline over the past week. Trading pairs show strongest volume against USDT on major exchanges.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Market order books display strong support levels around $0.35, with resistance clustering near the $0.45 mark. These levels may prove important for short-term price action as the market continues to develop.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/dogecoin-doge-price-whales-accumulate-550m-tokens-amid-technical-breakout-setup/">Dogecoin (DOGE) Price: Whales Accumulate 550M Tokens Amid Technical Breakout Setup</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">107779</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>JUSTICE Token ($JFP) Faces Market Challenges After High-Profile Launch</title>
		<link>https://blockonomi.com/justice-token-jfp-faces-market-challenges-after-high-profile-launch/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Oliver Dale]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 10:25:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blockonomi.com/?p=107698</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>TLDR Mark Longo&#8217;s pet memorial token (JUSTICE) crashed 99% after launch, with market cap falling to $375,960 Longo criticized others for profiting from his pets&#8217; story before launching his own token A second token (JFP) was launched December 6th, which also dropped 67% The story gained political attention with VP-elect Vance and Elon Musk commenting [...]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/justice-token-jfp-faces-market-challenges-after-high-profile-launch/">JUSTICE Token ($JFP) Faces Market Challenges After High-Profile Launch</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>TLDR</h2>
<ul>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Mark Longo&#8217;s pet memorial token (JUSTICE) crashed 99% after launch, with market cap falling to $375,960</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Longo criticized others for profiting from his pets&#8217; story before launching his own token</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">A second token (JFP) was launched December 6th, which also dropped 67%</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">The story gained political attention with VP-elect Vance and Elon Musk commenting</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">The original incident involved NY State officers euthanizing Longo&#8217;s pets for alleged wildlife violations</li>
</ul>
<hr />
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The cryptocurrency market witnessed a notable downturn in December as <a href="https://decrypt.co/295486/peanut-pet-owners-token-collapses-two-weeks-after-launch">two memorial tokens launched by Mark Longo, owner of the euthanized pets Peanut and Fred, experienced steep price declines within weeks of their release.</a></p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The initial token, Justice for Pnut and Fred (JUSTICE), launched on November 26 through the Solana-based platform Pump.fun, has seen its value drop by more than 99%. Current trading data shows the token price at $0.0003834, with a market capitalization that has fallen to $375,960.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Despite the price collapse, the token maintains over 31,000 holders, according to data from GeckoTerminal. This holder count suggests initial strong interest in the project, though it failed to sustain its early momentum.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The launch came with its share of controversy. Before creating the token, Longo had publicly criticized crypto traders for what he called &#8220;despicable&#8221; attempts to profit from his personal tragedy through the creation of the meme coin Peanut (PNUT).</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Members of the PNUT community responded by pointing to approximately $50,000 in donations made to Longo, which they claim he quickly converted to other currencies. These allegations added to the growing tensions surrounding the project.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The story took another turn on December 6, when the account associated with Longo announced a new contract address. This announcement effectively marked the launch of a second token, JUSTICE FOR PEANUT (JFP), just days after the first token&#8217;s decline.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Shoutout to the 4 news publications covering this story, Mark is extremely proud to be wearing <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24JFP&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">$JFP</a> in all photos. Because this is more than just a coin this is a movement. Despite all the bad actors, <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24JFP&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">$JFP</a> is here to stay.</p>
<p>No Dev<br />No bundle<br />Pumpfun CTO <br />Real Owner of PNUT <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/15.0.3/72x72/2764.png" alt="â¤" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/15.0.3/72x72/1f64f-1f3fb.png" alt="ðŸ™ðŸ»" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /></p>
<p>&mdash; Justice (@JusticePnutFred) <a href="https://twitter.com/JusticePnutFred/status/1864946210915914232?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">December 6, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The new JFP token has not fared better in the market, showing a 67% decrease in value since its creation. This parallel decline raises questions about the viability of memorial-based cryptocurrency projects.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The underlying events that sparked these token launches trace back to October 30, when New York State environmental officers conducted a raid on Longo&#8217;s Pine City animal sanctuary. The officers cited violations of wildlife protection laws as the basis for their actions.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">During this raid, Peanut, a squirrel who had gained over 500,000 social media followers, was euthanized along with Fred, a raccoon. Officials stated the euthanization occurred after one of the animals allegedly bit someone during the seizure operation.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The incident caught the attention of high-profile figures, including Vice President-elect JD Vance, who mentioned at a North Carolina rally that Donald Trump was &#8220;fired up&#8221; about the euthanization. Elon Musk&#8217;s comments on the situation led to increased trading activity in various related meme coins.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Both tokens were launched through Pump.fun, a platform that has changed the landscape of meme coin creation. The platform allows users to create tokens for just 0.02 SOL (approximately $4.8), removing many traditional barriers to entry in the cryptocurrency market.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Pump.fun&#8217;s system includes an automatic price adjustment mechanism based on market activity. While this feature aims to provide market efficiency, it can also lead to increased price volatility in trending tokens.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The platform&#8217;s accessibility has led to massive adoption, with over 3.85 million token launches recorded since January 2024. However, this ease of use has also raised concerns about market stability and token quality.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Recent developments show growing regulatory attention to these platforms. On December 6, Pump.fun banned UK users following warnings from British financial regulators, adding another layer of complexity to the platform&#8217;s operations.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The account &#8220;JusticePnutFred&#8221; maintains verification status on the X platform as an official organization, though attempts by Decrypt to confirm this status with X have not received a response. The account has claimed to have submitted listing requests to major cryptocurrency tracking sites CoinMarketCap and CoinGecko.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">On December 6, the account thanked &#8220;4 news publications&#8221; for covering the story of Mark Longo and the JFP launch, though the specific publications referenced remain unclear. Longo has not responded to requests for comment regarding the performance of either token.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The platform recently removed its live-streaming feature after reports emerged about inappropriate content, including self-harm and abuse, leading to community protests. This action preceded the UK user ban, suggesting increasing scrutiny of the platform&#8217;s operations.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/justice-token-jfp-faces-market-challenges-after-high-profile-launch/">JUSTICE Token ($JFP) Faces Market Challenges After High-Profile Launch</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">107698</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Memecoins Take Center Stage as Whales Make Their Move</title>
		<link>https://blockonomi.com/memecoins-take-center-stage-as-whales-make-their-move/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Oliver Dale]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 09:46:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blockonomi.com/?p=107694</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>TLDR Major memecoins including DOGE, PEPE, and WIF are seeing price increases while mainstream cryptocurrencies struggle Whale investors are showing increased interest in memecoins, driving the current price surge Analysis suggests DOGE could rise 18% to $0.58 if it maintains above $0.48 PEPE could see a 45% increase to $0.0000352 if it stays above $0.0000238 [...]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/memecoins-take-center-stage-as-whales-make-their-move/">Memecoins Take Center Stage as Whales Make Their Move</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>TLDR</h2>
<ul>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Major memecoins including DOGE, PEPE, and WIF are seeing price increases while mainstream cryptocurrencies struggle</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Whale investors are showing increased interest in memecoins, driving the current price surge</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Analysis suggests DOGE could rise 18% to $0.58 if it maintains above $0.48</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">PEPE could see a 45% increase to $0.0000352 if it stays above $0.0000238</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">WIF may rise 25% to $4.60 if it maintains above $3.40</li>
</ul>
<hr />
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">While major cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin and Ethereum face market pressures, <a href="https://ambcrypto.com/why-are-memecoins-rising-today-doge-pepe-wif-see-surges/">the memecoin sector is experiencing a notable upswing in December 2024</a>, driven by increased whale investor activity and technical breakouts across multiple tokens.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Data from on-chain analytics firm Santiment shows that large-scale investors, commonly known as whales, are moving funds into popular memecoins including Dogecoin (DOGE), Pepe (PEPE), and dogwifhat (WIF). This shift in institutional interest away from mainstream cryptocurrencies appears to be a key factor in the current price movement.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr"><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/15.0.3/72x72/1f436.png" alt="ðŸ¶" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/15.0.3/72x72/1f438.png" alt="ðŸ¸" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/15.0.3/72x72/1f63a.png" alt="ðŸ˜º" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> Meme coins are quietly having more mini breakouts this weekend. For coins like Dogecoin, Pepe, Dogwifhat, and Bonk, the larger wallets could continue to pump market caps longer until retail FOMO returns. Once the crowd catches wind and get greedy, the larger wallets sellâ€¦ <a href="https://t.co/KD9OeqnaBe">pic.twitter.com/KD9OeqnaBe</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Santiment (@santimentfeed) <a href="https://twitter.com/santimentfeed/status/1865621956399153273?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">December 8, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The price action comes as several memecoins break out of their previous trading ranges. Dogecoin, the largest memecoin by market capitalization, is testing key price levels that could lead to further gains. Technical analysis indicates that if<a href="https://moneycheck.com/best-doge-casinos/"> DOGE</a> maintains its position above $0.48 and successfully closes a daily candle above this threshold, it may see an 18% increase to reach $0.58.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words"><a href="https://moneycheck.com/best-pepe-casinos/">PEPE</a>, another prominent memecoin, is showing similar technical strength. The token is currently retesting a bullish flag pattern breakout. Analysis suggests that if PEPE holds above $0.0000238, it could experience a 45% surge, potentially reaching $0.0000352 in the coming days.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The newer entrant dogwifhat (WIF) has broken free from its recent consolidation zone. Technical indicators point to a possible 25% increase to $4.60 if the token maintains support above $3.40.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Market data reveals that whale investors are displaying strong confidence in these breakout patterns, contributing to the upward price momentum. Their buying activity has created noticeable price impacts across the memecoin sector.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The current rally appears to be primarily driven by institutional and whale investors rather than retail traders. This distinction is important as historical patterns show that whale-led movements often precede broader market attention.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Trading volumes across major memecoin pairs have increased, indicating growing market participation. This uptick in volume provides additional technical support for the ongoing price movements.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Bonk (BONK) and other smaller market cap memecoins are also experiencing price appreciation, suggesting the rally is broad-based across the sector rather than limited to a few tokens.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Price charts show that many memecoins are testing or breaking through key resistance levels that had previously contained price action. These technical breakouts are occurring against a backdrop of increased trading activity.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">On-chain metrics indicate substantial whale accumulation in recent days, with large wallets increasing their positions across multiple memecoin projects.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The timing of this memecoin movement is notable as it comes during a period when traditional cryptocurrencies are seeing relatively flat price action. This divergence suggests a deliberate rotation of capital within the crypto market.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Trading patterns indicate that whales may continue their accumulation until retail interest picks up. However, Santiment data suggests that once retail buyers enter the market, whale investors typically begin to reduce their positions.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The price action is accompanied by increased social media activity around memecoin projects, though current metrics suggest retail speculation remains below previous peak levels.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Current market data shows these tokens retesting their breakout levels with sustained buying pressure from large holders.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/memecoins-take-center-stage-as-whales-make-their-move/">Memecoins Take Center Stage as Whales Make Their Move</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">107694</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>POPCAT (POPCAT) Price Analysis: Key Metrics Point to Crucial Trading Period</title>
		<link>https://blockonomi.com/popcat-popcat-price-analysis-key-metrics-point-to-crucial-trading-period/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Oliver Dale]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 09:35:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blockonomi.com/?p=107688</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>TLDR POPCAT has achieved 8th place among memecoins by market cap, demonstrating strong growth potential Current price stands at $1.50 with a recent 13% surge over 7 days $2 million worth of POPCAT tokens being withdrawn by spot traders suggests market confidence Large whale addresses (100K+ POPCAT holders) have decreased their holdings over time Token [...]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/popcat-popcat-price-analysis-key-metrics-point-to-crucial-trading-period/">POPCAT (POPCAT) Price Analysis: Key Metrics Point to Crucial Trading Period</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>TLDR</h2>
<ul>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">POPCAT has achieved 8th place among memecoins by market cap, demonstrating strong growth potential</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Current price stands at $1.50 with a recent 13% surge over 7 days</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">$2 million worth of POPCAT tokens being withdrawn by spot traders suggests market confidence</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Large whale addresses (100K+ POPCAT holders) have decreased their holdings over time</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Token faces crucial resistance at $1.50, which needs to become support for further growth</li>
</ul>
<hr />
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">POPCAT&#8217;s recent market performance has captured the attention of crypto enthusiasts as t<a href="https://ambcrypto.com/popcat-eyes-2-how-speculation-over-fundamentals-could-hold-it-back/">he memecoin continues its volatile journey toward the $2 mark.</a> Currently trading at $1.50, the token has shown remarkable resilience in a challenging market environment.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The token&#8217;s rise to become the 8th largest memecoin by market capitalization marks a notable achievement in the competitive crypto landscape. This milestone comes after POPCAT surpassed Mog Coin, which itself experienced an 80% surge in the previous month.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Recent trading data reveals a 13% increase in POPCAT&#8217;s value over the past seven days, outperforming many of its competitors in the memecoin sector. The token&#8217;s Relative Strength Index (RSI) remains in neutral territory, suggesting room for potential upward movement.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Market analysts have noted increased activity in spot trading, with approximately $2 million worth of POPCAT tokens being withdrawn from exchanges. This movement often indicates a shift toward longer-term holding patterns among investors.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The token&#8217;s journey hasn&#8217;t been without challenges. After reaching an all-time high of $2.08 during the election rally, POPCAT experienced a substantial correction due to profit-taking activities. This pullback brought the price down to current levels, making it the only top-10 memecoin to show negative returns over a 30-day period.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Trading volumes have shown interesting patterns in recent weeks. Daily transaction counts have maintained steady levels, suggesting consistent market participation despite price volatility. This stability in trading activity provides a foundation for potential price recovery.</p>
<figure id="attachment_107692" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-107692" style="width: 847px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-107692" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-09-at-09-31-24-Popcat-Price-POPCAT-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko.png" alt="Popcat Price on CoinGecko" width="847" height="629" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-09-at-09-31-24-Popcat-Price-POPCAT-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko.png 847w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-09-at-09-31-24-Popcat-Price-POPCAT-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko-300x223.png 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-09-at-09-31-24-Popcat-Price-POPCAT-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko-768x570.png 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-09-at-09-31-24-Popcat-Price-POPCAT-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko-50x37.png 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-09-at-09-31-24-Popcat-Price-POPCAT-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko-150x111.png 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-09-at-09-31-24-Popcat-Price-POPCAT-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko-450x334.png 450w" sizes="(max-width: 847px) 100vw, 847px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-107692" class="wp-caption-text">Popcat Price on <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/popcat">CoinGecko</a></figcaption></figure>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Technical analysis indicates that the $1.50 price point represents a crucial level for POPCAT. Previous trading patterns show this area acted as strong resistance in mid-November, leading to a retreat toward $1.20. Market observers are closely watching whether this level can transform from resistance into support.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">On-chain data reveals changing dynamics in holder composition. While smaller holders have maintained their positions, addresses holding over 100,000 POPCAT tokens have reduced their holdings over time. This shift in large holder behavior presents both challenges and opportunities for price stability.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Market data from Coinglass shows evolving derivatives trading patterns for POPCAT. Open interest figures suggest traders are positioning themselves for potential price movements in both directions, indicating market uncertainty about near-term price action.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The token&#8217;s liquidity metrics have remained relatively stable, with depth charts showing substantial support at key price levels. This stability in market depth could provide a buffer against extreme price swings.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Recent withdrawal patterns from centralized exchanges point to increasing interest in self-custody solutions among POPCAT holders. This trend often correlates with longer-term holding intentions among market participants.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Price correlation data shows POPCAT maintaining independence from broader market movements, suggesting its price action is primarily driven by token-specific factors rather than general market sentiment.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Trading volume distribution across exchanges remains diverse, with no single platform dominating POPCAT trading activity. This decentralization of trading venues potentially reduces the impact of exchange-specific events on price action.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Order book analysis reveals clustered buy orders below the current price level, potentially providing support during market corrections. However, similar clusters of sell orders exist above current prices, suggesting potential resistance to upward movements.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The most recent market data shows POPCAT trading at $1.50, with 24-hour volume reaching sustained levels and market capitalization maintaining its position among top memecoins.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/popcat-popcat-price-analysis-key-metrics-point-to-crucial-trading-period/">POPCAT (POPCAT) Price Analysis: Key Metrics Point to Crucial Trading Period</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">107688</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>PEPE ($PEPE) Price: Shatters Records with $11 Billion Market Milestone</title>
		<link>https://blockonomi.com/pepe-pepe-price-shatters-records-with-11-billion-market-milestone/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Oliver Dale]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 09:27:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blockonomi.com/?p=107683</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>TLDR PEPE hits new all-time high of $0.00002708, with market cap exceeding $11 billion Token surges 21% in 24 hours and 150% over past 30 days Whales increased PEPE holdings by $1.14 billion over weekend PEPE now ranks 23rd by market cap, surpassing UNI and LTC Major exchanges including Robinhood and MoonPay add PEPE support [...]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/pepe-pepe-price-shatters-records-with-11-billion-market-milestone/">PEPE ($PEPE) Price: Shatters Records with $11 Billion Market Milestone</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>TLDR</h2>
<ul>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">PEPE hits new all-time high of $0.00002708, with market cap exceeding $11 billion</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Token surges 21% in 24 hours and 150% over past 30 days</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Whales increased PEPE holdings by $1.14 billion over weekend</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">PEPE now ranks 23rd by market cap, surpassing UNI and LTC</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Major exchanges including Robinhood and MoonPay add PEPE support</li>
</ul>
<hr />
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The meme cryptocurrency <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/meme-coins/pepe-hits-new-all-time-high-market-cap-surpasses-10-billion/">PEPE reached unprecedented levels this week, setting a new all-time high of $0.00002708 as its market capitalization surpassed $11 billion.</a> The token&#8217;s meteoric rise has been marked by strong whale activity and increased accessibility through major trading platforms.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">PEPE&#8217;s latest price movement represents a 21% increase in just 24 hours, building on momentum that has seen the token rise 150% over the past month. The surge has propelled PEPE to the 23rd position among all cryptocurrencies by market value, overtaking established projects like Uniswap and Litecoin.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words"><a href="https://decrypt.co/295502/pepe-flips-uni-and-ltc-surges-past-11-billion-market-cap-to-new-record">Data from blockchain analytics firms shows large investors, known as whales, increased their PEPE holdings by $1.14 billion over the weekend.</a> This accumulation suggests growing institutional interest in the meme token, which launched in April 2023.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The token&#8217;s rise coincides with broader market optimism, as Bitcoin crossed the $100,000 threshold for the first time. PEPE has emerged as one of the strongest performers in the current bull cycle, posting year-to-date gains of 1,900%.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Major cryptocurrency exchanges have taken notice of PEPE&#8217;s growth. Robinhood recently added support for the token, alongside other cryptocurrencies including <a href="https://moneycheck.com/best-solana-casinos/">Solana</a>, XRP, and <a href="https://moneycheck.com/best-cardano-casinos/">Cardano</a>. The move marks a reversal of previous restrictions implemented during last year&#8217;s regulatory crackdown.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Payment service provider MoonPay has also integrated <a href="https://moneycheck.com/best-pepe-casinos/">PEPE</a> into its platform, enabling over 20 million users across 180 countries to purchase the token using conventional payment methods like Apple Pay and Venmo. This integration has made the token more accessible to mainstream investors.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">PEPE&#8217;s market presence has grown substantially since its launch. The token now maintains its position as the third-largest meme cryptocurrency, behind only Dogecoin and <a href="https://moneycheck.com/best-shib-casinos/">Shiba Inu,</a> which have market caps of $67.8 billion and $18.9 billion respectively.</p>
<figure id="attachment_107684" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-107684" style="width: 847px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-107684" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-09-at-09-23-34-Pepe-Price-PEPE-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko.png" alt="PEPE Price on CoinGecko" width="847" height="631" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-09-at-09-23-34-Pepe-Price-PEPE-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko.png 847w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-09-at-09-23-34-Pepe-Price-PEPE-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko-300x223.png 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-09-at-09-23-34-Pepe-Price-PEPE-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko-768x572.png 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-09-at-09-23-34-Pepe-Price-PEPE-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko-50x37.png 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-09-at-09-23-34-Pepe-Price-PEPE-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko-150x112.png 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-09-at-09-23-34-Pepe-Price-PEPE-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko-450x335.png 450w" sizes="(max-width: 847px) 100vw, 847px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-107684" class="wp-caption-text">PEPE Price on <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/pepe">CoinGecko</a></figcaption></figure>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The token spent most of the past week consolidating around the $0.000022 level before breaking out to new highs. This followed a period of relative stability in October, after which November saw a parabolic price increase that broke through previous resistance levels.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Trading volume has increased substantially with the recent price movement, indicating strong market participation. The token&#8217;s liquidity has improved as more exchanges list PEPE for trading.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">PEPE&#8217;s foundation stems from the popular &#8220;Pepe the Frog&#8221; internet meme, created by artist Matt Furie in 2005. The project has developed a strong community following, characteristic of successful meme cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The meme coin sector has shown remarkable vitality this year, particularly following the launch of Solana-based platform Pump.fun, which enables free token creation. This has contributed to increased interest in meme-based cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Technical analysis shows PEPE breaking through several key resistance levels during its recent ascent. The token&#8217;s price action has formed a series of higher lows, suggesting sustained buying pressure.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Market data indicates a broad distribution of holders, from retail investors to large institutional players. This diverse holder base has contributed to the token&#8217;s market stability and growing trading volume.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Recent exchange listings have improved market access for U.S.-based investors, following regulatory clarity around certain digital assets. These developments have expanded PEPE&#8217;s potential investor base.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The latest price surge has sparked increased social media activity around the token, with PEPE trending on various cryptocurrency discussion forums and trading platforms.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/pepe-pepe-price-shatters-records-with-11-billion-market-milestone/">PEPE ($PEPE) Price: Shatters Records with $11 Billion Market Milestone</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">107683</post-id>	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
