<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	
	xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
	xmlns:geo="http://www.w3.org/2003/01/geo/wgs84_pos#"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Latest Crypto Gaming &amp; Gambling News &amp; Reviews from Blockonomi</title>
	<atom:link href="https://blockonomi.com/gaming/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://blockonomi.com/gaming/</link>
	<description>Cryptocurrency News &#38; Your Guide to the Blockchain Economy</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 09:04:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.7.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/fav-50x50.png</url>
	<title>Latest Crypto Gaming &amp; Gambling News &amp; Reviews from Blockonomi</title>
	<link>https://blockonomi.com/gaming/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
<site xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">134176212</site>	<item>
		<title>The Sandbox Expands with Launch of Hellboy &#038; Terminator Interactive Gaming Experiences</title>
		<link>https://blockonomi.com/the-sandbox-expands-with-launch-of-hellboy-terminator-interactive-gaming-experiences/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Oliver Dale]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 09:04:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Gaming]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Metaverse]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blockonomi.com/?p=107489</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>TLDR: The Sandbox launches two new games featuring Hellboy (2019) and Terminator franchises Players can experience iconic scenes from the 2019 Hellboy film as BPRD agents Terminator: Dark Fate game transports players to 2042 for resistance missions The platform&#8217;s Alpha Season 4 has broken previous engagement records Over 400 partners including major brands have joined [...]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/the-sandbox-expands-with-launch-of-hellboy-terminator-interactive-gaming-experiences/">The Sandbox Expands with Launch of Hellboy &#038; Terminator Interactive Gaming Experiences</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>TLDR:</h2>
<ul>
<li>The Sandbox launches two new games featuring Hellboy (2019) and Terminator franchises</li>
<li>Players can experience iconic scenes from the 2019 Hellboy film as BPRD agents</li>
<li>Terminator: Dark Fate game transports players to 2042 for resistance missions</li>
<li>The platform&#8217;s Alpha Season 4 has broken previous engagement records</li>
<li>Over 400 partners including major brands have joined The Sandbox platform</li>
</ul>
<hr />
<p>The Sandbox, a decentralized gaming platform and subsidiary of Animoca Brands, has expanded its virtual world with two new games based on popular movie franchises. The platform has launched gaming experiences inspired by <a href="https://www.sandbox.game/en/experiences/Hellboy%202019%20by%20LIONSGATE/9a61c449-af1d-4ece-8749-34f732d26064/page/">Hellboy (2019)</a> and <a href="https://www.sandbox.game/en/experiences/-0-10-terminator-future-hub/8c69d9de-8e6d-47e4-a7ca-93743754c351/page/">Terminator: Dark Fate</a>, allowing players to immerse themselves in these iconic universes.</p>
<p>The Hellboy game, presented by Lionsgate, puts players in the role of potential agents for the Bureau of Paranormal Research and Defense (BPRD). Players travel between Tijuana and the United Kingdom, moving across different time periods as they complete their missions.</p>
<p><iframe class="youtube-player" width="814" height="458" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/HpX5-bVw_EM?version=3&#038;rel=1&#038;showsearch=0&#038;showinfo=1&#038;iv_load_policy=1&#038;fs=1&#038;hl=en-US&#038;autohide=2&#038;wmode=transparent" allowfullscreen="true" style="border:0;" sandbox="allow-scripts allow-same-origin allow-popups allow-presentation allow-popups-to-escape-sandbox"></iframe></p>
<p>During their adventures, agents encounter well-known characters from the Hellboy universe, including the mysterious Baba Yaga and the fearsome Blood Queen, Nimue. The game features combat scenarios against demons and tasks players with tracking giants while uncovering hidden secrets throughout the storyline.</p>
<p>The Terminator: Dark Fate experience takes a different approach, setting players in a post-apocalyptic world of 2042. In this timeline, killer machines known as Terminators hunt the remaining human population, forcing players to join the resistance movement.</p>
<p>Players in the Terminator game must develop survival strategies, create weapons, and work to eliminate the mechanical threats. The game includes time travel elements as players search for ways to stop the Terminator threat.</p>
<p><iframe class="youtube-player" width="814" height="458" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/y4p7j0jK9xQ?version=3&#038;rel=1&#038;showsearch=0&#038;showinfo=1&#038;iv_load_policy=1&#038;fs=1&#038;hl=en-US&#038;autohide=2&#038;wmode=transparent" allowfullscreen="true" style="border:0;" sandbox="allow-scripts allow-same-origin allow-popups allow-presentation allow-popups-to-escape-sandbox"></iframe></p>
<p>These new releases coincide with The Sandbox&#8217;s Alpha Season 4, which has already broken previous player engagement records set during Alpha Season 3 in 2022. The platform continues to attract users with its diverse range of gaming experiences.</p>
<p>The Sandbox has built partnerships with more than 400 brands and creators, bringing together various entertainment forms in its virtual space. Partners include major names such as Warner Music Group, Gucci, and Ubisoft, alongside celebrities like Paris Hilton and Snoop Dogg.</p>
<p>Popular entertainment properties such as The Walking Dead, Attack on Titan, and The Smurfs have also established their presence on the platform. The Sandbox offers experiences ranging from Gordon Ramsay&#8217;s Hell&#8217;s Kitchen to Ubisoft&#8217;s Rabbids and Captain Laserhawk.</p>
<p>The platform operates as a metaverse environment where users can both play and create their own experiences. It incorporates Web3 technologies, allowing players to own their digital assets and creations through non-fungible tokens (NFTs).</p>
<p>Players can access these new games through The Sandbox&#8217;s free desktop application, available for both Windows and Mac operating systems. The platform&#8217;s map feature helps users navigate between different experiences and discover new content.</p>
<p>The Hellboy game recreates scenes from the 2019 film, offering fans a new way to interact with the franchise&#8217;s characters and storylines. Players face challenges and missions that align with the movie&#8217;s supernatural themes.</p>
<p>In the Terminator experience, players must navigate a dangerous future world while working with other resistance members. The game combines action elements with strategic planning as players fight against the machine threat.</p>
<p>The addition of these movie-based games represents The Sandbox&#8217;s ongoing efforts to blend popular entertainment properties with interactive gaming experiences. Each game maintains core elements from its source material while adapting them to the platform&#8217;s gaming format.</p>
<p>The platform allows users to monetize their creations, establishing a creator economy within its virtual space. This system enables both players and creators to benefit from their contributions to the platform&#8217;s growing ecosystem.</p>
<p>These new releases add to The Sandbox&#8217;s existing collection of branded experiences, which span gaming, entertainment, music, and art sectors. The platform continues to expand its offerings through partnerships with established entertainment brands.</p>
<p>The games are now available for players to access through The Sandbox&#8217;s platform, joining other recent additions like Dungeon Siege and various creator-developed experiences.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/the-sandbox-expands-with-launch-of-hellboy-terminator-interactive-gaming-experiences/">The Sandbox Expands with Launch of Hellboy &#038; Terminator Interactive Gaming Experiences</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">107489</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Nifty Island&#8217;s ISLAND Token to Debut After 140,000-User Campaign</title>
		<link>https://blockonomi.com/nifty-islands-island-token-to-debut-after-140000-user-campaign/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Oliver Dale]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 09:34:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Gaming]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NFTs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blockonomi.com/?p=107409</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>TLDR: Nifty Island announces ISLAND token launch for December 17, 2024 Play-to-airdrop campaign ended November 1 with 140,000+ active wallets and 70,000 islands created Users from campaign will receive 12.5% of total token supply (25% increase from initial plan) One million ISLAND tokens set aside for new users who missed the campaign Launch comes amid [...]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/nifty-islands-island-token-to-debut-after-140000-user-campaign/">Nifty Island&#8217;s ISLAND Token to Debut After 140,000-User Campaign</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>TLDR:</h2>
<ul>
<li>Nifty Island announces ISLAND token launch for December 17, 2024</li>
<li>Play-to-airdrop campaign ended November 1 with 140,000+ active wallets and 70,000 islands created</li>
<li>Users from campaign will receive 12.5% of total token supply (25% increase from initial plan)</li>
<li>One million ISLAND tokens set aside for new users who missed the campaign</li>
<li>Launch comes amid surge in gaming tokens, with SAND and MANA up 150%+ in past month</li>
</ul>
<hr />
<p>Ethereum-based metaverse gaming platform <a href="https://www.niftyisland.com/">Nifty Island</a> has set December 17, 2024, as the launch date for its ISLAND token, marking a major milestone for the project. The announcement comes after nine months of community building through a play-to-airdrop campaign that drew over 140,000 active participants.</p>
<p>The platform&#8217;s recent play-to-airdrop campaign, which concluded on November 1, proved more successful than initially anticipated. Users created nearly 70,000 playable islands within the game&#8217;s ecosystem, showing strong engagement with the platform&#8217;s creative tools.</p>
<p>In response to the campaign&#8217;s success, Nifty Island has increased the token allocation for participating users. The project will now distribute 12.5% of the total ISLAND token supply to campaign participants, representing a 25% increase from the original distribution plan.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Every community. Infinite islands. One token. </p>
<p>The dream of an open game world powered by web3 will be fulfilled.</p>
<p>On 12.17 <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24ISLAND&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">$ISLAND</a> TGE arrives <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/15.0.3/72x72/1f3dd.png" alt="🏝" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> <a href="https://t.co/9K54xETGyX">pic.twitter.com/9K54xETGyX</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Nifty Island <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/15.0.3/72x72/1f3dd.png" alt="🏝" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> (@Nifty_Island) <a href="https://twitter.com/Nifty_Island/status/1863997033951981753?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">December 3, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>To maintain momentum and attract new users, Nifty Island has partnered with several Web3 communities. These partnerships have led to the creation of a special allocation of one million ISLAND tokens, which will be available for claiming on launch day by users who missed the initial campaign.</p>
<p>Charles Smith, co-founder of Nifty Island, shared his vision for the platform&#8217;s future in November. &#8220;We now have a rock-solid foundation on which we can build the future of Nifty,&#8221; he told Decrypt, hinting at major developments ahead.</p>
<p>The platform&#8217;s development roadmap includes several ambitious goals. Plans are underway to bring Nifty Island to mobile devices, making the game more accessible to a broader audience. The team is also working on enhancing in-game content creation tools to improve the platform&#8217;s viral potential.</p>
<p>Smith believes these upcoming changes will transform the platform dramatically. &#8220;What we&#8217;re working on will be a new paradigm for Web3 gaming—as fundamental a shift as the emergence of play-to-airdrop was,&#8221; he explained, suggesting that current users might find the platform &#8220;unrecognizable&#8221; after future updates.</p>
<p>The ISLAND token launch comes at an opportune time in the gaming token market. Several established metaverse tokens have seen notable price increases over the past month. The Sandbox&#8217;s SAND token and Decentraland&#8217;s MANA have both recorded gains exceeding 150% in the last 30 days.</p>
<p>The Sandbox has been particularly active, with its SAND token showing a 32.3% increase in just 24 hours, reaching approximately $0.8. The token has maintained strong momentum with a 26.2% rise over seven days, according to CoinGecko data.</p>
<p>Within the broader gaming token market, this surge represents a reversal of previous market conditions. The sector has experienced renewed interest from investors and users alike, suggesting a potential shift in market sentiment toward gaming and metaverse projects.</p>
<p>Nifty Island&#8217;s approach to token distribution reflects a focus on community engagement. The increased allocation for play-to-airdrop participants rewards early adopters while the additional token pool for newcomers helps maintain an open ecosystem.</p>
<p>The platform&#8217;s sandbox-style gameplay allows users to create and share their own game worlds, called Islands. This user-generated content model aims to ensure a steady stream of fresh experiences for players, potentially supporting long-term engagement.</p>
<p>Technical development continues alongside the token launch preparations. The team has emphasized their commitment to building robust infrastructure for the platform&#8217;s growing user base.</p>
<p>The December 17 launch will position ISLAND alongside other established metaverse tokens in the market. As the date approaches, the project team continues to focus on platform development and community growth.</p>
<p>The timing of the launch aligns with increased market activity in the gaming token sector, where several major players have seen substantial price movements in recent weeks.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/nifty-islands-island-token-to-debut-after-140000-user-campaign/">Nifty Island&#8217;s ISLAND Token to Debut After 140,000-User Campaign</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">107409</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>My Neighbor Alice: Bridging Traditional Gaming &#038; Web3 Through Cozy Island Building</title>
		<link>https://blockonomi.com/my-neighbor-alice/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nicholas Say]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 10:37:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Gaming]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Guides]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blockonomi.com/?p=106755</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ever since Pong was released in 1972 and changed the world, Gaming has evolved into one of the world’s largest entertainment industries, surpassing even film and music in revenue. This growth has been propelled by the increasing accessibility of games and their ability to appeal to diverse audiences. Titles like Stardew Valley and Animal Crossing [...]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/my-neighbor-alice/">My Neighbor Alice: Bridging Traditional Gaming &#038; Web3 Through Cozy Island Building</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ever since Pong was released in 1972 and changed the world, Gaming has evolved into one of the world’s largest entertainment industries, surpassing even <a href="https://www.forbes.com/councils/forbesagencycouncil/2023/11/17/the-gaming-industry-a-behemoth-with-unprecedented-global-reach/">film and music</a> in revenue. This growth has been propelled by the increasing accessibility of games and their ability to appeal to diverse audiences.</p>
<p>Titles like Stardew Valley and Animal Crossing have been instrumental in this shift, offering experiences that emphasize relaxation, creativity, and social interaction.</p>
<p>These games have demonstrated that gaming can be a space for hardcore and casual players alike by focusing on fun and creativity rather than complex mechanics or intense competition. This inclusivity has helped break down barriers and build a sense of community among players.</p>
<p>The success of these games has highlighted a growing demand for non-competitive experiences, allowing players to engage in open-ended gameplay at their own pace.</p>
<p>Unlike traditional competitive titles such as League of Legends or Dark Souls, these games invite players to explore, create, and socialize without the pressure of high-stakes competition or difficult mechanics. This shift has opened new possibilities for game developers to reach a broader audience across all demographics, focusing on narrative and creativity rather than just action or skill-based challenges.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.myneighboralice.com/">My Neighbor Alice</a> is one of the web3 games taking this approach to bring new gamers to the blockchain space, a realm often seen as intimidating or complex for new players (or as gamers would put it, “Noobs”).</p>
<p>By combining the charm of cozy games with Web3 technology, it offers a non-intrusive way for players to experience blockchain features, like NFTs, while enjoying a casual yet complex and fun game. In doing so, My Neighbor Alice is set to introduce millions of players to the potential of blockchain gaming, just as Stardew Valley and Animal Crossing did for mainstream gaming.</p>
<p><img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-106899" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/game.jpg" alt="" width="1000" height="700" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/game.jpg 1000w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/game-300x210.jpg 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/game-768x538.jpg 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/game-50x35.jpg 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/game-150x105.jpg 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/game-450x315.jpg 450w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" /></p>
<hr />
<h2>What Is My Neighbor Alice All About?</h2>
<p><a href="https://www.myneighboralice.com/features">My Neighbor Alice describes itself as a multiplayer builder game</a> where players get to own their very own virtual islands, customizing them to their heart&#8217;s desire while inviting and visiting other players in the process. If you are a gamer and this sounds familiar, it is because the game was inspired by Animal Crossing itself, one of the most popular franchises ever created by Nintendo.</p>
<p>By combining a familiar genre with the many benefits of decentralization and digital assets, My Neighbor Alice gets to add an element that its traditional counterparts don’t offer: true ownership. Whereas games like Animal Crossing and Stardew Valley result in all of the hard work being “lost” once the player fulfills their objectives, game support ends, files get corrupted, etc, this is not the case with My Neighbor Alice.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-106900" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/map.jpg" alt="" width="1000" height="700" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/map.jpg 1000w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/map-300x210.jpg 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/map-768x538.jpg 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/map-50x35.jpg 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/map-150x105.jpg 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/map-450x315.jpg 450w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" /></p>
<p>By using NFTs, the game allows players to interact with the world in a whole new different way, transferring ownership in any way they want and unlocking interesting features that traditional in-game assets just don’t possess. This also allows players to, in the team’s words, “exercise power over the platform” through democratic governance. This means not only players get to exercise their creativity over their own islands but all over the virtual world.</p>
<p>Effectively, My Neighbor Alice is an online video game that can be played as a solo or multiplayer adventure, combining an exciting storyline experience most web3 games don’t possess and the creative freedom of a sandbox experience.</p>
<hr />
<h2>Features and Ecosystem</h2>
<p>Bringing blockchain and DeFi capabilities to the world of video games means that My Neighbor Alice has much more to offer than a satisfying gaming experience. In-game assets, virtual land, a decentralized marketplace, trading features, and decentralized governance all come together to create a world in which players are right at the center. Let’s take a look.</p>
<h3><strong>Decentralized Marketplace</strong></h3>
<p>With NFTs being a major pillar of My Neighbor Alice, it is not surprising that its marketplace plays one of the most important roles. However, while marketplaces in other games allow players to buy assets directly from the developers or with an infinite supply, this marketplace operates more similarly to those in the crypto world.</p>
<p><a href="https://play.myneighboralice.com/">My Neighbor Alice’s marketplace</a> is all about letting players buy and sell assets by directly interacting with other players.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-106901" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/marketplace.jpg" alt="" width="1000" height="700" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/marketplace.jpg 1000w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/marketplace-300x210.jpg 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/marketplace-768x538.jpg 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/marketplace-50x35.jpg 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/marketplace-150x105.jpg 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/marketplace-450x315.jpg 450w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" /></p>
<p>Most of these assets have some level of scarcity to them in the sense that they are not generated through infinite in-game faucets. This gives these assets an innate value that goes beyond their appearance, similar to the way that popular blockchain projects like Bored Yacht Ape Club have popularized.</p>
<h3><strong>Lummelunda Archipielago</strong></h3>
<p>Lummelunda Archipelago is the name of the world in which My Neighbor Alice’s titular Alice lives and players get to create. Divided into 6 islands with their own style and ecosystem, players will be able to buy virtual plots from Alice or other players in the marketplace, plots which will transform into something completely unique.</p>
<p>This is the virtual world players get to interact with and share, being the scenario for their very own stories. Players also get to interact with different Non-Player Characters like Alice, Björn the Bear, Beekeeper Bob, Ivan the Merchant, and Shipwright José. These neighbors will provide players with a plethora of content and directions, making the gaming experience much more rewarding and interactive.</p>
<h3><strong>Player Avatars and In-Game Assets</strong></h3>
<p>Identity plays a key role in My Neighbor Alice, and players are represented by customizable avatars that can be shaped in numerous ways. These avatars serve as the player’s identity within the game world, visible to others as they explore and socialize.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-106903" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/assets.jpg" alt="" width="1000" height="700" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/assets.jpg 1000w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/assets-300x210.jpg 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/assets-768x538.jpg 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/assets-50x35.jpg 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/assets-150x105.jpg 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/assets-450x315.jpg 450w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" /></p>
<p>In addition to avatars, players can acquire in-game assets such as houses, animals, decorations, and cosmetic items, all of which can be bought and sold in the marketplace.</p>
<p>Players can also use the NFT creator tool to design their own assets and monetize their creations, opening up new opportunities for creativity and entrepreneurship.</p>
<h3><strong>Progression System</strong></h3>
<p>One of the defining factors of sandbox games is that there is no predefined objective. This, while alluring to many players, can make it difficult for some players to get into the games as they lose focus along the way or are overwhelmed by the sheer freedom. Without clear goals, some may lose focus or feel discouraged, unsure of where to start or what to pursue next.</p>
<p>My Neighbor Alices has a progression system that manages to keep objective-oriented players engaged by providing feedback and general guidance, all without sacrificing player freedom. Players also get rewarded for completing these quests, and even for being recognized as “good citizens”, further developing the social aspect of the game.</p>
<hr />
<h2>The ALICE Token</h2>
<p>The ALICE token is the main currency in My Neighbor Alice, both serving as an in-game asset and as an ERC20 token. With a fixed supply, the token allows holders to engage in various aspects of the game, from purchasing assets and land to participating in governance and DeFi opportunities.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-106906" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/alice.jpg" alt="" width="1000" height="614" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/alice.jpg 1000w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/alice-300x184.jpg 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/alice-768x472.jpg 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/alice-50x31.jpg 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/alice-150x92.jpg 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/alice-450x276.jpg 450w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" /></p>
<p>In addition to its in-game utility, the ALICE token supports decentralized finance (DeFi) features. Token holders can stake ALICE to earn rewards, participate in governance by voting on platform developments, and influence key decisions in the virtual world. This integration of DeFi allows players to earn passive income, control in-game developments, and drive the game&#8217;s evolution.</p>
<hr />
<h2>The Team Behind the Curtain</h2>
<p>The development of My Neighbor Alice is backed by a strong team, with Chromia, a decentralized public blockchain, playing a critical role in the game’s infrastructure.</p>
<p>Chromia started and maintained by ChromaWay, is designed to offer blockchain scalability and ease of use for both developers and users. Its architecture combines relational databases with blockchain technology, making it an ideal solution for complex game designs, particularly those that involve dynamic, on-chain logic.</p>
<p>The game’s investors include names like NGC Ventures, The Sandbox, The Blockchain Game Alliance, Binance Labs, Ankr, Maker, and more. The team has also established important partnerships with brands like Elle, bringing even more customization and value to its players.</p>
<hr />
<h2>Conclusion</h2>
<p><a href="https://www.myneighboralice.com/">My Neighbor Alice</a> is a prime example of how gaming can evolve by embracing both creativity and the growing potential of blockchain technology.</p>
<p>By combining the charm of familiar sandbox games like Animal Crossing with decentralized features such as NFTs and DeFi, it offers players more than just a traditional gaming experience. Players not only get to create and own their virtual world but can also engage with a broader ecosystem that includes decentralized marketplaces, governance, and a progression system that rewards their efforts.</p>
<p>With gaming continuing to grow and solidify its position as a dominating industry, titles like My Neighbor Alice are just what web3 needs to go mainstream. By offering a seamless entry into the world of NFTs, DeFi, and virtual ownership, it is paving the way for the future of gaming to be more inclusive, innovative, and player-driven. Also, it is extremely fun!</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/my-neighbor-alice/">My Neighbor Alice: Bridging Traditional Gaming &#038; Web3 Through Cozy Island Building</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">106755</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>HMSTR Token Drops 66% as Hamster Kombat Experiences Mass Exodus</title>
		<link>https://blockonomi.com/hmstr-token-drops-66-as-hamster-kombat-experiences-mass-exodus/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Oliver Dale]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 10:51:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Gaming]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blockonomi.com/?p=105528</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>TLDR Game lost 259 million players (86% drop) in under 3 months Competitor Paws gained 20.5 million users in just 8 days HMSTR token fell 66% from its peak price Total wallet holders reached 3.5 million despite user decline Game faces regional political challenges and bans In a dramatic shift within the mobile gaming landscape, [...]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/hmstr-token-drops-66-as-hamster-kombat-experiences-mass-exodus/">HMSTR Token Drops 66% as Hamster Kombat Experiences Mass Exodus</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>TLDR</h2>
<ul>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Game lost 259 million players (86% drop) in under 3 months</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Competitor Paws gained 20.5 million users in just 8 days</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">HMSTR token fell 66% from its peak price</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Total wallet holders reached 3.5 million despite user decline</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Game faces regional political challenges and bans</li>
</ul>
<hr />
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">In a dramatic shift within the mobile gaming landscape,<a href="https://cryptobriefing.com/hamster-kombat-decline-millions-2/"> Telegram-based game Hamster Kombat has experienced an unprecedented decline in its user base, losing 259 million players in less than three months.</a></p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The tap-to-earn game, which once boasted a robust community, now reports just 41 million monthly active users as of November 5, 2024.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The numbers paint a stark picture of the gaming platform&#8217;s current trajectory. With an 86% reduction in its player base since August, Hamster Kombat&#8217;s decline coincides with the emergence of a new competitor in the Telegram gaming space.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">This competitor, Paws, a newly launched Telegram Mini App, has demonstrated remarkable growth in its initial launch phase.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">In just eight days, Paws attracted 20.5 million users, suggesting a rapid shift in player preferences within the Telegram gaming ecosystem.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The financial impact of this user exodus is reflected in the performance of Hamster Kombat&#8217;s native token, HMSTR.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The digital asset has experienced a 66% decrease from its peak value of $0.007, recorded on September 26, to $0.0024 as of November 5, according to data from CoinGecko.</p>
<figure id="attachment_105529" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-105529" style="width: 847px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-105529" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/Screenshot-2024-11-06-at-10-48-58-Hamster-Kombat-Price-HMSTR-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko.png" alt="Hamster Kombat Price on CoinGecko" width="847" height="630" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/Screenshot-2024-11-06-at-10-48-58-Hamster-Kombat-Price-HMSTR-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko.png 847w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/Screenshot-2024-11-06-at-10-48-58-Hamster-Kombat-Price-HMSTR-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko-300x223.png 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/Screenshot-2024-11-06-at-10-48-58-Hamster-Kombat-Price-HMSTR-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko-768x571.png 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/Screenshot-2024-11-06-at-10-48-58-Hamster-Kombat-Price-HMSTR-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko-50x37.png 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/Screenshot-2024-11-06-at-10-48-58-Hamster-Kombat-Price-HMSTR-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko-150x112.png 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/Screenshot-2024-11-06-at-10-48-58-Hamster-Kombat-Price-HMSTR-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko-450x335.png 450w" sizes="(max-width: 847px) 100vw, 847px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-105529" class="wp-caption-text">Hamster Kombat Price on<a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/hamster-kombat"> CoinGecko</a></figcaption></figure>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">However, an interesting counterpoint to the declining user numbers emerges in the wallet holder statistics. Despite the sharp drop in active players, the total number of addresses holding HMSTR tokens reached a 30-day high of 3.5 million holders on November 5<a href="https://app.intotheblock.com/coin/HMSTR/ton/deep-dive?group=network&amp;chart=addressStats">, as reported by IntoTheBlock.</a></p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Paws&#8217; rapid ascent in the market is further evidenced by its wallet integration metrics. The platform reports 10 million connected wallets, suggesting strong user engagement with its financial features.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Additionally, Paws has built a social media following of one million users on X (formerly Twitter).</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The challenges facing Hamster Kombat extend beyond market competition. The platform has encountered political headwinds in several regions, with Iranian government officials expressing criticism of the game.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Reports have also emerged suggesting potential bans in Uzbekistan, though these remain unconfirmed.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Regional restrictions and regulatory scrutiny have added another layer of complexity to Hamster Kombat&#8217;s operations.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">These political challenges have likely contributed to the platform&#8217;s difficulty in maintaining its user base in certain geographic areas.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The technical infrastructure of Hamster Kombat remains intact, with the platform continuing to process transactions and maintain its basic gaming functions. The development team maintains active management of the platform&#8217;s technical operations.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The gaming platform&#8217;s economic model, which includes the HMSTR token as a central component, continues to operate despite the reduced user engagement. Transaction volumes have adjusted to reflect the smaller user base.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Looking at user behavior patterns, data suggests that the migration of players from Hamster Kombat to alternative platforms like Paws occurred gradually over the three-month period, rather than in a single mass exodus.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The development team behind Hamster Kombat has responded to these challenges with new initiatives. Their roadmap includes plans to integrate additional payment systems, expand the game offerings, and introduce NFTs as in-game assets.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Market analysts have tracked the daily active user metrics, noting that the decline has shown signs of stabilizing at the current level of 41 million monthly active users. This suggests a core user base remains committed to the platform.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The platform&#8217;s technical performance metrics remain stable, with server uptime and transaction processing continuing to meet operational standards despite the reduced user load.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Recent data from November 5 shows that while new user acquisition has slowed, the platform continues to process gaming transactions and maintain its core services for the remaining active users.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/hmstr-token-drops-66-as-hamster-kombat-experiences-mass-exodus/">HMSTR Token Drops 66% as Hamster Kombat Experiences Mass Exodus</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">105528</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>40M-Player Telegram Game Tomarket Announces Token Launch Details</title>
		<link>https://blockonomi.com/40m-player-telegram-game-tomarket-announces-token-launch-details/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Oliver Dale]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 11:31:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Gaming]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blockonomi.com/?p=105161</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>TLDR Tomarket launching TOMA token on TON blockchain this Halloween (Oct 31, 2024) Game offering Premium Medal for 1 TON/$5 that boosts airdrop allocation Only 200,000 Premium Medals available for purchase Premium Medal holders get 100% of tokens at launch vs partial allocation Game has reached over 40 million players, plans to add &#8220;Farming Pool&#8221; [...]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/40m-player-telegram-game-tomarket-announces-token-launch-details/">40M-Player Telegram Game Tomarket Announces Token Launch Details</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>TLDR</h2>
<ul>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Tomarket launching TOMA token on TON blockchain this Halloween (Oct 31, 2024)</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Game offering Premium Medal for 1 TON/$5 that boosts airdrop allocation</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Only 200,000 Premium Medals available for purchase</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Premium Medal holders get 100% of tokens at launch vs partial allocation</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Game has reached over 40 million players, plans to add &#8220;Farming Pool&#8221; feature post-launch</li>
</ul>
<hr />
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words"><a href="https://tomarket.ai/">Tomarket,</a> the popular Telegram-based game with over 40 million players, is preparing for its token launch this Halloween with a new premium feature that promises to boost early adopters&#8217; rewards.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The game&#8217;s developers announced on Monday that players can now purchase a Premium Medal, priced at either 1 TON or 250 Telegram stars, roughly equivalent to $5.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The Premium Medal system introduces several benefits for holders, with the primary feature being an enhanced multiplier for the upcoming TOMA token allocation.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Users who purchase the medal will receive their entire token allocation immediately upon launch, while non-premium users may face a vesting period for their tokens.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The development team has limited the Premium Medal supply to 200,000 units, creating a cap on the number of users who can access these enhanced benefits.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">This scarcity model follows similar approaches seen in other successful token launches within the cryptocurrency gaming sector.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The token launch is scheduled for Thursday, October 31, 2024, at approximately 12 pm ET. According to a Tomarket representative, players can expect to receive their airdrop allocations within 24 hours of the token generation event.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The game&#8217;s structure revolves around earning in-game tomatoes, which function as points, and gold coins that help players advance through various levels. Players must achieve at least a Bronze level status to qualify for the upcoming token airdrop.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Premium Medal holders will gain additional advantages beyond the immediate token allocation. The development team has indicated that medal owners will receive bonus multipliers for future features and services, though specific details about these benefits remain under wraps.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The game&#8217;s earning mechanics include various activities such as farming tomatoes over three-hour periods, participating in a mini-game involving falling tomatoes, and completing tasks that direct players to YouTube videos and other Telegram communities.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Looking beyond the token launch, Tomarket&#8217;s developers have announced plans for a &#8220;Farming Pool&#8221; feature.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">This new addition will enable TOMA token holders to access farming opportunities for new projects and earn rewards by referring friends to these initiatives.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The Premium Medal&#8217;s pricing structure offers two payment options: <a href="https://moneycheck.com/best-ton-casinos/">1 TON</a> or 250 Telegram stars. This dual-currency approach provides flexibility for users already invested in either ecosystem.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The development team has implemented a straightforward distribution system for the airdrop. Unlike some previous token launches in the space that involved complex vesting schedules, Tomarket&#8217;s Premium Medal offers a clear path to immediate token access.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">For standard users who choose not to purchase the Premium Medal, the exact vesting schedule for their token allocations has not been revealed.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">This approach bears some resemblance to other successful Telegram-based games, such as Hamster Kombat, which implemented a months-long vesting schedule for player rewards.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The Premium Medal interface within the game displays the available benefits clearly, though the exact multiplication factor for token allocations remains undisclosed. The development team has not yet responded to requests for clarification on the specific multiplier values.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Players can currently access these features through the Telegram mini app, where the game continues to operate as usual leading up to the token launch. The gaming mechanics remain unchanged, with players still able to earn tomatoes and gold coins through regular gameplay.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Daily engagement remains a key focus, with the game offering various combinations of activities that players can complete to maximize their potential token earnings before the October 31 launch date.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/40m-player-telegram-game-tomarket-announces-token-launch-details/">40M-Player Telegram Game Tomarket Announces Token Launch Details</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">105161</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Gambling Market Statistics Report for 2024 by Blockonomi</title>
		<link>https://blockonomi.com/crypto-gambling-stats/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Oliver Dale]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2024 10:51:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Gaming]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blockonomi.com/?p=104717</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The cryptocurrency gambling industry has emerged as one of the fastest-growing segments in both the digital currency and online gaming sectors. The global crypto gambling market has surged from $50 million in 2019 to an impressive $250 million in 2024, marking a watershed moment in the convergence of digital assets and online gaming entertainment. This [...]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/crypto-gambling-stats/">Crypto Gambling Market Statistics Report for 2024 by Blockonomi</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The cryptocurrency gambling industry has emerged as one of the fastest-growing segments in both the digital currency and online gaming sectors.</p>
<p>The global crypto gambling market has surged from $50 million in 2019 to an impressive $250 million in 2024, marking a watershed moment in the convergence of digital assets and online gaming entertainment.</p>
<p>This growth trajectory, represented by a compound annual growth rate (CAGR) of 38% over the past five years, signals a fundamental shift in how players engage with online gambling platforms.</p>
<p>The market&#8217;s expansion reflects not only growing consumer confidence in cryptocurrency transactions but also the increasing sophistication of blockchain-based gaming technologies.</p>
<p>This comprehensive analysis explores the key drivers, trends, and challenges shaping the crypto gambling landscape in 2024, offering insights into market dynamics, user behavior, and future growth prospects.</p>
<hr />
<h2>Market Size and Growth</h2>
<p>The global crypto gambling market has experienced exponential growth in recent years. In 2024, it&#8217;s valued at approximately $250 million, up from $50 million in 2019. This represents a compound annual growth rate (CAGR) of nearly 38% over five years.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-104730" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/growth.jpg" alt="" width="1000" height="700" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/growth.jpg 1000w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/growth-300x210.jpg 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/growth-768x538.jpg 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/growth-50x35.jpg 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/growth-150x105.jpg 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/growth-450x315.jpg 450w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" /></p>
<h2>Betting Volume and Transactions</h2>
<p>The total value of crypto bets has seen a dramatic increase:</p>
<ul>
<li>In 2022, crypto gamblers placed nearly 3 billion in bets during the first half of the year</li>
<li>This doubled to 6.3 billion within a year</li>
<li>By Q1 2023, total crypto bets had increased by 44.6% compared to the previous year</li>
<li>The number of cryptocurrency bets has skyrocketed by 83.6% compared to mid-2022</li>
<li>Crypto transactions now account for nearly 30% of all wagers, up from 20% in 2022</li>
</ul>
<h2>Preferred Cryptocurrencies</h2>
<p>While Bitcoin remains dominant, other cryptocurrencies are gaining traction:</p>
<div>
<table>
<thead>
<tr>
<th>Cryptocurrency</th>
<th>Market Share</th>
</tr>
</thead>
<tbody>
<tr>
<td>Bitcoin</td>
<td>73.3%</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>Ethereum</td>
<td>14.5%</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>Litecoin</td>
<td>6.8%</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>Tether (USDT)</td>
<td>3.2%</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>Dogecoin</td>
<td>2.7%</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
</div>
<h2>Popular Games and Betting Trends</h2>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-104731" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/games-1.jpg" alt="" width="1000" height="700" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/games-1.jpg 1000w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/games-1-300x210.jpg 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/games-1-768x538.jpg 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/games-1-50x35.jpg 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/games-1-150x105.jpg 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/games-1-450x315.jpg 450w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" /></p>
<div>
<div>
<div></div>
</div>
</div>
<h2>Emerging trends:</h2>
<ul>
<li>eSports betting with cryptocurrencies has grown by 35% since 2023.</li>
<li>Live dealer games have seen a 28% increase in popularity among crypto gamblers.</li>
</ul>
<h2>User Demographics</h2>
<ul>
<li>Age distribution:
<ul>
<li>25-34: 40%</li>
<li>35-44: 30%</li>
<li>18-24: 15%</li>
<li>45-54: 10%</li>
<li>55+: 5%</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Gender: 70% male, 30% female</li>
<li>Education: 60% have a bachelor&#8217;s degree or higher</li>
</ul>
<h2>Mobile Gaming</h2>
<p>Mobile crypto gambling has seen significant growth:</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-104732" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/mobile-2.jpg" alt="" width="1000" height="700" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/mobile-2.jpg 1000w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/mobile-2-300x210.jpg 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/mobile-2-768x538.jpg 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/mobile-2-50x35.jpg 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/mobile-2-150x105.jpg 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/mobile-2-450x315.jpg 450w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" /></p>
<div>
<div>
<div></div>
</div>
</div>
<h2>Regional Adoption</h2>
<p>Crypto gambling adoption varies significantly by region:</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<div>
<div>
<div><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-104733" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/region-1.jpg" alt="" width="1000" height="700" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/region-1.jpg 1000w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/region-1-300x210.jpg 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/region-1-768x538.jpg 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/region-1-50x35.jpg 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/region-1-150x105.jpg 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/region-1-450x315.jpg 450w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" /></div>
</div>
</div>
<h2>Regulatory Landscape</h2>
<p>The regulatory environment for crypto gambling is evolving:</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-104734" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/regulation-2.jpg" alt="" width="1000" height="700" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/regulation-2.jpg 1000w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/regulation-2-300x210.jpg 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/regulation-2-768x538.jpg 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/regulation-2-50x35.jpg 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/regulation-2-150x105.jpg 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/regulation-2-450x315.jpg 450w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" /></p>
<div>
<div>
<div></div>
</div>
</div>
<h2>Security and Fraud Prevention</h2>
<ul>
<li>Blockchain technology has reduced fraud in crypto casinos by 60% compared to traditional online casinos.</li>
<li>95% of crypto casinos now use multi-factor authentication for enhanced security.</li>
<li>The implementation of smart contracts has increased transparency by 40%.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Future Outlook</h2>
<p>The crypto gambling industry is expected to continue its growth trajectory:</p>
<ul>
<li>Projected market size by 2028: $400 million</li>
<li>Expected CAGR from 2024 to 2028: 12.5%</li>
<li>Anticipated share of global online gambling market by 2026: 15%</li>
</ul>
<p>Key drivers for future growth include:</p>
<ol>
<li>Increased mainstream acceptance of cryptocurrencies</li>
<li>Advancements in blockchain technology</li>
<li>Growing interest in decentralized finance (DeFi) gambling platforms</li>
<li>Integration of virtual reality (VR) and augmented reality (AR) in crypto casinos</li>
</ol>
<p>Challenges remain, including regulatory uncertainties and cryptocurrency volatility. However, the industry is adapting rapidly, with 80% of crypto casinos now offering stablecoin options to mitigate volatility concerns.</p>
<hr />
<h2>Key Findings</h2>
<h3>Market Growth &amp; Financial Metrics</h3>
<ul>
<li>Market valuation increased 5x from $50M (2019) to $250M (2024)</li>
<li>Achieved 38% CAGR over five-year period</li>
<li>Betting volume doubled to 6.3B within one year</li>
<li>Q1 2023 showed 44.6% year-over-year growth in total bets</li>
<li>Cryptocurrency now represents 30% of all wagers, up from 20% in 2022</li>
</ul>
<h3>Cryptocurrency Usage Breakdown</h3>
<ul>
<li><a href="https://blockonomi.com/best-bitcoin-casino/">Bitcoin</a> dominates with 73.3% market share</li>
<li><a href="https://blockonomi.com/best-ethereum-casino/">Ethereum</a> holds second position at 14.5%</li>
<li>Alternative cryptocurrencies gaining traction:
<ul>
<li><a href="https://blockonomi.com/best-litecoin-casino/">Litecoin</a>: 6.8%</li>
<li><a href="https://blockonomi.com/best-tether-casino/">Tether</a> (USDT): 3.2%</li>
<li><a href="https://blockonomi.com/best-dogecoin-casino/">Dogecoin</a>: 2.7%</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h3>User Demographics &amp; Behavior</h3>
<ul>
<li>Core user base concentrated in 25-44 age range (70%)</li>
<li>Gender distribution shows male dominance (70% male, 30% female)</li>
<li>High education levels: 60% hold bachelor&#8217;s degree or higher</li>
<li>Mobile adoption trending upward:
<ul>
<li>2022: 50% mobile bets</li>
<li>2024: 65% mobile bets</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h3>Regional &amp; Game Preferences</h3>
<ul>
<li>European market leads adoption at 40%</li>
<li>Asia follows closely at 35%</li>
<li>Game popularity distribution:
<ul>
<li>Slots dominate at 52%</li>
<li>Roulette accounts for 25%</li>
<li>Blackjack and Poker each hold 10%</li>
<li>Other games comprise 3%</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h3>Security &amp; Technical Achievements</h3>
<ul>
<li>60% reduction in fraud compared to traditional online casinos</li>
<li>95% implementation rate of multi-factor authentication</li>
<li>40% increase in transparency through smart contracts</li>
<li>80% of platforms now offer stablecoin options</li>
</ul>
<h3>Key Trends</h3>
<ol>
<li>Substantial growth in eSports betting (35% increase since 2023)</li>
<li>Rising popularity of live dealer games (28% increase)</li>
<li>Accelerating mobile adoption</li>
<li>Strong regulatory development (75% of jurisdictions either have or are developing regulations)</li>
</ol>
<h3>Insights</h3>
<ol>
<li>The market shows consistent growth across all major metrics, indicating sustainable expansion rather than speculative inflation.</li>
<li>Mobile adoption and technological integration are primary drivers of market growth.</li>
<li>Regional disparities in adoption present significant growth opportunities, particularly in emerging markets.</li>
<li>Security improvements and regulatory development suggest increasing market maturity.</li>
<li>Demographic data indicates potential for market expansion beyond current core user base.</li>
</ol>
<hr />
<h2>Future Predictions</h2>
<p>The crypto gambling industry stands at the cusp of a transformative period, with market projections indicating a surge to $400 million by 2028.</p>
<p>This growth trajectory will likely be accompanied by significant market consolidation, as major traditional gambling operators begin acquiring crypto-native platforms.</p>
<p>The technological evolution of the industry will be particularly noteworthy over the next four years. Virtual Reality casinos are projected to capture 20% of crypto bets by 2026, while artificial intelligence will revolutionize personalized gaming experiences.</p>
<p>Smart contract automation is expected to streamline operations, potentially reducing operational costs by 40%. Perhaps most significantly, platforms will need to implement quantum-resistant encryption by 2027 to stay ahead of emerging security challenges.</p>
<p>Mobile technology will continue to dominate the industry&#8217;s development trajectory. By 2026, mobile betting is expected to account for 80% of all crypto gambling activity, with cross-platform integration becoming standard by 2025.</p>
<p>This shift will drive the creation of mobile-exclusive games and features, fundamentally changing how users interact with gambling platforms. The integration of social elements will further transform the user experience, with multiplayer experiences and tournament-style events becoming mainstream offerings.</p>
<p>The financial landscape of crypto gambling will undergo its own evolution. While Bitcoin&#8217;s dominance is expected to decrease to 60% by 2026, we&#8217;ll likely see the rise of gambling-specific tokens and increased integration of stablecoins.</p>
<p>The industry will also likely begin incorporating central bank digital currencies (CBDCs) by 2027, adding another layer of complexity to payment options. Transaction volumes are projected to exceed $10 billion by 2026, with average user deposit amounts increasing by 30%.</p>
<p>Regulatory developments will play a crucial role in shaping the industry&#8217;s future. By 2026, we anticipate the implementation of standardized international frameworks for crypto gambling, accompanied by <a href="https://blockonomi.com/best-no-kyc-casinos/">universal KYC/AML standards.</a></p>
<p>Dedicated crypto gambling licensing bodies will emerge, necessitating the development of automated compliance systems and real-time regulatory reporting capabilities. These changes will help legitimize the industry while potentially causing temporary market contractions during adjustment periods.</p>
<p>The gaming landscape itself will continue to evolve, with skill-based crypto gambling games gaining prominence and the lines between traditional gambling and gaming becoming increasingly blurred.</p>
<p>Technical innovations will support this evolution, with Layer-2 solutions expected to reduce transaction costs by 90% and cross-chain compatibility becoming standard. Zero-knowledge proofs will enhance privacy features, addressing growing user concerns about data protection.</p>
<p>Regional developments will significantly influence the industry&#8217;s growth patterns. The Asian market share is projected to grow to 40% by 2026, while Latin American adoption is expected to double by 2025. The African market shows particular promise, with predictions of the highest growth rate at 45% CAGR. Each region will develop its own unique characteristics, from localized cryptocurrency preferences to market-specific regulatory compliance requirements.</p>
<p>Success in this evolving landscape will depend on several critical factors. Platforms must prioritize enhanced security measures, maintain strict regulatory compliance, and continuously optimize user experience.</p>
<p>Mobile platform development and innovative game design will become increasingly important differentiators. Risk mitigation strategies, including cryptocurrency diversification and robust AML/KYC procedures, will be essential for long-term sustainability.</p>
<hr />
<h2>Conclusion</h2>
<p>The crypto gambling industry stands at a pivotal moment in its evolution. From its modest beginnings of $50 million in 2019 to its current valuation of $250 million in 2024, the sector has demonstrated remarkable resilience and growth potential. This five-fold increase over five years reflects not just market expansion, but a fundamental shift in how digital entertainment and blockchain technology intersect.</p>
<p>The data presents a compelling narrative of an industry in transition. With cryptocurrency transactions now representing 30% of all wagers, up from 20% in 2022, we&#8217;re witnessing the normalization of digital currency in gambling operations. The dominance of Bitcoin at 73.3% market share, while still significant, is gradually giving way to a more diverse cryptocurrency ecosystem, suggesting a maturing market that can support multiple digital payment options.</p>
<p>Perhaps most telling is the demographic shift occurring within the user base. The concentration of users in the 25-44 age range (70%) and the high proportion of educated participants (60% with bachelor&#8217;s degrees or higher) indicates an informed, technologically savvy customer base that&#8217;s likely to drive further innovation. The increasing mobile adoption rate, now at 65% of all bets, points to a future where accessibility and convenience will be paramount.</p>
<p>The regulatory landscape, while still evolving, shows promising signs of maturation. With 75% of jurisdictions either implementing or developing specific regulations, the industry is moving toward a more structured and secure operating environment. This regulatory framework, combined with the 60% reduction in fraud compared to traditional online casinos, suggests a future where crypto gambling can shed its early associations with regulatory uncertainty.</p>
<p>Looking ahead to 2028, the projected market size of $400 million represents more than just financial growth – it signifies the potential emergence of crypto gambling as a mainstream entertainment option. The expected 12.5% CAGR from 2024 to 2028 indicates sustainable growth rather than speculative expansion, while the anticipated 15% share of the global online gambling market by 2026 suggests increasing integration with traditional gambling sectors.</p>
<p>The success of crypto gambling will ultimately depend on its ability to balance three key factors: technological innovation, regulatory compliance, and user experience. Platforms that can maintain this balance while adapting to regional preferences and evolving security requirements will be best positioned to capitalize on the industry&#8217;s growth potential.</p>
<hr />
<h3>Sources:</h3>
<ul>
<li style="list-style-type: none;">
<ul>
<li>https://www.antiersolutions.com/whats-driving-the-crypto-development-craze-for-online-gambling-in-2024/</li>
<li>https://casinosblockchain.io/stats-and-fun-facts/</li>
<li>https://www.bitget.com/news/detail/12560604167773</li>
<li>https://www.ibdgaming.com/igaming-news/the-explosive-growth-of-crypto-casinos-in-2024</li>
<li>https://playtoday.co/blog/stats/crypto-gambling-statistics/</li>
<li>https://www.cryptolists.com/learn/crypto-market/</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/crypto-gambling-stats/">Crypto Gambling Market Statistics Report for 2024 by Blockonomi</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">104717</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>&#8220;Off The Grid&#8221; Leads Epic Games Store: Blockchain Gaming Gains Traction</title>
		<link>https://blockonomi.com/off-the-grid-leads-epic-games-store-blockchain-gaming-gains-traction/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Oliver Dale]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 10:13:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Gaming]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blockonomi.com/?p=104090</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>TLDR &#8220;Off The Grid&#8221; is currently the #1 free-to-play game on Epic Games store The game uses blockchain features built on an Avalanche subnet called GUNZ Players can mint in-game items as NFTs, allowing for secondary markets Off The Grid represents a shift from token-focused to gameplay-focused blockchain games A recent survey found wallet complexity [...]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/off-the-grid-leads-epic-games-store-blockchain-gaming-gains-traction/">&#8220;Off The Grid&#8221; Leads Epic Games Store: Blockchain Gaming Gains Traction</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>TLDR</h2>
<ul>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">&#8220;Off The Grid&#8221; is currently the #1 free-to-play game on Epic Games store</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">The game uses blockchain features built on an Avalanche subnet called GUNZ</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Players can mint in-game items as NFTs, allowing for secondary markets</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Off The Grid represents a shift from token-focused to gameplay-focused blockchain games</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">A recent survey found wallet complexity as a major barrier to blockchain gaming adoption</li>
</ul>
<hr />
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words"><a href="https://gameoffthegrid.com">&#8220;Off The Grid,&#8221;</a> a free-to-play battle royale game developed by Gunzilla Games, has climbed to the number one spot on the Epic Games store&#8217;s free-to-play chart.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">This early-access title has also gained significant traction on Twitch, with over <a href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/off-the-grid-exposes-mainstream-audiences-blockchain-gaming">150,000 viewers tuning in to watch streamers play the game on October 11.</a></p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">What sets &#8220;Off The Grid&#8221; apart from many other blockchain-based games is its focus on creating a compelling gameplay experience first, with blockchain elements integrated to enhance player ownership and control over in-game assets.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The game&#8217;s blockchain features are built on an Avalanche subnet called GUNZ, which allows players to mint non-fungible tokens (NFTs) representing in-game items such as weapons and skins.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">This approach to blockchain gaming represents a departure from earlier models that prioritized token economics over gameplay.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Many critics have argued that these token-centric games are not sustainable, as they often see a sharp decline in user numbers following initial airdrops or reward distributions.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">By allowing players to mint in-game items as NFTs, &#8220;Off The Grid&#8221; ensures that players maintain control over their virtual assets and enables the emergence of secondary markets.</p>
<figure id="attachment_104091" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-104091" style="width: 1920px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-104091" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/media-6.webp" alt="Off The Grid" width="1920" height="1080" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/media-6.webp 1920w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/media-6-300x169.webp 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/media-6-1400x788.webp 1400w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/media-6-768x432.webp 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/media-6-1536x864.webp 1536w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/media-6-50x28.webp 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/media-6-150x84.webp 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/media-6-450x253.webp 450w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/media-6-1200x675.webp 1200w" sizes="(max-width: 1920px) 100vw, 1920px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-104091" class="wp-caption-text"><a href="https://gameoffthegrid.com/#gallery">Off The Grid</a></figcaption></figure>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">This model aims to provide long-term value to players beyond immediate token rewards.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The success of &#8220;Off The Grid&#8221; comes at a time when the blockchain gaming industry is facing challenges in user adoption. A recent survey conducted by Elympics, the Blockchain Game Alliance, and PlayToEarn highlighted some of these hurdles.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The study, which polled over 1,000 individuals worldwide, found that more than 10% of respondents had never tried blockchain games, citing the complexity of connecting crypto wallets as a major deterrent.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Interestingly, the same survey revealed that approximately 57% of respondents said they played pay-to-win games to collect airdrops.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">This statistic underscores the ongoing appeal of reward-based gaming models, even as the industry seeks to evolve towards more sustainable and engaging gameplay experiences.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">As a AAA title, &#8220;Off The Grid&#8221; represents a significant step towards bridging the gap between traditional gaming and blockchain technology.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">By prioritizing gameplay and user experience while incorporating blockchain elements, the game aims to attract mainstream gamers who might otherwise be hesitant to engage with crypto-based games.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The game&#8217;s success on the Epic Games store and Twitch suggests that there is indeed an appetite for high-quality blockchain games among mainstream audiences.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">If &#8220;Off The Grid&#8221; can maintain its popularity and demonstrate the benefits of blockchain integration in gaming, it could pave the way for more widespread adoption of blockchain technology in the gaming industry.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/off-the-grid-leads-epic-games-store-blockchain-gaming-gains-traction/">&#8220;Off The Grid&#8221; Leads Epic Games Store: Blockchain Gaming Gains Traction</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">104090</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Exploring Rocky Rabbit: A Project Making Waves in the Gaming World</title>
		<link>https://blockonomi.com/exploring-rocky-rabbit-a-project-making-waves-in-the-gaming-world/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[CryptoPR]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 08:32:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Gaming]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blockchain]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blockonomi.com/?p=103482</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In the fast-evolving world of digital gaming, projects come and go. Some capture fleeting attention, while others make a lasting impact by redefining engagement and community interaction. One project that is making a mark in this ever-competitive space is the Rocky Rabbit initiative. With its impressive traction, strong social presence, and a commitment to transparency, [...]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/exploring-rocky-rabbit-a-project-making-waves-in-the-gaming-world/">Exploring Rocky Rabbit: A Project Making Waves in the Gaming World</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400">In the fast-evolving world of digital gaming, projects come and go. Some capture fleeting attention, while others make a lasting impact by redefining engagement and community interaction. One project that is making a mark in this ever-competitive space is the </span><b>Rocky Rabbit</b><span style="font-weight: 400"> initiative. With its impressive traction, strong social presence, and a commitment to transparency, Rocky Rabbit has rapidly grown into a standout contender in the digital entertainment and blockchain space.</span></p>
<h3><b>The Rise of Rocky Rabbit: Understanding Its Traction</b></h3>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The numbers behind Rocky Rabbit speak volumes about its success and appeal. To date, the project has garnered over </span><b>29 million players</b><span style="font-weight: 400">, a staggering figure that places it among the most widely played games in its category. This large player base is not just a statistic—it is a testament to the appeal of Rocky Rabbit’s content, game mechanics, and overall user experience. In a sector where attracting players is hard and retaining them is even harder, Rocky Rabbit has managed to strike the perfect balance.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">But what’s even more impressive is the level of engagement within this vast community. Every 30 minutes, over </span><b>700,000 users</b><span style="font-weight: 400"> are active on the platform, highlighting a level of participation that goes beyond casual play. This sustained engagement is often the hallmark of a well-designed game that offers ongoing value and entertainment to its players. It suggests that Rocky Rabbit has tapped into something uniquely compelling, making it more than just a one-time attraction.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Daily and monthly active user metrics further solidify Rocky Rabbit’s place as a leader in the space. With </span><b>6 million daily active users (DAU)</b><span style="font-weight: 400"> and </span><b>18 million monthly active users (MAU)</b><span style="font-weight: 400">, the project has managed to build a community that isn’t just large, but consistently engaged. For any game or digital platform, DAU and MAU are crucial indicators of health and longevity. They show that players are not only trying out the game but are returning to it regularly—a feat that only a few projects manage to achieve.</span></p>
<h3><b>Building a Thriving Community: The Role of Social Media</b></h3>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Beyond just attracting players, Rocky Rabbit has also succeeded in creating a thriving community across various social platforms. Social media plays a crucial role in any project’s outreach, engagement, and growth, and Rocky Rabbit’s numbers here are equally impressive.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">On </span><b>Telegram</b><span style="font-weight: 400">, one of the go-to platforms for many digital communities, Rocky Rabbit has amassed a following of over </span><b>9.5 million</b><span style="font-weight: 400"> users. This massive presence highlights the project’s ability to foster discussions, provide updates, and build a sense of belonging among its community members. Telegram is particularly important for blockchain-based projects, as it serves as a direct line of communication between developers and users.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Meanwhile, on </span><a href="https://x.com/rockyrabbitio"><b>X</b></a><span style="font-weight: 400">, Rocky Rabbit has </span><b>1.5 million</b><span style="font-weight: 400"> followers, showcasing its reach and influence on a platform known for real-time updates and industry conversations. Twitter is where many gaming and blockchain enthusiasts congregate to share insights, discuss trends, and engage with project updates. Rocky Rabbit’s presence here is indicative of its proactive approach to keeping its community informed and engaged.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">But the project’s reach doesn’t end there. With </span><b>2.9 million</b><span style="font-weight: 400"> followers on </span><a href="https://www.instagram.com/rockyrabbitio/"><b>Instagram</b></a><span style="font-weight: 400">, Rocky Rabbit has tapped into a visually driven audience that values creativity, aesthetics, and bite-sized updates. Instagram is a powerful tool for showcasing game art, behind-the-scenes content, and community highlights. Rocky Rabbit’s success on this platform suggests that it understands the power of visual storytelling in building deeper connections with its audience.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Additionally, the project’s </span><b>2.4 million</b><span style="font-weight: 400"> subscribers on </span><a href="https://www.youtube.com/@rockyrabbitio"><b>YouTube</b></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> underscore its commitment to multimedia engagement. YouTube is a unique platform for gaming communities, offering a space for tutorials, walkthroughs, event live streams, and more. Having such a large subscriber base here means that Rocky Rabbit is leveraging video content effectively to complement its other social strategies.</span></p>
<h3><b>Transparency and Accessibility: Making Information Available</b></h3>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">A key component of Rocky Rabbit’s success is its commitment to transparency and ease of access to information. In the world of digital gaming and blockchain, clarity and openness are paramount for building trust. Rocky Rabbit has made a variety of resources readily available for its community and potential newcomers, ensuring that everyone has access to the information they need to make informed decisions.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">For those looking to learn more, Rocky Rabbit offers a </span><a href="https://rockyrabbit.io"><b>game website</b></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> that serves as a hub for all things related to its offerings. Here, users can explore game features, updates, and community events. Additionally, the </span><a href="https://rabbitcoin.org"><b>token website</b></a> <span style="font-weight: 400">provides insights into the project’s cryptocurrency elements, making it easier for both gamers and investors to understand the ecosystem.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Beyond these websites, Rocky Rabbit’s detailed </span><a href="https://rockyrabbit.io/docs/RockyRabbit_Whitepaperv0.2.pdf"><b>whitepaper</b></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> and </span><a href="https://rockyrabbit.io/docs/RockyRabbit_Deck2024_v0.2.pdf"><b>project deck</b></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> offer an in-depth look into its vision, goals, and technical structure. These documents are crucial for anyone looking to delve deeper into the project’s mechanics and long-term roadmap. Furthermore, being listed on prominent platforms like </span><a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/rockyrabbit/"><b>Coinmarketcap</b></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> and</span><a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/rabbitcoin"> <b>Coingecko</b> </a><span style="font-weight: 400">gives the project additional credibility and visibility in the broader blockchain and crypto community.</span></p>
<h3><b>The Road Ahead: What Makes Rocky Rabbit Unique</b></h3>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">So, what sets Rocky Rabbit apart from the multitude of other gaming projects out there? It’s a combination of engaging content, strong community ties, and a commitment to transparency. While many projects struggle to maintain momentum after the initial hype, Rocky Rabbit has built a foundation that is likely to sustain its growth in the long run.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">By focusing on creating a robust ecosystem that values its players, engaging with its community across multiple channels, and providing transparent access to information, Rocky Rabbit is positioning itself as more than just a game—it’s becoming a thriving digital world that invites players and enthusiasts to be a part of something bigger.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">As the project continues to evolve, it will be interesting to see how Rocky Rabbit leverages its strong community and engagement metrics to push the boundaries of what’s possible in digital gaming and blockchain integration. With its impressive traction and strong foundations, Rocky Rabbit is well on its way to becoming a major player in the digital entertainment space.</span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/exploring-rocky-rabbit-a-project-making-waves-in-the-gaming-world/">Exploring Rocky Rabbit: A Project Making Waves in the Gaming World</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">103482</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum Card Game &#8216;Shardbound&#8217; Enters Open Beta on Major Gaming Platforms</title>
		<link>https://blockonomi.com/ethereum-card-game-shardbound-enters-open-beta-on-major-gaming-platforms/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Oliver Dale]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 09:40:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gaming]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NFTs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blockonomi.com/?p=103442</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>TLDR Shardbound, an Ethereum strategy card game, enters open beta on October 9 Available on Steam and Epic Games Store without NFT integration initially Blends deck-building, card-collecting, and turn-based battlefield elements NFTs will be available separately, with plans for future in-game integration Originally crowdfunded in 2017, now revived with Web3 elements by new developers Shardbound, [...]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/ethereum-card-game-shardbound-enters-open-beta-on-major-gaming-platforms/">Ethereum Card Game &#8216;Shardbound&#8217; Enters Open Beta on Major Gaming Platforms</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>TLDR</h2>
<ul>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Shardbound, an Ethereum strategy card game, enters open beta on October 9</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Available on Steam and Epic Games Store without NFT integration initially</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Blends deck-building, card-collecting, and turn-based battlefield elements</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">NFTs will be available separately, with plans for future in-game integration</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Originally crowdfunded in 2017, now revived with Web3 elements by new developers</li>
</ul>
<hr />
<p><a href="https://www.shardbound.com/">Shardbound</a>, a strategy card game built on the Ethereum layer-2 scaling network Immutable zkEVM, is set to enter open beta on October 9, 2024.</p>
<p>The game will be available on both Steam and the Epic Games Store, marking a significant step in its development journey that began with a Kickstarter campaign in 2017.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Developed by Bazooka Tango and published by Immutable Games, Shardbound combines elements of deck-building and card-collecting games with turn-based battlefield fighting.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The game has been described as a blend of popular titles like Hearthstone and Fire Emblem, with additional role-playing elements.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">One of Shardbound&#8217;s key features is its multiple paths to victory. Players can craft decks focused on all-out war for a military victory or prepare for more strategic approaches to achieve an economic victory.</p>
<p><iframe class="youtube-player" width="814" height="458" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/z5AeP9wLgGo?version=3&#038;rel=1&#038;showsearch=0&#038;showinfo=1&#038;iv_load_policy=1&#038;fs=1&#038;hl=en-US&#038;autohide=2&#038;start=1&#038;wmode=transparent" allowfullscreen="true" style="border:0;" sandbox="allow-scripts allow-same-origin allow-popups allow-presentation allow-popups-to-escape-sandbox"></iframe></p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">This mechanic is reminiscent of the classic strategy series Sid Meier&#8217;s Civilization, offering players diverse strategies to explore.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The open beta period will run for an undefined length of time. Bazooka Tango co-founder and CTO Stephan Sherman explained that the duration will depend on community feedback and how quickly the team can adapt and improve the game.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">While <a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/586030/Shardbound_Forge_Your_Path_Master_Your_Strategy/">Shardbound is built on blockchain technology, the initial release on Steam</a> and Epic Games Store will not include direct NFT integration due to platform restrictions.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">However, players will receive NFTs that match their in-game cards, either sent to a connected Immutable Passport wallet or claimable via an emailed redemption code.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The developers have stated that they are carefully crafting their Web3 strategy to ensure compliance with platform rules while maintaining a consistent player experience across all platforms.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">More details about future in-game NFT integration are expected to be shared in the coming weeks.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Shardbound&#8217;s journey to this point has been long and winding. Originally funded through Kickstarter in 2017, the game only resulted in an incomplete &#8220;Early Access&#8221; release by Spiritwalk Games.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Bazooka Tango and Immutable Games acquired the rights to the game last year and began working on adding Web3 elements to revitalize the project.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The game allows players to trade cards as NFTs and upgrade them to suit different play styles. However, the full extent of the planned Web3 implementation remains under wraps, with Sherman hinting at exciting developments to come.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">As the open beta launches, the developers are focusing on gathering player feedback and rapidly iterating on the game. They aim to create the best possible experience before moving to a full release.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The launch of Shardbound&#8217;s open beta represents a significant moment in the blockchain gaming space, as it brings a Web3 game to major traditional gaming platforms.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">While the initial release will not feature direct NFT integration, it sets the stage for potential future developments that could bridge the gap between conventional and blockchain-based gaming.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/ethereum-card-game-shardbound-enters-open-beta-on-major-gaming-platforms/">Ethereum Card Game &#8216;Shardbound&#8217; Enters Open Beta on Major Gaming Platforms</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">103442</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>HMSTR Token Drops 42% in First Three Days of Trading</title>
		<link>https://blockonomi.com/hmstr-token-drops-42-in-first-three-days-of-trading/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Oliver Dale]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 08:57:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Gaming]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blockonomi.com/?p=103219</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>TLDR HMSTR token dropped 14% in one day, 42% in three days Current price: $0.005613, all-time low reached on Sunday Market cap: $365 million, ranked 193rd among cryptocurrencies 64,375,000,000 HMSTR in circulation, $248 million traded in 24 hours Top 5 wallets hold 93.95% of total HMSTR supply The TON-based cryptocurrency Hamster Kombat (HMSTR) has seen [...]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/hmstr-token-drops-42-in-first-three-days-of-trading/">HMSTR Token Drops 42% in First Three Days of Trading</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>TLDR</h2>
<ul>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">HMSTR token dropped 14% in one day, 42% in three days</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Current price: $0.005613, all-time low reached on Sunday</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Market cap: $365 million, ranked 193rd among cryptocurrencies</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">64,375,000,000 HMSTR in circulation, $248 million traded in 24 hours</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Top 5 wallets hold 93.95% of total HMSTR supply</li>
</ul>
<hr />
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The TON-based cryptocurrency<a href="https://blockonomi.com/hamster-kombat-token-launch-faces-backlash-as-hmstr-price-plummets-users-cry-foul/"> Hamster Kombat (HMSTR) has seen a substantial decline in value since its recent launch. </a></p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Data from Sunday, September 29, 2024, shows that the token&#8217;s price fell by 14% against the U.S. dollar in a single day, contributing to a total decrease of over 42% in just three days since its debut on major exchanges.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">HMSTR, the native token for the Web3 game Hamster Kombat, initially traded at $0.009993 when it first appeared on exchanges.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">However, by Sunday, the price had plummeted to $0.005613, marking a new all-time low for the cryptocurrency. This sharp decline follows a reported 30% drop in value on its opening day of trading.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Hamster Kombat is a click-to-earn game hosted on the TON blockchain through Telegram. Players earn HMSTR coins by tapping on digital hamsters, which can then be used for in-game upgrades, participating in mini-games, and advancing their operations.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The game includes features such as daily missions, social elements, and mining mechanics to engage players.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The HMSTR token was distributed through an airdrop to active players, rewarding them for their achievements and engagement within the game.</p>
<figure id="attachment_103222" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-103222" style="width: 847px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-103222" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/Screenshot-2024-09-30-at-09-55-52-Hamster-Kombat-Price-HMSTR-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko.png" alt="Hamster Kombat Price on CoinGecko" width="847" height="635" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/Screenshot-2024-09-30-at-09-55-52-Hamster-Kombat-Price-HMSTR-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko.png 847w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/Screenshot-2024-09-30-at-09-55-52-Hamster-Kombat-Price-HMSTR-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko-300x225.png 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/Screenshot-2024-09-30-at-09-55-52-Hamster-Kombat-Price-HMSTR-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko-768x576.png 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/Screenshot-2024-09-30-at-09-55-52-Hamster-Kombat-Price-HMSTR-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko-50x37.png 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/Screenshot-2024-09-30-at-09-55-52-Hamster-Kombat-Price-HMSTR-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko-150x112.png 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/Screenshot-2024-09-30-at-09-55-52-Hamster-Kombat-Price-HMSTR-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko-450x337.png 450w" sizes="(max-width: 847px) 100vw, 847px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-103222" class="wp-caption-text">Hamster Kombat Price on <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/hamster-kombat">CoinGecko</a></figcaption></figure>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Despite its recent price struggles, HMSTR still maintains a market capitalization of $365 million, positioning it as the 193rd largest cryptocurrency out of more than 10,000 digital assets.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Currently, there are 64,375,000,000 HMSTR tokens in circulation. In the past 24 hours, the token has seen $248 million in global trading activity, with Binance emerging as the most active exchange for HMSTR trades.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">According to data from <a href="https://tonscan.com/EQAJ8uWd7EBqsmpSWaRdf_I-8R8-XHwh3gsNKhy-UrdrPcUo?tab=holders">tonscan.com</a>, HMSTR has 12,498,400 holders, and its maximum supply is set at one hundred billion tokens.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The distribution of HMSTR tokens shows a high concentration among a small number of wallets. The top wallet holds 61,362,223,003 tokens, which represents 61.36% of the total supply.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Binance&#8217;s hot wallet ranks second, holding 14,356,128,737 HMSTR, or about 14.36% of the total supply. Notably, the top five wallets collectively control 93.95% of the entire HMSTR supply, indicating a significant concentration of ownership.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">This concentration of tokens in a small number of wallets could potentially impact the token&#8217;s price stability and liquidity in the future.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The success and stability of HMSTR may depend on its ability to broaden its holder base and maintain player engagement in the Hamster Kombat game.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The trading volume for HMSTR over the past 24 hours reached $248 million, suggesting active interest in the token despite its price decline. However, like many newly launched cryptocurrencies, HMSTR has experienced a volatile start in the market, which may present challenges for its future stability.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/hmstr-token-drops-42-in-first-three-days-of-trading/">HMSTR Token Drops 42% in First Three Days of Trading</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">103219</post-id>	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
