<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	
	xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
	xmlns:geo="http://www.w3.org/2003/01/geo/wgs84_pos#"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Blockonomi</title>
	<atom:link href="https://blockonomi.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://blockonomi.com/</link>
	<description>Cryptocurrency News &#38; Your Guide to the Blockchain Economy</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 16:05:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.7.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/fav-50x50.png</url>
	<title>Blockonomi</title>
	<link>https://blockonomi.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
<site xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">134176212</site>	<item>
		<title>PoSciDonDAO Unveils a Decentralized Future for Personalized Medicine Research</title>
		<link>https://blockonomi.com/poscidondao-unveils-a-decentralized-future-for-personalized-medicine-research/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[chainwire]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 16:05:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[PR]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blockonomi.com/?p=108062</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Panama City, Panama, 12th December 2024, Chainwire</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/poscidondao-unveils-a-decentralized-future-for-personalized-medicine-research/">PoSciDonDAO Unveils a Decentralized Future for Personalized Medicine Research</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span><strong>Panama City, Panama, December 12th, 2024, Chainwire</strong></span></p>
<p></p>
<p><a href="https://www.poscidondao.com/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">PoSciDonDAO</a>, an emerging organization in the Decentralized Science (DeSci) domain, has announced the launch of a decentralized autonomous organization (DAO) dedicated to funding personalized medicine research. Leveraging blockchain technology, PoSciDonDAO aims to improve efficiencies and transparency in research funding while enabling global collaboration to address life-altering diseases such as cancer, multiple sclerosis, and Alzheimer’s disease.</p>
<p><strong>A Vision for Advancing Patient Care</strong></p>
<p>Personalized medicine, which tailors treatments to patients based on genetic and molecular profiles, offers a path toward more effective therapies and better patient outcomes. This field has been hindered by limited funding and systemic inefficiencies. PoSciDonDAO’s mission is to address these challenges by providing resources to explore novel approaches such as viro-immunotherapies and gene and cell therapies.</p>
<p>By funding early-stage, pre-patented research, PoSciDonDAO seeks to drive innovation from academic labs to commercial viability. This initiative is designed to improve healthcare outcomes for patients worldwide by advancing patient-tailored therapies and making innovative treatments more accessible.</p>
<p><strong>Empowering Community Governance</strong></p>
<p>PoSciDonDAO introduces incentive models to foster long-term engagement among scientists, innovators, and DeSci enthusiasts. Its governance framework enables community members to actively participate in DAO operations and funding decisions, ensuring resources are allocated to projects aligned with the shared goal of advancing personalized medicine.</p>
<p><strong>Building Partnerships in Decentralized Science</strong></p>
<p>Since its inception, PoSciDonDAO has been an active participant in Decentralized Science discussions and collaborations. Notably, it engages with other DeSci initiatives such as the Health Data Alliance, which includes projects like AxonDAO, DataLake, and Hippocrat, underscoring its commitment to advancing the DeSci movement. More partnerships and collaborations will be announced in the near future.</p>
<p><strong>About PoSciDonDAO</strong></p>
<p>By combining blockchain technology with scientific innovation, <a href="https://www.poscidondao.com/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">PoSciDonDAO</a> is establishing a collaborative platform for research in personalized medicine. This approach aims to accelerate discoveries and democratize access to resulting treatments, benefiting patients and healthcare systems globally. The PoSciDonDAO team includes experts in virology, immunology, oncology, epidemiology, and Web3. With in-house expertise and contributions from its community members, the DAO can identify which projects have the most potential to impact the personalized medicine field. </p>
<p>The PoSciDonDAO token (SCI) is central to the DAO’s governance model, allowing community members to participate in decision-making processes. This decentralized and transparent mechanism ensures resources are directed toward impactful research projects.</p>
<p>For more information about PoSciDonDAO, users can visit the official PoSciDonDAO <a href="https://www.poscidondao.com/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">website</a>.</p>
<p><strong>Joining the Community</strong></p>
<p><a href="https://www.poscidondao.com/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">PoSciDonDAO</a> offers scientists, innovators, and DeSci enthusiasts to become part of this transformative initiative. By advancing research in personalized medicine, PoSciDonDAO aims to contribute to improved therapies and better outcomes for patients worldwide.</p>
<p><a href="https://x.com/PoSciDonDAO" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">Twitter/X</a> | <a href="https://t.me/OfficialPoSciDonDAO" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">Telegram</a> |<a href="https://discord.com/invite/75SrHpcNSZ" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"> Discord</a></p>
<p><strong>Disclaimer</strong></p>
<p>The information provided herein is for informational or educational purposes only and does not constitute financial, legal, or tax advice. Any purchase, sale, or other transaction related to SCI tokens is undertaken at the sole discretion and risk of the participant. PoSciDonDAO does not assume responsibility for any loss, damages, or other consequences arising out of such transactions.</p>
<p>The SCI token is not and shall not be offered or sold to persons in the United States or individuals/entities on OFAC sanctioned lists. Further, this release does not constitute an offer to sell or a solicitation of an offer to buy any securities or financial instruments in any jurisdiction. Participants are strongly encouraged to conduct their own due diligence and seek independent advice from qualified legal, tax, or financial advisors before engaging with SCI tokens, blockchain technology, and digital assets generally. Participation in any token-related activities is subject to compliance with applicable laws, regulations, reporting, and eligibility requirements, including KYC/AML processes. PoSciDonDAO makes no guarantees or promises regarding the future performance, value, or regulatory compliance of the SCI tokens.</p>
<p></p>
<h5>Contact</h5>
<p><span><strong>Marketing Representative</strong><br /></span><span><strong>Ayat Abourashed</strong><br /></span><span><strong>PoSciDonDAO Foundation</strong><br /></span><span><strong>ayat@poscidon.com</strong><br /></span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/poscidondao-unveils-a-decentralized-future-for-personalized-medicine-research/">PoSciDonDAO Unveils a Decentralized Future for Personalized Medicine Research</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">108062</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>PEPE Price Plunge Creates Opportunity for this Undervalued Token, Could it Reach 41,011% Growth?</title>
		<link>https://blockonomi.com/pepe-price-plunge-creates-opportunity-for-this-undervalued-token-could-it-reach-41011-growth/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Oliver Dale]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 16:00:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[PR]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blockonomi.com/?p=108036</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Pepe (PEPE) remains one of the best-performing cryptocurrencies in the entire market over the past year. However, the 24-hour double-digit PEPE price drop and modest gains over the week have cast a shadow of uncertainty over the meme coin&#8217;s near future. Yet, the Pepe slump has prompted investors to identify a rival altcoin that can [...]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/pepe-price-plunge-creates-opportunity-for-this-undervalued-token-could-it-reach-41011-growth/">PEPE Price Plunge Creates Opportunity for this Undervalued Token, Could it Reach 41,011% Growth?</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Pepe (PEPE) remains one of the best-performing cryptocurrencies in the entire market over the past year. However, the 24-hour double-digit PEPE price drop and modest gains over the week have cast a shadow of uncertainty over the meme coin&#8217;s near future.</p>
<p>Yet, the Pepe slump has prompted investors to identify a rival altcoin that can match PEPE’s meteoric rise. Just as the PEPE price has soared 43,847% since its CEX listing, <a href="https://propichain.finance/?utm_source=blockonomi&amp;utm_medium=p1s1&amp;utm_campaign=1212p1s1">PropiChain (PCHAIN)</a> is projected to surge 41,011% by Q1 2025.</p>
<h2>PEPE Price Drops as Meme Coins Make Way for Altcoins</h2>
<p>The PEPE price hit a new all-time high of <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/pepe/">$0.00002825</a> yesterday, underscoring an outstanding year for the meme coin.</p>
<p>With this performance, Pepe (PEPE) shows extreme resilience, as most top meme coins lost momentum with the start of the altcoin season. Yet, just as experts anticipated, the PEPE price will stabilize and retrace as investors take profits.</p>
<p>As predicted, a PEPE price correction is already underway, with Pepe falling 14.94% over the past day alone. While Pepe (PEPE) is still a top crypto for this bull cycle, a double-digit drop prompts investors to look for other promising alternatives.</p>
<p>Ironically, investors searching for the <a href="https://propichain.finance/">best cryptos to buy now</a> point to PropiChain (PCHAIN), an altcoin that can rival the iconic meme coin’s explosive 40,645% surge.</p>
<h2>PCHAIN Poised for Early 41,011% Run From PropiChain Real Estate Revolution</h2>
<p>It was only last year Pepe (PEPE) minted many millionaires within just months of launching. So when investors discovered PropiChain (PCHAIN), an altcoin that can mirror the 400x PEPE price surge, they unsurprisingly wasted no time joining the <a href="https://propichain.finance/">presale</a>, with over $1.3 million already raised in round one.</p>
<p>However, while PEPE relies purely on speculation to drive demand, PCHAIN is a utility token powering the revolutionary blockchain platform for the $634 trillion industry. Although blockchain tech isn&#8217;t new in real estate, we&#8217;re still waiting to witness a business solution on the level of what PropiChain (PCHAIN) offers.</p>
<p>The audience must understand that <a href="https://propichain.finance/?utm_source=blockonomi&amp;utm_medium=p1s1&amp;utm_campaign=1212p1s1">PropiChain (PCHAIN)</a> isn&#8217;t just a blockchain platform for recording real estate ownership and transactions.</p>
<p>Instead, PropiChain (PCHAIN) is a full-service real estate solution for tokenizing real estate, discovering valuable assets, and trading properties. Additionally, PropiChain is innovating digital asset management and property investing with smart contract automation and artificial intelligence.</p>
<p>Many features set PropiChain (PCHAIN) miles apart from its competitors.</p>
<p>Besides the <a href="https://propichain.gitbook.io/propichain/real-estate-tokenization/fractional-ownership">fractional ownership</a> model, PropiChain is pioneering in removing the financial barrier to real estate investing, and the platform is launching a metaverse marketplace for global trading. This means users can seamlessly tokenize, transact, and store digital property assets from a single place.</p>
<p>Smart contracts extend PropiChain’s services to asset managers and landlords with smart features like auto property leasing, auto rent collection, and auto renewals. Together, these features eliminate lengthy legal processes and cut out expensive middlemen.</p>
<p><a href="https://propichain.finance/">PCHAIN-holding investors</a>, on the other hand, can access powerful data-driven AI tools that can boost business efficiency and ultimately increase profits with features like personalized property searches, 24/7 virtual assistance, automatic asset valuations, and automatic trading.</p>
<h3><strong>Is PropiChain the Next Pepe (PEPE) Rival?</strong></h3>
<p>With the PEPE price significantly dropping after Pepe set another all-time high, analysts warn that investing in the meme coin now might be a bad idea as the market stabilizes.</p>
<p>However, a better opportunity for investors may have presented itself with the <a href="https://propichain.finance/">PropiChain (PCHAIN) presale</a>. Coincidentally, PCHAIN is projected for a 41,011% surge by Q1 2025, mirroring the 400x PEPE price rally shortly after its launch.</p>
<h2>Investors Spend $1.3 Million, Calling PropiChain the Best Presale Project</h2>
<p>Investors only thought once when presented with an unmatched real estate blockchain service revolutionizing one of the largest industries on the planet. Just weeks into round one of the PCHAIN <a href="https://propichain.finance/">presale</a>, PropiChain raised $1.3 million as investors rushed to acquire the altcoin at the lowest price the altcoin will ever be.</p>
<p>Enormous participation in this stage can be attributed to the <a href="https://github.com/Block-Audit-Report/Propichain">BlockAudit</a> security audit and <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/propichain/">PropiChain CoinMarketCap listing</a>, which revealed no vulnerabilities and skyrocketed excitement around the project.</p>
<p>The bad news is that massive traffic has pushed the presale to the edge of round one, meaning <a href="https://propichain.finance/?utm_source=blockonomi&amp;utm_medium=p1s1&amp;utm_campaign=1212p1s1">PropiChain (PCHAIN)</a> will never be this cheap again as the next stage begins.</p>
<p>Round-one participants await a generous 208.17% and 801.41% yield by the second and final round. Yet, PCHAIN holders will undoubtedly be greedy as a modest $865 investment in round one can return $355,610 by Q1 2025!</p>
<p>But with a quickly advancing presale, there&#8217;s no better time to join than now to make the maximum gains from the PCHAIN boom. Click the links below to join round one and acquire PropiChain (PCHAIN) at its lowest price.</p>
<p><strong>For more information about the PropiChain Presale:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Website:</strong><a href="https://propichain.finance/"><strong> https://propichain.finance/</strong></a></li>
<li><strong>Join Community:</strong><a href="https://linktr.ee/propichain"><strong> https://linktr.ee/propichain</strong></a></li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/pepe-price-plunge-creates-opportunity-for-this-undervalued-token-could-it-reach-41011-growth/">PEPE Price Plunge Creates Opportunity for this Undervalued Token, Could it Reach 41,011% Growth?</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">108036</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>xHaven Launches XVN Token</title>
		<link>https://blockonomi.com/xhaven-launches-xvn-token/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[chainwire]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 14:54:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[PR]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blockonomi.com/?p=108059</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Dubai, United Arab Emirates, 12th December 2024, Chainwire</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/xhaven-launches-xvn-token/">xHaven Launches XVN Token</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span><strong>Dubai, United Arab Emirates, December 12th, 2024, Chainwire</strong></span></p>
<p></p>
<p><a href="https://www.xhaven.io/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">xHaven</a>, the leading digital collectibles marketplace and blockchain infrastructure provider on Flare, is thrilled to announce the launch of its native governance token, XVN. Available now on <a href="https://sparkdex.ai/swap" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">Sparkdex</a>, a leading decentralized exchange on Flare, this milestone signifies xHaven’s evolution from a marketplace into an expansive Web3 ecosystem, empowering users with new utility and rewards.</p>
<p><strong>XVN: Powering the Future of xHaven</strong></p>
<p>The launch of the XVN token is a pivotal step in xHaven’s journey to broaden its horizons, offering enhanced services and a seamless user experience across its platform.</p>
<h4><strong>Unlocking Exclusive Utility and Rewards</strong></h4>
<p>XVN unlocks possibilities within the xHaven platform, offering benefits such as:</p>
<ul>
<li>Exclusive Discounts on Trading Fees: Lower costs to encourage more trading activity. </li>
<li>Platform Rewards: Earning XVN from a dedicated reward pool for every transaction made on the platform, rewarding both buyers and sellers.</li>
<li>Marketplace Rewards: Earning voting power from marketplace activity, distributed to XVN stakers through the Governance Token Distribution Mechanism. </li>
<li>Incentives for Liquidity Provision: Rewards for providing liquidity on Automated Market Makers (AMMs). </li>
<li>Simple Staking Rewards:  Yields for staking XVN, in order to promote long-term holding. </li>
<li>Governance Participation: Having a say in the platform&#8217;s future development and decisions.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Strengthening Liquidity Through Strategic Alliances</strong></p>
<p>To ensure a robust and sustainable ecosystem, xHaven has forged key partnerships with industry leaders Ichi and Sparkdex.</p>
<p><strong>Ichi</strong></p>
<p><a href="https://xhaven.io/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">xHaven</a> leverages Ichi’s innovative single-token deposit vaults to simplify liquidity provision to a more stake-like experience. These vaults enable single-token deposits into ICHI Vaults via Sparkdex, eliminating the need for both tokens to be deposited into the liquidity pool. This simplified approach to liquidity management enhances price stability, and yield opportunities, and supports xHaven’s ecosystem growth.</p>
<p><strong>SparkDEX</strong></p>
<p>Using SparkDEX V3.1 DEX platform, xHaven is launching liquidity pools that empower users by concentrating assets in designated price ranges. This reduces the risk of Impermanent Loss (IL). </p>
<p><strong>Empowering the xHaven Community</strong></p>
<p>This launch is about the celebration of the vibrant xHaven community. Since its inception in 2021, xHaven (formerly Sparkles) aimed to become a trusted platform for NFT infrastructure on Songbird and Flare. The XVN token reflects this growth, fostering active community participation and enabling users to shape the platform’s future.</p>
<p><strong>About xHaven</strong></p>
<p><a href="https://xhaven.io" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">xHaven</a> is a leader in the digital collectibles industry on the Flare network. Dedicated to expanding the possibilities within Web3, xHaven offers a comprehensive suite of tools and services to empower its users. For more information, users can visit <a href="https://xhaven.io/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">https://xhaven.io</a>.</p>
<p><strong>About Ichi</strong></p>
<p><a href="https://docs.ichi.org/home" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">ICHI</a> is a non-custodial, automated protocol that optimizes capital efficiency in decentralized finance (DeFi). By utilizing single-sided concentrated liquidity pools, Ichi simplifies liquidity provision for users across various AMMs, making DeFi accessible and efficient. For more information, users can visit <a href="https://docs.ichi.org/home" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">https://docs.ichi.org/home</a>.</p>
<p><strong>About Sparkdex</strong></p>
<p><a href="https://sparkdex.ai" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">SparkDEX</a> is the first AI-powered Super dApp on the Flare Network, offering a seamless DeFi experience through innovative derivatives and cutting-edge user experience. Powered by AI, SparkDEX is poised to become the premier gateway for Flare-based trading, being the first to launch Perpetuals on Flare Network. For more information: <a href="https://sparkdex.ai/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">https://sparkdex.ai</a>. </p>
<p></p>
<h5>Contact</h5>
<p><span><strong>Marketing Team</strong><br /></span><span><strong>xHaven</strong><br /></span><span><strong>admin@xhaven.io</strong><br /></span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/xhaven-launches-xvn-token/">xHaven Launches XVN Token</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">108059</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Karrier One Launches Decentralized WiFi Hotspot Devices on Sui Network to Expand Global Connectivity</title>
		<link>https://blockonomi.com/karrier-one-launches-decentralized-wifi-hotspot-devices-on-sui-network-to-expand-global-connectivity/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[chainwire]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 14:17:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[PR]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blockonomi.com/?p=108056</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Florida, USA, 12th December 2024, Chainwire</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/karrier-one-launches-decentralized-wifi-hotspot-devices-on-sui-network-to-expand-global-connectivity/">Karrier One Launches Decentralized WiFi Hotspot Devices on Sui Network to Expand Global Connectivity</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span><strong>Florida, USA, December 12th, 2024, Chainwire</strong></span></p>
<p></p>
<p><a href="https://karrier.one/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">Karrier One</a>, a decentralized physical infrastructure network (DePIN) built on the Sui Network, is excited to announce the worldwide launch of its innovative WiFi Hotspot devices. These devices empower individuals to contribute to a decentralized connectivity ecosystem, providing WiFi offloading services to various carriers and earning KONE tokens in return.</p>
<p>This development signifies a significant advancement in decentralized networks, seamlessly integrating Web3 technology with practical, real-world applications.</p>
<p><strong>Unlocking the Potential of WiFi Offloading</strong></p>
<p>As global internet usage continues to surge, traditional networks face increasing pressure from high traffic volumes. Karrier One addresses this challenge by introducing a decentralized WiFi offloading network powered by user-owned hotspot devices. These devices enable participants to offload data traffic from conventional carriers to the Karrier One Network, enhancing efficiency and reducing costs for all involved parties.</p>
<p>The network operates on a straightforward principle: device owners provide WiFi connectivity to mobile carriers and other entities requiring offloading solutions, earning <strong>KONE tokens</strong> in exchange. This decentralized infrastructure fosters an ecosystem where anyone, anywhere, can participate and reap rewards while contributing to a more efficient internet.</p>
<p><strong>Strategic Partnership with Sui Network</strong></p>
<p>Karrier One&#8217;s collaboration with Sui is pivotal to its mission, in addition to enabling the deployment of SCION Services, Walrus Nodes, and Validator Nodes on the Sui blockchain, now Karrier One will enable WiFi Hotspots to the Sui ecosystem. This partnership highlights the shared vision of leveraging cutting-edge blockchain technology for enhanced network functionality and scalability.</p>
<blockquote><p>“At a time when traditional telecom providers are struggling to keep pace with growing demand, KarrierOne is leveraging Sui&#8217;s technology to add much-needed capacity and expand access to underserved areas,” said Jameel Khalfan, Head of Ecosystem Development for Sui Foundation. “Most importantly, with the launch and distribution of KarrierOne’s WiFi hotspot devices, those benefiting from the added coverage will also be able to participate and earn from their contributions.”</p></blockquote>
<p><strong>Empowering a Decentralized Future</strong></p>
<p>Karrier One’s vision centers on democratizing access to connectivity. The introduction of WiFi Hotspot devices offers individuals an unprecedented opportunity to contribute to a decentralized internet infrastructure while earning token rewards as a result. This aligns with the broader objectives of Web3 by redistributing value and control from centralized entities to the community.</p>
<blockquote><p>Samer Bishay, Co-Founder and CEO of Karrier One, stated, &#8220;By participating in the Karrier One Network, users not only unlock the ability to earn tokens but also play a pivotal role in revolutionizing global connectivity.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p><strong>About Karrier One</strong></p>
<p><a href="https://karrier.one/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">Karrier One</a> is the first carrier-grade decentralized mobile network that connects smartphones and users seamlessly and anonymously using the Sui blockchain. Karrier One is the only network of its kind to power Micro Networks or Mobile Independent Network Operators agnostic of any frequency or spectrum limitations.</p>
<p><strong>About Sui</strong></p>
<p><a href="https://sui.io" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">Sui</a> is a first-of-its-kind Layer 1 blockchain and smart contract platform designed from the ground up to make digital asset ownership fast, private, secure, and accessible to everyone. Its object-centric model, based on the Move programming language, enables parallel execution, sub-second finality, and rich on-chain assets. With horizontally scalable processing and storage, Sui supports a wide range of applications with unrivaled speed at low cost. Sui is a step-function advancement in blockchain and a platform on which creators and developers can build amazing user-friendly experiences. For more information about Sui, users can visit <a href="https://sui.io" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">https://sui.io</a>.</p>
<p></p>
<h5>Contact</h5>
<p><span><strong>Chief Strategy Officer</strong><br /></span><span><strong>Nahid Masad</strong><br /></span><span><strong>Karrier One</strong><br /></span><span><strong>pr@karrier.one</strong><br /></span><span><strong>416 900 0010</strong><br /></span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/karrier-one-launches-decentralized-wifi-hotspot-devices-on-sui-network-to-expand-global-connectivity/">Karrier One Launches Decentralized WiFi Hotspot Devices on Sui Network to Expand Global Connectivity</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">108056</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Atoma Launches Private, Decentralized AI on Sui</title>
		<link>https://blockonomi.com/atoma-launches-private-decentralized-ai-on-sui/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[chainwire]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 14:05:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[PR]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blockonomi.com/?p=108053</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Grand Cayman, Cayman Islands, 12th December 2024, Chainwire</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/atoma-launches-private-decentralized-ai-on-sui/">Atoma Launches Private, Decentralized AI on Sui</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span><strong>Grand Cayman, Cayman Islands, December 12th, 2024, Chainwire</strong></span></p>
<p></p>
<h3>Demos fully private and decentralized AI chat app with performance on par with ChatGPT and Perplexity AI</h3>
<p><a href="https://sui.io" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">Sui</a>, the Layer 1 blockchain that delivers unparalleled scalability and speed, and <a href="https://www.atoma.network/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank">Atoma Network</a>, a next generation decentralized AI engine, today announced that Atoma’s fully decentralized AI layer, first announced earlier this year, is live on Sui’s Mainnet. The team also offered reporters a first glimpse into the potential of decentralized AI with a decentralized AI Chat app (code named “Utopia”) built on Sui that enables users to have full ownership of their private data while still providing a user experience on par with centralized alternatives. </p>
<p>With its integration currently live in its alpha version on Sui’s Mainnet, Atoma is actively expanding its decentralized ecosystem with new nodes and application builders. For these developers, building on Atoma is an easy transition because Atoma’s API endpoints are directly analogous to those provided by the OpenAI API, which many of them are already familiar with. Then, with Atoma, they can create personalized applications like chatbots connected to social media, finances, or health applications that still maintain individuals’ control over their data. </p>
<p>One of the unique strengths of Atoma’s structure is that all of its AI processing occurs in secure areas within a processor — called Trusted Execution Environments, or TEEs. As a result, AI computations are isolated from the rest of the system and AI inputs and outputs are fully private and beyond access by AI companies.<strong> </strong>Unlike centralized AI applications like ChatGPT, Claude, or Perplexity, where the companies that created the technology can associate inputs with individual accounts, Atoma protects users with complete privacy and censorship resistance. At the same time, by leveraging one of the world’s fastest blockchains, Atoma can offer a user experience with speed and efficiency on par with the centralized versions. </p>
<p>While the AI chat app Atoma created as an initial demonstration represents one application of its technology, Atoma’s infrastructure empowers developers to create private AI agents that perform a multitude of tasks while protecting individual user data. Because the private AI agents on Atoma can access and process personal information without exposing user data, they are ideal for applications that require personalization and confidentiality. </p>
<p>For example, Atoma-powered decentralized AI can:</p>
<p><strong>In DeFi</strong>: </p>
<ul>
<li>Manage portfolios, balance assets, and mitigate risks automatically. </li>
<li>Execute trading strategies in real-time on market conditions.</li>
<li>Interact securely with smart contracts for yield farming, lending, and staking. </li>
</ul>
<p><strong>In Social Media</strong>:</p>
<ul>
<li>Automate content moderation, curation, and community management. </li>
<li>Deliver personalized recommendations for content, connections, and ads. </li>
<li>Verify interactions and maintain user privacy.</li>
</ul>
<p>Private AI agents can also provide significant value across areas like personal assistants, shopping, gaming, and decentralized science (DeSci). </p>
<p>Atoma leverages Sui-related technology platforms to provide its best-in-class service. Atoma relies on the Sui blockchain for settlement, managing payments, and validating transactions, building on Sui’s industry-leading sub-second transaction finality, support for high volumes, and predictable, low-cost transactions. Atoma also integrates Walrus, a decentralized storage solution built on Sui for fast, secure access to private data. This integration ensures that sensitive information is securely stored and easily accessible, supporting AI models in retrieving external data for context-rich insights. By automatically managing data retrieval during long interactions, Walrus enhances memory, contextual understanding, and workflow efficiency, enabling more accurate AI responses.</p>
<blockquote><p>“Decentralized AI requires a blockchain with high degrees of scalability, lightning fast transaction speeds, and low, predictable transaction costs and on these metrics, Sui and Walrus really shine,” ​​said Jorge Antonio, CTO and Co-founder at Atoma. “Sui and Walrus offer a combination of performance, cost effectiveness, reliability, and ease of integration that is unique in our industry and we are thrilled to build on the foundation they provide.”</p></blockquote>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;AI technology is advancing at an unprecedented pace, transforming industries and reshaping how we interact with the world. As adoption accelerates, decentralized and scalable solutions will be critical to safeguarding user control over personal information,&#8221; said Jameel Khalfan, Head of Ecosystem Development at the Sui Foundation. &#8220;Atoma&#8217;s work, built on the highly scalable platforms of Sui and Walrus, ensures that users can leverage the transformative power of AI without compromising the security and privacy of their data.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p></p>
<h5>Contact</h5>
<p><span><strong>Sui Foundation</strong><br /></span><span><strong>media@sui.io</strong><br /></span></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/atoma-launches-private-decentralized-ai-on-sui/">Atoma Launches Private, Decentralized AI on Sui</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">108053</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>POPCAT ($POP) Price: Shows Rising Momentum as Bulls Defend Critical $1 Level</title>
		<link>https://blockonomi.com/popcat-pop-price-shows-rising-momentum-as-bulls-defend-critical-1-level/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Oliver Dale]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 11:14:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blockonomi.com/?p=108032</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>TLDR POPCAT has found strong buyer support at the $1 level, showing resilience after a recent pullback The 4-hour RSI indicates increasing buyer momentum as it moves out of oversold territory toward 50% 1-day RSI shows selling pressure decreasing with a reversal trend from 40% level Key resistance levels to watch are the 100-day SMA [...]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/popcat-pop-price-shows-rising-momentum-as-bulls-defend-critical-1-level/">POPCAT ($POP) Price: Shows Rising Momentum as Bulls Defend Critical $1 Level</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>TLDR</h2>
<ul>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">POPCAT has found strong buyer support at the $1 level, showing resilience after a recent pullback</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">The 4-hour RSI indicates increasing buyer momentum as it moves out of oversold territory toward 50%</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">1-day RSI shows selling pressure decreasing with a reversal trend from 40% level</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Key resistance levels to watch are the 100-day SMA and $1.50 mark</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Current trading price is $1.20 with next support at $0.80 if bullish momentum fades</li>
</ul>
<hr />
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words"><a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/popcat-holds-firm-at-1-support/">POPCAT&#8217;s price has established firm support at the $1 level, marking a potential turning point for the token after its recent market pullback.</a> Trading data from the past 24 hours shows increased buying activity as the price stabilizes and begins showing signs of upward momentum.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The digital asset, currently trading at $1.20, has attracted renewed buyer interest after testing the crucial dollar support level. Market data indicates a steady increase in trading volume, with buyers stepping in to defend the price floor established at $1.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Technical analysis of the 4-hour chart reveals improving market conditions for POPCAT. The Relative Strength Index (RSI), a key momentum indicator, has moved out of oversold territory and is approaching the 50% level. This movement suggests growing buyer confidence and could signal the start of a new upward trend.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Looking at the daily timeframe, the RSI shows a notable reversal from the 40% level, indicating that selling pressure may be easing. This technical indicator&#8217;s recovery provides additional evidence that market sentiment could be shifting in favor of buyers.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The token&#8217;s price action around the $1 support level has caught the attention of traders and market participants. Data from multiple exchanges shows increasing bid orders near this price point, suggesting strong buyer interest in accumulating POPCAT at current levels.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Trading volumes have seen an uptick during this period of price stabilization. Exchange data reveals a 24-hour trading volume of over $10 million, showing active market participation as traders position themselves for potential future price movements.</p>
<figure id="attachment_108034" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-108034" style="width: 847px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-108034" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-12-at-11-13-05-Popcat-Price-POPCAT-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko.png" alt="Popcat Price on CoinGecko" width="847" height="631" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-12-at-11-13-05-Popcat-Price-POPCAT-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko.png 847w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-12-at-11-13-05-Popcat-Price-POPCAT-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko-300x223.png 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-12-at-11-13-05-Popcat-Price-POPCAT-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko-768x572.png 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-12-at-11-13-05-Popcat-Price-POPCAT-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko-50x37.png 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-12-at-11-13-05-Popcat-Price-POPCAT-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko-150x112.png 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-12-at-11-13-05-Popcat-Price-POPCAT-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko-450x335.png 450w" sizes="(max-width: 847px) 100vw, 847px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-108034" class="wp-caption-text">Popcat Price on <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/popcat">CoinGecko</a></figcaption></figure>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The current market structure shows several resistance levels that POPCAT needs to overcome for continued upward movement. The first major hurdle lies at the 100-day Simple Moving Average, which has historically served as a key technical reference point for the token&#8217;s price action.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Beyond the moving average, the $1.50 price level represents the next major resistance zone. This level previously acted as support during earlier trading periods and now serves as a target for bulls looking to push the price higher.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Market order books show concentrated seller interest around these resistance levels. However, the gradual accumulation of buy orders at current prices suggests traders are preparing for potential upward price movements.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The token&#8217;s price behavior has maintained a pattern of higher lows since finding support, indicating growing buyer conviction. This technical pattern often precedes larger price moves, though market conditions can change rapidly.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">If POPCAT fails to maintain its current price levels, the next support zone lies at $0.80. This level aligns with previous trading ranges and could serve as a secondary support if market sentiment weakens.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Short-term price action shows consolidation above the $1 mark, with decreasing volatility as the market establishes a new base. Trading ranges have tightened in recent hours, often a predecessor to larger price movements.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Exchange data reveals an increase in wallet addresses holding POPCAT, suggesting growing distributed ownership of the token. This metric often indicates longer-term holder conviction, though it doesn&#8217;t guarantee future price appreciation.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Recent trading patterns show declining sell-side pressure compared to previous weeks. Order flow data indicates more balanced trading activity, with buy and sell orders reaching closer to equilibrium.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The most recent market data shows POPCAT trading at $1.20, maintaining its position above the crucial $1 support level as traders watch for further signs of price direction.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/popcat-pop-price-shows-rising-momentum-as-bulls-defend-critical-1-level/">POPCAT ($POP) Price: Shows Rising Momentum as Bulls Defend Critical $1 Level</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">108032</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>VeChain (VET) Price Analysis: Network Upgrade Drives 12% Daily Gain</title>
		<link>https://blockonomi.com/vechain-vet-price-analysis-network-upgrade-drives-12-daily-gain/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Oliver Dale]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 11:10:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blockonomi.com/?p=108027</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>TLDR VeChain (VET) experienced a 12% surge in price, marking a 120% increase over 30 days The project announced a &#8220;VeChain Renaissance&#8221; plan focused on mass adoption preparation Current trading price is at $0.0585, with CoinCodex predicting $0.057 by end of 2024 Projections show VET reaching $0.063 by February 2025 and potentially $0.14 by May [...]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/vechain-vet-price-analysis-network-upgrade-drives-12-daily-gain/">VeChain (VET) Price Analysis: Network Upgrade Drives 12% Daily Gain</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>TLDR</h2>
<ul>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">VeChain (VET) experienced a 12% surge in price, marking a 120% increase over 30 days</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">The project announced a &#8220;VeChain Renaissance&#8221; plan focused on mass adoption preparation</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Current trading price is at $0.0585, with CoinCodex predicting $0.057 by end of 2024</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Projections show VET reaching $0.063 by February 2025 and potentially $0.14 by May</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">The cryptocurrency aims to challenge its previous all-time high of $0.28</li>
</ul>
<hr />
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The cryptocurrency <a href="https://watcher.guru/news/vechain-surges-12-how-high-will-vet-end-2024">VeChain (VET) has demonstrated remarkable price action in recent weeks, recording a 12% increase in the latest trading session.</a> This surge adds to an impressive 120% gain over the past 30 days, bringing its current trading value to $0.0585.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The project&#8217;s recent announcement of a &#8220;VeChain Renaissance&#8221; initiative has sparked renewed interest among investors. This strategic plan focuses on preparing the network&#8217;s infrastructure for anticipated widespread adoption, suggesting confidence in future blockchain technology usage.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Market data indicates VET&#8217;s strong performance comes during a period of broader cryptocurrency market growth. Bitcoin&#8217;s recent achievement of reaching six figures has created positive sentiment throughout the entire crypto sector, benefiting alternative cryptocurrencies like VeChain.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Trading volume for VET has shown consistent growth, indicating increased investor participation. The token&#8217;s market performance has attracted attention from both retail and institutional investors, contributing to its price appreciation.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Current market analysis from CoinCodex suggests VET will maintain stability near its present levels through the remainder of 2024, with an end-of-year target of $0.057. This projection represents a slight consolidation from current prices.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Looking ahead to 2025, price forecasts become increasingly optimistic. Analysts project VET to reach $0.063 by February, marking the beginning of what could be a substantial upward trend.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The progression continues into spring, with predictions indicating VET could surpass the $0.1 threshold by April 2025. This would represent nearly double the current trading price.</p>
<figure id="attachment_108028" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-108028" style="width: 847px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-108028" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-12-at-10-55-36-VeChain-Price-VET-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko.png" alt="VeChain Price on CoinGecko" width="847" height="628" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-12-at-10-55-36-VeChain-Price-VET-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko.png 847w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-12-at-10-55-36-VeChain-Price-VET-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko-300x222.png 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-12-at-10-55-36-VeChain-Price-VET-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko-768x569.png 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-12-at-10-55-36-VeChain-Price-VET-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko-50x37.png 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-12-at-10-55-36-VeChain-Price-VET-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko-150x111.png 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-12-at-10-55-36-VeChain-Price-VET-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko-450x334.png 450w" sizes="(max-width: 847px) 100vw, 847px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-108028" class="wp-caption-text">VeChain Price on <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/vechain">CoinGecko</a></figcaption></figure>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">May 2025 emerges as a potentially crucial month for VET holders, with projections suggesting a price surge to $0.14. This would translate to a 280% increase from current levels, should these predictions materialize.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Historical context adds perspective to these projections. VET&#8217;s previous all-time high stands at $0.28, setting a benchmark for potential future price action.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The &#8220;VeChain Renaissance&#8221; initiative demonstrates the project&#8217;s focus on technological advancement. This development plan aims to enhance network capabilities in preparation for increased adoption.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Market observers note that VET&#8217;s price movement aligns with broader cryptocurrency market trends. The approval and launch of crypto-based ETFs has generated renewed interest in digital assets across the board.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Trading patterns show VET maintaining steady support levels during its recent price increases. This suggests the possibility of sustained upward momentum rather than speculative short-term gains.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Technical indicators reveal strong buying pressure in recent weeks. The combination of increased trading volume and price appreciation points to growing market confidence in VET.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Market participants are closely monitoring VET&#8217;s price action for signs of continuation or reversal. The token&#8217;s ability to maintain current price levels could indicate future growth potential.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Recent developments in the broader blockchain industry have created favorable conditions for projects like VeChain. The increasing acceptance of cryptocurrency technology continues to provide opportunities for growth across the sector.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/vechain-vet-price-analysis-network-upgrade-drives-12-daily-gain/">VeChain (VET) Price Analysis: Network Upgrade Drives 12% Daily Gain</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">108027</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Riot Platforms Completes $525M Note Offering for Bitcoin Acquisition</title>
		<link>https://blockonomi.com/riot-platforms-completes-525m-note-offering-for-bitcoin-acquisition/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Oliver Dale]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 10:50:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regulation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blockonomi.com/?p=108025</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>TLDR Riot Platforms secured $525M through senior notes offering, netting $511.5M after expenses The notes will mature in 2030 with a 0.75% interest rate Company plans to use funds for Bitcoin purchases and operations Recently acquired 705 Bitcoin for $68.45M Currently holds 12,000 Bitcoin (~$1.2B), second only to Marathon Digital&#8217;s 40,000 BTC Riot Platforms, one [...]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/riot-platforms-completes-525m-note-offering-for-bitcoin-acquisition/">Riot Platforms Completes $525M Note Offering for Bitcoin Acquisition</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>TLDR</h2>
<ul>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Riot Platforms secured $525M through senior notes offering, netting $511.5M after expenses</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">The notes will mature in 2030 with a 0.75% interest rate</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Company plans to use funds for Bitcoin purchases and operations</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Recently acquired 705 Bitcoin for $68.45M</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Currently holds 12,000 Bitcoin (~$1.2B), second only to Marathon Digital&#8217;s 40,000 BTC</li>
</ul>
<hr />
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words"><a href="https://cryptobriefing.com/riot-platforms-525m-bitcoin-offering/">Riot Platforms, one of the largest Bitcoin mining companies in North America, has completed a $525 million senior note offering to expand its Bitcoin holdings</a> and support ongoing operations. The company announced the completion of the private offering through a <a href="https://www.sec.gov/Archives/edgar/data/1167419/000110465924127656/tm2430044d5_8k.htm">filing with the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC).</a></p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">After covering expenses related to the offering, Riot Platforms netted approximately $511.5 million. The senior notes come with a 0.75% interest rate and will reach maturity in 2030, providing the company with long-term financing at relatively low interest rates in the current market environment.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The terms of the offering include a provision that allows noteholders to convert their holdings into common stock starting in 2029. However, earlier conversion options may become available under certain conditions, giving both the company and investors some flexibility in managing their investments.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words"><a href="https://intel.arkm.com/explorer/entity/riot-platforms">Recent data from Arkham Intelligence</a> reveals that Riot Platforms currently holds approximately 12,000 Bitcoin in its treasury. At current market prices, this holding is valued at around $1.2 billion, placing Riot as the second-largest Bitcoin holder among mining companies.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The company&#8217;s position in the mining sector is notable but still trails behind industry leader Marathon Digital, which maintains a larger Bitcoin treasury of over 40,000 Bitcoin,<a href="https://treasuries.bitbo.io/miners/"> according to data from Bitbo.</a> This gap highlights the competitive nature of Bitcoin accumulation among major mining operations.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Riot has been actively growing its Bitcoin holdings through both mining operations and direct purchases. The company recently completed an acquisition of 705 Bitcoin for $68.45 million, demonstrating its commitment to expanding its cryptocurrency assets.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The senior note offering represents a strategic move by Riot to secure additional funding without immediately diluting shareholder value through stock offerings. The low interest rate of 0.75% suggests strong investor confidence in the company&#8217;s business model and future prospects.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The mining company&#8217;s decision to raise funds through notes rather than selling equity comes at a time when <a href="https://moneycheck.com/best-bitcoin-casinos/">Bitcoin</a> mining companies are seeking efficient ways to fund their operations and growth. This approach allows Riot to maintain its current ownership structure while accessing substantial capital.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The funds from the offering will serve multiple purposes, with Bitcoin acquisition being a primary focus. The company plans to use the proceeds for both direct Bitcoin purchases and general corporate purposes, giving it flexibility in how it deploys the capital.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Riot&#8217;s mining operations require substantial ongoing investment in equipment and infrastructure. The new funding will help support these operational needs while allowing the company to continue building its Bitcoin reserves.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The company&#8217;s strategy aligns with a broader trend among Bitcoin mining firms to maintain large Bitcoin holdings rather than immediately selling all mined coins. This approach allows miners to benefit from potential price appreciation while maintaining a strong asset base.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The conversion feature of the notes, beginning in 2029, provides future flexibility for both Riot and the noteholders. This structure allows the company to potentially reduce its debt burden while giving investors the option to participate in any future equity appreciation.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The successful completion of this offering comes during a period of renewed interest in Bitcoin mining operations. Rising Bitcoin prices have improved the profitability metrics for mining companies, making it easier to raise capital on favorable terms.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Riot&#8217;s position as the second-largest Bitcoin holder among mining companies reflects its success in executing its mining and accumulation strategy. The company has consistently worked to build its Bitcoin reserves while maintaining operational efficiency.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The timing of this offering coincides with a period of expansion in the Bitcoin mining sector, as companies seek to strengthen their positions in the market. Riot&#8217;s ability to secure funding at attractive rates indicates continued institutional interest in the Bitcoin mining industry.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/riot-platforms-completes-525m-note-offering-for-bitcoin-acquisition/">Riot Platforms Completes $525M Note Offering for Bitcoin Acquisition</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">108025</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>18+ Best Telegram Casinos &#038; Gambling Sites: Our Top Picks &#038; Reviews</title>
		<link>https://blockonomi.com/best-telegram-casino/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Oliver Dale]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 10:45:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Best]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blockonomi.com/?p=89450</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Are you on the hunt for the ultimate online gambling experience that seamlessly integrates with your favorite messaging app? Look no further than the world of Telegram casinos! In this guide, we&#8217;ll dive into the best Telegram casinos available, offering you a comprehensive guide to the most exciting, secure, and user-friendly platforms. Telegram, the popular [...]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/best-telegram-casino/">18+ Best Telegram Casinos &#038; Gambling Sites: Our Top Picks &#038; Reviews</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Are you on the hunt for the ultimate online gambling experience that seamlessly integrates with your favorite messaging app? Look no further than the world of Telegram casinos!</p>
<p>In this guide, we&#8217;ll dive into the best Telegram casinos available, offering you a comprehensive guide to the most exciting, secure, and user-friendly platforms.</p>
<p>Telegram, the popular instant messaging app, has revolutionized the way we communicate and now, it&#8217;s transforming the online casino landscape. With its robust security features, lightning-fast speeds, and user-friendly interface, Telegram provides the perfect foundation for an immersive gambling experience.</p>
<p>We have personally tested and reviewed each site on the list, you can read our in depth reviews below.</p>
<p>Let’s dig in…</p>
<p><div class="fcrp-toptab">
		
        <div class="fcrp-toptab-row">

			 <div class="fcrp-toptab-col fcrp-site_list">	<a  rel="nofollow"  href="https://blockonomi.com/out/wallstreetmeme"><img decoding="async" width="300" height="300" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/wsm-300x300.jpg" class="scfeat_logo fcrpimg-res wp-post-image" alt="" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/wsm-300x300.jpg 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/wsm-150x150.jpg 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/wsm-50x50.jpg 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/wsm.jpg 400w" sizes="(max-width: 300px) 100vw, 300px" /></a>
						 <span><a  rel="nofollow"  href="https://blockonomi.com/out/wallstreetmeme">WSM Casino</a></span></div><div class="fcrp-toptab-col fcrp-feat_list"><ul><li>Wide range of over 5,000 games from top providers</li><li>Accepts over a dozen popular cryptocurrencies</li><li>Generous 200% up to $25,000 welcome bonus</li><li>Very fast payouts, often within 10 minutes</li><li>Slick modern website design with meme/crypto styling</li></ul></div><div class="fcrp-toptab-col fcrp-bonus_list">
			
			<span class="fcrp-rate rmbottom"><span class="fcrp-rate-total" style="width:100%"></span></span>

			<span class="fcrpbonus_text">200% Match up to $25,000 + 200 Free Spins</span><span><a href="https://blockonomi.com/wall-street-memes-casino-review/" class="revlink tc">Read Our Full Review Here</a></span></div><div class="fcrp-toptab-col fcrp-vis_list">
			
				<a  rel="nofollow"  href="https://blockonomi.com/out/wallstreetmeme" class="fcrp-button playb"> 	  	Play Now </a></div>

         </div></div></p>
<hr />
<h2>Best Telegram Casinos</h2>
<div class="organic1">
<p><div class="fcrp-toptab">
		
        <div class="fcrp-toptab-row">

			 <div class="fcrp-toptab-col fcrp-site_list">	<a  rel="nofollow"  href="https://blockonomi.com/out/bc-game"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="150" height="150" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/bc-game-review.gif" class="scfeat_logo fcrpimg-res wp-post-image" alt="BC.Game Review" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/bc-game-review.gif 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/bc-game-review-50x50.gif 50w" sizes="(max-width: 150px) 100vw, 150px" /></a>
						 <span><a  rel="nofollow"  href="https://blockonomi.com/out/bc-game">BC.Game</a></span></div><div class="fcrp-toptab-col fcrp-feat_list"><ul><li>8,000+ games including slots, casino, sports betting, crypto betting</li><li>Generous welcome bonuses up to 300%</li><li>Supports 18+ major cryptocurrencies for deposits and withdrawals</li><li>Smooth and user-friendly interface</li></ul></div><div class="fcrp-toptab-col fcrp-bonus_list">
			
			<span class="fcrp-rate rmbottom"><span class="fcrp-rate-total" style="width:100%"></span></span>

			<span class="fcrpbonus_text">Earn up to $20,000 welcome bonus</span><span><a href="https://blockonomi.com/bc-game-review/" class="revlink tc">Read Our Full Review Here</a></span></div><div class="fcrp-toptab-col fcrp-vis_list">
			
				<a  rel="nofollow"  href="https://blockonomi.com/out/bc-game" class="fcrp-button playb"> 	  	Play Now </a></div>

         </div></div></p>
<p><div class="fcrp-toptab">
		
        <div class="fcrp-toptab-row">

			 <div class="fcrp-toptab-col fcrp-site_list">	<a  rel="nofollow"  href="https://blockonomi.com/out/empireio"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="150" height="150" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/empire-review.jpg" class="scfeat_logo fcrpimg-res wp-post-image" alt="" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/empire-review.jpg 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/empire-review-50x50.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 150px) 100vw, 150px" /></a>
						 <span><a  rel="nofollow"  href="https://blockonomi.com/out/empireio">Empire Casino</a></span></div><div class="fcrp-toptab-col fcrp-feat_list"><ul><li>Huge selection of 2000+ games from top providers</li><li>Supports popular cryptocurrencies for fast, anonymous payments</li><li>24/7 live chat customer support</li><li>Lucrative loyalty program with VIP rewards</li></ul></div><div class="fcrp-toptab-col fcrp-bonus_list">
			
			<span class="fcrp-rate rmbottom"><span class="fcrp-rate-total" style="width:100%"></span></span>

			<span class="fcrpbonus_text">100% Match Bonus up to 1 BTC</span><span><a href="https://blockonomi.com/empire-casino-review/" class="revlink tc">Read Our Full Review Here</a></span></div><div class="fcrp-toptab-col fcrp-vis_list">
			
				<a  rel="nofollow"  href="https://blockonomi.com/out/empireio" class="fcrp-button playb"> 	  	Play Now </a></div>

         </div></div></p>
</div>
<div class="fcrp-toptab">
		
        <div class="fcrp-toptab-row">

			 <div class="fcrp-toptab-col fcrp-site_list">	<a  rel="nofollow"  href="https://blockonomi.com/out/luckyblock"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="300" height="300" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/Lucky-Block-300x300.gif" class="scfeat_logo fcrpimg-res wp-post-image" alt="Lucky Block" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/Lucky-Block-300x300.gif 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/Lucky-Block-150x150.gif 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/Lucky-Block-50x50.gif 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/Lucky-Block-450x450.gif 450w" sizes="(max-width: 300px) 100vw, 300px" /></a>
						 <span><a  rel="nofollow"  href="https://blockonomi.com/out/luckyblock">Lucky Block Casino</a></span></div><div class="fcrp-toptab-col fcrp-feat_list"><ul><li>Huge selection of over 2,700 games from top providers</li><li>Lucrative 200% deposit bonus up to €25,000</li><li>Wide variety of cryptos supported</li><li>Instant withdrawals</li><li>Cutting-edge Telegram & WalletConnect integration</li></ul></div><div class="fcrp-toptab-col fcrp-bonus_list">
			
			<span class="fcrp-rate rmbottom"><span class="fcrp-rate-total" style="width:100%"></span></span>

			<span class="fcrpbonus_text">Welcome Bonus of 200% match on first deposits up to €25,000</span><span><a href="https://blockonomi.com/lucky-block-casino-review/" class="revlink tc">Read Our Full Review Here</a></span></div><div class="fcrp-toptab-col fcrp-vis_list">
			
				<a  rel="nofollow"  href="https://blockonomi.com/out/luckyblock" class="fcrp-button playb"> 	  	Play Now </a></div>

         </div>
		
        <div class="fcrp-toptab-row">

			 <div class="fcrp-toptab-col fcrp-site_list">	<a  rel="nofollow"  href="https://blockonomi.com/out/megadice"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="150" height="150" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Mega-Dice.gif" class="scfeat_logo fcrpimg-res wp-post-image" alt="Mega Dice" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Mega-Dice.gif 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Mega-Dice-50x50.gif 50w" sizes="(max-width: 150px) 100vw, 150px" /></a>
						 <span><a  rel="nofollow"  href="https://blockonomi.com/out/megadice">Mega Dice</a></span></div><div class="fcrp-toptab-col fcrp-feat_list"><ul><li>Instant withdrawals processed on the blockchain</li><li>Generous welcome bonus of 200% up to 1 BTC + 50 free spins</li><li>Wide selection of games from top providers like Evolution, Pragmatic Play, Hacksaw</li><li>Offers a sportsbook in addition to casino games</li><li>Innovative features like Telegram integration and WalletConnect</li></ul></div><div class="fcrp-toptab-col fcrp-bonus_list">
			
			<span class="fcrp-rate rmbottom"><span class="fcrp-rate-total" style="width:100%"></span></span>

			<span class="fcrpbonus_text">200% match up to 1 BTC + 50 free spins</span><span><a href="https://blockonomi.com/mega-dice-review/" class="revlink tc">Read Our Full Review Here</a></span></div><div class="fcrp-toptab-col fcrp-vis_list">
			
				<a  rel="nofollow"  href="https://blockonomi.com/out/megadice" class="fcrp-button playb"> 	  	Play Now </a></div>

         </div>
		
        <div class="fcrp-toptab-row">

			 <div class="fcrp-toptab-col fcrp-site_list">	<a  rel="nofollow"  href="https://blockonomi.com/out/betplay"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="300" height="300" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/Betplay-300x300.gif" class="scfeat_logo fcrpimg-res wp-post-image" alt="" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/Betplay-300x300.gif 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/Betplay-150x150.gif 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/Betplay-50x50.gif 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/Betplay-450x450.gif 450w" sizes="(max-width: 300px) 100vw, 300px" /></a>
						 <span><a  rel="nofollow"  href="https://blockonomi.com/out/betplay">Betplay</a></span></div><div class="fcrp-toptab-col fcrp-feat_list"><ul><li>Large game selection with over 6,000 titles from top providers</li><li>Generous crypto welcome bonus up to 50 mBTC</li><li>Fast withdrawals through cryptocurrency support</li><li>Slick, intuitive site design optimized for mobile</li><li>Live chat provides quick customer support</li></ul></div><div class="fcrp-toptab-col fcrp-bonus_list">
			
			<span class="fcrp-rate rmbottom"><span class="fcrp-rate-total" style="width:100%"></span></span>

			<span class="fcrpbonus_text">Welcome Bonus Matches 100% up to 50 mBTC</span><span><a href="https://blockonomi.com/betplay-casino-review/" class="revlink tc">Read Our Full Review Here</a></span></div><div class="fcrp-toptab-col fcrp-vis_list">
			
				<a  rel="nofollow"  href="https://blockonomi.com/out/betplay" class="fcrp-button playb"> 	  	Play Now </a></div>

         </div>
		
        <div class="fcrp-toptab-row">

			 <div class="fcrp-toptab-col fcrp-site_list">	<a  rel="nofollow"  href="https://blockonomi.com/out/playgram"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="150" height="150" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/Playgram.gif" class="scfeat_logo fcrpimg-res wp-post-image" alt="" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/Playgram.gif 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/Playgram-50x50.gif 50w" sizes="(max-width: 150px) 100vw, 150px" /></a>
						 <span><a  rel="nofollow"  href="https://blockonomi.com/out/playgram">Playgram</a></span></div><div class="fcrp-toptab-col fcrp-feat_list"><ul><li>Innovative Telegram-based platform for easy access and use</li><li>No traditional registration required, enhancing privacy</li><li>Wide range of cryptocurrency options for deposits and withdrawals</li><li>Fast transaction processing, especially for withdrawals</li><li>Loyalty program with cashback and exclusive bonuses</li></ul></div><div class="fcrp-toptab-col fcrp-bonus_list">
			
			<span class="fcrp-rate rmbottom"><span class="fcrp-rate-total" style="width:100%"></span></span>

			<span class="fcrpbonus_text">Welcome Bonus of 100 Free Spins</span><span><a href="https://blockonomi.com/playgram-review/" class="revlink tc">Read Our Full Review Here</a></span></div><div class="fcrp-toptab-col fcrp-vis_list">
			
				<a  rel="nofollow"  href="https://blockonomi.com/out/playgram" class="fcrp-button playb"> 	  	Play Now </a></div>

         </div>
		
        <div class="fcrp-toptab-row">

			 <div class="fcrp-toptab-col fcrp-site_list">	<a  rel="nofollow"  href="https://blockonomi.com/out/bc-game"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="150" height="150" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/bc-game-review.gif" class="scfeat_logo fcrpimg-res wp-post-image" alt="BC.Game Review" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/bc-game-review.gif 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/bc-game-review-50x50.gif 50w" sizes="(max-width: 150px) 100vw, 150px" /></a>
						 <span><a  rel="nofollow"  href="https://blockonomi.com/out/bc-game">BC.Game</a></span></div><div class="fcrp-toptab-col fcrp-feat_list"><ul><li>8,000+ games including slots, casino, sports betting, crypto betting</li><li>Generous welcome bonuses up to 300%</li><li>Supports 18+ major cryptocurrencies for deposits and withdrawals</li><li>Smooth and user-friendly interface</li></ul></div><div class="fcrp-toptab-col fcrp-bonus_list">
			
			<span class="fcrp-rate rmbottom"><span class="fcrp-rate-total" style="width:100%"></span></span>

			<span class="fcrpbonus_text">Earn up to $20,000 welcome bonus</span><span><a href="https://blockonomi.com/bc-game-review/" class="revlink tc">Read Our Full Review Here</a></span></div><div class="fcrp-toptab-col fcrp-vis_list">
			
				<a  rel="nofollow"  href="https://blockonomi.com/out/bc-game" class="fcrp-button playb"> 	  	Play Now </a></div>

         </div>
		
        <div class="fcrp-toptab-row">

			 <div class="fcrp-toptab-col fcrp-site_list">	<a  rel="nofollow"  href="https://blockonomi.com/out/wallstreetmeme"><img decoding="async" width="300" height="300" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/wsm-300x300.jpg" class="scfeat_logo fcrpimg-res wp-post-image" alt="" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/wsm-300x300.jpg 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/wsm-150x150.jpg 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/wsm-50x50.jpg 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/wsm.jpg 400w" sizes="(max-width: 300px) 100vw, 300px" /></a>
						 <span><a  rel="nofollow"  href="https://blockonomi.com/out/wallstreetmeme">WSM Casino</a></span></div><div class="fcrp-toptab-col fcrp-feat_list"><ul><li>Wide range of over 5,000 games from top providers</li><li>Accepts over a dozen popular cryptocurrencies</li><li>Generous 200% up to $25,000 welcome bonus</li><li>Very fast payouts, often within 10 minutes</li><li>Slick modern website design with meme/crypto styling</li></ul></div><div class="fcrp-toptab-col fcrp-bonus_list">
			
			<span class="fcrp-rate rmbottom"><span class="fcrp-rate-total" style="width:100%"></span></span>

			<span class="fcrpbonus_text">200% Match up to $25,000 + 200 Free Spins</span><span><a href="https://blockonomi.com/wall-street-memes-casino-review/" class="revlink tc">Read Our Full Review Here</a></span></div><div class="fcrp-toptab-col fcrp-vis_list">
			
				<a  rel="nofollow"  href="https://blockonomi.com/out/wallstreetmeme" class="fcrp-button playb"> 	  	Play Now </a></div>

         </div>
		
        <div class="fcrp-toptab-row">

			 <div class="fcrp-toptab-col fcrp-site_list">	<a  rel="nofollow"  href="https://blockonomi.com/out/wildio"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="150" height="150" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/wild-io-revew.gif" class="scfeat_logo fcrpimg-res wp-post-image" alt="wild.io" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/wild-io-revew.gif 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/wild-io-revew-50x50.gif 50w" sizes="(max-width: 150px) 100vw, 150px" /></a>
						 <span><a  rel="nofollow"  href="https://blockonomi.com/out/wildio">Wild.io</a></span></div><div class="fcrp-toptab-col fcrp-feat_list"><ul><li>Instant withdrawals for crypto currencies</li><li>Huge selection of slots and table games</li><li>Instant play site needs no downloading</li><li>VIP program rewards loyal players</li></ul></div><div class="fcrp-toptab-col fcrp-bonus_list">
			
			<span class="fcrp-rate rmbottom"><span class="fcrp-rate-total" style="width:100%"></span></span>

			<span class="fcrpbonus_text">400% Welcome Bonus up to $10,000 + 300 Free Spins</span><span><a href="https://blockonomi.com/wild-io-review/" class="revlink tc">Read Our Full Review Here</a></span></div><div class="fcrp-toptab-col fcrp-vis_list">
			
				<a  rel="nofollow"  href="https://blockonomi.com/out/wildio" class="fcrp-button playb"> 	  	Play Now </a></div>

         </div>
		
        <div class="fcrp-toptab-row">

			 <div class="fcrp-toptab-col fcrp-site_list">	<a  rel="nofollow"  href="https://blockonomi.com/out/metaspins"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="150" height="150" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/Metaspins.gif" class="scfeat_logo fcrpimg-res wp-post-image" alt="" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/Metaspins.gif 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/Metaspins-50x50.gif 50w" sizes="(max-width: 150px) 100vw, 150px" /></a>
						 <span><a  rel="nofollow"  href="https://blockonomi.com/out/metaspins">Metaspins</a></span></div><div class="fcrp-toptab-col fcrp-feat_list"><ul><li>Generous welcome bonus up to 1 BTC</li><li>2,500+ casino games from top providers</li><li>Great selection of provably fair games</li><li>Lucrative loyalty program with up to 60% rakeback</li><li>Fast withdrawals in under 10 minutes</li></ul></div><div class="fcrp-toptab-col fcrp-bonus_list">
			
			<span class="fcrp-rate rmbottom"><span class="fcrp-rate-total" style="width:100%"></span></span>

			<span class="fcrpbonus_text">Welcome Bonus of 100% Deposit Match Up To 1 BTC</span><span><a href="https://blockonomi.com/metaspins-review/" class="revlink tc">Read Our Full Review Here</a></span></div><div class="fcrp-toptab-col fcrp-vis_list">
			
				<a  rel="nofollow"  href="https://blockonomi.com/out/metaspins" class="fcrp-button playb"> 	  	Play Now </a></div>

         </div>
		
        <div class="fcrp-toptab-row">

			 <div class="fcrp-toptab-col fcrp-site_list">	<a  rel="nofollow"  href="https://blockonomi.com/out/stakecom"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="150" height="150" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/stake-review.gif" class="scfeat_logo fcrpimg-res wp-post-image" alt="Stake Review" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/stake-review.gif 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/stake-review-50x50.gif 50w" sizes="(max-width: 150px) 100vw, 150px" /></a>
						 <span><a  rel="nofollow"  href="https://blockonomi.com/out/stakecom">Stake</a></span></div><div class="fcrp-toptab-col fcrp-feat_list"><ul><li>Large selection of casino games (3,000+ slots) and sports betting options (40+ sports)</li><li>Accepts deposits in 20+ major cryptocurrencies</li><li>Monthly and birthday bonuses for active players</li><li>Fast and user-friendly web-based platform works on mobile</li></ul></div><div class="fcrp-toptab-col fcrp-bonus_list">
			
			<span class="fcrp-rate rmbottom"><span class="fcrp-rate-total" style="width:100%"></span></span>

			<span class="fcrpbonus_text">200% Match Bonus Up To $1000</span><span><a href="https://blockonomi.com/stake-com-review/" class="revlink tc">Read Our Full Review Here</a></span></div><div class="fcrp-toptab-col fcrp-vis_list">
			
				<a  rel="nofollow"  href="https://blockonomi.com/out/stakecom" class="fcrp-button playb"> 	  	Play Now </a></div>

         </div>
		
        <div class="fcrp-toptab-row">

			 <div class="fcrp-toptab-col fcrp-site_list">	<a  rel="nofollow"  href="https://blockonomi.com/out/7bit"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="150" height="150" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/7bitcasino.gif" class="scfeat_logo fcrpimg-res wp-post-image" alt="" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/7bitcasino.gif 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/7bitcasino-50x50.gif 50w" sizes="(max-width: 150px) 100vw, 150px" /></a>
						 <span><a  rel="nofollow"  href="https://blockonomi.com/out/7bit">7Bit Casino</a></span></div><div class="fcrp-toptab-col fcrp-feat_list"><ul><li>Massive selection of over 3000 games from top providers</li><li>Quick withdrawals, especially for cryptocurrencies</li><li>Great recurring promos and VIP program for loyal players</li><li>Mobile optimized - play anywhere on smartphone or tablet</li></ul></div><div class="fcrp-toptab-col fcrp-bonus_list">
			
			<span class="fcrp-rate rmbottom"><span class="fcrp-rate-total" style="width:100%"></span></span>

			<span class="fcrpbonus_text">Bonuses Up to 5 BTC Plus 300 Free Spins</span><span><a href="https://blockonomi.com/7bit-casino-review/" class="revlink tc">Read Our Full Review Here</a></span></div><div class="fcrp-toptab-col fcrp-vis_list">
			
				<a  rel="nofollow"  href="https://blockonomi.com/out/7bit" class="fcrp-button playb"> 	  	Play Now </a></div>

         </div></div>
<hr />
<h2>Telegram Casino Site Reviews</h2>
<h3>Lucky Block Casino</h3>
<p>



<div class="fcrp-scfeatured">

  <div class="scfeatleft">

    <div class="scfeat-content">	<a  rel="nofollow"  href="https://blockonomi.com/out/luckyblock"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="300" height="300" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/Lucky-Block-300x300.gif" class="scfeat_logo fcrpimg-res wp-post-image" alt="Lucky Block" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/Lucky-Block-300x300.gif 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/Lucky-Block-150x150.gif 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/Lucky-Block-50x50.gif 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/Lucky-Block-450x450.gif 450w" sizes="(max-width: 300px) 100vw, 300px" /></a>     <span class="scfeatrate">Overall Rating</span>

                         <span class="fcrp-ratebig rmbottom"><span class="fcrp-ratebig-total" style="width:100%"></span></span>	  <a  rel="nofollow"  href="https://blockonomi.com/out/luckyblock" class="fcrp-button playb"> 	  	Play Now  	</a>    </div><!--block-content ends-->

</div>



  <div class="scfeatright ">



    <h3>Lucky Block Casino</h3>



    <h4 class="fcrpbonus_text">Welcome Bonus of 200% match on first deposits up to €25,000</h4><span><a href="https://blockonomi.com/lucky-block-casino-review/" class="revlink tc">Read Our Full Review Here</a></span>  <p><p>Lucky Block offers a world-class crypto casino and sports betting platform with thousands of games, generous rewards for loyal players, fast payouts, and an overall premium interactive gambling experience.</p>
</p>

					<ul><li>Huge selection of over 2,700 games from top providers</li><li>Lucrative 200% deposit bonus up to €25,000</li><li>Wide variety of cryptos supported</li><li>Instant withdrawals</li><li>Cutting-edge Telegram & WalletConnect integration</li></ul>   </div><!--block-right ends-->  </div><!--widget-block-rounded ends--></p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap">Lucky Block is a new, feature-rich crypto casino making waves in the online gambling space since its launch in late 2022. Backed by an existing cryptocurrency brand, Lucky Block leverages its solid reputation to offer players a modern casino and sportsbook supporting popular cryptos like Bitcoin, Ethereum, and Tether for deposits and withdrawals.</p>
<figure id="attachment_86378" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-86378" style="width: 1000px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-86378" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/Lucky-Block-Homepage.jpg" alt="Lucky Block Homepage" width="1000" height="700" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/Lucky-Block-Homepage.jpg 1000w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/Lucky-Block-Homepage-300x210.jpg 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/Lucky-Block-Homepage-768x538.jpg 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/Lucky-Block-Homepage-50x35.jpg 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/Lucky-Block-Homepage-150x105.jpg 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/Lucky-Block-Homepage-450x315.jpg 450w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-86378" class="wp-caption-text">Lucky Block Homepage</figcaption></figure>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap">Slick website design optimized for desktop and mobile coupled with around-the-clock chat support cement Lucky Block’s accessibility for crypto holders worldwide.</p>
<hr />
<h4>Key Points</h4>
<ul>
<li>Large selection of over 2,700 casino games from 50+ top providers like NetEnt and Pragmatic Play, including slots, table games, jackpots, and live casino</li>
<li>Generous welcome bonus of 200% match up to €10,000 plus 50 free spins</li>
<li>Wide variety of 10+ cryptocurrencies supported for fast, anonymous deposits and withdrawals</li>
<li>Instant crypto withdrawals processed directly to players' wallets</li>
<li>Lucrative loyalty program coming soon with cashback, birthday bonuses, and rewards for frequent players</li>
<li>Innovative features like daily jackpot drops, lottery betting, and native LBLOCK token perks</li>
</ul>
<hr />
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap">Lucky Block emerged as one of our top recommendations for crypto gamblers seeking a leading destination supporting both casino games and sports betting with digital currencies</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap">Backed by reputable licensing and a globally-recognized crypto brand, Lucky Block offers players a secure, legal platform to enjoy thousands of slots, jackpots, live table games, and betting markets across sports leagues like the NBA and esports tournaments</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap">Fast and easy account setup via email or Telegram allows new players to claim a generous 200% welcome bonus up to €10,000 and start playing within minutes. Lucrative ongoing promotions and imminent loyalty perks provide recurring value for regular players</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap">It's a great place for gamblers, sports bettors and crypto enthusiasts - check it out!</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><a class="infobutton" href="https://blockonomi.com/out/luckyblock">Visit Lucky Block</a></p>
<hr />
<h3>Playgram</h3>
<p>



<div class="fcrp-scfeatured">

  <div class="scfeatleft">

    <div class="scfeat-content">	<a  rel="nofollow"  href="https://blockonomi.com/out/playgram"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="150" height="150" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/Playgram.gif" class="scfeat_logo fcrpimg-res wp-post-image" alt="" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/Playgram.gif 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/Playgram-50x50.gif 50w" sizes="(max-width: 150px) 100vw, 150px" /></a>     <span class="scfeatrate">Overall Rating</span>

                         <span class="fcrp-ratebig rmbottom"><span class="fcrp-ratebig-total" style="width:100%"></span></span>	  <a  rel="nofollow"  href="https://blockonomi.com/out/playgram" class="fcrp-button playb"> 	  	Play Now  	</a>    </div><!--block-content ends-->

</div>



  <div class="scfeatright ">



    <h3>Playgram</h3>



    <h4 class="fcrpbonus_text">Welcome Bonus of 100 Free Spins</h4><span><a href="https://blockonomi.com/playgram-review/" class="revlink tc">Read Our Full Review Here</a></span>  <p><p>Playgram Casino offers an innovative, user-friendly gambling experience by seamlessly integrating a wide range of crypto-based casino games and services into the Telegram messaging app, prioritizing privacy, speed, and mobile accessibility for modern players.</p>
</p>

					<ul><li>Innovative Telegram-based platform for easy access and use</li><li>No traditional registration required, enhancing privacy</li><li>Wide range of cryptocurrency options for deposits and withdrawals</li><li>Fast transaction processing, especially for withdrawals</li><li>Loyalty program with cashback and exclusive bonuses</li></ul>   </div><!--block-right ends-->  </div><!--widget-block-rounded ends--></p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Playgram Casino is an innovative online gambling platform that launched in August 2024. It stands out from traditional online casinos by operating entirely through the popular Telegram messaging app.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">This unique approach combines the convenience of mobile messaging with the excitement of online gambling, offering players a seamless and user-friendly gaming experience.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The casino boasts an impressive selection of over 3,000 games, including slots, table games, live casino options, and game shows from top providers in the industry.</p>
<figure id="attachment_104196" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-104196" style="width: 485px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-104196" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/Playgram-Homepage.jpg" alt="Playgram Homepage" width="485" height="736" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/Playgram-Homepage.jpg 485w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/Playgram-Homepage-198x300.jpg 198w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/Playgram-Homepage-33x50.jpg 33w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/Playgram-Homepage-150x228.jpg 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/Playgram-Homepage-450x683.jpg 450w" sizes="(max-width: 485px) 100vw, 485px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-104196" class="wp-caption-text">Playgram Homepage</figcaption></figure>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Playgram caters to the growing demand for cryptocurrency-based gambling by supporting over 12 different cryptocurrencies for both deposits and withdrawals, ensuring quick transactions and enhanced privacy for its users.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">With its mobile-first design, attractive bonuses, and focus on user privacy, Playgram Casino represents a forward-thinking approach to online gambling that caters to the preferences of modern, tech-savvy players.</p>
<hr />
<h4>Key Points</h4>
<ul>
<li>Innovative concept: Playgram Casino operates entirely through the Telegram messaging app, offering a unique and convenient gambling experience.</li>
<li>Extensive game selection: Over 3,000 games including slots, table games, live casino, and game shows from top providers.</li>
<li>Cryptocurrency focus: Supports 12+ cryptocurrencies for deposits and withdrawals, ensuring quick transactions and enhanced privacy.</li>
<li>Attractive welcome bonus: 100 free spins with no wagering requirements on a minimum $30 deposit.</li>
<li>Regular promotions: Offers Drops &amp; Wins events, a referral program, and weekend reload bonuses.</li>
<li>Loyalty program: Tiered system with increasing benefits including cashback rewards and exclusive bonuses.</li>
<li>Fast payouts: Withdrawals typically processed within minutes.</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">24/7 customer support: Readily accessible through Telegram's chat feature.</li>
</ul>
<hr />
<p>Playgram Casino offers an exciting and innovative approach to online gambling, seamlessly blending the convenience of Telegram messaging with a comprehensive casino experience. Its user-friendly interface, extensive game selection, and cryptocurrency focus make it an attractive option for both newcomers and experienced players alike.</p>
<p>The platform's emphasis on quick transactions, privacy, and mobile accessibility positions it at the forefront of modern online gaming trends. With its unique Telegram-based operation, attractive bonuses, and commitment to user convenience, Playgram Casino stands out as a forward-thinking choice in the competitive world of online casinos.</p>
<p>As the gambling industry continues to evolve, Playgram's innovative model could well represent the future of online casino gaming, offering a fresh and engaging way to enjoy favorite casino games on the go.</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><a class="infobutton" href="https://blockonomi.com/out/playgram">Visit Playgram</a></p>
<hr />
<h3>Mega Dice</h3>
<p>



<div class="fcrp-scfeatured">

  <div class="scfeatleft">

    <div class="scfeat-content">	<a  rel="nofollow"  href="https://blockonomi.com/out/megadice"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="150" height="150" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Mega-Dice.gif" class="scfeat_logo fcrpimg-res wp-post-image" alt="Mega Dice" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Mega-Dice.gif 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Mega-Dice-50x50.gif 50w" sizes="(max-width: 150px) 100vw, 150px" /></a>     <span class="scfeatrate">Overall Rating</span>

                         <span class="fcrp-ratebig rmbottom"><span class="fcrp-ratebig-total" style="width:100%"></span></span>	  <a  rel="nofollow"  href="https://blockonomi.com/out/megadice" class="fcrp-button playb"> 	  	Play Now  	</a>    </div><!--block-content ends-->

</div>



  <div class="scfeatright ">



    <h3>Mega Dice</h3>



    <h4 class="fcrpbonus_text">200% match up to 1 BTC + 50 free spins</h4><span><a href="https://blockonomi.com/mega-dice-review/" class="revlink tc">Read Our Full Review Here</a></span>  <p><p>Mega Dice Casino is a legitimate and innovative online crypto gambling platform that offers an extensive game library, generous bonuses, top-notch security features, and seamless integration with popular apps like Telegram.</p>
</p>

					<ul><li>Instant withdrawals processed on the blockchain</li><li>Generous welcome bonus of 200% up to 1 BTC + 50 free spins</li><li>Wide selection of games from top providers like Evolution, Pragmatic Play, Hacksaw</li><li>Offers a sportsbook in addition to casino games</li><li>Innovative features like Telegram integration and WalletConnect</li></ul>   </div><!--block-right ends-->  </div><!--widget-block-rounded ends--></p>
<p>Mega Dice is an innovative online cryptocurrency casino and sportsbook that has been operating since 2023. It stands out as the world's first officially licensed casino platform accessible via the popular Telegram messaging app.</p>
<figure id="attachment_91852" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-91852" style="width: 1000px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-91852" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Mega-Dice-Homepage.jpg" alt="Mega Dice Homepage" width="1000" height="700" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Mega-Dice-Homepage.jpg 1000w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Mega-Dice-Homepage-300x210.jpg 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Mega-Dice-Homepage-768x538.jpg 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Mega-Dice-Homepage-50x35.jpg 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Mega-Dice-Homepage-150x105.jpg 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/Mega-Dice-Homepage-450x315.jpg 450w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-91852" class="wp-caption-text">Mega Dice Homepage</figcaption></figure>
<p>With top-notch security features, generous bonuses, and a user-friendly interface, Mega Dice Casino has quickly established itself as a premier destination for crypto gambling enthusiasts.</p>
<hr />
<h4>Key Points</h4>
<ul>
<li>Extensive game library with slots, table games, live casino, sportsbook, and unique crypto games</li>
<li>Generous welcome bonus of 200% match up to 1 BTC + 50 free spins for new players</li>
<li>Supports a wide range of cryptocurrencies for fast and secure deposits/withdrawals, including Bitcoin, Ethereum, Litecoin, and more</li>
<li>Instant withdrawals processed on the blockchain for added convenience</li>
<li>Regular promotions, reload bonuses, and a loyalty program to reward existing players</li>
<li>Comprehensive sportsbook covering major sports leagues, events, and esports tournaments</li>
</ul>
<hr />
<p>Mega Dice Casino is a standout platform in the online cryptocurrency gambling space. With its innovative features like Telegram integration, diverse game offerings from top providers, generous bonuses, robust security measures, and a comprehensive sportsbook, it delivers an exceptional and convenient gaming experience.</p>
<p>The casino's commitment to providing a secure, transparent, and user-friendly environment, coupled with its focus on cutting-edge technology and instant payouts on the blockchain, solidifies its position as a trailblazer in the industry. </p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><a class="infobutton" href="https://blockonomi.com/out/megadice">Visit Mega Dice</a></p>
<hr />
<h3>Betplay</h3>
<p>



<div class="fcrp-scfeatured">

  <div class="scfeatleft">

    <div class="scfeat-content">	<a  rel="nofollow"  href="https://blockonomi.com/out/betplay"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="300" height="300" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/Betplay-300x300.gif" class="scfeat_logo fcrpimg-res wp-post-image" alt="" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/Betplay-300x300.gif 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/Betplay-150x150.gif 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/Betplay-50x50.gif 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/Betplay-450x450.gif 450w" sizes="(max-width: 300px) 100vw, 300px" /></a>     <span class="scfeatrate">Overall Rating</span>

                         <span class="fcrp-ratebig rmbottom"><span class="fcrp-ratebig-total" style="width:100%"></span></span>	  <a  rel="nofollow"  href="https://blockonomi.com/out/betplay" class="fcrp-button playb"> 	  	Play Now  	</a>    </div><!--block-content ends-->

</div>



  <div class="scfeatright ">



    <h3>Betplay</h3>



    <h4 class="fcrpbonus_text">Welcome Bonus Matches 100% up to 50 mBTC</h4><span><a href="https://blockonomi.com/betplay-casino-review/" class="revlink tc">Read Our Full Review Here</a></span>  <p><p>With thousands of high-quality games, lucrative crypto bonuses, sleek mobile compatibility, and excellent customer support, emerging online casino Betplay delivers a polished, feature-rich experience catering to modern player preferences across devices.</p>
</p>

					<ul><li>Large game selection with over 6,000 titles from top providers</li><li>Generous crypto welcome bonus up to 50 mBTC</li><li>Fast withdrawals through cryptocurrency support</li><li>Slick, intuitive site design optimized for mobile</li><li>Live chat provides quick customer support</li></ul>   </div><!--block-right ends-->  </div><!--widget-block-rounded ends--></p>
<p>Betplay is an emerging online crypto casino that aims to provide a modern, entertaining gambling experience through its extensive games library, lucrative bonuses, and slick platform design. Established in 2020 and licensed under a Costa Rica-based ownership group, Betplay offers over 6,000 titles across slots, table games, live dealer options and more from leading developers.</p>
<figure id="attachment_85503" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-85503" style="width: 1000px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-85503" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/Betplay-Homepage.gif" alt="Betplay Homepage" width="1000" height="700" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-85503" class="wp-caption-text">Betplay Homepage</figcaption></figure>
<p>The site incentivizes new players with a generous 100% deposit bonus up to 50 mBTC while rewarding loyalty through weekly cashback and daily rakeback programs.</p>
<p>Betplay accepts major cryptocurrencies for fast, secure transactions and implements reasonable security controls around encryption and infrastructure monitoring.</p>
<p>With its expanding features and focus on user experience, Betplay shapes up as an intriguing new contender in the bitcoin casino space.</p>
<hr />
<h4>Key Points</h4>
<ul>
<li>Offers over 6,000 casino games including slots, table games, live dealer games, and more from top providers like Microgaming and Evolution Gaming</li>
<li>Lucrative welcome bonus of 100% deposit match up to 50 mBTC</li>
<li>10% weekly cashback on losses and daily rakeback rewards for loyal players</li>
<li>Quick deposits and fast withdrawals through support of major cryptocurrencies</li>
<li>24/7 customer support via live chat and email with knowledgeable agents</li>
<li>Allows play in free demo modes to try games risk-free before betting real money</li>
</ul>
<hr />
<p>For players seeking a modern, cryptocurrency-focused online casino, Betplay shapes up as an appealing option worth exploring.</p>
<p>Betplay makes a strong initial impression by getting the fundamentals right - offering a smooth, easily navigable platform across devices, expanding games library with titles from top studios, and reliable customer support response times.</p>
<p>The generous 100% welcome bonus matches competitors while daily rakeback and weekly cashback promotions cater to loyalty long-term.</p>
<p>Betplay has all the makings of a rising star worth betting on for crypto gamblers seeking quality gameplay and modern convenience.</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><a class="infobutton" href="https://blockonomi.com/out/betplay">Visit Betplay</a></p>
<hr />
<h3>BC Game</h3>
<p>



<div class="fcrp-scfeatured">

  <div class="scfeatleft">

    <div class="scfeat-content">	<a  rel="nofollow"  href="https://blockonomi.com/out/bc-game"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="150" height="150" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/bc-game-review.gif" class="scfeat_logo fcrpimg-res wp-post-image" alt="BC.Game Review" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/bc-game-review.gif 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/bc-game-review-50x50.gif 50w" sizes="(max-width: 150px) 100vw, 150px" /></a>     <span class="scfeatrate">Overall Rating</span>

                         <span class="fcrp-ratebig rmbottom"><span class="fcrp-ratebig-total" style="width:100%"></span></span>	  <a  rel="nofollow"  href="https://blockonomi.com/out/bc-game" class="fcrp-button playb"> 	  	Play Now  	</a>    </div><!--block-content ends-->

</div>



  <div class="scfeatright ">



    <h3>BC.Game</h3>



    <h4 class="fcrpbonus_text">Earn up to $20,000 welcome bonus</h4><span><a href="https://blockonomi.com/bc-game-review/" class="revlink tc">Read Our Full Review Here</a></span>  <p><p><a href="https://blockonomi.com/out/bc-game">BC.Game</a> is a popular crypto-focused online casino launched in 2017 that offers over 8,000 games, generous bonuses up to 300%, and supports 18+ major cryptocurrencies and various payment methods across its sports betting, slots, table games, and live casino.</p>
</p>

					<ul><li>8,000+ games including slots, casino, sports betting, crypto betting</li><li>Generous welcome bonuses up to 300%</li><li>Supports 18+ major cryptocurrencies for deposits and withdrawals</li><li>Smooth and user-friendly interface</li></ul>   </div><!--block-right ends-->  </div><!--widget-block-rounded ends--></p>
<p>BC.Game is a feature-rich crypto gambling platform launched in 2017 that has quickly become a top choice for enthusiasts seeking an exciting and generous online casino.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-81121" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/screenshot-bc.game-2023.10.25-16_02_57.png" alt="" width="1280" height="536" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/screenshot-bc.game-2023.10.25-16_02_57.png 1280w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/screenshot-bc.game-2023.10.25-16_02_57-300x126.png 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/screenshot-bc.game-2023.10.25-16_02_57-768x322.png 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/screenshot-bc.game-2023.10.25-16_02_57-50x21.png 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/screenshot-bc.game-2023.10.25-16_02_57-150x63.png 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/screenshot-bc.game-2023.10.25-16_02_57-450x188.png 450w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/screenshot-bc.game-2023.10.25-16_02_57-1200x503.png 1200w" sizes="(max-width: 1280px) 100vw, 1280px" /></p>
<p>With over 8,000 games spanning slots, table games, live casino, sportsbook, and more, BC.Game offers a smooth, mobile-friendly gambling experience for players around the world.</p>
<hr />
<h4>Keypoints</h4>
<ul>
<li>Launched in 2017, BC.Game offers over 8,000 crypto-focused games including slots, table games, sports betting, and live casino</li>
<li>Generous welcome bonuses up to 300% for new players</li>
<li>Supports 18+ major cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin, Ethereum, Tether for deposits and withdrawals</li>
<li>Good selection of sports betting options including football, tennis, esports</li>
<li>10,000+ slot games available from top providers like Pragmatic Play and Spinomenal</li>
<li>Classic table games on offer including roulette, baccarat and blackjack</li>
<li>Live casino games streamed in HD quality for an immersive experience</li>
<li>Fun games like crypto price betting, lottery, bingo and horse racing also available</li>
<li>Fast and helpful 24/7 live chat customer support</li>
<li>User-friendly interface and mobile apps for iOS and Android</li>
</ul>
<hr />
<p>With over 8,000 games, generous bonuses, multiple crypto payment options, and a slick user interface, BC.Game has positioned itself as a top choice for crypto casino gaming since its launch in 2017.</p>
<p>Powered by leading gaming providers like Pragmatic Play and Evolution Gaming, the sheer variety coupled with rapid payouts across 18 cryptocurrencies makes BC.Game a one-stop shop for thrilling, trustworthy online gambling with crypto.</p>
<p>Throw in 24/7 live support, regular promotions, and a rewarding VIP program, and BC.Game checks off all the perks players desire in an online casino.</p>
<p>With so many strengths powering this nascent yet wildly popular platform, crypto gambling fans would be remiss not to give BC.Game a spin.</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><a class="infobutton" href="https://blockonomi.com/out/bc-game">Visit BC.Game</a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<hr />
<h3>Wall Street Memes</h3>
<p>



<div class="fcrp-scfeatured">

  <div class="scfeatleft">

    <div class="scfeat-content">	<a  rel="nofollow"  href="https://blockonomi.com/out/wallstreetmeme"><img decoding="async" width="300" height="300" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/wsm-300x300.jpg" class="scfeat_logo fcrpimg-res wp-post-image" alt="" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/wsm-300x300.jpg 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/wsm-150x150.jpg 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/wsm-50x50.jpg 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/wsm.jpg 400w" sizes="(max-width: 300px) 100vw, 300px" /></a>     <span class="scfeatrate">Overall Rating</span>

                         <span class="fcrp-ratebig rmbottom"><span class="fcrp-ratebig-total" style="width:100%"></span></span>	  <a  rel="nofollow"  href="https://blockonomi.com/out/wallstreetmeme" class="fcrp-button playb"> 	  	Play Now  	</a>    </div><!--block-content ends-->

</div>



  <div class="scfeatright ">



    <h3>WSM Casino</h3>



    <h4 class="fcrpbonus_text">200% Match up to $25,000 + 200 Free Spins</h4><span><a href="https://blockonomi.com/wall-street-memes-casino-review/" class="revlink tc">Read Our Full Review Here</a></span>  <p><p>Wall Street Memes Casino is a brand new crypto gambling site that blends a massive game library of over 5,000 titles, generous bonuses &amp; fast payouts to provide an immersive experience tailored for the crypto community.</p>
</p>

					<ul><li>Wide range of over 5,000 games from top providers</li><li>Accepts over a dozen popular cryptocurrencies</li><li>Generous 200% up to $25,000 welcome bonus</li><li>Very fast payouts, often within 10 minutes</li><li>Slick modern website design with meme/crypto styling</li></ul>   </div><!--block-right ends-->  </div><!--widget-block-rounded ends--></p>
<p>Wall Street Memes Casino is a brand new online gambling platform that blends the themes of cryptocurrency, internet memes, and finance. </p>
<figure id="attachment_92077" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-92077" style="width: 1000px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-92077" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/WSM-Homepage.jpg" alt="WSM Homepage" width="1000" height="700" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/WSM-Homepage.jpg 1000w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/WSM-Homepage-300x210.jpg 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/WSM-Homepage-768x538.jpg 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/WSM-Homepage-50x35.jpg 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/WSM-Homepage-150x105.jpg 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/WSM-Homepage-450x315.jpg 450w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-92077" class="wp-caption-text">WSM Homepage</figcaption></figure>
<p>What sets Wall Street Memes Casino apart is its deep integration with cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin, Ethereum, Dogecoin, and its native WSM token. It offers anonymous play, fast payouts, and a 200% welcome bonus up to $25,000 for crypto deposits. The meme-inspired branding and design create an immersive environment for the crypto community.</p>
<hr />
<h4>Key Points</h4>
<ul>
<li>Massive game library of over 5,000 titles covering slots, table games, live dealer, game shows, and provably fair "crash" games</li>
<li>Fully integrated sportsbook offering betting on 35+ sports markets, including esports</li>
<li>Generous 200% welcome bonus up to $25,000 + 200 free spins for depositing with WSM token</li>
<li>Anonymous play allowed without KYC up to $2,000 deposit/withdrawal limits</li>
<li>Supports over a dozen popular cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin, Ethereum, Dogecoin, and its native WSM token</li>
<li>24/7 live chat support and well-resourced FAQ knowledge base</li>
</ul>
<hr />
<p>Wall Street Memes Casino emerges as a fresh and innovative option in the online gambling space, delivering a tailored experience for crypto enthusiasts and internet culture fans alike.</p>
<p>The casino excels in providing an engaging user experience, prioritizing anonymity, security, and ultra-fast payouts facilitated by crypto payments. While still establishing its reputation, Wall Street Memes Casino shows impressive potential to carve out a unique niche by blending cutting-edge technology with creative community-driven features.</p>
<p>For those seeking a modern, crypto-focused gambling platform that stands out from the crowd, Wall Street Memes Casino is undoubtedly worth exploring.</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><a class="infobutton" href="https://blockonomi.com/out/wallstreetmeme">Visit Wall Street Memes Casino</a></p>
<hr />
<h3>Wild.io</h3>
<p>



<div class="fcrp-scfeatured">

  <div class="scfeatleft">

    <div class="scfeat-content">	<a  rel="nofollow"  href="https://blockonomi.com/out/wildio"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="150" height="150" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/wild-io-revew.gif" class="scfeat_logo fcrpimg-res wp-post-image" alt="wild.io" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/wild-io-revew.gif 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/wild-io-revew-50x50.gif 50w" sizes="(max-width: 150px) 100vw, 150px" /></a>     <span class="scfeatrate">Overall Rating</span>

                         <span class="fcrp-ratebig rmbottom"><span class="fcrp-ratebig-total" style="width:100%"></span></span>	  <a  rel="nofollow"  href="https://blockonomi.com/out/wildio" class="fcrp-button playb"> 	  	Play Now  	</a>    </div><!--block-content ends-->

</div>



  <div class="scfeatright ">



    <h3>Wild.io</h3>



    <h4 class="fcrpbonus_text">400% Welcome Bonus up to $10,000 + 300 Free Spins</h4><span><a href="https://blockonomi.com/wild-io-review/" class="revlink tc">Read Our Full Review Here</a></span>  <p><p>With generous crypto bonuses, instant payouts, and a smooth cross-device gameplay experience, Wild.io provides a compelling new option for cryptocurrency gamblers</p>
</p>

					<ul><li>Instant withdrawals for crypto currencies</li><li>Huge selection of slots and table games</li><li>Instant play site needs no downloading</li><li>VIP program rewards loyal players</li></ul>   </div><!--block-right ends-->  </div><!--widget-block-rounded ends--></p>
<p>Bringing innovation to the expanding galaxy of crypto gambling sites, Wild.io has offered premium entertainment since 2022. Obtaining credentials from the reputable Curacao egaming authorities and enlisting talented developers, Wild.io furnishes an abundant game selection spanning over 1,600 titles presently.</p>
<p>Slots steal the spotlight, but blackjack devotees, roulette fans and live stream enthusiasts find tailored action through variants and dedicated studios.</p>
<figure id="attachment_82018" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-82018" style="width: 1000px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-82018" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/website-1.jpg" alt="Wild.io Design" width="1000" height="700" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/website-1.jpg 1000w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/website-1-300x210.jpg 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/website-1-768x538.jpg 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/website-1-50x35.jpg 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/website-1-150x105.jpg 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/website-1-450x315.jpg 450w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-82018" class="wp-caption-text">Wild.io Design</figcaption></figure>
<p>Lucrative matched deposits give way to ongoing cashback incentives, surprise bonus drops and contest entries across desktop and mobile. While constraints exist around eligibility in several countries presently, Wild.io focuses on usability, security and entertainment for crypto gamblers looking to explore modern iGaming frontiers.</p>
<hr />
<h4>Key Points</h4>
<ul>
<li>Lucrative welcome bonus up to $5,000 + 300 free spins</li>
<li>Instant withdrawals with no limits for cryptocurrencies</li>
<li>Generous ongoing promotions like 77% reload matches</li>
<li>Smooth, contemporary site design for desktop and mobile</li>
<li>Exclusive focus on major cryptocurrencies only</li>
<li>Innovative games like Crash, Plinko, Mines</li>
<li>eSports and sports betting planned for the future</li>
</ul>
<hr />
<p>In an increasingly crowded crypto gambling landscape, Wild.io has carved out a distinctive niche since its 2022 founding by merging innovation with entertainment.</p>
<p>Lucrative sign-up rewards in the form of matched deposits and free spins continue through passive cashback, surprise bonus drops and contest entries incentivizing gameplay daily.</p>
<p>Swift verifications and rapid payouts cement convenience while robust cryptography and responsible gambling protocols safeguard activities for customers globally.</p>
<p>For those seeking a contemporary online casino experience, Wild.io makes an appealing choice to wager at your own pace.</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><a class="infobutton" href="https://blockonomi.com/out/wildio">Visit Wild.io</a></p>
<hr />
<h3>Meta Spins</h3>
<p>



<div class="fcrp-scfeatured">

  <div class="scfeatleft">

    <div class="scfeat-content">	<a  rel="nofollow"  href="https://blockonomi.com/out/metaspins"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="150" height="150" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/Metaspins.gif" class="scfeat_logo fcrpimg-res wp-post-image" alt="" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/Metaspins.gif 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/Metaspins-50x50.gif 50w" sizes="(max-width: 150px) 100vw, 150px" /></a>     <span class="scfeatrate">Overall Rating</span>

                         <span class="fcrp-ratebig rmbottom"><span class="fcrp-ratebig-total" style="width:100%"></span></span>	  <a  rel="nofollow"  href="https://blockonomi.com/out/metaspins" class="fcrp-button playb"> 	  	Play Now  	</a>    </div><!--block-content ends-->

</div>



  <div class="scfeatright ">



    <h3>Metaspins</h3>



    <h4 class="fcrpbonus_text">Welcome Bonus of 100% Deposit Match Up To 1 BTC</h4><span><a href="https://blockonomi.com/metaspins-review/" class="revlink tc">Read Our Full Review Here</a></span>  <p><p>Metaspins is a new, feature-rich crypto casino with a solid lineup of games, generous bonuses, ultra-fast payouts, and a modern, easy-to-use interface that positions it as a top choice for online gambling enthusiasts.</p>
</p>

					<ul><li>Generous welcome bonus up to 1 BTC</li><li>2,500+ casino games from top providers</li><li>Great selection of provably fair games</li><li>Lucrative loyalty program with up to 60% rakeback</li><li>Fast withdrawals in under 10 minutes</li></ul>   </div><!--block-right ends-->  </div><!--widget-block-rounded ends--></p>
<div class="contents">
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap">Metaspins is an exciting new online crypto casino making a splash since its launch in 2022. Operating on a license from the Government of Curacao, this provably fair platform offers players a modern, mobile-friendly website with over 2,500 top-quality games, generous welcome bonuses, ultra-fast payouts, and 24/7 customer support.</p>
<figure id="attachment_86875" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-86875" style="width: 1000px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-86875" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/Metaspin-Homepage.jpg" alt="Metaspin Homepage" width="1000" height="700" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/Metaspin-Homepage.jpg 1000w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/Metaspin-Homepage-300x210.jpg 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/Metaspin-Homepage-768x538.jpg 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/Metaspin-Homepage-50x35.jpg 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/Metaspin-Homepage-150x105.jpg 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/Metaspin-Homepage-450x315.jpg 450w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-86875" class="wp-caption-text">Metaspin Homepage</figcaption></figure>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap">Led by industry veterans, Metaspins provides a robust gaming suite spanning slots, table games, live dealer options, and even unique lotto-style games. Popular cryptocurrencies enable swift real-money transactions, while top-notch security protocols ensure safe gameplay.</p>
</div>
<hr />
<h4>Key Points</h4>
<ul>
<li>Offers over 2,500 games from top providers like NetEnt and Microgaming</li>
<li>Generous 100% welcome bonus up to 1 BTC with reasonable 7x wagering requirement</li>
<li>Accepts popular cryptos like BTC, ETH, LTC, BCH, DOGE</li>
<li>Wide selection of provably fair casino games for transparency</li>
<li>Lucrative Mega Lotto game with huge jackpot potential</li>
<li>Ongoing promotions like cashback, reloads, prize drops, and challenges</li>
</ul>
<hr />
<div class="contents">
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap">With just over a year in operation, Metaspins has already established itself as one of the premier crypto casinos catering to virtual gamblers across experience levels. This rising platform clearly focused efforts toward crafting long-term leadership foundations centered on trust, variety and innovation right from the outset – hitting the mark on all aspects.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap">A legitimate license and transparent operations provide accountability. Premium gaming libraries supply endless engagement. Lucrative promotions inspire consistent participation. </p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap">We wholly recommend signing up at Metaspins for a superlative crypto gambling experience that responsibly entertains while duly prioritizing user security through best-in-class technology protocols at every corner.</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><a class="infobutton" href="https://blockonomi.com/out/metaspins">Visit Metaspin</a></p>
</div>
<hr />
<h3>Stake</h3>
<p>



<div class="fcrp-scfeatured">

  <div class="scfeatleft">

    <div class="scfeat-content">	<a  rel="nofollow"  href="https://blockonomi.com/out/stakecom"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="150" height="150" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/stake-review.gif" class="scfeat_logo fcrpimg-res wp-post-image" alt="Stake Review" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/stake-review.gif 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/10/stake-review-50x50.gif 50w" sizes="(max-width: 150px) 100vw, 150px" /></a>     <span class="scfeatrate">Overall Rating</span>

                         <span class="fcrp-ratebig rmbottom"><span class="fcrp-ratebig-total" style="width:100%"></span></span>	  <a  rel="nofollow"  href="https://blockonomi.com/out/stakecom" class="fcrp-button playb"> 	  	Play Now  	</a>    </div><!--block-content ends-->

</div>



  <div class="scfeatright ">



    <h3>Stake</h3>



    <h4 class="fcrpbonus_text">200% Match Bonus Up To $1000</h4><span><a href="https://blockonomi.com/stake-com-review/" class="revlink tc">Read Our Full Review Here</a></span>  <p><p>Stake.com is a leading crypto gambling site founded in 2017 that offers over 1,000 casino games and bets on 40+ sports, provides birthday/monthly bonuses to players, accepts deposits in 20+ cryptocurrencies, and has a user-friendly web-based platform accessible on mobile.</p>
</p>

					<ul><li>Large selection of casino games (3,000+ slots) and sports betting options (40+ sports)</li><li>Accepts deposits in 20+ major cryptocurrencies</li><li>Monthly and birthday bonuses for active players</li><li>Fast and user-friendly web-based platform works on mobile</li></ul>   </div><!--block-right ends-->  </div><!--widget-block-rounded ends--></p>
<p>Launched in 2017, Stake.com is a leading online crypto-gambling platform that offers users access to over 1,000 casino games and betting options on 40+ different sports.</p>
<p>The Curacao-licensed site accepts deposits in 20+ major cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin and Ethereum, making payments fast and secure. Stake.com provides a smooth user experience with its intuitive web-based platform that works seamlessly across desktop and mobile devices.</p>
<figure id="attachment_84203" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-84203" style="width: 1000px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-84203" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/12/Stake-Homepage.gif" alt="Stake Homepage" width="1000" height="700" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-84203" class="wp-caption-text">Stake Homepage</figcaption></figure>
<p>The site offers competitive odds and a variety of betting choices across its sportsbook and expansive casino game selection. Active players can qualify for special monthly and birthday bonus rewards.</p>
<p>With its wide array of gaming options, crypto payment support, and rewards program, Stake.com aims to be a top destination for crypto-based sports betting and online casino gambling.</p>
<hr />
<h4>Key Points</h4>
<ul>
<li>Offers over 1,000 casino games including 3,000+ slots, plus betting on 40+ different sports like esports, soccer, tennis, MMA, esports etc.</li>
<li>Accepts deposits in 20+ major cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin, Ethereum, Dogecoin etc</li>
<li>Provides monthly and birthday bonus rewards to active players.</li>
<li>User-friendly web-based platform works seamlessly on desktop and mobile.</li>
<li>Competitive odds and a wide variety of betting options across casino games and sports.</li>
</ul>
<hr />
<p>With over 1,000 high-quality casino games and betting options across 40+ sports, Stake.com establishes itself as a premier destination for crypto-based gambling.</p>
<p>Its smooth web-platform works flawlessly across devices, while the integration of 20+ major cryptocurrencies enables swift, anonymous payments and withdrawals.</p>
<p>Active engagement is rewarded through monthly and birthday bonuses. Stake.com also prioritizes user security through encryption, 2FA, and licensing via the Government of Curacao. Combined with competitive odds, an abundance of gaming variety, and a user-friendly interface, Stake.com offers an accessible and engaging experience for the modern crypto gambling enthusiast.</p>
<p>For those seeking a trusted, feature-complete crypto gambling platform, Stake.com checks all the boxes.</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><a class="infobutton" href="https://blockonomi.com/out/stakecom">Visit Stake</a></p>
<hr />
<h3>7Bit Casino</h3>
<p>



<div class="fcrp-scfeatured">

  <div class="scfeatleft">

    <div class="scfeat-content">	<a  rel="nofollow"  href="https://blockonomi.com/out/7bit"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="150" height="150" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/7bitcasino.gif" class="scfeat_logo fcrpimg-res wp-post-image" alt="" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/7bitcasino.gif 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/7bitcasino-50x50.gif 50w" sizes="(max-width: 150px) 100vw, 150px" /></a>     <span class="scfeatrate">Overall Rating</span>

                         <span class="fcrp-ratebig rmbottom"><span class="fcrp-ratebig-total" style="width:100%"></span></span>	  <a  rel="nofollow"  href="https://blockonomi.com/out/7bit" class="fcrp-button playb"> 	  	Play Now  	</a>    </div><!--block-content ends-->

</div>



  <div class="scfeatright ">



    <h3>7Bit Casino</h3>



    <h4 class="fcrpbonus_text">Bonuses Up to 5 BTC Plus 300 Free Spins</h4><span><a href="https://blockonomi.com/7bit-casino-review/" class="revlink tc">Read Our Full Review Here</a></span>  <p><p>7Bit Casino is a long-running, licensed online crypto casino with a huge games library, generous bonuses, and fast payouts across multiple traditional and digital currencies.</p>
</p>

					<ul><li>Massive selection of over 3000 games from top providers</li><li>Quick withdrawals, especially for cryptocurrencies</li><li>Great recurring promos and VIP program for loyal players</li><li>Mobile optimized - play anywhere on smartphone or tablet</li></ul>   </div><!--block-right ends-->  </div><!--widget-block-rounded ends--></p>
<p>As one of the longest-running crypto casinos online since 2014, 7Bit continues providing a premier destination for provably fair gambling and lightning-fast payouts.</p>
<figure id="attachment_86202" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-86202" style="width: 1000px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-86202" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/12/Homepage-4-1.gif" alt="7Bit Casino Hompage" width="1000" height="700" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-86202" class="wp-caption-text">7Bit Casino Hompage</figcaption></figure>
<p>Lucrative matched deposits continue through ongoing reload incentives, cashback deals and contest entries.</p>
<p>Across desktop and mobile, the platform focuses on usability from simplified verification to readily available customer assistance. </p>
<hr />
<h4>Key Points</h4>
<ul>
<li>Over 3,000 games from leading providers like Betsoft and BGaming</li>
<li>Lucrative welcome bonus up to 5 BTC plus 300 free spins</li>
<li>Cryptocurrency support for fast, anonymous banking with BTC, ETH, LTC</li>
<li>8-tier VIP program with escalating rewards for loyal players</li>
<li>Generous ongoing promotions like 25% Monday deposit match</li>
<li>Instant payouts for withdrawal methods like Bitcoin and Ethereum</li>
<li>Exclusive crypto games section provides unique gambling options</li>
</ul>
<hr />
<p>As one of the original Bitcoin-friendly online casinos since 2014, 7Bit Casino continues providing an enjoyable iGaming destination for crypto enthusiasts and traditional players alike.</p>
<p>Their Curacao license upholds legitimacy while a vast game selection from renowned studios guarantees entertainment across devices. Lucrative sign-up bonuses give way to recurring reload matches, cashback deals and contest entries incentivizing gameplay daily.</p>
<p>7Bit Casino has upheld the pillars of strong support, banking diversity and provably fair entertainment that made crypto casinos so revolutionary over the past decade for gamblers who value anonymity and instant transactions.</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><a class="infobutton" href="https://blockonomi.com/out/7bit">Visit 7Bit Casino</a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<hr />
<h2>Guide to Telegram Casinos</h2>
<p>Telegram casinos are online gambling platforms that operate within the Telegram messaging app. Telegram is a secure and encrypted messaging app that allows users to communicate with one another.</p>
<p>In addition to its messaging capabilities, Telegram also offers a wide range of other features, including the ability to create and join Telegram casino groups.</p>
<p>These casinos leverage the interactive nature of Telegram to create a social and engaging gaming experience for users. From classic card games like poker and blackjack to exciting slot machines, Telegram casinos offer a diverse selection of games to cater to different preferences.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-large wp-image-39899" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/telegram-1024x682.jpg" alt="Telegram" width="814" height="542" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/telegram-1024x682.jpg 1024w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/telegram-300x200.jpg 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/telegram-768x512.jpg 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/telegram-50x33.jpg 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/telegram-270x180.jpg 270w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/telegram-370x245.jpg 370w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/03/telegram.jpg 1400w" sizes="(max-width: 814px) 100vw, 814px" /></p>
<h3 id="4">Benefits of Using Telegram Casinos</h3>
<p>There are several benefits to using Telegram casinos.</p>
<ul>
<li>Telegram offers enhanced privacy and security compared to traditional online casinos. Since Telegram is encrypted, you can play your favorite casino games without worrying about your personal information falling into the wrong hands.</li>
<li>Telegram casinos often offer a wide range of games and attractive bonuses to entice players. The convenience of being able to play casino games directly within the Telegram app is another major benefit for many players.</li>
<li>Telegram casinos provide a seamless and user-friendly gaming experience. With just a few taps on your smartphone, you can access a plethora of casino games and join live tournaments with players from around the world.</li>
<li>The real-time interaction and instant messaging features of Telegram enhance the social aspect of online gambling, allowing players to chat, strategize, and celebrate their wins together.</li>
</ul>
<figure id="attachment_87852" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-87852" style="width: 1000px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-87852" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/02/luckyblock-1.jpg" alt="LuckyBlock has some great bonuses for new players" width="1000" height="700" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/02/luckyblock-1.jpg 1000w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/02/luckyblock-1-300x210.jpg 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/02/luckyblock-1-768x538.jpg 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/02/luckyblock-1-50x35.jpg 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/02/luckyblock-1-150x105.jpg 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/02/luckyblock-1-450x315.jpg 450w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-87852" class="wp-caption-text"><a href="https://blockonomi.com/out/luckyblock">LuckyBlock has some great bonuses for new players</a></figcaption></figure>
<hr />
<h2 id="5">How to Choose a Telegram Casino</h2>
<p>When it comes to selecting the best Telegram casino for your online gaming experience, there are several key factors to take into consideration.</p>
<p>Prioritizing security and privacy should be at the top of your list. Opt for casinos that implement cutting-edge encryption technology to safeguard your personal and financial data. It&#8217;s also wise to delve into the reputation of the casino by perusing player reviews, ensuring that you are entrusting your gaming endeavors to a reputable and dependable platform.</p>
<h3 id="6">Evaluating Security and Privacy</h3>
<p>When choosing a Telegram casino, it is important to prioritize security and privacy. Look for casinos that use advanced encryption technology to protect your personal and financial information.</p>
<p>Consider the reputation of the casino and read reviews from other players to ensure that it is a trustworthy and reliable platform.</p>
<figure id="attachment_93038" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-93038" style="width: 1000px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-93038" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/megadice.jpg" alt="Mega Dice is a top tier crypto casino" width="1000" height="700" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/megadice.jpg 1000w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/megadice-300x210.jpg 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/megadice-768x538.jpg 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/megadice-50x35.jpg 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/megadice-150x105.jpg 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/megadice-450x315.jpg 450w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-93038" class="wp-caption-text"><a href="https://blockonomi.com/out/megadice">Mega Dice is a top tier crypto casino</a></figcaption></figure>
<h3 id="7">Assessing Game Selection and Quality</h3>
<p>Seek out casinos that boast a diverse array of games, ranging from classic favorites like slots, blackjack, roulette, to the ever-popular poker.</p>
<p>Take a moment to evaluate the game graphics and sound effects as well, as these elements contribute to creating an immersive and enjoyable gaming environment.</p>
<h3 id="8">Considering Payment Options and Speed</h3>
<p>Another crucial aspect to contemplate before finalizing your choice of a Telegram casino is the range of payment options available and the efficiency of withdrawals and deposits.</p>
<p>Opt for casinos that provide a selection of secure and user-friendly payment methods, such as credit cards, e-wallets, and cryptocurrencies. It is equally important to verify the processing times for withdrawals and deposits to ensure seamless and prompt transactions, enabling you to focus on your gaming experience without unnecessary delays.</p>
<hr />
<h2 id="4">How We Chose The Casinos on This List</h2>
<p>Choosing the best crypto casinos in Canada involved a comprehensive evaluation process.</p>
<p>We considered various factors, including:</p>
<ol>
<li>Reputation and trustworthiness of the casino,</li>
<li>Range of crypto gambling options available,</li>
<li>Quality and security of the gaming platform,</li>
<li>Customer support,</li>
<li>Overall user experience.</li>
<li>Variety of cryptocurrencies accepted,</li>
<li>Availability of bonuses and promotions,</li>
<li>Ease of deposits and withdrawals,</li>
<li>Fairness and transparency of the gaming outcomes.</li>
</ol>
<p>By taking all these factors into consideration, we were able to select <a href="https://blockonomi.com/best-telegram-casino/">the best Telegram Casinos</a> that provide a safe and enjoyable gambling experience for players.</p>
<hr />
<h2 id="9">Getting Started with Telegram Casinos</h2>
<h3 id="10">Setting Up Your Telegram Account</h3>
<p>To get started with Telegram casinos, you will need to first set up a Telegram account.</p>
<p>Simply download the Telegram app on your mobile device or visit the Telegram website on your computer.</p>
<p>Follow the on-screen instructions to create your account, and verify your phone number to gain access to the Telegram messaging app.</p>
<p>Once you have successfully set up your Telegram account, you can further personalize it by adding a profile picture, updating your status, and exploring the various settings available to customize your messaging experience.</p>
<figure id="attachment_94891" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-94891" style="width: 1000px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="wp-image-94891 size-full" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/bcgame.jpg" alt="BC.Game is a top destination with great bonuses" width="1000" height="700" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/bcgame.jpg 1000w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/bcgame-300x210.jpg 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/bcgame-768x538.jpg 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/bcgame-50x35.jpg 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/bcgame-150x105.jpg 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/bcgame-450x315.jpg 450w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-94891" class="wp-caption-text"><a href="https://blockonomi.com/out/bc-game">BC.Game is a top destination with great bonuses</a></figcaption></figure>
<h3 id="11">Finding and Joining a Casino Group</h3>
<p>Once you have set up your Telegram account, you can start finding and joining casino groups. Casino groups are communities within Telegram where players gather to discuss and share information about different casinos and games.</p>
<p>Use the search function in the Telegram app to find relevant casino groups and join the ones that interest you.</p>
<p>Joining a casino group on Telegram opens up a world of opportunities to connect with like-minded individuals, participate in group discussions, and stay updated on the latest casino promotions and bonuses.</p>
<hr />
<h2 id="12">Tips for Playing in Telegram Casinos</h2>
<h3 id="13">Understanding the Rules and Etiquette</h3>
<p>Before diving into playing casino games on Telegram, take the time to familiarize yourself with the rules and etiquette of each game.</p>
<p>Understanding the rules will help you make informed decisions and improve your chances of winning.</p>
<p>When it comes to rules, each casino game has its own set of guidelines that dictate how the game is played. For example, in blackjack, understanding when to hit, stand, double down, or split can significantly impact your success at the table.</p>
<h3 id="14">Strategies for Different Casino Games</h3>
<p>Developing effective strategies for different casino games is key to maximizing your chances of winning. Whether you are playing slots, blackjack, or roulette, take the time to learn and implement proven strategies.</p>
<p>There are numerous resources available online that offer tips and advice on how to improve your gameplay.</p>
<p>For slot games, understanding the volatility of the game can help you choose between high-risk high-reward slots or low-risk steady slots.</p>
<p>In blackjack, card counting is a popular strategy that can give you an edge over the house if done correctly.</p>
<p>Roulette players often follow betting systems like the Martingale or Fibonacci to manage their bets and potentially increase their winnings. By honing your skills and strategies in each game, you can enhance your overall casino experience and potentially walk away with more winnings.</p>
<figure id="attachment_94892" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-94892" style="width: 1000px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="wp-image-94892 size-full" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/wall-street-memes.jpg" alt="Wall Street Memes is a fun casino for crypto players" width="1000" height="700" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/wall-street-memes.jpg 1000w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/wall-street-memes-300x210.jpg 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/wall-street-memes-768x538.jpg 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/wall-street-memes-50x35.jpg 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/wall-street-memes-150x105.jpg 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/wall-street-memes-450x315.jpg 450w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-94892" class="wp-caption-text"><a href="https://blockonomi.com/out/wallstreetmeme">Wall Street Memes is a fun casino for crypto players</a></figcaption></figure>
<hr />
<h2 id="15">Staying Safe While Playing in Telegram Casinos</h2>
<p>When it comes to playing in Telegram casinos, ensuring your safety is paramount. While these platforms do provide enhanced security measures, it is still essential to remain vigilant and cautious to avoid falling victim to scams.</p>
<p>One of the key practices to keep in mind is to be wary of unsolicited messages or suspicious links that may come from unknown individuals. It&#8217;s always best to exercise caution and refrain from engaging with such content to protect your personal information and financial security.</p>
<p>In addition to being cautious of potential scams, another crucial aspect of staying safe while playing in Telegram casinos is to choose reputable and trusted casino groups.</p>
<p>By selecting well-known and established groups with positive reputations, you can significantly reduce the risk of encountering fraudulent activities. Remember, your safety and security should always be a top priority when engaging in online gambling.</p>
<figure id="attachment_87853" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-87853" style="width: 1000px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-87853" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/02/wild-1-1.jpg" alt="Wild.io Casino is another top option for crypto players" width="1000" height="700" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/02/wild-1-1.jpg 1000w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/02/wild-1-1-300x210.jpg 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/02/wild-1-1-768x538.jpg 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/02/wild-1-1-50x35.jpg 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/02/wild-1-1-150x105.jpg 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/02/wild-1-1-450x315.jpg 450w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-87853" class="wp-caption-text"><a href="https://blockonomi.com/out/wildio">Wild.io Casino is another top option for crypto players</a></figcaption></figure>
<h3 id="16">Recognizing and Avoiding Scams</h3>
<p>While Telegram casinos offer enhanced security, it is still important to stay vigilant and avoid scams. Be cautious of unsolicited messages or suspicious links from unknown individuals.</p>
<p>Only play in reputable and trusted casino groups, and do not share your personal or financial information with anyone you do not trust.</p>
<h3 id="17">Responsible Gambling in Telegram Casinos</h3>
<p>Responsible gambling is crucial to ensure a positive and safe gaming experience. Set limits for yourself, both in terms of time and money spent on gambling. Avoid chasing losses and take breaks whenever you feel overwhelmed or stressed. Remember, gambling should be an enjoyable and recreational activity.</p>
<hr />
<h2>Conclusion</h2>
<p>Telegram casinos have emerged as a game-changer in the online gambling industry, offering players an unparalleled combination of convenience, security, and excitement. By seamlessly integrating with the popular messaging app, these casinos have brought the thrill of the casino floor directly to your fingertips.</p>
<p>Throughout this article, we&#8217;ve explored the best Telegram casinos available, each offering a unique blend of games, bonuses, and features that cater to every type of player.</p>
<p>From the adrenaline-pumping action of slots to the strategic challenge of poker and the immersive experience of live casino games, these platforms have something for everyone.</p>
<p>The rise of Telegram casinos has not only revolutionized the way we gamble online but has also set a new standard for security and user-friendliness. With robust encryption, fast transactions, and a familiar interface, players can enjoy their favorite casino games with peace of mind and ease.</p>
<hr />
<h2>FAQs</h2>
<h3>What are Telegram casinos?</h3>
<p>Telegram casinos are online gambling platforms that integrate with the Telegram messaging app, allowing users to play casino games directly through the app.</p>
<h3>Are Telegram casinos safe and secure?</h3>
<p>Yes, reputable Telegram casinos use robust encryption and security measures to protect user data and ensure safe transactions. However, always research and choose licensed and trusted casinos.</p>
<h3>What types of games can I play at Telegram casinos?</h3>
<p>Telegram casinos offer a wide variety of games, including slots, poker, blackjack, roulette, baccarat, and live casino games, catering to different preferences.</p>
<h3>Can I claim bonuses at Telegram casinos?</h3>
<p>Yes, many Telegram casinos offer bonuses and promotions, such as welcome bonuses, free spins, and reload bonuses, to enhance your gaming experience.</p>
<h3>How do I deposit and withdraw funds at Telegram casinos?</h3>
<p>Telegram casinos typically support various payment methods, such as credit/debit cards, e-wallets, and cryptocurrencies. The specific options may vary depending on the casino.</p>
<h3>Are Telegram casinos legal?</h3>
<p>The legality of Telegram casinos depends on your jurisdiction. Always check your local laws and regulations before engaging in online gambling.</p>
<h3>Can I play at Telegram casinos on my mobile device?</h3>
<p>Yes, Telegram casinos are designed to be mobile-friendly, allowing you to play your favorite games on your smartphone or tablet through the Telegram app.</p>
<h3>How do I get started with Telegram casinos?</h3>
<p>To get started, you&#8217;ll need to find a reputable Telegram casino, register an account, and link it to your Telegram profile. Once set up, you can deposit funds and start playing.</p>
<h3>Are there any fees associated with using Telegram casinos?</h3>
<p>Fees may vary depending on the casino and payment method used. Some casinos may charge transaction fees, while others offer fee-free options. Always review the casino&#8217;s terms and conditions.</p>
<h3>Can I set limits on my gambling at Telegram casinos?</h3>
<p>Yes, responsible Telegram casinos offer tools to help you manage your gambling, such as deposit limits, loss limits, and self-exclusion options, promoting safe and controlled gaming habits.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/best-telegram-casino/">18+ Best Telegram Casinos &#038; Gambling Sites: Our Top Picks &#038; Reviews</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">89450</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Stablecoin Market Analysis: From $190B to $200B in Two Weeks</title>
		<link>https://blockonomi.com/stablecoin-market-analysis-from-190b-to-200b-in-two-weeks/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Oliver Dale]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 10:44:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blockonomi.com/?p=108023</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>TLDR Stablecoin market has reached a historic $200 billion total market cap, with Tether (USDT) leading at $139 billion and USDC following at $41 billion Growth driven by increased crypto trading activity and expanding use cases in payments, remittances, and savings, particularly in regions with unstable financial systems Abu Dhabi Global Market&#8217;s Financial Services Regulatory [...]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/stablecoin-market-analysis-from-190b-to-200b-in-two-weeks/">Stablecoin Market Analysis: From $190B to $200B in Two Weeks</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>TLDR</h2>
<ul>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Stablecoin market has reached a historic $200 billion total market cap, with Tether (USDT) leading at $139 billion and USDC following at $41 billion</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Growth driven by increased crypto trading activity and expanding use cases in payments, remittances, and savings, particularly in regions with unstable financial systems</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Abu Dhabi Global Market&#8217;s Financial Services Regulatory Authority has recognized USDT as an Accepted Virtual Asset, boosting institutional adoption</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Market experts, including Bitwise, project potential growth to $400 billion by 2025, contingent on favorable U.S. regulatory developments</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Traditional financial institutions like Goldman Sachs are poised to enter the market once regulatory clarity improves</li>
</ul>
<hr />
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words"><a href="https://coingape.com/stablecoin-market-hits-record-200b-milestone-400b-by-2025/">The stablecoin market has crossed a historic threshold, reaching $200 billion in total market capitalization.</a> Data from CCData and DefiLlama reveals this achievement came after adding $10 billion in just two weeks, surpassing the previous peak of $190 billion seen during the 2022 crypto rally.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">At the forefront of this growth stands Tether (USDT), which has achieved a record market value of $139 billion. This represents a 12% increase in a single month, <a href="https://defillama.com/stablecoins">according to DefiLlama&#8217;s latest data</a>. The stablecoin&#8217;s widespread adoption is evident in its user base, with over 109 million on-chain wallets holding USDT by Q4 2024.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Circle&#8217;s USD Coin (USDC) maintains its position as the second-largest stablecoin, reaching nearly $41 billion in market value. This represents a 5% growth during the same period, highlighting the continued expansion of major stablecoin platforms.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The surge in stablecoin usage extends beyond traditional crypto trading. These digital assets have found increasing utility in everyday financial transactions, particularly in regions experiencing economic instability or high inflation rates. Users are turning to stablecoins for remittances, payments, and as a store of value.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Recent developments in the Middle East have further legitimized stablecoin usage. The Abu Dhabi Global Market&#8217;s Financial Services Regulatory Authority has officially recognized USDT as an Accepted Virtual Asset. This designation enables licensed entities to offer USDT-related services, supporting the UAE&#8217;s ambition to become a global digital finance hub.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The market&#8217;s expansion has caught the attention of traditional financial institutions. Goldman Sachs CEO David Solomon has indicated the firm&#8217;s readiness to expand into cryptocurrency services, pending regulatory clarity. The bank has already developed digital asset infrastructure but awaits clearer legal frameworks before full engagement.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Innovation in the stablecoin sector continues to drive growth. New products like Ethena&#8217;s USDe token, which employs a strategy of shorting Bitcoin and Ether, have gained traction among investors seeking yield-generating opportunities in the digital asset space.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Looking ahead, asset manager Bitwise projects the stablecoin market could reach $400 billion by 2025. This forecast assumes favorable regulatory developments in the United States, which could catalyze increased adoption by businesses and consumers.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">PayPal&#8217;s introduction of PYUSD has set a precedent for fintech companies integrating stablecoins into their services. This trend is expected to continue as more companies recognize the potential of stablecoins for global payments and cross-border transactions.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Research from Standard Chartered and Zodia Markets suggests stablecoins could eventually comprise 10% of U.S. money supply and foreign exchange transactions, a substantial increase from the current 1% share.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The growth in stablecoin adoption reflects broader changes in global payment systems. Businesses increasingly view stablecoins as a practical solution for international transactions, offering faster settlement times and reduced costs compared to traditional banking channels.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Market data shows that daily transaction volumes for stablecoins have consistently increased throughout 2024. This trend indicates growing comfort with digital assets among both retail and institutional users.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The expansion of stablecoin use cases has attracted attention from payment processors and financial service providers. These entities are developing infrastructure to support stablecoin transactions, contributing to the ecosystem&#8217;s growth.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Recent partnerships between stablecoin issuers and traditional financial institutions have created new pathways for mainstream adoption. These collaborations focus on integrating stablecoins into existing payment networks and banking systems.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The market&#8217;s growth has been particularly notable in emerging economies, where stablecoins offer an alternative to volatile local currencies and limited banking services.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/stablecoin-market-analysis-from-190b-to-200b-in-two-weeks/">Stablecoin Market Analysis: From $190B to $200B in Two Weeks</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">108023</post-id>	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
