<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	
	xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
	xmlns:geo="http://www.w3.org/2003/01/geo/wgs84_pos#"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Latest Cryptocurrency Price News, Predictions &amp; Updates from Blockonomi</title>
	<atom:link href="https://blockonomi.com/analysis/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://blockonomi.com/analysis/</link>
	<description>Cryptocurrency News &#38; Your Guide to the Blockchain Economy</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 11:14:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.7.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/fav-50x50.png</url>
	<title>Latest Cryptocurrency Price News, Predictions &amp; Updates from Blockonomi</title>
	<link>https://blockonomi.com/analysis/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
<site xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">134176212</site>	<item>
		<title>POPCAT ($POP) Price: Shows Rising Momentum as Bulls Defend Critical $1 Level</title>
		<link>https://blockonomi.com/popcat-pop-price-shows-rising-momentum-as-bulls-defend-critical-1-level/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Oliver Dale]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 11:14:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blockonomi.com/?p=108032</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>TLDR POPCAT has found strong buyer support at the $1 level, showing resilience after a recent pullback The 4-hour RSI indicates increasing buyer momentum as it moves out of oversold territory toward 50% 1-day RSI shows selling pressure decreasing with a reversal trend from 40% level Key resistance levels to watch are the 100-day SMA [...]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/popcat-pop-price-shows-rising-momentum-as-bulls-defend-critical-1-level/">POPCAT ($POP) Price: Shows Rising Momentum as Bulls Defend Critical $1 Level</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>TLDR</h2>
<ul>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">POPCAT has found strong buyer support at the $1 level, showing resilience after a recent pullback</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">The 4-hour RSI indicates increasing buyer momentum as it moves out of oversold territory toward 50%</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">1-day RSI shows selling pressure decreasing with a reversal trend from 40% level</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Key resistance levels to watch are the 100-day SMA and $1.50 mark</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Current trading price is $1.20 with next support at $0.80 if bullish momentum fades</li>
</ul>
<hr />
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words"><a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/popcat-holds-firm-at-1-support/">POPCAT&#8217;s price has established firm support at the $1 level, marking a potential turning point for the token after its recent market pullback.</a> Trading data from the past 24 hours shows increased buying activity as the price stabilizes and begins showing signs of upward momentum.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The digital asset, currently trading at $1.20, has attracted renewed buyer interest after testing the crucial dollar support level. Market data indicates a steady increase in trading volume, with buyers stepping in to defend the price floor established at $1.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Technical analysis of the 4-hour chart reveals improving market conditions for POPCAT. The Relative Strength Index (RSI), a key momentum indicator, has moved out of oversold territory and is approaching the 50% level. This movement suggests growing buyer confidence and could signal the start of a new upward trend.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Looking at the daily timeframe, the RSI shows a notable reversal from the 40% level, indicating that selling pressure may be easing. This technical indicator&#8217;s recovery provides additional evidence that market sentiment could be shifting in favor of buyers.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The token&#8217;s price action around the $1 support level has caught the attention of traders and market participants. Data from multiple exchanges shows increasing bid orders near this price point, suggesting strong buyer interest in accumulating POPCAT at current levels.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Trading volumes have seen an uptick during this period of price stabilization. Exchange data reveals a 24-hour trading volume of over $10 million, showing active market participation as traders position themselves for potential future price movements.</p>
<figure id="attachment_108034" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-108034" style="width: 847px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-108034" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-12-at-11-13-05-Popcat-Price-POPCAT-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko.png" alt="Popcat Price on CoinGecko" width="847" height="631" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-12-at-11-13-05-Popcat-Price-POPCAT-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko.png 847w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-12-at-11-13-05-Popcat-Price-POPCAT-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko-300x223.png 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-12-at-11-13-05-Popcat-Price-POPCAT-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko-768x572.png 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-12-at-11-13-05-Popcat-Price-POPCAT-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko-50x37.png 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-12-at-11-13-05-Popcat-Price-POPCAT-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko-150x112.png 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-12-at-11-13-05-Popcat-Price-POPCAT-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko-450x335.png 450w" sizes="(max-width: 847px) 100vw, 847px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-108034" class="wp-caption-text">Popcat Price on <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/popcat">CoinGecko</a></figcaption></figure>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The current market structure shows several resistance levels that POPCAT needs to overcome for continued upward movement. The first major hurdle lies at the 100-day Simple Moving Average, which has historically served as a key technical reference point for the token&#8217;s price action.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Beyond the moving average, the $1.50 price level represents the next major resistance zone. This level previously acted as support during earlier trading periods and now serves as a target for bulls looking to push the price higher.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Market order books show concentrated seller interest around these resistance levels. However, the gradual accumulation of buy orders at current prices suggests traders are preparing for potential upward price movements.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The token&#8217;s price behavior has maintained a pattern of higher lows since finding support, indicating growing buyer conviction. This technical pattern often precedes larger price moves, though market conditions can change rapidly.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">If POPCAT fails to maintain its current price levels, the next support zone lies at $0.80. This level aligns with previous trading ranges and could serve as a secondary support if market sentiment weakens.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Short-term price action shows consolidation above the $1 mark, with decreasing volatility as the market establishes a new base. Trading ranges have tightened in recent hours, often a predecessor to larger price movements.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Exchange data reveals an increase in wallet addresses holding POPCAT, suggesting growing distributed ownership of the token. This metric often indicates longer-term holder conviction, though it doesn&#8217;t guarantee future price appreciation.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Recent trading patterns show declining sell-side pressure compared to previous weeks. Order flow data indicates more balanced trading activity, with buy and sell orders reaching closer to equilibrium.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The most recent market data shows POPCAT trading at $1.20, maintaining its position above the crucial $1 support level as traders watch for further signs of price direction.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/popcat-pop-price-shows-rising-momentum-as-bulls-defend-critical-1-level/">POPCAT ($POP) Price: Shows Rising Momentum as Bulls Defend Critical $1 Level</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">108032</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>VeChain (VET) Price Analysis: Network Upgrade Drives 12% Daily Gain</title>
		<link>https://blockonomi.com/vechain-vet-price-analysis-network-upgrade-drives-12-daily-gain/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Oliver Dale]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 11:10:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blockonomi.com/?p=108027</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>TLDR VeChain (VET) experienced a 12% surge in price, marking a 120% increase over 30 days The project announced a &#8220;VeChain Renaissance&#8221; plan focused on mass adoption preparation Current trading price is at $0.0585, with CoinCodex predicting $0.057 by end of 2024 Projections show VET reaching $0.063 by February 2025 and potentially $0.14 by May [...]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/vechain-vet-price-analysis-network-upgrade-drives-12-daily-gain/">VeChain (VET) Price Analysis: Network Upgrade Drives 12% Daily Gain</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>TLDR</h2>
<ul>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">VeChain (VET) experienced a 12% surge in price, marking a 120% increase over 30 days</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">The project announced a &#8220;VeChain Renaissance&#8221; plan focused on mass adoption preparation</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Current trading price is at $0.0585, with CoinCodex predicting $0.057 by end of 2024</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Projections show VET reaching $0.063 by February 2025 and potentially $0.14 by May</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">The cryptocurrency aims to challenge its previous all-time high of $0.28</li>
</ul>
<hr />
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The cryptocurrency <a href="https://watcher.guru/news/vechain-surges-12-how-high-will-vet-end-2024">VeChain (VET) has demonstrated remarkable price action in recent weeks, recording a 12% increase in the latest trading session.</a> This surge adds to an impressive 120% gain over the past 30 days, bringing its current trading value to $0.0585.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The project&#8217;s recent announcement of a &#8220;VeChain Renaissance&#8221; initiative has sparked renewed interest among investors. This strategic plan focuses on preparing the network&#8217;s infrastructure for anticipated widespread adoption, suggesting confidence in future blockchain technology usage.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Market data indicates VET&#8217;s strong performance comes during a period of broader cryptocurrency market growth. Bitcoin&#8217;s recent achievement of reaching six figures has created positive sentiment throughout the entire crypto sector, benefiting alternative cryptocurrencies like VeChain.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Trading volume for VET has shown consistent growth, indicating increased investor participation. The token&#8217;s market performance has attracted attention from both retail and institutional investors, contributing to its price appreciation.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Current market analysis from CoinCodex suggests VET will maintain stability near its present levels through the remainder of 2024, with an end-of-year target of $0.057. This projection represents a slight consolidation from current prices.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Looking ahead to 2025, price forecasts become increasingly optimistic. Analysts project VET to reach $0.063 by February, marking the beginning of what could be a substantial upward trend.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The progression continues into spring, with predictions indicating VET could surpass the $0.1 threshold by April 2025. This would represent nearly double the current trading price.</p>
<figure id="attachment_108028" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-108028" style="width: 847px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-108028" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-12-at-10-55-36-VeChain-Price-VET-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko.png" alt="VeChain Price on CoinGecko" width="847" height="628" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-12-at-10-55-36-VeChain-Price-VET-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko.png 847w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-12-at-10-55-36-VeChain-Price-VET-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko-300x222.png 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-12-at-10-55-36-VeChain-Price-VET-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko-768x569.png 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-12-at-10-55-36-VeChain-Price-VET-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko-50x37.png 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-12-at-10-55-36-VeChain-Price-VET-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko-150x111.png 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-12-at-10-55-36-VeChain-Price-VET-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko-450x334.png 450w" sizes="(max-width: 847px) 100vw, 847px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-108028" class="wp-caption-text">VeChain Price on <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/vechain">CoinGecko</a></figcaption></figure>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">May 2025 emerges as a potentially crucial month for VET holders, with projections suggesting a price surge to $0.14. This would translate to a 280% increase from current levels, should these predictions materialize.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Historical context adds perspective to these projections. VET&#8217;s previous all-time high stands at $0.28, setting a benchmark for potential future price action.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The &#8220;VeChain Renaissance&#8221; initiative demonstrates the project&#8217;s focus on technological advancement. This development plan aims to enhance network capabilities in preparation for increased adoption.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Market observers note that VET&#8217;s price movement aligns with broader cryptocurrency market trends. The approval and launch of crypto-based ETFs has generated renewed interest in digital assets across the board.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Trading patterns show VET maintaining steady support levels during its recent price increases. This suggests the possibility of sustained upward momentum rather than speculative short-term gains.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Technical indicators reveal strong buying pressure in recent weeks. The combination of increased trading volume and price appreciation points to growing market confidence in VET.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Market participants are closely monitoring VET&#8217;s price action for signs of continuation or reversal. The token&#8217;s ability to maintain current price levels could indicate future growth potential.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Recent developments in the broader blockchain industry have created favorable conditions for projects like VeChain. The increasing acceptance of cryptocurrency technology continues to provide opportunities for growth across the sector.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/vechain-vet-price-analysis-network-upgrade-drives-12-daily-gain/">VeChain (VET) Price Analysis: Network Upgrade Drives 12% Daily Gain</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">108027</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Stablecoin Market Analysis: From $190B to $200B in Two Weeks</title>
		<link>https://blockonomi.com/stablecoin-market-analysis-from-190b-to-200b-in-two-weeks/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Oliver Dale]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 10:44:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blockonomi.com/?p=108023</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>TLDR Stablecoin market has reached a historic $200 billion total market cap, with Tether (USDT) leading at $139 billion and USDC following at $41 billion Growth driven by increased crypto trading activity and expanding use cases in payments, remittances, and savings, particularly in regions with unstable financial systems Abu Dhabi Global Market&#8217;s Financial Services Regulatory [...]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/stablecoin-market-analysis-from-190b-to-200b-in-two-weeks/">Stablecoin Market Analysis: From $190B to $200B in Two Weeks</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>TLDR</h2>
<ul>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Stablecoin market has reached a historic $200 billion total market cap, with Tether (USDT) leading at $139 billion and USDC following at $41 billion</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Growth driven by increased crypto trading activity and expanding use cases in payments, remittances, and savings, particularly in regions with unstable financial systems</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Abu Dhabi Global Market&#8217;s Financial Services Regulatory Authority has recognized USDT as an Accepted Virtual Asset, boosting institutional adoption</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Market experts, including Bitwise, project potential growth to $400 billion by 2025, contingent on favorable U.S. regulatory developments</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Traditional financial institutions like Goldman Sachs are poised to enter the market once regulatory clarity improves</li>
</ul>
<hr />
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words"><a href="https://coingape.com/stablecoin-market-hits-record-200b-milestone-400b-by-2025/">The stablecoin market has crossed a historic threshold, reaching $200 billion in total market capitalization.</a> Data from CCData and DefiLlama reveals this achievement came after adding $10 billion in just two weeks, surpassing the previous peak of $190 billion seen during the 2022 crypto rally.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">At the forefront of this growth stands Tether (USDT), which has achieved a record market value of $139 billion. This represents a 12% increase in a single month, <a href="https://defillama.com/stablecoins">according to DefiLlama&#8217;s latest data</a>. The stablecoin&#8217;s widespread adoption is evident in its user base, with over 109 million on-chain wallets holding USDT by Q4 2024.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Circle&#8217;s USD Coin (USDC) maintains its position as the second-largest stablecoin, reaching nearly $41 billion in market value. This represents a 5% growth during the same period, highlighting the continued expansion of major stablecoin platforms.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The surge in stablecoin usage extends beyond traditional crypto trading. These digital assets have found increasing utility in everyday financial transactions, particularly in regions experiencing economic instability or high inflation rates. Users are turning to stablecoins for remittances, payments, and as a store of value.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Recent developments in the Middle East have further legitimized stablecoin usage. The Abu Dhabi Global Market&#8217;s Financial Services Regulatory Authority has officially recognized USDT as an Accepted Virtual Asset. This designation enables licensed entities to offer USDT-related services, supporting the UAE&#8217;s ambition to become a global digital finance hub.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The market&#8217;s expansion has caught the attention of traditional financial institutions. Goldman Sachs CEO David Solomon has indicated the firm&#8217;s readiness to expand into cryptocurrency services, pending regulatory clarity. The bank has already developed digital asset infrastructure but awaits clearer legal frameworks before full engagement.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Innovation in the stablecoin sector continues to drive growth. New products like Ethena&#8217;s USDe token, which employs a strategy of shorting Bitcoin and Ether, have gained traction among investors seeking yield-generating opportunities in the digital asset space.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Looking ahead, asset manager Bitwise projects the stablecoin market could reach $400 billion by 2025. This forecast assumes favorable regulatory developments in the United States, which could catalyze increased adoption by businesses and consumers.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">PayPal&#8217;s introduction of PYUSD has set a precedent for fintech companies integrating stablecoins into their services. This trend is expected to continue as more companies recognize the potential of stablecoins for global payments and cross-border transactions.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Research from Standard Chartered and Zodia Markets suggests stablecoins could eventually comprise 10% of U.S. money supply and foreign exchange transactions, a substantial increase from the current 1% share.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The growth in stablecoin adoption reflects broader changes in global payment systems. Businesses increasingly view stablecoins as a practical solution for international transactions, offering faster settlement times and reduced costs compared to traditional banking channels.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Market data shows that daily transaction volumes for stablecoins have consistently increased throughout 2024. This trend indicates growing comfort with digital assets among both retail and institutional users.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The expansion of stablecoin use cases has attracted attention from payment processors and financial service providers. These entities are developing infrastructure to support stablecoin transactions, contributing to the ecosystem&#8217;s growth.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Recent partnerships between stablecoin issuers and traditional financial institutions have created new pathways for mainstream adoption. These collaborations focus on integrating stablecoins into existing payment networks and banking systems.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The market&#8217;s growth has been particularly notable in emerging economies, where stablecoins offer an alternative to volatile local currencies and limited banking services.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/stablecoin-market-analysis-from-190b-to-200b-in-two-weeks/">Stablecoin Market Analysis: From $190B to $200B in Two Weeks</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">108023</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance Coin (BNB) Price: Surpasses $700 Amid Increased Trading Volume</title>
		<link>https://blockonomi.com/binance-coin-bnb-price-surpasses-700-amid-increased-trading-volume/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Oliver Dale]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 10:11:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blockonomi.com/?p=107994</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>TLDR BNB price has broken above $700 and shown strong upward momentum Technical analysis indicates a break above a key bearish trend line at $705 Next major resistance levels are at $735 and $750 Strong support established at $700 and $675 levels If price maintains above $700, analysts expect potential push toward $750-$800 range The [...]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/binance-coin-bnb-price-surpasses-700-amid-increased-trading-volume/">Binance Coin (BNB) Price: Surpasses $700 Amid Increased Trading Volume</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>TLDR</h2>
<ul>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">BNB price has broken above $700 and shown strong upward momentum</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Technical analysis indicates a break above a key bearish trend line at $705</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Next major resistance levels are at $735 and $750</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Strong support established at $700 and $675 levels</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">If price maintains above $700, analysts expect potential push toward $750-$800 range</li>
</ul>
<hr />
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The cryptocurrency market has witnessed a notable price movement as BNB, the native token of the <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/bnb/bnb-bulls-eye-750/">Binance ecosystem, broke above the $700 price level.</a> The upward movement comes after establishing strong support near the $650 zone, with technical indicators suggesting potential for further gains.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Market data shows that BNB initiated its latest upward movement after successfully holding above the crucial $675 support level. The price action demonstrated steady buying pressure, leading to a breakthrough above several key resistance levels, including the psychologically important $700 mark.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Technical analysis of the hourly chart reveals a break above a bearish trend line that had previously acted as resistance at $705. This technical development has caught the attention of traders and analysts, as it represents a shift in short-term market structure.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The price movement has taken <a href="https://moneycheck.com/best-bnb-casinos/">BNB</a> above the 100-hourly simple moving average, a technical indicator often used to gauge market momentum. This positioning above key moving averages suggests that buyers have gained control of the immediate price action.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Data from trading charts indicates that BNB has surpassed the 50% Fibonacci retracement level, measured from the recent swing high of $761 to the low of $650. This technical achievement adds weight to the bullish case, as Fibonacci levels often serve as important reference points for traders.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Trading volume analysis shows increased participation during the upward move, lending credibility to the price action. The volume surge coincides with the break above key resistance levels, suggesting genuine buying interest rather than a technical bounce.</p>
<figure id="attachment_107995" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-107995" style="width: 847px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-107995" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-12-at-09-55-41-BNB-Price-BNB-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko.png" alt="BNB Price on CoinGecko" width="847" height="631" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-12-at-09-55-41-BNB-Price-BNB-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko.png 847w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-12-at-09-55-41-BNB-Price-BNB-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko-300x223.png 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-12-at-09-55-41-BNB-Price-BNB-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko-768x572.png 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-12-at-09-55-41-BNB-Price-BNB-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko-50x37.png 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-12-at-09-55-41-BNB-Price-BNB-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko-150x112.png 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-12-at-09-55-41-BNB-Price-BNB-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko-450x335.png 450w" sizes="(max-width: 847px) 100vw, 847px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-107995" class="wp-caption-text">BNB Price on <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/bnb">CoinGecko</a></figcaption></figure>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The immediate price structure shows the formation of higher lows and higher highs, a pattern typically associated with bullish market conditions. This pattern development has occurred alongside the break above the bearish trend line, reinforcing the potential for continued upward movement.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Looking at key resistance levels, traders are closely watching the $720 area, which coincides with the 61.8% Fibonacci retracement level. This price point may present the next challenge for bulls attempting to push the price higher.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The $735 level represents another crucial resistance zone that market participants are monitoring. A clear break above this level could open the path toward the $750 price target, according to technical analysis of the current market structure.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Support levels have been established during this move, with the $705 area now serving as immediate support. The psychological $700 level adds another layer of support, with buyers showing interest at this round number.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The market structure suggests that the $675 level has transformed into a strong support zone. This price point previously acted as resistance before the latest move higher, demonstrating the market principle of resistance turning into support.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The hourly Relative Strength Index (RSI) remains above the 50 level, indicating that momentum favors the buyers in the current market context. This technical indicator helps traders gauge the strength of price movements and potential reversal points.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Trading data shows that if the price maintains above the $700 support zone, the possibility of testing higher levels remains intact. The next major targets include the $735 and $750 resistance levels, based on current chart patterns.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">In the event of a pullback, multiple support levels have been established. The $705 and $700 levels provide immediate support, while the $675 zone represents a more substantial support area based on recent price action.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Market participants note that a move below $675 could trigger a deeper correction toward the $662 level. However, the overall market structure remains constructive as long as the price holds above the $650 support zone.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The most recent price data shows BNB trading above the $700 level, with increased trading volume supporting the move higher. The price continues to show strength above key moving averages and technical support levels.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/binance-coin-bnb-price-surpasses-700-amid-increased-trading-volume/">Binance Coin (BNB) Price: Surpasses $700 Amid Increased Trading Volume</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">107994</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Solana (SOL) Price to $500? Network Records $32.46B Weekly Trading Volume</title>
		<link>https://blockonomi.com/solana-sol-price-to-500-network-records-32-46b-weekly-trading-volume/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Oliver Dale]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 10:11:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blockonomi.com/?p=107996</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>TLDR Solana (SOL) showed resilience during a recent crypto market crash, defending the $200 support level despite a 15% drop Bull traders have deployed $237 million in leveraged long positions, outpacing short positions by 26% SOL tokens on exchanges decreased by 13% in seven days to 282.24 million, with a 65% staking ratio Solana network [...]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/solana-sol-price-to-500-network-records-32-46b-weekly-trading-volume/">Solana (SOL) Price to $500? Network Records $32.46B Weekly Trading Volume</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>TLDR</h2>
<ul>
<li>Solana (SOL) showed resilience during a recent crypto market crash, defending the $200 support level despite a 15% drop</li>
<li>Bull traders have deployed $237 million in leveraged long positions, outpacing short positions by 26%</li>
<li>SOL tokens on exchanges decreased by 13% in seven days to 282.24 million, with a 65% staking ratio</li>
<li>Solana network handled $32.46 billion in trading volume over the past week, surpassing Ethereum&#8217;s $25 billion</li>
<li>Technical analysis suggests potential for upward movement, with price targets ranging from $230 to $500</li>
</ul>
<hr />
<p>Solana (SOL) has maintained its position above the crucial $200 support level despite recent market turbulence that triggered $1.5 billion in crypto liquidations. The digital asset opened trading at $213 on December 11, following a 15% decline during Monday&#8217;s market downturn.</p>
<p>The cryptocurrency has shown remarkable recovery strength, rebounding 8.23% within twelve hours and reaching $220 in the early hours of December 11. This recovery comes as traders actively defend the $200 price level, demonstrating strong market confidence in the asset.</p>
<figure id="attachment_107997" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-107997" style="width: 858px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-107997" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/sol-price.png" alt=" SolanaSOL Price" width="858" height="658" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/sol-price.png 858w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/sol-price-300x230.png 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/sol-price-768x589.png 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/sol-price-50x38.png 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/sol-price-150x115.png 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/sol-price-450x345.png 450w" sizes="(max-width: 858px) 100vw, 858px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-107997" class="wp-caption-text">Solana<br /><a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/solana">SOL Price</a></figcaption></figure>
<p>Data from derivatives trading reveals that investors are predominantly holding their positions rather than exiting under current market conditions. Bull traders have deployed an impressive $237 million in leveraged long positions, surpassing short positions by 26%, suggesting growing optimism about SOL&#8217;s price trajectory.</p>
<p>On-chain metrics paint an interesting picture of supply dynamics. Exchange data indicates a 13% reduction in SOL tokens held on trading platforms over the past week, bringing the total to 282.24 million. This decline suggests that investors are increasingly moving their holdings to self-custody wallets or participating in staking activities.</p>
<p>The staking landscape for Solana has become particularly compelling, with the network maintaining a 65% staking ratio. This figure surpasses several major competitors, including Ethereum, Polkadot, and Cosmos, indicating strong long-term holder conviction.</p>
<p>Trading volume<a href="https://moneycheck.com/best-solana-casinos/"> on the Solana network</a> has reached remarkable levels, processing $32.46 billion in transactions over a seven-day period. This volume surpassed Ethereum&#8217;s $25 billion, highlighting Solana&#8217;s growing role in the decentralized finance ecosystem.</p>
<p>Technical indicators suggest potential upward movement for SOL price. The Relative Strength Index shows an upward reversal after approaching oversold conditions, while the Donchian Channels indicator identifies $233 as a key resistance level to watch.</p>
<p>The Volume Delta indicator has turned positive, suggesting that the current recovery is supported by genuine market demand and improving liquidity conditions. A successful close above the $233 resistance could pave the way for further price appreciation.</p>
<p>Network usage metrics reinforce Solana&#8217;s market position, with the platform collecting over $672 million in fees during the current year. This revenue generation demonstrates sustained network activity and user engagement.</p>
<p>Market analysts have identified several technical patterns that could influence future price action. A bullish flag pattern has formed on the daily chart, typically considered a continuation pattern in upward trends.</p>
<p>The weekly chart displays a cup-and-handle formation with a 97% depth, suggesting potential for extended upward movement. Some analysts project that this pattern could support price movement toward the $500 range, though such projections remain speculative.</p>
<p>Support levels have been established at $203 and $180, providing potential cushioning against downward pressure. However, the current positioning of leveraged trades suggests limited likelihood of a dramatic breakdown under present market conditions.</p>
<p>The cryptocurrency&#8217;s price action has included a break-and-retest pattern at the $210 level, which previously served as resistance in March. Such retests often precede continuation of the primary trend when successfully defended.</p>
<p>Network developments continue to support Solana&#8217;s market position, with increasing adoption in gaming and decentralized infrastructure projects. These fundamental developments provide additional context for the market&#8217;s resilient price action.</p>
<p>Trading volumes and market depth remain robust, indicating healthy market participation despite recent volatility. The distribution of trades across various price levels suggests balanced market interest.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/solana-sol-price-to-500-network-records-32-46b-weekly-trading-volume/">Solana (SOL) Price to $500? Network Records $32.46B Weekly Trading Volume</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">107996</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ethereum (ETH) Price: Approaches $4,000 as Van de Poppe Projects Higher Targets</title>
		<link>https://blockonomi.com/ethereum-eth-price-approaches-4000-as-van-de-poppe-projects-higher-targets/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Oliver Dale]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 09:31:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blockonomi.com/?p=107989</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>TLDR ETH currently trading at $3,929.46 with a 7.39% daily increase and 2.17% weekly gain Van de Poppe predicts bull run to continue into 2025 if ETH breaks $3,800 resistance Strong support at $3,715 according to IOMAP metrics suggests buyer confidence Key resistance levels between $3,830-$4,274 with potential targets of $4,096 and $4,500 Critical support [...]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/ethereum-eth-price-approaches-4000-as-van-de-poppe-projects-higher-targets/">Ethereum (ETH) Price: Approaches $4,000 as Van de Poppe Projects Higher Targets</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>TLDR</h2>
<ul>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">ETH currently trading at $3,929.46 with a 7.39% daily increase and 2.17% weekly gain</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Van de Poppe predicts bull run to continue into 2025 if ETH breaks $3,800 resistance</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Strong support at $3,715 according to IOMAP metrics suggests buyer confidence</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Key resistance levels between $3,830-$4,274 with potential targets of $4,096 and $4,500</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Critical support level at $3,505 must hold to maintain bullish outlook</li>
</ul>
<hr />
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Ethereum&#8217;s price momentum continues to build as the leading smart contract platform approaches the psychologically important $4,000 level. <a href="https://www.crypto-news-flash.com/ethereum-news-eth-bull-run-to-resume-and-last-into-2025-michael-van-de-poppe-says/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=ethereum-news-eth-bull-run-to-resume-and-last-into-2025-michael-van-de-poppe-says">Trading data shows ETH has gained over 7% in the past 24 hours, reaching $3,929.46 as buyers step in at crucial support levels.</a></p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The recent price action has caught the attention of veteran crypto analyst Michael van de Poppe, who sees the current consolidation phase as a healthy pullback within a larger upward trend. According to van de Poppe, ETH&#8217;s ability to maintain support above $3,715 signals strong buyer interest at current levels.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Technical indicators paint an optimistic picture for Ethereum&#8217;s near-term prospects. The In/Out of Money Around Price (IOMAP) metric reveals substantial buying activity clustering around the $3,715 price point, suggesting this level could serve as a springboard for future moves higher.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Market data shows ETH has posted impressive gains over multiple timeframes, with a 7.39% increase over the past day and 2.17% growth over the week. This steady appreciation comes despite some resistance encountered near the $4,000 mark.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr"><a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24ETH&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">$ETH</a> actually provides an excellent opportunity to accumulate. </p>
<p>Standard correction after testing a new resistance area. </p>
<p>I expect we&#39;ll continue to run from later this month into the new year. <a href="https://t.co/zFSwvtFvDH">pic.twitter.com/zFSwvtFvDH</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Michaël van de Poppe (@CryptoMichNL) <a href="https://twitter.com/CryptoMichNL/status/1866774172468236351?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">December 11, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Trading volume patterns indicate growing institutional interest in Ethereum. Professional traders appear to be using the recent consolidation phase as an opportunity to accumulate ETH at what they consider attractive price levels below $4,000.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Van de Poppe identifies several key price zones that could determine ETH&#8217;s trajectory in the coming months. The immediate resistance band lies between $3,830 and $4,274, with potential targets at $4,096 and $4,500 if these levels are breached decisively.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The current market structure suggests a continuation of the upward trend, provided<a href="https://moneycheck.com/best-ethereum-casinos/"> ETH</a> maintains support above $3,505. This level represents a crucial floor that bulls must defend to preserve the positive momentum.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Recent price action shows ETH finding steady support during dips, indicating healthy market dynamics. Buyers have consistently stepped in to absorb selling pressure, preventing any sustained moves below key support levels.</p>
<figure id="attachment_107990" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-107990" style="width: 847px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-107990" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-12-at-09-27-43-Ethereum-Price-ETH-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko.png" alt="Ethereum Price on CoinGecko" width="847" height="628" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-12-at-09-27-43-Ethereum-Price-ETH-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko.png 847w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-12-at-09-27-43-Ethereum-Price-ETH-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko-300x222.png 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-12-at-09-27-43-Ethereum-Price-ETH-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko-768x569.png 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-12-at-09-27-43-Ethereum-Price-ETH-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko-50x37.png 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-12-at-09-27-43-Ethereum-Price-ETH-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko-150x111.png 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-12-at-09-27-43-Ethereum-Price-ETH-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko-450x334.png 450w" sizes="(max-width: 847px) 100vw, 847px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-107990" class="wp-caption-text">Ethereum Price on <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/ethereum">CoinGecko</a></figcaption></figure>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Looking at broader market indicators, Ethereum&#8217;s network metrics continue to show robust activity. Transaction volumes and active addresses remain elevated, supporting the case for sustained price appreciation.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Van de Poppe&#8217;s analysis suggests the current consolidation phase could set up ETH for an extended bull run lasting into 2025. This projection assumes the cryptocurrency can successfully break above the $3,800 resistance zone.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The analyst notes that while temporary pullbacks are normal within bull markets, the overall trend remains positive as long as ETH holds above $3,505. A break below this level could trigger a retreat toward $3,182.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Market participants appear to be positioning for further upside, with derivatives data showing increasing long positions at current price levels. This accumulation pattern often precedes sustained price moves higher.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Recent trading sessions have seen ETH repeatedly testing the $3,800 resistance level, suggesting building pressure for a potential breakout. The repeated tests of this level without sharp rejections indicate growing buyer confidence.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Order book data reveals strong bid support has formed in the $3,700-$3,800 range, providing a cushion against potential downside moves. This price floor appears well-defended by buyers looking to accumulate positions.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The most recent price data shows ETH trading at $3,929.46, maintaining its position above key moving averages and technical support levels as market participants await a potential break above $4,000.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/ethereum-eth-price-approaches-4000-as-van-de-poppe-projects-higher-targets/">Ethereum (ETH) Price: Approaches $4,000 as Van de Poppe Projects Higher Targets</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">107989</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin (BTC) Price: Whale Accumulation Surges with 342 New Large Wallets Created</title>
		<link>https://blockonomi.com/bitcoin-btc-price-whale-accumulation-surges-with-342-new-large-wallets-created/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Oliver Dale]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 09:23:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blockonomi.com/?p=107986</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>TLDR Bitcoin recovered from a $94,500 dip and surged past $100,000 after US CPI data aligned with market expectations, with analysts predicting potential rises to $275,000 based on cup and handle pattern analysis Heavy whale accumulation occurred during consolidation, with 342 new wallets holding over 100 BTC created during the recent price drop from $104,000 [...]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/bitcoin-btc-price-whale-accumulation-surges-with-342-new-large-wallets-created/">Bitcoin (BTC) Price: Whale Accumulation Surges with 342 New Large Wallets Created</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>TLDR</h2>
<ul>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Bitcoin recovered from a $94,500 dip and surged past $100,000 after US CPI data aligned with market expectations, with analysts predicting potential rises to $275,000 based on cup and handle pattern analysis</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Heavy whale accumulation occurred during consolidation, with 342 new wallets holding over 100 BTC created during the recent price drop from $104,000 to $90,000</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Spot Bitcoin ETF inflows remain strong, with BlackRock&#8217;s IBIT reaching over $35 billion in net inflows since launch</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Analysts predict a 96-97% chance of a 25 basis point rate cut at next week&#8217;s FOMC meeting, potentially catalyzing further price movement</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Technical analysis suggests Bitcoin broke out of its $94,500-$98,000 trading range, with altcoins showing stronger relative performance</li>
</ul>
<hr />
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words"><a href="https://coingape.com/will-bitcoin-price-hit-new-all-time-high-heading-into-fomc/">Bitcoin has pushed past the $100,000 mark, recovering swiftly from yesterday&#8217;s dip to $94,500.</a> The rebound comes as new data reveals substantial whale accumulation and continued strong inflows into spot Bitcoin ETFs, painting a picture of robust institutional and high-net-worth investor interest.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The latest market movements follow the release of US Consumer Price Index (CPI) data, which aligned with market expectations. This development has strengthened predictions of a potential Federal Reserve rate cut at next week&#8217;s Federal Open Market Committee (FOMC) meeting, with analysts estimating a 96-97% probability of a 25 basis point reduction.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">During the recent consolidation period around $96,000, large investors demonstrated strong buying activity. Data from blockchain analytics reveals that 342 new wallets holding more than 100 BTC were created as Bitcoin&#8217;s price fluctuated between $104,000 and $90,000, indicating substantial accumulation by wealthy investors during the price dip.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The institutional adoption of Bitcoin continues to expand through spot ETF products. BlackRock&#8217;s IBIT has reached a new milestone, exceeding $35 billion in net inflows since its launch. The ETF sector has maintained positive inflows for nine consecutive trading sessions, highlighting sustained institutional interest in the asset class.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Technical analysis from crypto analyst Ali Martinez identifies a cup and handle pattern forming on Bitcoin&#8217;s weekly chart. This traditional bullish formation suggests a potential price target of $275,000, though Martinez advises traders to maintain caution and avoid excessive leverage.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Buy the dip, and don&#39;t overleverage! <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Bitcoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Bitcoin</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24BTC&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">$BTC</a> will reach $275,000, based on this cup and handle pattern! <a href="https://t.co/cqf99cBtmB">pic.twitter.com/cqf99cBtmB</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Ali (@ali_charts) <a href="https://twitter.com/ali_charts/status/1866517510268330035?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">December 10, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Market data from Coinglass shows over $478 million worth of contracts were liquidated in the past 24 hours during the recent price volatility. Interestingly, altcoin positions experienced higher liquidation volumes compared to Bitcoin positions, suggesting more stable holding patterns for BTC.</p>
<figure id="attachment_107987" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-107987" style="width: 847px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-107987" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-12-at-09-19-34-Bitcoin-Price-BTC-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko.png" alt="Bitcoin Price on CoinGecko" width="847" height="623" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-12-at-09-19-34-Bitcoin-Price-BTC-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko.png 847w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-12-at-09-19-34-Bitcoin-Price-BTC-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko-300x221.png 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-12-at-09-19-34-Bitcoin-Price-BTC-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko-768x565.png 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-12-at-09-19-34-Bitcoin-Price-BTC-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko-50x37.png 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-12-at-09-19-34-Bitcoin-Price-BTC-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko-150x110.png 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-12-at-09-19-34-Bitcoin-Price-BTC-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko-450x331.png 450w" sizes="(max-width: 847px) 100vw, 847px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-107987" class="wp-caption-text">Bitcoin Price on <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/bitcoin">CoinGecko</a></figcaption></figure>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The cryptocurrency&#8217;s price recovery appears supported by declining exchange reserves, which have reached multi-year lows. This trend typically indicates reduced selling pressure as fewer coins are available for immediate sale on exchanges.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Corporate adoption of <a href="https://moneycheck.com/best-bitcoin-casinos/">Bitcoin</a> continues to expand, with Canadian video-sharing platform Rumble becoming the latest company to announce a Bitcoin treasury strategy. This follows a broader trend of companies exploring cryptocurrency as a treasury asset, despite Microsoft shareholders recently rejecting a proposal to allocate 1% of the company&#8217;s assets to Bitcoin.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Former investment banker Anthony Scaramucci has suggested that China might establish its own Bitcoin reserve if the United States proceeds with strategic Bitcoin reserve plans. Such national adoption could further impact the supply-demand dynamics of the cryptocurrency.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The altcoin market has shown even stronger performance during this recovery period.<a href="https://moneycheck.com/best-ethereum-casinos/"> Ethereum</a> has registered a 7% increase, trading near $3,920, while other major cryptocurrencies like <a href="https://moneycheck.com/best-xrp-casinos/">XRP</a>, <a href="https://moneycheck.com/best-bnb-casinos/">BNB</a>, <a href="https://moneycheck.com/best-solana-casinos/">SOL</a>, and <a href="https://moneycheck.com/best-doge-casinos/">DOGE</a> have posted gains between 4-5%.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Analysis from 10x Research notes that Bitcoin&#8217;s price often rallies after declining ahead of inflation reports, particularly when the data meets market expectations and calms inflation concerns. The firm expects measured market movements through year-end as many investors typically close their positions following the FOMC meeting.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Looking at short-term price action, Bitcoin has broken out of its previous trading range between $94,500 and $98,000. The movement above $100,000 represents a clear break from this consolidation pattern, though traders remain watchful of key support levels around $90,000.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The overall market structure suggests continued strength, with Bitcoin maintaining prices above previous resistance levels. The combination of institutional inflow through ETFs, whale accumulation, and broader market adoption provides multiple support factors for current price levels.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Trading volume has remained robust, with daily volumes consistently supporting price action above $100,000. The market currently shows a healthy balance between spot and derivatives trading, indicating sustainable price discovery.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">At press time, Bitcoin trades at $100,453, representing a 4.1% increase over the past 24 hours.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/bitcoin-btc-price-whale-accumulation-surges-with-342-new-large-wallets-created/">Bitcoin (BTC) Price: Whale Accumulation Surges with 342 New Large Wallets Created</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">107986</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>XRP (XRP) Price: Surges Past $2.25 as Ripple&#8217;s RLUSD Stablecoin Gains Regulatory Approval</title>
		<link>https://blockonomi.com/xrp-xrp-price-surges-past-2-25-as-ripples-rlusd-stablecoin-gains-regulatory-approval/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Oliver Dale]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 09:13:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blockonomi.com/?p=107983</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>TLDR Ripple&#8217;s RLUSD stablecoin received final approval from the New York Department of Financial Services, triggering a 10% surge in XRP price RLUSD currently has a total supply of $52 million split between Ethereum ($41.7M) and XRPL ($10.4M) XRP broke above key resistance at $2.25, showing strong upward momentum and outperforming Bitcoin and Ethereum The [...]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/xrp-xrp-price-surges-past-2-25-as-ripples-rlusd-stablecoin-gains-regulatory-approval/">XRP (XRP) Price: Surges Past $2.25 as Ripple&#8217;s RLUSD Stablecoin Gains Regulatory Approval</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>TLDR</h2>
<ul>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Ripple&#8217;s RLUSD stablecoin received final approval from the New York Department of Financial Services, triggering a 10% surge in XRP price</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">RLUSD currently has a total supply of $52 million split between Ethereum ($41.7M) and XRPL ($10.4M)</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">XRP broke above key resistance at $2.25, showing strong upward momentum and outperforming Bitcoin and Ethereum</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">The stablecoin is backed by short-term U.S. government bonds and will operate on both XRP Ledger and Ethereum networks</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Technical indicators show bullish signals with XRP trading above the 100-hourly Simple Moving Average and MACD gaining momentum</li>
</ul>
<hr />
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The price of <a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/xrp/xrp-price-winning-streak-2-50/">XRP experienced a sharp increase of 10% on Tuesday</a> after Ripple announced it had received regulatory approval for its RLUSD stablecoin from the New York Department of Financial Services. The news propelled XRP&#8217;s value above the $2.25 mark, outpacing broader cryptocurrency market performance.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Ripple CEO Brad Garlinghouse shared the announcement on social media platform X, stating &#8220;This just in&#8230;we have final approval from NYDFS for RLUSD! Exchange and partner listings will be live soon.&#8221; The approval marks a key milestone for Ripple as it enters the competitive stablecoin market.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">This just in…we have final approval from <a href="https://twitter.com/NYDFS?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@NYDFS</a> for <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24RLUSD&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">$RLUSD</a>! Exchange and partner listings will be live soon – and reminder: when RLUSD is live, you’ll hear it from <a href="https://twitter.com/Ripple?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@Ripple</a> first.</p>
<p>&mdash; Brad Garlinghouse (@bgarlinghouse) <a href="https://twitter.com/bgarlinghouse/status/1866571228464460215?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">December 10, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">RLUSD, which is backed by short-term U.S. government bonds, is currently undergoing beta testing on both the XRP Ledger and Ethereum networks. Data from CryptoQuant reveals that the stablecoin already has a supply of $52 million, with $41.7 million on Ethereum and $10.4 million on XRPL.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words"><a href="https://bravenewcoin.com/insights/xrp-surges-as-ripples-stablecoin-secures-regulatory-approval">The stablecoin&#8217;s development aligns with Ripple&#8217;s strategy to expand its presence in the digital asset space.</a> Monica Long, Ripple&#8217;s President, emphasized that RLUSD will play an essential role in real-world asset tokenization, stating, &#8220;We aim to be a key intermediary for bridging traditional financial assets onto blockchain rails.&#8221;</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Technical analysis shows that XRP&#8217;s price movement broke through several resistance levels during the surge. The cryptocurrency moved above the 61.8% Fibonacci retracement level, calculated from the previous swing high of $2.64 to the low of $1.899.</p>
<figure id="attachment_107984" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-107984" style="width: 847px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-107984" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-12-at-09-09-07-XRP-Price-XRP-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko.png" alt="XRP Price on CoinGecko" width="847" height="634" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-12-at-09-09-07-XRP-Price-XRP-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko.png 847w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-12-at-09-09-07-XRP-Price-XRP-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko-300x225.png 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-12-at-09-09-07-XRP-Price-XRP-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko-768x575.png 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-12-at-09-09-07-XRP-Price-XRP-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko-50x37.png 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-12-at-09-09-07-XRP-Price-XRP-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko-150x112.png 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-12-at-09-09-07-XRP-Price-XRP-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko-450x337.png 450w" sizes="(max-width: 847px) 100vw, 847px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-107984" class="wp-caption-text">XRP Price on <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/xrp">CoinGecko</a></figcaption></figure>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Trading indicators suggest continued bullish momentum, with the MACD showing positive movement in the bullish zone. The Relative Strength Index (RSI) remains above the 50 level, indicating healthy buying pressure in the market.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The surge erased earlier losses in XRP&#8217;s value, with the token maintaining strength above key support levels. Trading volumes increased notably during the price movement, suggesting genuine market interest in the development.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Market observers note that RLUSD enters a stablecoin market currently valued at approximately $200 billion. The sector is primarily dominated by established players Tether (USDT) and Circle&#8217;s USDC, but industry projections suggest substantial growth potential.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Ripple&#8217;s approach to launching RLUSD has emphasized regulatory compliance from the start. The company first unveiled its stablecoin plans in April, focusing on institutional adoption and integration with traditional financial systems.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The NYDFS approval opens the door for RLUSD&#8217;s public launch and upcoming exchange listings. The regulatory green light may help attract institutional players seeking regulated blockchain-based payment solutions.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Current market data shows support levels for <a href="https://moneycheck.com/best-xrp-casinos/">XRP</a> near $2.280 and $2.200, with resistance levels identified at $2.4750 and $2.6450. These technical levels may influence short-term price action as the market digests the news.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The price movement coincides with increased trading activity across major cryptocurrency exchanges. Market depth data indicates healthy liquidity for XRP trading pairs, supporting price stability at new levels.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Trading volume distribution shows balanced activity across global markets, with Asian and European sessions showing particular strength. The increased volume suggests broad-based participation in the price rally.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Chart patterns indicate the formation of higher lows, typically considered a bullish market structure. The price maintains position above the 100-hour Simple Moving Average, reinforcing the current upward trend.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Recent price action places XRP&#8217;s next technical resistance at $2.50, with potential for movement toward $2.550 if buying pressure continues. Support has formed around the $2.280 level, providing a foundation for current price levels.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/xrp-xrp-price-surges-past-2-25-as-ripples-rlusd-stablecoin-gains-regulatory-approval/">XRP (XRP) Price: Surges Past $2.25 as Ripple&#8217;s RLUSD Stablecoin Gains Regulatory Approval</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">107983</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Pudgy Penguins NFT Collection Floor Price Hits 27 ETH as $PENGU Token Launch Approaches</title>
		<link>https://blockonomi.com/pudgy-penguins-nft-collection-floor-price-hits-27-eth-as-pengu-token-launch-approaches/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Oliver Dale]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 09:08:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NFTs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blockonomi.com/?p=107977</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>TLDR Pudgy Penguins NFT floor price has reached 27 ETH ($102,600), surpassing Bitcoin&#8217;s price of $101,000 for the first time in its history The project ranks second among NFT collections behind CryptoPunks (39.5 ETH floor price) The upcoming launch of $PENGU token on Solana in 2024 has driven increased interest, with NFT prices rising 194% [...]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/pudgy-penguins-nft-collection-floor-price-hits-27-eth-as-pengu-token-launch-approaches/">Pudgy Penguins NFT Collection Floor Price Hits 27 ETH as $PENGU Token Launch Approaches</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>TLDR</h2>
<ul>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Pudgy Penguins NFT floor price has reached 27 ETH ($102,600), surpassing Bitcoin&#8217;s price of $101,000 for the first time in its history</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">The project ranks second among NFT collections behind CryptoPunks (39.5 ETH floor price)</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">The upcoming launch of $PENGU token on Solana in 2024 has driven increased interest, with NFT prices rising 194% in the past month</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">NFT sales volume peaked at over $180M in early December with over 12,000 active wallets</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">The most expensive Pudgy Penguin is currently listed at 50.3093 ETH ($197,508.78) on OpenSea</li>
</ul>
<hr />
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The popular NFT collection <a href="https://cryptobriefing.com/pudgy-penguins-nfts-surge/">Pudgy Penguins has achieved a remarkable milestone in December 2024,</a> with its floor price surpassing $100,000 and exceeding the price of Bitcoin. The collection&#8217;s minimum entry price reached 27 ETH, equivalent to $102,600, marking a new all-time high for the project.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">This price breakthrough positions <a href="https://crypto.news/pudgypenguin-nft-price-exceeds-bitcoins-price-opensea/">Pudgy Penguins as the second-largest NFT collection in terms of floor price,</a> trailing only behind the legendary CryptoPunks collection, which maintains a floor price of 39.5 ETH ($150,000). The collection&#8217;s most expensive piece is currently listed at 50.3093 ETH, approximately $197,508.78 on the NFT marketplace OpenSea.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The surge in value comes amid heightened trading activity, with the project experiencing a 194% price increase over the past month according to data from CoinGecko. The collection has seen its market dominance rise to 21.88%, surpassing the previous market leader, Bored Ape Yacht Club, which now holds 16.31% of the market share.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The timing of this price rally coincides with the announcement of the project&#8217;s upcoming ecosystem token, $PENGU, scheduled for release on the Solana blockchain. While the exact launch date remains undisclosed, the team has confirmed the token will debut in 2024, with less than 20 days remaining in the current year.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The introduction of $PENGU represents a strategic cross-chain expansion for the project. Despite the NFT collection remaining on Ethereum, the decision to launch the token on Solana demonstrates the team&#8217;s approach to leveraging opportunities across multiple blockchain networks.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Introducing <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24PENGU&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">$PENGU</a>, the official coin of Pudgy Penguins.</p>
<p>Launching in 2024. Learn more below. <a href="https://t.co/J715bODcM6">pic.twitter.com/J715bODcM6</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Pudgy Penguins (@pudgypenguins) <a href="https://twitter.com/pudgypenguins/status/1864851993094664602?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">December 6, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The tokenomics structure for $PENGU has been carefully planned, with a total supply set at 88,888,888,888 tokens. The distribution allocates 25.9% to the existing Pudgy Penguins community, while 24.12% is reserved for other communities and new &#8220;Huddle&#8221; members.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Team allocation has been structured with long-term alignment in mind, with current and future team members receiving 17.8% of the supply. This portion is subject to a one-year cliff and three-year vesting period. The company will retain 11.48% under identical vesting conditions.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The project&#8217;s recent success is reflected in its trading volumes, with NFT sales reaching over $180 million in early December. The number of active market wallets exceeded 12,000, indicating strong market participation and investor interest.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Looking at the collection&#8217;s growth trajectory, Pudgy Penguins has seen its market dominance more than triple since October 2024, when it held just 9.5% of the market share. This increase aligns with a broader recovery in the NFT market, which saw total sales volumes rise 57.8% to $562 million in November, reaching the highest monthly figure since May.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The collection&#8217;s rise to prominence began in 2021, and it has since expanded beyond the digital realm through strategic retail partnerships with major brands including Walmart and Target. These real-world connections have helped establish Pudgy Penguins as more than just a digital art collection.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The project consists of 8,888 unique NFTs, each with distinct characteristics and varying levels of rarity. The current floor price of 27.65 ETH ($108,460) represents the minimum investment required to join the collection&#8217;s ownership group.</p>
<figure id="attachment_107981" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-107981" style="width: 847px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-107981" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-12-at-09-06-14-Pudgy-Penguins-NFT-Floor-Price-Chart-CoinGecko.png" alt="Pudgy Penguins Price on CoinGecko" width="847" height="635" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-12-at-09-06-14-Pudgy-Penguins-NFT-Floor-Price-Chart-CoinGecko.png 847w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-12-at-09-06-14-Pudgy-Penguins-NFT-Floor-Price-Chart-CoinGecko-300x225.png 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-12-at-09-06-14-Pudgy-Penguins-NFT-Floor-Price-Chart-CoinGecko-768x576.png 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-12-at-09-06-14-Pudgy-Penguins-NFT-Floor-Price-Chart-CoinGecko-50x37.png 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-12-at-09-06-14-Pudgy-Penguins-NFT-Floor-Price-Chart-CoinGecko-150x112.png 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-12-at-09-06-14-Pudgy-Penguins-NFT-Floor-Price-Chart-CoinGecko-450x337.png 450w" sizes="(max-width: 847px) 100vw, 847px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-107981" class="wp-caption-text">Pudgy Penguins Price on <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/nft/pudgy-penguins">CoinGecko</a></figcaption></figure>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Market data shows particular strength in blue-chip NFT collections, with both CryptoPunks and Pudgy Penguins leading the recent market recovery. The floor price for Pudgy Penguins demonstrated this momentum with a 262% increase during November, rising from 8.7 ETH to 13 ETH before its current levels.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Trading activity has remained robust through December, with daily volumes consistently showing strong market interest. The 21.88% market dominance achieved by Pudgy Penguins represents a major shift in the NFT landscape, particularly in displacing Bored Ape Yacht Club from its previous market-leading position.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The current floor price statistics show the collection maintaining steady value above the $100,000 mark, with Bitcoin prices hovering around $101,445 at the time of writing.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/pudgy-penguins-nft-collection-floor-price-hits-27-eth-as-pengu-token-launch-approaches/">Pudgy Penguins NFT Collection Floor Price Hits 27 ETH as $PENGU Token Launch Approaches</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">107977</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Chainlink (LINK) Price Surge: Sets Sights on $100 Following Major Announcements</title>
		<link>https://blockonomi.com/chainlink-link-price-surge-sets-sights-on-100-following-major-announcements/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Oliver Dale]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 08:44:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blockonomi.com/?p=107972</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>TLDR Chainlink (LINK) has surged over 20% in 24 hours, outperforming both Bitcoin and Ethereum Analysts predict LINK could reach $100, representing a 354% increase from current levels Major partnerships announced with Coinbase, SWIFT, and other financial institutions Exchange balances are declining as more investors hold or stake their LINK Technical analysis suggests an initial [...]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/chainlink-link-price-surge-sets-sights-on-100-following-major-announcements/">Chainlink (LINK) Price Surge: Sets Sights on $100 Following Major Announcements</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h1>TLDR</h1>
<ul>
<li>Chainlink (LINK) has surged over 20% in 24 hours, outperforming both Bitcoin and Ethereum</li>
<li>Analysts predict LINK could reach $100, representing a 354% increase from current levels</li>
<li>Major partnerships announced with Coinbase, SWIFT, and other financial institutions</li>
<li>Exchange balances are declining as more investors hold or stake their LINK</li>
<li>Technical analysis suggests an initial target of $40 before potential move to $100</li>
</ul>
<hr />
<p>Chainlink (LINK) has emerged as a standout performer in the cryptocurrency market, with its price reaching $28 <a href="https://blockonomi.com/eth-aave-link-soar-as-trumps-world-liberty-financial-buys-12m-of-tokens/">amid a series of high-profile partnerships</a> and declining exchange balances. The token has demonstrated remarkable growth, posting gains of 20% in the last 24 hours and 84.5% over the previous month.</p>
<p>The cryptocurrency&#8217;s recent price movement has caught the attention of market analysts, particularly following its selection as the oracle technology provider for Coinbase, the largest cryptocurrency exchange in the United States. This partnership represents a major validation of Chainlink&#8217;s technology and its potential role in the evolving digital asset landscape.</p>
<p>Adding to the momentum, Chainlink has secured partnerships with several traditional financial powerhouses. The SWIFT network, which processes over $150 trillion in transactions annually, has chosen Chainlink for integration into its systems. This development has led analysts to project potential market capitalization growth exceeding $500 billion for the protocol.</p>
<p>The protocol has also attracted attention from major banking institutions, with BNP Paribas, Citi, Franklin Templeton, UBS, and Vontobel all engaging with Chainlink&#8217;s technology. These partnerships demonstrate growing institutional acceptance of blockchain technology in traditional finance.</p>
<p>Market data reveals a notable trend in LINK token holdings. Exchange balances have been steadily declining, indicating that investors are increasingly moving their tokens to private wallets or participating in staking activities. This behavior typically suggests a long-term holding strategy among investors.</p>
<p>Technical analysis of LINK&#8217;s price movement shows the formation of a cup and handle pattern on the weekly chart. The pattern&#8217;s completion at $22.64 suggests potential for further upward movement. Analysts note that this technical formation often precedes continued price appreciation.</p>
<figure id="attachment_107973" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-107973" style="width: 835px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-107973" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/link-price.png" alt="Chainlink
LINK Price
" width="835" height="636" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/link-price.png 835w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/link-price-300x229.png 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/link-price-768x585.png 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/link-price-50x38.png 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/link-price-150x114.png 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/link-price-450x343.png 450w" sizes="(max-width: 835px) 100vw, 835px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-107973" class="wp-caption-text"><br />Chainlink<br /><a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/chainlink">LINK Price</a></figcaption></figure>
<p>The depth of the cup pattern provides insights into possible price targets. Using standard technical analysis methodologies, measuring 77% from the cup&#8217;s upper edge suggests an initial target of $40.8. This level coincides with the 23.6% Fibonacci retracement level, adding technical validity to the projection.</p>
<p>Reports from the Abu Dhabi Finance Week have sparked additional market interest, with rumors circulating about potential discussions between Chainlink representatives and BlackRock. While unconfirmed, these reports have contributed to positive market sentiment around LINK.</p>
<p>Market analysts, including WSB Trader Rocko, maintain bullish predictions for LINK&#8217;s price trajectory. Their analysis suggests potential movement toward $100, representing a 354% increase from current levels. However, they note that reaching this target would require first breaking through the $40 resistance level and then surpassing the previous all-time high of $52.90.</p>
<p>CoinCodex&#8217;s technical analysis presents an optimistic outlook, projecting LINK to reach $66.77 by February 21, 2024. This forecast would represent a 138.98% increase from current price levels and establish a new all-time high for the token.</p>
<p>The broader cryptocurrency market context appears supportive of LINK&#8217;s growth potential. Bitcoin&#8217;s recent move above $101,000 has created positive momentum across the entire crypto sector. This market-wide optimism has contributed to increased interest in alternative cryptocurrencies like Chainlink.</p>
<p>Looking at year-over-year performance, LINK has shown strong growth with a 79.3% increase since December 2023. This sustained upward trend has occurred despite periodic market volatility and broader economic uncertainties.</p>
<p>Current market data shows LINK trading approximately 48.4% below its all-time high of $52.70, which was reached in May 2021. This price history provides context for current growth projections and potential resistance levels.</p>
<p>Exchange data indicates strong trading volume across major platforms, suggesting active market participation and liquidity. This trading activity supports price discovery and market efficiency for LINK tokens.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/chainlink-link-price-surge-sets-sights-on-100-following-major-announcements/">Chainlink (LINK) Price Surge: Sets Sights on $100 Following Major Announcements</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">107972</post-id>	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
