<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	
	xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
	xmlns:geo="http://www.w3.org/2003/01/geo/wgs84_pos#"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Cryptocurrency Exchanges Reviews: All the Latest info from Blockonomi</title>
	<atom:link href="https://blockonomi.com/exchanges/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://blockonomi.com/exchanges/</link>
	<description>Cryptocurrency News &#38; Your Guide to the Blockchain Economy</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 14:52:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.7.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/fav-50x50.png</url>
	<title>Cryptocurrency Exchanges Reviews: All the Latest info from Blockonomi</title>
	<link>https://blockonomi.com/exchanges/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
<site xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">134176212</site>	<item>
		<title>World’s First Licensed DEX GRVT: Ready to Shake Up CEX dominance</title>
		<link>https://blockonomi.com/worlds-first-licensed-dex-grvt-ready-to-shake-up-cex-dominance/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[CryptoPR]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 14:51:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchanges]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blockonomi.com/?p=107761</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Picture this: all major financial institutions and millions of individuals trading on decentralized exchanges (DEXs). In such a future, would centralized exchanges (CEXs) even exist? Perhaps not. The very concept of “CEXs” might fade away, as “crypto exchanges” will naturally have to build on-chain, rather than running on centralized servers, as all leading CEXs currently [...]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/worlds-first-licensed-dex-grvt-ready-to-shake-up-cex-dominance/">World’s First Licensed DEX GRVT: Ready to Shake Up CEX dominance</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Picture this: all major financial institutions and millions of individuals trading on decentralized exchanges (DEXs). In such a future, would </span><a href="https://www.investopedia.com/tech/what-are-centralized-cryptocurrency-exchanges/?ref=grvt.io"><span style="font-weight: 400">centralized exchanges</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400"> (CEXs) even exist? Perhaps not. The very concept of “CEXs” might fade away, as “crypto exchanges” will naturally have to build on-chain, rather than running on centralized servers, as all leading CEXs currently do, which goes against the original intent of Bitcoin, blockchain, and the vision of decentralization.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Yet here we are. Users are so comfortable with CEXs that they ignore a basic fact: centralized exchanges have little to do with blockchain technology. They run on private servers, not on-chain. They settle trades in closed systems, not on-chain.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Technically, any CEX could face another </span><a href="https://www.investopedia.com/what-went-wrong-with-ftx-6828447?ref=grvt.io"><span style="font-weight: 400">FTX-like collapse</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400">. It’s a sobering thought, but not far-fetched.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Despite repeated wake-up calls like the FTX collapse, CEXs still account for almost 90% of crypto trading volume as of November 2024. Why? Convenience and familiarity outweigh the glaring risks for many users. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">However, the centralized nature of these exchanges means another FTX-style implosion could occur at any moment.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">DeFi could be the answer, but it’s not there yet, and it shares some of the blame for the stalled popularity: </span></p>
<ol>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">Horrible user experience: Unintuitive interfaces make DEXs inaccessible to most people.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">Technological vulnerabilities: Exploits and hacks continue to erode trust.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">Institutional reluctance: Institutions don’t trust a system that operates like the Wild West.</span></li>
</ol>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">In a sandbox discussion, everyone agrees that DEXs are amazing—eliminating counterparty risks, on-chain transparency, and trust in code over intermediaries. But in the real world, institutions see DeFi as untested, unsafe, and unregulated. They need a trusted gateway to participate.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Current financial systems are built to block interactions with unlicensed entities. Banks, asset managers, and other licensed players are structurally unable to engage with non-regulated entities. That’s why institutions stick to CEXs—not because they love them, but because they have no alternative.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Like it or not, TradFi has centuries of regulations that allow it to stay mainstream despite systemic failures like the 2008 crisis. DeFi, by contrast, lacks regulatory standards, which has left it stuck in the margins. Regulation isn’t the enemy—it’s the foundation for scaling this technology.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">The unregulated status of DeFi is the biggest reason institutions avoid it. And it matters. Without institutional liquidity, DEXs lack credibility and trading volume. Institutions are the backbone of any financial market, and without them, DeFi can’t grow.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">GRVT’s DABA license is a game changer, not just for DEXs but for the entire DeFi ecosystem. It’s the first regulated DEX, setting a precedent for how institutions and mainstream users can safely engage with DeFi.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Regulations, when implemented thoughtfully, can be a catalyst for DeFi’s growth. Here’s why:</span></p>
<ol>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">Security and Compliance: Regulatory frameworks establish operational standards and safeguards against fraud and misconduct. For example, licensing ensures adherence to KYC (Know Your Customer) and AML (Anti-Money Laundering) protocols, addressing one of the biggest hurdles for institutional investors.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">Institutional Trust: Trust is the currency of institutional finance. Regulated entities provide assurance to traditional financial players. For instance, GRVT’s DABA license creates a bridge, enabling banks, hedge funds, and asset managers to confidently explore DeFi without the fear of regulatory backlash.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">Counterparty Risk Mitigation: Unlike CEXs, where users must trust the exchange to hold and settle assets, GRVT leverages blockchain technology for self-custodial settlements, eliminating the risk of mismanagement and fraud.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">Mainstream Adoption: TradFi regulations have evolved over centuries, enabling global financial markets to thrive. DeFi must adopt similar standards to gain mainstream legitimacy.</span></li>
</ol>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">From day one, GRVT has been committed to setting a new standard for DEXs and DeFi. Our General Counsel was the fourth hire, underscoring our dedication to compliance and regulatory excellence. Achieving regulatory approval as the world’s first licensed DEX is more than a badge of honor—it’s a practical step toward reshaping how the world interacts with DeFi.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Key features of GRVT include:</span></p>
<ol>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">Blockchain-powered self-custody: Users retain full control of their assets.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">On-chain transparency: Every transaction is recorded on the blockchain, ensuring trust and accountability.</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400"><span style="font-weight: 400">Institution-ready security: Enhanced safeguards that mirror traditional finance.</span></li>
</ol>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">If the hurdles in DeFi—user experience, security, and regulatory clarity—are addressed, the vision of a world where all institutions trade on DEXs becomes achievable. In such a world, the term “CEXs” might vanish, and “crypto exchanges” would inherently mean on-chain platforms.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">This isn’t just a vision. With GRVT, it’s </span><a href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/grvt-crypto-exchange-bermuda-license?ref=grvt.io"><span style="font-weight: 400">already happening</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400">.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">GRVT has now become the first DEX to secure regulatory approval, having obtained the Class M Digital Asset Business License from the Bermuda Monetary Authority (BMA). </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">This sets a new global standard for decentralized finance and marks a pivotal moment in the industry’s evolution toward a more regulated, secure, and compliant approach &#8211; paving the way for mainstream and wider institutional adoption of DeFi. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">GRVT is continuing its pursuit of a Full Class F license in Bermuda, demonstrating its dedication to comprehensive regulatory compliance and its readiness to offer a broad spectrum of digital asset services within Bermuda’s robust regulatory framework.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400">Simultaneously, GRVT is actively engaging with regulatory authorities in multiple jurisdictions to advance its licensing efforts. These initiatives include aligning with the Markets in Crypto-Assets (</span><a href="https://www.esma.europa.eu/esmas-activities/digital-finance-and-innovation/markets-crypto-assets-regulation-mica?ref=grvt.io"><span style="font-weight: 400">MiCA</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400">) framework in the European Union and collaborating with the Abu Dhabi Global Market (</span><a href="https://www.adgm.com/?ref=grvt.io"><span style="font-weight: 400">ADGM</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400">), a leading financial center known for its innovative approach to digital asset regulation.</span></p>
<p><br style="font-weight: 400" /><br style="font-weight: 400" /></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/worlds-first-licensed-dex-grvt-ready-to-shake-up-cex-dominance/">World’s First Licensed DEX GRVT: Ready to Shake Up CEX dominance</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">107761</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coinbase Cuts USDC Rewards in EU Due to MICA Regulation</title>
		<link>https://blockonomi.com/coinbase-cuts-usdc-rewards-in-eu-due-to-mica-regulation/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nicholas Say]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 10:28:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchanges]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regulation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blockonomi.com/?p=107131</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Coinbase is winding down its USDC Rewards program for users in the European Economic Area (EEA) to comply with the Markets in Crypto Assets Regulation (MiCA), which went into effect on June 30. The exchange said that MiCA regulation will affect e-money tokens. With more regulations, more enforcement will follow. The move was first shared [...]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/coinbase-cuts-usdc-rewards-in-eu-due-to-mica-regulation/">Coinbase Cuts USDC Rewards in EU Due to MICA Regulation</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Coinbase is winding down its USDC Rewards program for <a href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/coinbase-europe-users-frustrated-usdc-yield-scrapped-mica">users in the European Economic Area (EEA)</a> to comply with the Markets in Crypto Assets Regulation (MiCA), which went into effect on June 30.</p>
<p>The exchange said that MiCA regulation will affect e-money tokens. With more regulations, more enforcement will follow.</p>
<p>The move was first shared by Marina Markezic, an X (formerly Twitter) user, on November 28. In an email sent to users who may be affected by the change, Coinbase stated that users will still be able to earn rewards until November 30 before it officially suspends the program on December 1.</p>
<h2>More EU Regulations</h2>
<p>Coinbase will distribute the final USDC Rewards payout for impacted users within the first 10 business days of December.</p>
<p>Launched on November 20, the USDC Rewards program allows users to earn an annual percentage yield of around 4.7% by <a href="https://blockonomi.com/best-usd-coin-casino/">holding USDC</a> in their Coinbase Wallet. Rewards are paid out monthly, directly into users&#8217; wallets, and there are no lock-up periods required.</p>
<p>Through the program, Coinbase aims to promote the use of stablecoins while providing users with a way to earn passive income on their digital assets. The program is available to users in various regions worldwide, although specific eligibility may depend on local regulations and requirements.</p>
<p>Earlier in October, the exchange said it will delist certain stablecoins that fail to meet the new compliance standards by year’s end. That raises concerns about Coinbase’s potential removal of Tether’s USDT, the leading stablecoin by market cap, though the exchange has not yet officially confirmed that.</p>
<p>The MiCA regulation introduces stringent standards for stablecoin issuers, focusing on transparency, liquidity, and consumer protection. These requirements are aimed at enhancing the stability and reliability of stablecoins within the EU market</p>
<p>The rules are set to come into full force on December 30, 2024. To prepare for its full implementation, several major cryptocurrency exchanges have ended support for non-compliant stablecoins.</p>
<p>OKX has taken steps to limit the availability of non-compliant stablecoins, while Bitstamp and Uphold both have imposed restrictions on these tokens, including USDT.</p>
<p>Other platforms are also reassessing their stablecoin offerings as part of their efforts to comply with MiCA regulations.</p>
<h2>Tether to Shift Focus to MiCA-compliant stablecoins</h2>
<p>As the largest stablecoin with $133 billion in market value, a delisting from a major exchange like Coinbase could impact USDT&#8217;s liquidity and trading volumes in the EEA.</p>
<p>The potential removal also gives an edge to competitors like Circle&#8217;s USDC, one of the few stablecoins that is fully compliant with the MiCA in the European Union. The second-largest stablecoin could capitalize on this opportunity to gain market share, especially in the European Union.</p>
<p>In response to the delisting speculation, Tether announced Wednesday the discontinuation of support for its euro-pegged stablecoin, EURT. The firm said the decision was made due to regulatory changes associated with the MiCA regulation.</p>
<p>Minting new EURT has been suspended since 2022, according to Tether. As part of the shutdown, holders are urged to redeem their tokens by November 27, 2025.</p>
<p>The firm said it is now focusing on developing stablecoins that comply with MiCA regulations. Tether and Quantoz Payments are working on EURQ and USDQ, its claimed MiCA-compliant stablecoins backed by Tether&#8217;s Hadron technology.</p>
<p>Tether has faced scrutiny regarding its reserve practices and transparency. MiCA regulations will likely require Tether to enhance its disclosures and undergo audits, which could affect its operational flexibility in Europe.</p>
<p>Tether&#8217;s CEO, Paolo Ardoino, previously explained that MiCA’s stringent cash reserve requirements could pose systemic risks to both banks and digital assets. While Ardoino praised the EU lawmakers’ efforts to set forth a clear legal framework for digital assets, he was also concerned about its side effect on Tether’s business model.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/coinbase-cuts-usdc-rewards-in-eu-due-to-mica-regulation/">Coinbase Cuts USDC Rewards in EU Due to MICA Regulation</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">107131</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Celsius Initiates Second $127M Payout to Creditors</title>
		<link>https://blockonomi.com/celsius-initiates-second-127m-payout-to-creditors/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nicholas Say]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 08:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchanges]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blockonomi.com/?p=107025</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Cryptocurrency lender Celsius Network is set to allocate additional $127 million funds to its creditors as part of its reorganization plan. It will be the firm’s second distribution, following a $2.53 billion payout made earlier this year. The amount of Bitcoin distributed in these payouts is based on a predetermined price of $95,836.23 per Bitcoin [...]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/celsius-initiates-second-127m-payout-to-creditors/">Celsius Initiates Second $127M Payout to Creditors</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Cryptocurrency lender Celsius Network is set to allocate additional $127 million funds to its creditors as part of its reorganization plan. It will be the firm’s <a href="https://x.com/CelsiusNetwork/status/1861896567789375742">second distribution</a>, following a $2.53 billion payout made earlier this year.</p>
<p>The amount of Bitcoin distributed in these payouts is based on a predetermined price of $95,836.23 per Bitcoin</p>
<p>According to a notice dated Nov. 27, creditors who fall into five categories—”retail borrower deposits, general earn claims, withhold claims, unsecured loan claims, and general unsecured claims”—may be eligible to get back a portion of their claims.</p>
<h2>The Process Grinds On</h2>
<p>Each eligible creditor will receive a total distribution amounting to approximately 60.4% of their original claim. They reportedly received around 57.65% of their claims during the first payout in January.</p>
<p>The second distribution will be made in either cash or cryptocurrency, likely Bitcoin. The Bitcoin repayment will be set at a predetermined price of $95,836.23 per coin.</p>
<p>In other words, creditors are likely to receive a lower value in Bitcoin than what they might have expected. At the time of Celsius&#8217;s bankruptcy filing in July 2022, Bitcoin was valued at less than $40,000. Currently, it is trading above $95,000, up 137% from its price at the time of Celsius&#8217;s bankruptcy filing, according to CoinGecko data.</p>
<p>Some creditors may have received a slightly higher initial distribution due to a correction, as noted in the notice. For those who have not yet received their initial distribution, Celsius states it will send both distributions this time.</p>
<p>Repayment will be made through PayPal or Venmo for creditors who chose these methods previously in the first distribution. Celsius also notes that all creditors must pass the KYC/AML process to receive their distributions.</p>
<p>For creditors who were supposed to receive funds through Coinbase but haven&#8217;t received them by November 9, Celsius will automatically switch transfer assets to a different platform.</p>
<p>With a high BYC price, the creditors will be getting a nice amount based on their holdings.</p>
<h2>Bankruptcy Nears Finish Line</h2>
<p>The collapse of Terra&#8217;s LUNA/UST triggered a market-wide downturn that ultimately led to the demise of Celsius Network. The once-prominent cryptocurrency lending platform filed for Chapter 11 bankruptcy in July 2022, leaving its customers reeling from huge financial losses.</p>
<p>At the time of its bankruptcy filing, Celsius held approximately $4.7 billion in customer assets but had only $167 million in liquidity remaining.</p>
<p>In September 2023, creditors approved a reorganization plan that proposed repaying customers through a combination of cryptocurrency and shares in a newly formed Bitcoin mining company called Ionic Digital Inc.</p>
<p>As part of the bankruptcy resolution, Celsius began distributing funds to creditors. The plan is to repay over $3 billion to 375,000 creditors. By August 2024, 251,000 creditors reportedly received a total of $2.53 billion in crypto and fiat assets, meaning many yet to claim their funds.</p>
<p>The forthcoming distribution of funds is expected to bring the Celsius Network bankruptcy case closer to its final resolution. Yet, there are legal troubles associated with former leaders.</p>
<p>Alex Mashinsky, the ex-CEO of Celsius, is facing seven criminal charges related to the company&#8217;s collapse, including the alleged manipulation of the Celsius (CEL) token.</p>
<p>Mashinsky filed a motion to dismiss charges against him. However, earlier this month, a federal judge denied the request. The case will move forward, with Mashinsky facing trial on two counts of commodities fraud.</p>
<p>If convicted on all seven charges, Mashinsky could face a maximum prison sentence of up to 115 years. His trial is scheduled to begin in January 2025.</p>
<p>Marc Mukasey, previously represented Mashinsky, has been chosen to be attorney of Sam Bankman-Fried, FTX’s former CEO.</p>
<p>The shared legal representation could lead to conflicts since both cases involve allegations of fraud in the cryptocurrency sector. However, Judge Kaplan allowed Bankman-Fried to retain his attorneys.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/celsius-initiates-second-127m-payout-to-creditors/">Celsius Initiates Second $127M Payout to Creditors</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">107025</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>HECO Chain Announces January 2025 Closure, Users Urged to Redeem Assets</title>
		<link>https://blockonomi.com/heco-chain-announces-january-2025-closure-users-urged-to-redeem-assets/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nicholas Say]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 09:19:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchanges]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blockonomi.com/?p=106769</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>HECO Network, a decentralized blockchain platform built by Huobi, one of the largest crypto exchanges, will officially discontinue its services on January 15, ending its journey after four years of operations. HECO Bridge suffered a $87 million hack last year. Users holding HRC20 assets are urged to redeem their holdings before the network’s closure. The [...]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/heco-chain-announces-january-2025-closure-users-urged-to-redeem-assets/">HECO Chain Announces January 2025 Closure, Users Urged to Redeem Assets</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>HECO Network, a decentralized blockchain platform built by Huobi, one of the largest crypto exchanges, will <a href="https://www.heco123.com/en-us/">officially discontinue</a> its services on January 15, ending its journey after four years of operations.</p>
<p>HECO Bridge suffered a $87 million hack last year.</p>
<p>Users holding HRC20 assets are urged to redeem their holdings before the network’s closure. The list of affected HRC20 assets includes HRC20ETH, HRC20TUSD, HRC20LINK, HRC20USDC, HRC20UNI, HRC20SHIB, HRC20HBTC, and HRC20USDT, as noted in a Nov. 24 statement.</p>
<p>Holders of these assets are advised to deposit their holdings to the designated address before January 10, 2025, in order to avoid potential losses. These deposited assets will then be converted into points, which will then be redeemed for a new token, HTX.</p>
<h2>The Fall of HECO</h2>
<p>The distribution of HTX will occur in 12 equal batches, starting on January 15, 2025. Users will need to provide their TRON network address during the redemption process to receive their allocated HTX.</p>
<p>Launched in December 2020, HECO aims to provide a low-cost, efficient environment for developers to build decentralized applications (dApps) and engage in decentralized finance (DeFi).</p>
<p>The blockchain has played an important role in the development of the Huobi ecosystem. At its peak in 2021, HECO Network’s total value locked reached approximately $3 billion.</p>
<p>However, the blockchain has struggled due to the prolonged market downturn and steady growth of its competitors.</p>
<p>Ethereum, Solana, Binance Smart Chain remain leading layer-1 blockchains. The arrival of newcomers like Avalanche and TRON also challenges the position of HECO. Not only that, HECO was also hit by a hack that prompted users to move to other platforms.</p>
<h2>Hacks Kill Platforms</h2>
<p>In November 2023, the HECO Bridge was <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-11-22/two-crypto-platforms-linked-to-justin-sun-hit-by-hacker-attacks">exploited</a>, leading to the theft of approximately $87 million in various cryptocurrencies. Hackers reportedly gained access to the bridge’s private key and stole various cryptocurrencies, including a large amount of Ether and Tether.</p>
<p>Alongside the HECO Bridge exploit, cryptocurrency exchange HTX, a prominent project in the Huobi ecosystem, suffered a separate attack that resulted in an additional loss of about $30 million from its hot wallets around the same timeframe.</p>
<p>These attacks followed an attack targeting Poloniex, another Justin Sun-backed exchange, which lost over $100 million.</p>
<p>Following the attacks, HTX took measures to secure remaining funds. Sun also confirmed that HTX would fully compensate for the losses incurred from these breaches.</p>
<p>HTX (formerly Huobi) was acquired by TRON’s founder in 2020. In January this year, Sun said the platform’s original token, HT, was completely converted to a new token called HTX. The transition replaced nearly all HT-related benefits with HTX equivalents, including transaction fee discounts.</p>
<p>In addition to the conversion, HTX also introduced HTX DAO, a decentralized autonomous organization based on HTX&#8217;s governance token. The DAO was created to enhance community governance and transparency.</p>
<p>At the time, the conversion sparked controversy among crypto members. Some users felt that the transition meant an abandonment of the original Heco chain and the HT token, particularly following a hack that affected both HTX and Heco.</p>
<h2>Falling Prices</h2>
<p>Data from CoinGecko shows that HTX DAO’s HTX token dropped by 5% to $0.00000178 following the closure announcement of HECO. It is now trading at around $0.00000183, down around 2% in the last 24 hours.</p>
<p>The decline might also be linked to the recent Bitcoin pullback. Bitcoin dropped below $96,000 on Sunday before surging above $98,000.</p>
<p>Yet, the HTX token recorded a 9% weekly growth. Over the past 30 days, its value has surged 27%.</p>
<p>Huobi Korea, a cryptocurrency exchange originally established as the South Korean branch of Huobi Global (now HTX), announced its shutdown earlier this year. The closure, following the severance of ties with HTX in January 2023, was due to a challenging business environment.</p>
<p>Some regional exchanges also announced its termination around the time, like Cashierest and Coinbit, due to tough market conditions and increasing competition.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/heco-chain-announces-january-2025-closure-users-urged-to-redeem-assets/">HECO Chain Announces January 2025 Closure, Users Urged to Redeem Assets</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">106769</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance Launches BFUSD Trading Asset with 19.55% Annual Yield</title>
		<link>https://blockonomi.com/binance-launches-bfusd-trading-asset-with-19-55-annual-yield/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Oliver Dale]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 10:02:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchanges]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blockonomi.com/?p=106379</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>TLDR: Binance launched BFUSD, a reward-bearing margin asset offering ~19.55% APY BFUSD is not a stablecoin but a futures trading product with daily rewards The token maintains 105.54% collateralization ratio backed by USDT reserves Not available in regions where Binance Futures are restricted or under MiCA regulation User holding limits are based on VIP levels [...]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/binance-launches-bfusd-trading-asset-with-19-55-annual-yield/">Binance Launches BFUSD Trading Asset with 19.55% Annual Yield</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>TLDR:</h2>
<ul>
<li>Binance launched BFUSD, a reward-bearing margin asset offering ~19.55% APY</li>
<li>BFUSD is not a stablecoin but a futures trading product with daily rewards</li>
<li>The token maintains 105.54% collateralization ratio backed by USDT reserves</li>
<li>Not available in regions where Binance Futures are restricted or under MiCA regulation</li>
<li>User holding limits are based on VIP levels and KYC verification</li>
</ul>
<hr />
<p>Binance, the world&#8217;s largest cryptocurrency exchange, has introduced BFUSD, a new reward-bearing margin asset for futures trading. The product offers users an annual percentage yield (APY) of approximately 19.55%, leading to both interest and concern within the crypto community.</p>
<p><a href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/binance-clarifies-bfusd-not-stablecoin-x-users-question-yield">The announcement of BFUSD initially created confusion in the market</a>, with some users mistaking it for a stablecoin. Binance quickly clarified that BFUSD is not a stablecoin but rather a specialized trading asset designed for futures and perpetuals traders.</p>
<p>Users can acquire BFUSD through Tether USD (USDT) swaps. The asset maintains stability through a collateralization ratio of 105.54%, with a reserve fund currently holding 1.1 million USDT as of November 17, 2024.</p>
<p>The high yield offering sparked immediate comparisons to Terra&#8217;s failed Anchor protocol, which previously offered 20% yields before its collapse in May 2022. This prompted Binance to emphasize the fundamental differences between BFUSD and algorithmic stablecoins.</p>
<p>BFUSD rewards are distributed daily to users&#8217; UM Futures accounts, based on the lowest balance recorded from hourly snapshots throughout the day. Unlike traditional yield-bearing products, BFUSD doesn&#8217;t require staking or locking up funds.</p>
<p>The product includes several user restrictions and safety measures. Each trader has a BFUSD holding limit determined by their VIP level on Binance, which can be increased through know-your-customer (KYC) verification and meeting trading volume thresholds.</p>
<p>Geographic restrictions apply to the product. Users from regions where Binance Futures are not permitted, including Brazil, cannot access BFUSD. Additionally, rewards are not available in countries where the Markets in Crypto-Assets (MiCA) regulation is in effect.</p>
<p>In Multi-Asset Mode, BFUSD can serve as collateral with a 100% collateral ratio, allowing traders to expand their trading potential across various assets on the platform.</p>
<p>The launch comes at a notable time in Binance&#8217;s history with pegged assets. The exchange has been transitioning away from Binance USD (BUSD) since February 2023, when U.S. regulators ordered Paxos to stop issuing the stablecoin.</p>
<p>The current stablecoin landscape shows diverse offerings, <a href="https://moneycheck.com/best-tether-casinos/">with Tether&#8217;s USDT</a> dominating 74% of the market. Competitors like Ethena&#8217;s sUSDe present similar high yields at 29% APY, while traditional finance enters the space with products like BlackRock&#8217;s BUIDL tokenized money funds.</p>
<p>Binance&#8217;s customer support team has actively addressed community concerns, emphasizing that BFUSD is a margin trading product rather than a stablecoin. The exchange continues to provide detailed information about the product&#8217;s mechanics and risk management features.</p>
<p>The implementation of BFUSD includes sophisticated technical features. The hourly snapshot system ensures accurate reward calculations, while the collateralization ratio provides a buffer against market volatility.</p>
<p>Trading features include seamless integration with Binance&#8217;s futures platform, allowing users to utilize BFUSD as trading collateral while earning rewards. This dual functionality sets it apart from traditional yield-bearing products.</p>
<p>The exchange has implemented strict compliance measures for BFUSD, including comprehensive KYC requirements and trading volume thresholds. These measures aim to ensure responsible usage and risk management.</p>
<p>Monitoring systems are in place to track BFUSD&#8217;s reserve fund and collateralization ratio, with regular updates provided to users through the Binance platform.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/binance-launches-bfusd-trading-asset-with-19-55-annual-yield/">Binance Launches BFUSD Trading Asset with 19.55% Annual Yield</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">106379</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Binance Reaches $100 Trillion Trading Volume: Will it Trigger a BNB Rally?</title>
		<link>https://blockonomi.com/binance-reaches-100-trillion-trading-volume-will-it-trigger-a-bnb-rally/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Oliver Dale]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 08:31:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchanges]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blockonomi.com/?p=104601</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>TLDR: Binance reached $100 trillion in combined spot and derivatives trading volume OKX is the second-largest exchange with $25 trillion lifetime volume Binance expanded mobile money payments in 6 African countries BNB price trading around $600, with potential to rally towards $800 Binance&#8217;s success strengthens its market position and impacts BNB price Binance, the world&#8217;s [...]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/binance-reaches-100-trillion-trading-volume-will-it-trigger-a-bnb-rally/">Binance Reaches $100 Trillion Trading Volume: Will it Trigger a BNB Rally?</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>TLDR:</h2>
<ul>
<li>Binance reached $100 trillion in combined spot and derivatives trading volume</li>
<li>OKX is the second-largest exchange with $25 trillion lifetime volume</li>
<li>Binance expanded mobile money payments in 6 African countries</li>
<li>BNB price trading around $600, with potential to rally towards $800</li>
<li>Binance&#8217;s success strengthens its market position and impacts BNB price</li>
</ul>
<hr />
<p>Binance, the world&#8217;s largest cryptocurrency exchange, has reached a historic milestone by becoming the first centralized exchange (CEX) to surpass $100 trillion in combined spot and derivatives trading volume.</p>
<p>This achievement solidifies Binance&#8217;s position as the dominant player in the crypto exchange market and has significant implications for its native token, Binance Coin (BNB).</p>
<p><a href="https://ccdata.io/research/chart-of-the-week">According to data from CCData</a>, Binance&#8217;s trading volume, which includes both spot and derivatives markets, has now crossed the $100 trillion mark. This figure dwarfs that of its closest competitor, OKX, which has recorded a lifetime trading volume of $25 trillion. Following OKX are Bybit and Bitget, with volumes of $13.2 trillion and $10.9 trillion, respectively.</p>
<p>The massive trading volume on Binance reflects the platform&#8217;s extensive reach and the substantial capital inflows into the cryptocurrency sector. It also highlights the growing interest in digital asset trading among retail and institutional investors alike.</p>
<p>Binance has been expanding its services in emerging markets. The exchange recently added mobile money payment options for cryptocurrency transactions in six African countries: Benin, Cameroon, Ivory Coast, the Democratic Republic of Congo, Togo, and Senegal.</p>
<p>This move follows the successful launch of Binance&#8217;s One Click Buy and Sell (OCBS) service in other African nations earlier this year.</p>
<p>By integrating mobile money payments, Binance aims to improve financial inclusion and provide more accessible entry points to the digital economy for African users. This expansion strategy could potentially increase Binance&#8217;s user base and trading volume in the region, further solidifying its market dominance.</p>
<p>The success of Binance has naturally drawn attention <a href="https://blockonomi.com/best-bnb-casino/">to its native token, BNB</a>. As of the latest data, BNB is trading at approximately $597, showing resilience in a fluctuating market. The token has seen a 3.61% increase over the past week, with its market capitalization standing at $87.16 billion and a 24-hour trading volume of $1.48 billion.</p>
<p>Analysts are closely monitoring BNB&#8217;s price action, particularly as it approaches the $620 resistance level. Some speculate that if BNB breaks through this barrier, it could potentially rally towards $800, representing a 35% increase from its current value.</p>
<p>The relationship between Binance&#8217;s trading volume and BNB&#8217;s price is complex. While increased trading activity on the platform doesn&#8217;t directly translate to higher BNB prices, it can contribute to positive sentiment around the token. BNB is used for various purposes within the Binance ecosystem, including trading fee discounts and participation in token sales on the Binance Launchpad.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/binance-reaches-100-trillion-trading-volume-will-it-trigger-a-bnb-rally/">Binance Reaches $100 Trillion Trading Volume: Will it Trigger a BNB Rally?</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">104601</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Kraken Launches kBTC: Bitcoin-Backed Token for Ethereum and OP Mainnet</title>
		<link>https://blockonomi.com/kraken-launches-kbtc-bitcoin-backed-token-for-ethereum-and-op-mainnet/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Oliver Dale]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 08:48:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchanges]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blockonomi.com/?p=104477</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>TLDR: Kraken launched kBTC, a fully backed 1:1 Bitcoin ERC-20 token kBTC is compatible with Ethereum and OP Mainnet networks Reserves are held by Kraken Financial, a Wyoming-chartered SPDI On-chain verification of reserves is available for transparency Kraken plans to expand kBTC compatibility to additional networks Kraken, a leading cryptocurrency exchange, has launched a new [...]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/kraken-launches-kbtc-bitcoin-backed-token-for-ethereum-and-op-mainnet/">Kraken Launches kBTC: Bitcoin-Backed Token for Ethereum and OP Mainnet</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>TLDR:</h2>
<ul>
<li>Kraken launched kBTC, a fully backed 1:1 Bitcoin ERC-20 token</li>
<li>kBTC is compatible with Ethereum and OP Mainnet networks</li>
<li>Reserves are held by Kraken Financial, a Wyoming-chartered SPDI</li>
<li>On-chain verification of reserves is available for transparency</li>
<li>Kraken plans to expand kBTC compatibility to additional networks</li>
</ul>
<hr />
<p>Kraken, a leading cryptocurrency exchange, <a href="https://blog.kraken.com/news/kbtc">has launched a new product called kBT</a>C, a Bitcoin-backed ERC-20 token designed to enhance Bitcoin&#8217;s utility across different blockchain networks.</p>
<p>This move places Kraken in direct competition with other major players in the wrapped Bitcoin market, including BitGo&#8217;s Wrapped Bitcoin (WBTC), Coinbase&#8217;s cbBTC, and 21.co&#8217;s 21BTC.</p>
<p>kBTC is a fully backed, cross-network-compatible token that represents Bitcoin on the Ethereum and OP Mainnet (formerly Optimism) networks. Each kBTC token is backed 1:1 by an equivalent amount of Bitcoin held in Kraken&#8217;s custody. This allows Bitcoin holders to participate in decentralized finance (DeFi) activities on these networks while maintaining exposure to Bitcoin&#8217;s value.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Introducing <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24kBTC&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">$kBTC</a> – an ERC-20 token fully backed 1:1 by Bitcoin, held securely by Kraken and always verifiable onchain. </p>
<p>More possibilities.<br />More functionality.<br />More transparency.</p>
<p>Let’s take a closer look <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/15.0.3/72x72/2935.png" alt="⤵" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> <a href="https://t.co/VammHbyJKm">pic.twitter.com/VammHbyJKm</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Kraken Pro (@krakenpro) <a href="https://twitter.com/krakenpro/status/1846889522409165172?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">October 17, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>Transparency and security are key features of kBTC. Kraken emphasizes its commitment to on-chain verification of reserves, allowing users to independently confirm the backing of their kBTC tokens.</p>
<p>The Bitcoin reserves are held by Kraken Financial, a Wyoming-chartered Special Purpose Depository Institution (SPDI), which provides an additional layer of regulatory oversight and security.</p>
<p>At launch, Kraken has allocated 100 Bitcoin (worth approximately $6.7 million) to back the initial supply of kBTC.</p>
<p>This is split with 80% on the Ethereum network and 20% on OP Mainnet. The company plans to expand kBTC&#8217;s compatibility to additional blockchain networks in the future, including non-EVM (Ethereum Virtual Machine) ecosystems.</p>
<p>The introduction of kBTC comes at a time of increased competition in the wrapped Bitcoin market. Coinbase and 21.co launched their respective wrapped Bitcoin products last month, while BitGo&#8217;s WBTC remains the market leader with a $10 billion market cap. This heightened activity reflects the growing importance of Bitcoin interoperability in the expanding DeFi landscape.</p>
<p>Kraken&#8217;s Global Head of Asset Growth and Management, Mark Greenberg, stated that &#8220;the future is on-chain&#8221; and that kBTC &#8220;enables users to put their BTC to work and accelerates the adoption of DeFi.&#8221; This sentiment underscores the broader industry trend of making Bitcoin more accessible and useful within various blockchain ecosystems.</p>
<p>The launch of kBTC also follows recent debates surrounding the custody arrangements of other wrapped Bitcoin products.</p>
<p>For instance, WBTC faced scrutiny due to a joint venture between its custodian, BitGo, and a Hong Kong-based custody platform with connections to Tron co-founder Justin Sun. Kraken aims to differentiate itself by emphasizing its long-standing reputation in the industry and its commitment to transparency.</p>
<p>To ensure the security of kBTC, Kraken had the ERC-20 smart contract audited by Trail of Bits, an external security firm. This audit involved a comprehensive examination of the codebase and client architecture to identify and address potential vulnerabilities.</p>
<p>Several projects have already partnered with Kraken for the kBTC launch, including deBridge, Definitive, Gauntlet, ParaSwap, and Yearn. These partnerships aim to integrate kBTC into various DeFi applications and services, further expanding its utility.</p>
<p>While Kraken has emphasized the potential of kBTC, it&#8217;s worth noting that at launch, no spot markets for kBTC will be available on the Kraken exchange. However, users will have the option to redeem their kBTC for Bitcoin at any time, providing flexibility in how they manage their assets.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/kraken-launches-kbtc-bitcoin-backed-token-for-ethereum-and-op-mainnet/">Kraken Launches kBTC: Bitcoin-Backed Token for Ethereum and OP Mainnet</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">104477</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cryptomus Review: The Cryptocurrency Exchange You Can Rely On</title>
		<link>https://blockonomi.com/cryptomus-review/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Oliver Dale]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 15:00:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchanges]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Reviews]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blockonomi.com/?p=104399</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Cryptomus exchange is a multi-functional trading platform that combines high liquidity with an extensive selection of useful options. Profitable spot trading, the strongest security measures, favourable commissions and working terms will be suitable for users of any level of interacting with digital assets. By the way, the intuitive UI of the exchange will please both [...]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/cryptomus-review/">Cryptomus Review: The Cryptocurrency Exchange You Can Rely On</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://cryptomus.com/?utm_source=blockonomi&amp;utm_medium=review&amp;utm_campaign=16-10">Cryptomus exchange</a> is a multi-functional trading platform that combines high liquidity with an extensive selection of useful options. Profitable spot trading, the strongest security measures, favourable commissions and working terms will be suitable for users of any level of interacting with digital assets.</p>
<p>By the way, the intuitive UI of the exchange will please both beginners and experienced traders since it offers better navigation, making the working process more pleasant and efficient.</p>
<p>Their goal is to make cryptocurrency trading accessible for everyone due to functionality’s improvements, adding new options, and facilitating the crypto trading process.</p>
<p><img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-105087" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/Screenshot_Blockonomi.png" alt="" width="1187" height="561" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/Screenshot_Blockonomi.png 1187w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/Screenshot_Blockonomi-300x142.png 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/Screenshot_Blockonomi-768x363.png 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/Screenshot_Blockonomi-50x24.png 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/Screenshot_Blockonomi-150x71.png 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/Screenshot_Blockonomi-450x213.png 450w" sizes="(max-width: 1187px) 100vw, 1187px" /></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<hr />
<h2>What Assists To Get Most Profit?</h2>
<h3>Low commissions.</h3>
<p>Affordable fees from 0.4%, decreasing to 0.05% with higher trading volumes, can be found on Cryptomus exchange. Save profit on commissions, and spend it for the more essential deals.</p>
<h3>Best working terms.</h3>
<p>Cryptomus exchange excels in trust and quality, providing its users with an effective crypto trading process with up-to-date market data and the most affordable terms of working with digital assets even without passing the KYC procedure (if the withdrawal volume is up to $100K).</p>
<figure id="attachment_104401" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-104401" style="width: 1400px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-104401" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/cryptomus-review.jpg" alt="Convert" width="1400" height="933" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/cryptomus-review.jpg 1400w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/cryptomus-review-300x200.jpg 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/cryptomus-review-768x512.jpg 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/cryptomus-review-50x33.jpg 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/cryptomus-review-150x100.jpg 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/cryptomus-review-450x300.jpg 450w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/cryptomus-review-1200x800.jpg 1200w" sizes="(max-width: 1400px) 100vw, 1400px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-104401" class="wp-caption-text">Convert</figcaption></figure>
<p><img decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-large wp-image-104402" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/convert.png" alt="" width="814" height="443" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/convert.png 1335w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/convert-300x163.png 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/convert-768x418.png 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/convert-50x27.png 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/convert-150x82.png 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/convert-450x245.png 450w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/convert-1200x653.png 1200w" sizes="(max-width: 814px) 100vw, 814px" /></p>
<h3>High liquidity.</h3>
<p>When it comes to the liquidity aspect, Cryptomus is a leading one. The exchange provides users with reliable trading resources and widely-traded pairs to get the most profit. In addition to these points, Cryptomus offers fast transaction processing and good integration opportunities, making crypto trading even more beneficial.</p>
<h3>Diverse trading options.</h3>
<p>The outstanding advantage of Cryptomus exchange is its range of trading tools, which are accessible to everyone. In-built cryptocurrency converter, allowing to easily exchange one coin to another; convenient P2P exchange, which gives the opportunity to directly trade with other counterparts; and, also, staking option, enhancing your potential for getting a passive income.</p>
<hr />
<h2>What are the Features?</h2>
<h3>Intuitive interface and best navigation.</h3>
<p>Minimalistic design will make the process of working with crypto more enjoyable. No matter what level of experience you have, this trading platform is suitable both for newbies and advanced crypto traders.</p>
<h3>Supporting an array of languages.</h3>
<p>We’re working on 17 languages, offering users the ability to interact with crypto with comfort. Just select any preferred language and enjoy the ease and convenience while making a profit.</p>
<h3>Robust security measures.</h3>
<p>The 2FA and PIN code system are also available here. Setting up a PIN code as a security lock on a personal or business account and enabling 2FA to access the wallet is a must-do for everyone interacting with cryptocurrency.</p>
<p>The Whitelist feature can also become a reliable security assistant, containing all the “allowed” wallet addresses where users can withdraw money from a personal wallet. This way, the process becomes much safer and simpler, reducing the risk of making a mistake to a minimum.</p>
<h3>Participation in cryptocurrency development.</h3>
<p>Cryptomus is more than just the exchange. It offers the opportunity to become a part of the supporting CRMS team, a promising cryptocurrency project, the platform’s native coin, uniting the Cryptomus community.</p>
<hr />
<h2>Are There Additional Services?</h2>
<h3>Convenient Cryptocurrency Wallet.</h3>
<p>Despite the exchange, Cryptomus stands out with its secure cryptocurrency <a href="https://cryptomus.com/wallet?utm_source=blockonomi&amp;utm_medium=review&amp;utm_campaign=16-10">wallet</a>  to store trading assets in the most convenient way. Strong security, a user-friendly interface, and a number of useful options, such as auto-convert, auto-withdrawal, and more, will definitely become a great bonus to your cryptocurrency management.</p>
<figure id="attachment_104405" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-104405" style="width: 1302px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-104405" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/wallet.png" alt="Cryptomus Wallet" width="1302" height="686" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/wallet.png 1302w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/wallet-300x158.png 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/wallet-768x405.png 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/wallet-50x26.png 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/wallet-150x79.png 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/wallet-450x237.png 450w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/wallet-1200x632.png 1200w" sizes="(max-width: 1302px) 100vw, 1302px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-104405" class="wp-caption-text">Cryptomus Wallet</figcaption></figure>
<h3>Beneficial P2P exchange.</h3>
<p>In addition to centralized exchange, users can experience the advantages of a P2P. Cryptomus <a href="https://p2p.cryptomus.com/?utm_source=blockonomi&amp;utm_medium=review&amp;utm_campaign=16-10">P2P exchange</a>  provides crypto traders with reliability and transparency, involving a great variety of ads and trustful buyers and sellers. Just select the ad suitable to your conditions, contact the seller or buyer, and make a deal in just a few clicks. A low commission of 0.1% will be a nice bonus.</p>
<h3>Staking with Rewards Up to 20% APR.</h3>
<p>Ever wondered how to get passive income with cryptocurrency? With the Cryptomus staking option, it’s possible! Cryptomus exchange provides users with impressive staking terms that significantly increase the benefits.</p>
<figure id="attachment_104404" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-104404" style="width: 1345px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-104404" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/staking.png" alt="crypto staking in Cryptomus wallet" width="1345" height="561" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/staking.png 1345w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/staking-300x125.png 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/staking-768x320.png 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/staking-50x21.png 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/staking-150x63.png 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/staking-450x188.png 450w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/staking-1200x501.png 1200w" sizes="(max-width: 1345px) 100vw, 1345px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-104404" class="wp-caption-text">crypto staking in Cryptomus wallet</figcaption></figure>
<p>Traders can stake the most popular crypto, such as BNB, TRX, ETH, USDT, etc., and get valuable bonuses. Particularly, it’s available to stake TRX with up to <a href="https://cryptomus.com/staking?utm_source=blockonomi&amp;utm_medium=review&amp;utm_campaign=16-10">20% APR</a></p>
<h3>White Label Gateway.</h3>
<p>Interacting with digital assets on Cryptomus, traders are able to start cryptocurrency acceptance with their own branding. It’ll be very relevant, especially for those who are interested in business positioning since <a href="https://cryptomus.com/white_label?utm_source=blockonomi&amp;utm_medium=review&amp;utm_campaign=16-10">White Label</a> solution allows merchants to maintain the identity of the company while using third-party services.</p>
<figure id="attachment_104403" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-104403" style="width: 1251px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-104403" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/whitelabel.png" alt="White Label Crypto Payment Gateway" width="1251" height="642" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/whitelabel.png 1251w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/whitelabel-300x154.png 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/whitelabel-768x394.png 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/whitelabel-50x26.png 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/whitelabel-150x77.png 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/whitelabel-450x231.png 450w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/whitelabel-1200x616.png 1200w" sizes="(max-width: 1251px) 100vw, 1251px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-104403" class="wp-caption-text">White Label Crypto Payment Gateway</figcaption></figure>
<p>Also, it will be useful for newcomers to the business who want to quickly launch their own cryptocurrency product without having to develop it from scratch. Easily change the style and design of your gateway itself while the transaction fee remains unchanged, from 0.4%</p>
<hr />
<h2>Conclusion</h2>
<p>Cryptomus is a reliable, impressive, and transparent trading platform, representing a balanced combination of multi-functionality, understandable navigation, and affordable working terms. Due to its variety of popular coins to trade, responsive support service, acceptable fees, high speed, and a diversity of additional trading tools, this exchange is a universal option both for regular cryptocurrency operations and business deals.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/cryptomus-review/">Cryptomus Review: The Cryptocurrency Exchange You Can Rely On</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">104399</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Kraken Introduces Ethereum Restaking Feature Using EigenLayer Protocol</title>
		<link>https://blockonomi.com/kraken-introduces-ethereum-restaking-feature-using-eigenlayer-protocol/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Oliver Dale]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 08:54:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[DeFi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchanges]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blockonomi.com/?p=104286</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>TLDR: Kraken launched Ethereum restaking via EigenLayer for non-U.S. customers Restaking allows users to earn additional rewards on already staked ETH Kraken subsidiary Staked will act as the validator for restaked ETH Total value locked in liquid restaking tokens has grown over 3000% this year EigenLayer&#8217;s EIGEN token recently unlocked for trading at a $6.7 [...]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/kraken-introduces-ethereum-restaking-feature-using-eigenlayer-protocol/">Kraken Introduces Ethereum Restaking Feature Using EigenLayer Protocol</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>TLDR:</h2>
<ul>
<li>Kraken launched Ethereum restaking via EigenLayer for non-U.S. customers</li>
<li>Restaking allows users to earn additional rewards on already staked ETH</li>
<li>Kraken subsidiary Staked will act as the validator for restaked ETH</li>
<li>Total value locked in liquid restaking tokens has grown over 3000% this year</li>
<li>EigenLayer&#8217;s EIGEN token recently unlocked for trading at a $6.7 billion valuation</li>
</ul>
<hr />
<p>Kraken, a leading cryptocurrency exchange, <a href="https://blog.kraken.com/product/staking/eth-restaking">has announced the launch of Ethereum restaking via the EigenLayer protocol</a> for its non-U.S. customers.</p>
<p>This new feature allows users to earn additional rewards on their already staked Ethereum (ETH) by participating in the security of decentralized applications (dApps) built on the EigenLayer network.</p>
<p>Restaking is a process that enables users to extend the utility of their staked assets by providing security to multiple protocols without unstaking them from the original blockchain. This innovative approach allows investors to potentially increase their overall yield while contributing to the broader ecosystem&#8217;s security.</p>
<p>The introduction of restaking on Kraken comes at a time of significant growth in the sector. According to data from DefiLlama, the total value locked in liquid restaking tokens has experienced a remarkable surge of over 3000% this year, reaching approximately $11 billion. This rapid expansion highlights the increasing interest and adoption of restaking among cryptocurrency investors.</p>
<p>Kraken&#8217;s restaking feature aims to simplify the process for its users, making it more accessible to a wider range of clients. Mark Greenberg, Kraken&#8217;s global head of asset growth, stated that the integration &#8220;significantly lowers&#8221; investors&#8217; barriers to entry, as most crypto users are already familiar with centralized exchanges.</p>
<p>To implement this new offering, Kraken has partnered with its subsidiary, Staked, which will serve as the validator for ETH restaked through the exchange. Staked is a prominent EigenLayer operator, typically catering to institutional clients. This collaboration allows Kraken to leverage Staked&#8217;s expertise in the restaking space.</p>
<p>Users participating in restaking through Kraken will have the option to hold their rewards on the exchange or trade them for fiat currency or other cryptocurrencies. This flexibility provides investors with various options for managing their earnings.</p>
<p>It&#8217;s important to note that while the restaking feature is available in many parts of Europe, it is not accessible to customers in the United States and other jurisdictions where &#8220;geographic restrictions apply,&#8221; according to Kraken.</p>
<p>The launch of Ethereum restaking on Kraken coincides with recent developments in the EigenLayer ecosystem.<a href="https://blockonomi.com/eigenlayer-launches-eigen-token-market-valuation-and-exchange-listings/"> The protocol&#8217;s native token, EIGEN,</a> was recently unlocked for trading, nearly five months <a href="https://blockonomi.com/eigenlayers-eigen-token-airdrop-sparks-controversy-among-users/">after the initial airdrop to early users.</a></p>
<p>The Eigen Foundation announced that the token would be unlocked on September 30, 2024, with major exchanges like Binance listing it for trading in pairs with other cryptocurrencies, including Bitcoin and Tether.</p>
<p>Kraken&#8217;s implementation of restaking involves using staked ETH to secure various decentralized platforms, known as Actively Validated Services (AVSs).</p>
<p>By providing security to these dApps, users become eligible for additional rewards on top of their standard ETH staking rewards. These rewards are typically paid out in AVS tokens, which represent the dApps that the restaked ETH helps secure.</p>
<p>Restaking comes with some additional considerations. EigenLayer implements a minimum 7-day escrow period, in addition to the unbonding period required to unstake assets from the Ethereum network. This means that accessing restaked ETH may take longer compared to standard staking on Ethereum.</p>
<p>To participate in EigenLayer restaking through Kraken, users need a verified Kraken Pro account at the Intermediate level or above, ETH in their spot or staked balance, and residency outside prohibited geographies, <a href="https://moneycheck.com/best-crypto-casinos-usa/">such as the United States.</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/kraken-introduces-ethereum-restaking-feature-using-eigenlayer-protocol/">Kraken Introduces Ethereum Restaking Feature Using EigenLayer Protocol</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">104286</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Seized Ethereum from PlusToken Scheme Moves Towards Exchanges</title>
		<link>https://blockonomi.com/seized-ethereum-from-plustoken-scheme-moves-towards-exchanges/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Oliver Dale]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 10:49:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exchanges]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blockonomi.com/?p=104098</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>TLDR Up to $1.3 billion in Ethereum from PlusToken Ponzi scheme may soon be sold 7,000 ETH ($17.2 million) has already been sent to exchanges PlusToken operated in China from 2018-2019, attracting 2.6 million participants Chinese authorities seized various cryptocurrencies, including 1% of Bitcoin&#8217;s total supply Potential sale could increase selling pressure on Ethereum A [...]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/seized-ethereum-from-plustoken-scheme-moves-towards-exchanges/">Seized Ethereum from PlusToken Scheme Moves Towards Exchanges</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>TLDR</h2>
<ul>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Up to $1.3 billion in Ethereum from PlusToken Ponzi scheme may soon be sold</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">7,000 ETH ($17.2 million) has already been sent to exchanges</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">PlusToken operated in China from 2018-2019, attracting 2.6 million participants</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Chinese authorities seized various cryptocurrencies, including 1% of Bitcoin&#8217;s total supply</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Potential sale could increase selling pressure on Ethereum</li>
</ul>
<hr />
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">A significant amount of Ethereum, valued at up to $1.3 billion, <a href="https://decrypt.co/285873/ethereum-seized-plustoken-ponzi-hit-market">seized from the infamous PlusToken Ponzi scheme is reportedly on the verge of being sold on cryptocurrency exchanges. </a></p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">This development has caught the attention of market analysts and investors, as it could potentially impact Ethereum&#8217;s price and overall market dynamics.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">PlusToken, a fraudulent investment scheme that operated in China between 2018 and 2019, attracted approximately 2.6 million participants before authorities shut it down.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">During the crackdown, law enforcement agencies seized substantial amounts of various cryptocurrencies, including Ethereum, Bitcoin, and others.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">According to recent on-chain data analysis by OXT Research, some of these funds have already begun moving.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Pseudonymous analyst Free Samourai reported that about 7,000 ETH, worth around $17.2 million, has been transferred to cryptocurrency exchanges such as BitGet, Binance, and OKX. This movement suggests an intention to start selling the remaining tokens.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">In early August, the remnants of ETH seized from the multibillion dollar PlusToken scheme awoke on-chain for the first time since 2021.</p>
<p>Over the last 24h about 7k ETH of the remaining 542k ETH ($1.3b) was sent to exchanges indicating intent to begin selling the remaining tokens. <a href="https://t.co/tu2o7y4o4L">pic.twitter.com/tu2o7y4o4L</a></p>
<p>&mdash; ∴FreeSamourai∴ (@ErgoBTC) <a href="https://twitter.com/ErgoBTC/status/1844117289123410303?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">October 9, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The total amount of Ethereum seized from PlusToken and potentially available for sale is estimated at 542,000 ETH, valued at approximately $1.3 billion.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">This large sum has raised concerns about its potential impact on the market if sold.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Blockchain analytics firm AMLBot confirmed OXT Research&#8217;s findings through an independent investigation. An AMLBot representative noted that the remaining Ethereum was distributed across numerous wallets and began moving in August, eventually being consolidated into 294 separate addresses.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The movement of these funds comes after a period of dormancy. In early August, the <a href="https://moneycheck.com/best-ethereum-casinos/">Ethereum</a> assets seized from PlusToken showed on-chain activity for the first time since 2021.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">This awakening of previously static funds has drawn attention from market observers.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Calvin Ferreira, head of ecosystem and growth at Bitcoin layer-2 network BitcoinOS, commented on the potential market impact, stating,</p>
<blockquote>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">&#8220;Given that the total amount involved is about $1.3 billion, any significant liquidation could dramatically increase selling pressure, leading to a further drop in Ethereum&#8217;s price.&#8221;</p>
</blockquote>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Anmol Jain, head of investigations at AMLBot, echoed these concerns, suggesting that the movement could lead to increased sell pressure, worsen market sentiment, and potentially cause a liquidity decline.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">However, he also noted that the actual impact would depend on various factors, including the amount of ETH involved, the timing of the transfers, and the overall market context.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">It&#8217;s worth noting that the PlusToken case resulted in one of the largest cryptocurrency seizures to date.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Chinese police confiscated approximately 1% of Bitcoin&#8217;s total supply, along with significant amounts of other cryptocurrencies, including over 830,000 ETH, 1.4 million LTC, 27 million EOS, and others.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">In 2020, Chinese authorities prosecuted six PlusToken team members.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">A court document from that time revealed that the seized assets were transferred to Zhifan Technology Beijing for liquidation, with the intention of eventually distributing the funds to victims of the scheme.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">According to OXT Research, it is believed that the seized Bitcoin was sold on exchanges, and some of the Ethereum was liquidated, leaving the current 542,000 ETH remaining.</p>
<figure id="attachment_104067" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-104067" style="width: 847px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-104067" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/Screenshot-2024-10-14-at-09-25-19-Ethereum-Price-ETH-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko.png" alt="Ethereum Price on CoinGecko" width="847" height="627" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/Screenshot-2024-10-14-at-09-25-19-Ethereum-Price-ETH-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko.png 847w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/Screenshot-2024-10-14-at-09-25-19-Ethereum-Price-ETH-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko-300x222.png 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/Screenshot-2024-10-14-at-09-25-19-Ethereum-Price-ETH-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko-768x569.png 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/Screenshot-2024-10-14-at-09-25-19-Ethereum-Price-ETH-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko-50x37.png 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/Screenshot-2024-10-14-at-09-25-19-Ethereum-Price-ETH-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko-150x111.png 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/Screenshot-2024-10-14-at-09-25-19-Ethereum-Price-ETH-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko-450x333.png 450w" sizes="(max-width: 847px) 100vw, 847px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-104067" class="wp-caption-text">Ethereum Price on <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/ethereum">CoinGecko</a></figcaption></figure>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">As of the latest data, the price of Ethereum has shown a slight decline of 1.5% over the past day, trading at around $2,448. However, it remains relatively stable over the past week, according to data from <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/ethereum">CoinGecko.</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/seized-ethereum-from-plustoken-scheme-moves-towards-exchanges/">Seized Ethereum from PlusToken Scheme Moves Towards Exchanges</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">104098</post-id>	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
