<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	
	xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
	xmlns:geo="http://www.w3.org/2003/01/geo/wgs84_pos#"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Cryptocurrency Guides &amp; Information for Beginners from Blockonomi</title>
	<atom:link href="https://blockonomi.com/guides/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://blockonomi.com/guides/</link>
	<description>Cryptocurrency News &#38; Your Guide to the Blockchain Economy</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 10:26:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.7.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/fav-50x50.png</url>
	<title>Cryptocurrency Guides &amp; Information for Beginners from Blockonomi</title>
	<link>https://blockonomi.com/guides/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
<site xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">134176212</site>	<item>
		<title>CrossFi: Crypto Banking and Blockchain Solutions</title>
		<link>https://blockonomi.com/crossfi/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nicholas Say]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 10:26:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[DeFi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Guides]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blockonomi.com/?p=107123</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The global banking system, burdened by decades-old infrastructure, has struggled to keep pace with the demands of the digital age. Transactions in countries like the U.S. still take at least one business day to process due to reliance on outdated networks like ACH despite many countries and regions, as well as fintech apps, being able [...]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/crossfi/">CrossFi: Crypto Banking and Blockchain Solutions</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The global banking system, burdened by decades-old infrastructure, has struggled to keep pace with the demands of the digital age. Transactions in countries like the U.S. still take at least one business day to process due to reliance on outdated networks like ACH despite many countries and regions, as well as fintech apps, being able to offer instant transfers.</p>
<p><a href="https://crossfi.org/">CrossFi</a> was born from the mission to usher this transformation, bridging the traditional and digital financial worlds into one unified ecosystem with truly global capabilities.</p>
<p>By integrating the advantages of blockchain&#8217;s decentralization, security, and transparency with the reliability and familiarity of traditional banking, CrossFi delivers a platform designed for the modern age, empowering users to seamlessly transition between fiat and cryptocurrency.</p>
<p><img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-107138" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/site-1.jpg" alt="" width="1000" height="700" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/site-1.jpg 1000w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/site-1-300x210.jpg 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/site-1-768x538.jpg 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/site-1-50x35.jpg 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/site-1-150x105.jpg 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/site-1-450x315.jpg 450w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" /></p>
<p>Many banks continue to use programming languages such as COBOL, a relic of the mid-20th century, making system updates complex and costly. Meanwhile, their user-facing apps and web platforms often lack intuitive design and functionality, leaving customers dissatisfied in an era dominated by seamless digital experiences.</p>
<p>In contrast, fintech and open banking have redefined financial services, allowing them to experience rapid and sustained growth over the last few years.</p>
<p>Free from legacy constraints, these innovators leverage modern technologies to offer instant payments, global interoperability, and deep integration with digital ecosystems.</p>
<p>Solutions like real-time settlement, advanced API-based integrations, and tailored user experiences have positioned fintech as a more agile and consumer-friendly alternative to traditional banks. The only problem? They still rely on existing legacy financial structures, centralized networks, and local currencies.</p>
<p>The potential for programmable money and automated smart contracts unlocks a future where financial services are faster, more accessible, and more equitable.</p>
<p>Blockchain and crypto take this revolution further by fixing the limits that fintech and open banking still face today. By enabling decentralized, borderless, and transparent financial systems, they promise to eliminate intermediaries, reduce costs, and increase financial inclusion while offering truly global financial assets.</p>
<hr />
<h2>What is CrossFi?</h2>
<p>Founded in 2023, <a href="https://crossfi.org/about-us/">CrossFi is a decentralized financial ecosystem designed to bridge traditional banking with the world of cryptocurrency.</a> At its core, it offers a Layer 1 blockchain with modular architecture capable of delivering levels of interoperability, scalability, performance, and functionality not offered by any major blockchain network.</p>
<p>The CrossFi ecosystem is built to address inefficiencies in both traditional finance and decentralized finance (DeFi). It includes a non-custodial payment gateway that connects directly with Web3 wallets, enabling users to maintain control of their funds without relying on intermediaries. This approach ensures secure, transparent transactions and seamless integration of crypto and fiat currencies.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-107139" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/about.jpg" alt="" width="1000" height="700" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/about.jpg 1000w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/about-300x210.jpg 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/about-768x538.jpg 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/about-50x35.jpg 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/about-150x105.jpg 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/about-450x315.jpg 450w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" /></p>
<p>In addition to its blockchain, the CrossFi ecosystem encompasses a comprehensive suite of tools and services, such as its DeFi platform, digital asset mining and exchange platform, and an all-in-one banking app.</p>
<p>The ecosystem also includes a decentralized debit card, which allows users to spend cryptocurrencies directly from their wallets. To drive ecosystem development, the CrossFi Foundation supports innovation and growth within the network.</p>
<p>CrossFi’s first feature was launched in March of 2023 when the CrossFi chain went live, serving as the base of the ecosystem.</p>
<p>The project has reached multiple major milestones ever since, like being listed on major exchanges like MEXC Global and HTX, platforms like CoinMarketCap, running its own large-scale events in Vietnam, winning HTX’s Huobi Prime Vote 7 contest, launching the foundation, etc.</p>
<p>Over these years, CrossFi has also established partners with projects like Beatland, Uniswap, PancakeSwap, Metamask, Gnome Finance, and many more.</p>
<hr />
<h2>CrossFi’s Features</h2>
<p>The CrossFi ecosystem combines cutting-edge blockchain technology with practical tools to create a bridge between traditional and decentralized financial systems. By combining both web3 and traditional technologies, CrossFi is easily accessible to users who might be new to crypto while remaining valuable for long-time crypto veterans.</p>
<h3>CrossFi Chain</h3>
<p><a href="https://crossfi.org/blockchain/">CrossFi Chain</a> is a Layer 1 blockchain built for scalability and interoperability. Its modular architecture integrates Cosmos and Ethereum Virtual Machine (EVM), enabling the chain to achieve up to 1 million operations per second. This unprecedented capacity allows for seamless integration across networks, supporting developers with intuitive tools and offering users a reliable, high-performance environment for financial interactions.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-107141" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/chain.jpg" alt="" width="1000" height="700" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/chain.jpg 1000w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/chain-300x210.jpg 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/chain-768x538.jpg 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/chain-50x35.jpg 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/chain-150x105.jpg 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/chain-450x315.jpg 450w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" /></p>
<p>Both Cosmos and Ethereum play different roles in the CrossFi chain. Whereas Cosmos is responsible for reaching consensus, coin emission, and the production, verification, and transaction of blocks, Ethereum’s Virtual Machine handles the smart contracts, and deployment of dApps, and ensures full EVM compatibility.</p>
<p>The result is the use of a Delegated Proof of Stake consensus protocol which block time can be reduced to as little as 1 second, allowing the network to process up to 100 operations per transaction and 10,000 transactions per second. All of this with a basic transaction fee to the user of only $0.02 per transaction.</p>
<h3>CrossFi APP</h3>
<p><a href="https://crossfi.org/web3-bank/">The CrossFi APP</a> serves as a comprehensive Web3 banking solution that combines fiat and cryptocurrency functionalities.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-107142" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/app.jpg" alt="" width="1000" height="700" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/app.jpg 1000w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/app-300x210.jpg 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/app-768x538.jpg 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/app-50x35.jpg 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/app-150x105.jpg 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/app-450x315.jpg 450w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" /></p>
<p>Through this platform, users can access the VISA network via the CrossFi Card for non-custodial payments, execute cross-border transfers through SWIFT and IBAN, and manage peer-to-peer transfers by card number. The app’s multi-currency card feature, paired with competitive currency exchange rates, simplifies global transactions.</p>
<h3>CrossFi xAPP</h3>
<p>Designed for DeFi enthusiasts and newcomers alike, <a href="https://crossfi.org/xapp/">the CrossFi xAPP</a> expands the ecosystem with tools for advanced decentralized finance operations.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-107143" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/defi.jpg" alt="" width="1000" height="700" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/defi.jpg 1000w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/defi-300x210.jpg 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/defi-768x538.jpg 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/defi-50x35.jpg 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/defi-150x105.jpg 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/defi-450x315.jpg 450w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" /></p>
<p>Users can explore investment strategies, acquire native CrossFi assets like XFI and XUSD, and engage with liquidity pools through the CrossFi Automated Market Maker (AMM). Other features include currency swapping, bridge functionality, staking, rewards, escrows, and more.</p>
<h3>CrossFi Foundation</h3>
<p><a href="https://xfi.foundation/">The CrossFi Foundation</a> powers the ecosystem’s growth through innovation and community engagement. This self-regulating non-profit organization supports development by funding grants such as its $50 million grant program, hosting hackathons, and facilitating the integration of new projects.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-107144" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/foundation.jpg" alt="" width="1000" height="700" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/foundation.jpg 1000w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/foundation-300x210.jpg 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/foundation-768x538.jpg 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/foundation-50x35.jpg 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/foundation-150x105.jpg 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/foundation-450x315.jpg 450w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" /></p>
<p>With campaigns aimed at user acquisition and influencer collaboration, the foundation strengthens CrossFi’s mission to revolutionize financial services by bringing new key players and products to the ecosystem.</p>
<hr />
<h2>The Team</h2>
<p>The CrossFi team is made up of professionals with solid expertise across various sectors, from blockchain to traditional finance, ensuring that the project benefits from a wealth of experience and knowledge.</p>
<p>The leadership, for instance, includes experts like Alexander Mamasidikov, a recognized figure in the blockchain and digital marketing space, who’s been behind numerous successful international projects and currently serves as the CEO and Chief Ideologist of the project.</p>
<p>Alexander is joined by Chief Growth Officer Philip Alexeev, who brings a wealth of experience in growth strategy from top Web3 projects like Binance and Decentraland, playing a crucial role in CrossFi&#8217;s expansion. Additionally, Christina Sidfeldt Welin serves as CEO in Hong Kong, adding a strong foundation of governance and compliance to ensure CrossFi adheres to the highest standards across global markets.</p>
<p>What sets CrossFi apart is not only its leadership but also its partnerships with some of the biggest names in the industry. Collaborations with projects like Beatland, Uniswap, PancakeSwap, and Metamask provide CrossFi with a strong foundation in DeFi and blockchain ecosystems, further solidifying its reputation as an innovative, reliable player in the market.</p>
<hr />
<h2>Conclusion</h2>
<p>For years, the evolution of financial services has been promised but slow to materialize. Despite numerous discussions around modernization, it has taken far too long for these changes to come to fruition. CrossFi is breaking the walls between traditional finance and the finance that prevented this modernization by addressing the core inefficiencies that plague existing banking systems.</p>
<p>By merging decentralized finance and established banking solutions, CrossFi aims to provide a modern platform for users to fluidly navigate between fiat and cryptocurrencies. It tackles the critical issues of slow, costly transactions by implementing a blockchain’s top scalability, reliability, and low transaction fee capabilities.</p>
<p>The ecosystem enables users to enjoy fluid integration with Web3 wallets, non-custodial payments via its Visa-connected card, and advanced DeFi functionalities like liquidity pools and staking, all while staying compliant with global standards.</p>
<p><a href="https://crossfi.org/">CrossFi’s</a> innovative approach fills that gap, paving the way for the transformation that the financial world and, most importantly, its users, have been waiting for.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/crossfi/">CrossFi: Crypto Banking and Blockchain Solutions</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">107123</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>My Neighbor Alice: Bridging Traditional Gaming &#038; Web3 Through Cozy Island Building</title>
		<link>https://blockonomi.com/my-neighbor-alice/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nicholas Say]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 10:37:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Gaming]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Guides]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blockonomi.com/?p=106755</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ever since Pong was released in 1972 and changed the world, Gaming has evolved into one of the world’s largest entertainment industries, surpassing even film and music in revenue. This growth has been propelled by the increasing accessibility of games and their ability to appeal to diverse audiences. Titles like Stardew Valley and Animal Crossing [...]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/my-neighbor-alice/">My Neighbor Alice: Bridging Traditional Gaming &#038; Web3 Through Cozy Island Building</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ever since Pong was released in 1972 and changed the world, Gaming has evolved into one of the world’s largest entertainment industries, surpassing even <a href="https://www.forbes.com/councils/forbesagencycouncil/2023/11/17/the-gaming-industry-a-behemoth-with-unprecedented-global-reach/">film and music</a> in revenue. This growth has been propelled by the increasing accessibility of games and their ability to appeal to diverse audiences.</p>
<p>Titles like Stardew Valley and Animal Crossing have been instrumental in this shift, offering experiences that emphasize relaxation, creativity, and social interaction.</p>
<p>These games have demonstrated that gaming can be a space for hardcore and casual players alike by focusing on fun and creativity rather than complex mechanics or intense competition. This inclusivity has helped break down barriers and build a sense of community among players.</p>
<p>The success of these games has highlighted a growing demand for non-competitive experiences, allowing players to engage in open-ended gameplay at their own pace.</p>
<p>Unlike traditional competitive titles such as League of Legends or Dark Souls, these games invite players to explore, create, and socialize without the pressure of high-stakes competition or difficult mechanics. This shift has opened new possibilities for game developers to reach a broader audience across all demographics, focusing on narrative and creativity rather than just action or skill-based challenges.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.myneighboralice.com/">My Neighbor Alice</a> is one of the web3 games taking this approach to bring new gamers to the blockchain space, a realm often seen as intimidating or complex for new players (or as gamers would put it, “Noobs”).</p>
<p>By combining the charm of cozy games with Web3 technology, it offers a non-intrusive way for players to experience blockchain features, like NFTs, while enjoying a casual yet complex and fun game. In doing so, My Neighbor Alice is set to introduce millions of players to the potential of blockchain gaming, just as Stardew Valley and Animal Crossing did for mainstream gaming.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-106899" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/game.jpg" alt="" width="1000" height="700" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/game.jpg 1000w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/game-300x210.jpg 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/game-768x538.jpg 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/game-50x35.jpg 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/game-150x105.jpg 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/game-450x315.jpg 450w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" /></p>
<hr />
<h2>What Is My Neighbor Alice All About?</h2>
<p><a href="https://www.myneighboralice.com/features">My Neighbor Alice describes itself as a multiplayer builder game</a> where players get to own their very own virtual islands, customizing them to their heart&#8217;s desire while inviting and visiting other players in the process. If you are a gamer and this sounds familiar, it is because the game was inspired by Animal Crossing itself, one of the most popular franchises ever created by Nintendo.</p>
<p>By combining a familiar genre with the many benefits of decentralization and digital assets, My Neighbor Alice gets to add an element that its traditional counterparts don’t offer: true ownership. Whereas games like Animal Crossing and Stardew Valley result in all of the hard work being “lost” once the player fulfills their objectives, game support ends, files get corrupted, etc, this is not the case with My Neighbor Alice.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-106900" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/map.jpg" alt="" width="1000" height="700" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/map.jpg 1000w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/map-300x210.jpg 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/map-768x538.jpg 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/map-50x35.jpg 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/map-150x105.jpg 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/map-450x315.jpg 450w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" /></p>
<p>By using NFTs, the game allows players to interact with the world in a whole new different way, transferring ownership in any way they want and unlocking interesting features that traditional in-game assets just don’t possess. This also allows players to, in the team’s words, “exercise power over the platform” through democratic governance. This means not only players get to exercise their creativity over their own islands but all over the virtual world.</p>
<p>Effectively, My Neighbor Alice is an online video game that can be played as a solo or multiplayer adventure, combining an exciting storyline experience most web3 games don’t possess and the creative freedom of a sandbox experience.</p>
<hr />
<h2>Features and Ecosystem</h2>
<p>Bringing blockchain and DeFi capabilities to the world of video games means that My Neighbor Alice has much more to offer than a satisfying gaming experience. In-game assets, virtual land, a decentralized marketplace, trading features, and decentralized governance all come together to create a world in which players are right at the center. Let’s take a look.</p>
<h3><strong>Decentralized Marketplace</strong></h3>
<p>With NFTs being a major pillar of My Neighbor Alice, it is not surprising that its marketplace plays one of the most important roles. However, while marketplaces in other games allow players to buy assets directly from the developers or with an infinite supply, this marketplace operates more similarly to those in the crypto world.</p>
<p><a href="https://play.myneighboralice.com/">My Neighbor Alice’s marketplace</a> is all about letting players buy and sell assets by directly interacting with other players.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-106901" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/marketplace.jpg" alt="" width="1000" height="700" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/marketplace.jpg 1000w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/marketplace-300x210.jpg 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/marketplace-768x538.jpg 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/marketplace-50x35.jpg 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/marketplace-150x105.jpg 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/marketplace-450x315.jpg 450w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" /></p>
<p>Most of these assets have some level of scarcity to them in the sense that they are not generated through infinite in-game faucets. This gives these assets an innate value that goes beyond their appearance, similar to the way that popular blockchain projects like Bored Yacht Ape Club have popularized.</p>
<h3><strong>Lummelunda Archipielago</strong></h3>
<p>Lummelunda Archipelago is the name of the world in which My Neighbor Alice’s titular Alice lives and players get to create. Divided into 6 islands with their own style and ecosystem, players will be able to buy virtual plots from Alice or other players in the marketplace, plots which will transform into something completely unique.</p>
<p>This is the virtual world players get to interact with and share, being the scenario for their very own stories. Players also get to interact with different Non-Player Characters like Alice, Björn the Bear, Beekeeper Bob, Ivan the Merchant, and Shipwright José. These neighbors will provide players with a plethora of content and directions, making the gaming experience much more rewarding and interactive.</p>
<h3><strong>Player Avatars and In-Game Assets</strong></h3>
<p>Identity plays a key role in My Neighbor Alice, and players are represented by customizable avatars that can be shaped in numerous ways. These avatars serve as the player’s identity within the game world, visible to others as they explore and socialize.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-106903" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/assets.jpg" alt="" width="1000" height="700" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/assets.jpg 1000w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/assets-300x210.jpg 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/assets-768x538.jpg 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/assets-50x35.jpg 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/assets-150x105.jpg 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/assets-450x315.jpg 450w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" /></p>
<p>In addition to avatars, players can acquire in-game assets such as houses, animals, decorations, and cosmetic items, all of which can be bought and sold in the marketplace.</p>
<p>Players can also use the NFT creator tool to design their own assets and monetize their creations, opening up new opportunities for creativity and entrepreneurship.</p>
<h3><strong>Progression System</strong></h3>
<p>One of the defining factors of sandbox games is that there is no predefined objective. This, while alluring to many players, can make it difficult for some players to get into the games as they lose focus along the way or are overwhelmed by the sheer freedom. Without clear goals, some may lose focus or feel discouraged, unsure of where to start or what to pursue next.</p>
<p>My Neighbor Alices has a progression system that manages to keep objective-oriented players engaged by providing feedback and general guidance, all without sacrificing player freedom. Players also get rewarded for completing these quests, and even for being recognized as “good citizens”, further developing the social aspect of the game.</p>
<hr />
<h2>The ALICE Token</h2>
<p>The ALICE token is the main currency in My Neighbor Alice, both serving as an in-game asset and as an ERC20 token. With a fixed supply, the token allows holders to engage in various aspects of the game, from purchasing assets and land to participating in governance and DeFi opportunities.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-106906" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/alice.jpg" alt="" width="1000" height="614" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/alice.jpg 1000w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/alice-300x184.jpg 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/alice-768x472.jpg 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/alice-50x31.jpg 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/alice-150x92.jpg 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/alice-450x276.jpg 450w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" /></p>
<p>In addition to its in-game utility, the ALICE token supports decentralized finance (DeFi) features. Token holders can stake ALICE to earn rewards, participate in governance by voting on platform developments, and influence key decisions in the virtual world. This integration of DeFi allows players to earn passive income, control in-game developments, and drive the game&#8217;s evolution.</p>
<hr />
<h2>The Team Behind the Curtain</h2>
<p>The development of My Neighbor Alice is backed by a strong team, with Chromia, a decentralized public blockchain, playing a critical role in the game’s infrastructure.</p>
<p>Chromia started and maintained by ChromaWay, is designed to offer blockchain scalability and ease of use for both developers and users. Its architecture combines relational databases with blockchain technology, making it an ideal solution for complex game designs, particularly those that involve dynamic, on-chain logic.</p>
<p>The game’s investors include names like NGC Ventures, The Sandbox, The Blockchain Game Alliance, Binance Labs, Ankr, Maker, and more. The team has also established important partnerships with brands like Elle, bringing even more customization and value to its players.</p>
<hr />
<h2>Conclusion</h2>
<p><a href="https://www.myneighboralice.com/">My Neighbor Alice</a> is a prime example of how gaming can evolve by embracing both creativity and the growing potential of blockchain technology.</p>
<p>By combining the charm of familiar sandbox games like Animal Crossing with decentralized features such as NFTs and DeFi, it offers players more than just a traditional gaming experience. Players not only get to create and own their virtual world but can also engage with a broader ecosystem that includes decentralized marketplaces, governance, and a progression system that rewards their efforts.</p>
<p>With gaming continuing to grow and solidify its position as a dominating industry, titles like My Neighbor Alice are just what web3 needs to go mainstream. By offering a seamless entry into the world of NFTs, DeFi, and virtual ownership, it is paving the way for the future of gaming to be more inclusive, innovative, and player-driven. Also, it is extremely fun!</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/my-neighbor-alice/">My Neighbor Alice: Bridging Traditional Gaming &#038; Web3 Through Cozy Island Building</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">106755</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Synesis One: Transforming AI Data Sourcing and Monetization</title>
		<link>https://blockonomi.com/synesis-one/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nicholas Say]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 10:00:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blockonomi.com/?p=106749</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The rapid rise of artificial intelligence has brought with it an uncomfortable truth that many would rather ignore: our AI models are only as good as the data they&#8217;re trained on. For some, like the lawyers who found himself facing sanctions after submitting completely fabricated court cases to a federal judge after blindly trusting ChatGPT, [...]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/synesis-one/">Synesis One: Transforming AI Data Sourcing and Monetization</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The rapid rise of artificial intelligence has brought with it an uncomfortable truth that many would rather ignore: our AI models are only as good as the data they&#8217;re trained on.</p>
<p>For some, like the lawyers who found himself facing sanctions after submitting completely fabricated court cases to a federal judge after <a href="https://www.reuters.com/legal/new-york-lawyers-sanctioned-using-fake-chatgpt-cases-legal-brief-2023-06-22/">blindly trusting</a> ChatGPT, this reality has come crashing down. The incident highlighted that the &#8220;garbage in, garbage out&#8221; principle was becoming a serious problem, something that industry insiders had known for yearsAI&#8217;s</p>
<p>This issue has only become more evident as enterprise adoption increases and powerful corporations continue to push their AI models to the world. Google&#8217;s Gemini made headlines when it generated historically inaccurate images, while ChatGPT has repeatedly been caught fabricating scientific papers, quotes, and statistics.</p>
<p>These aren&#8217;t just embarrassing mishaps but symptoms of a deeper problem: the questionable quality of training data being fed into these increasingly powerful models.</p>
<p>Today, most AI systems are trained on data scraped from the internet, including content farms, questionable databases, and often copyrighted material which has led to huge lawsuits.</p>
<p>Whereas many of these data sources have questionable credibility, others are controlled by a handful of tech giants with little transparency or accountability. This centralized approach to data collection has created a precarious situation where mistakes can cascade through systems that millions now rely on daily.</p>
<p>This is where <a href="https://www.synesis.one/">Synesis One</a> comes in.</p>
<p>By leveraging blockchain technology and Web3 principles, this platform aims to revolutionize how AI training data is sourced and validated. Unlike traditional data marketplaces, Synesis One operates as a decentralized crowdsourcing platform where expert contributors can earn $SNS tokens for completing micro-tasks that directly train AI models.</p>
<p>The result?</p>
<p>A transparent, accountable system that not only improves data quality but also ensures fair compensation for those helping to build the future of artificial intelligence.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-106894" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/site.jpg" alt="" width="1000" height="700" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/site.jpg 1000w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/site-300x210.jpg 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/site-768x538.jpg 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/site-50x35.jpg 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/site-150x105.jpg 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/site-450x315.jpg 450w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" /></p>
<hr />
<h2>What is Synesis One?</h2>
<p>While Synesis One&#8217;s success largely stems from its innovative approach to data crowdsourcing and validation, the ecosystem powering is what makes this truly unique and possible. At its core, Synesis One operates as a Web3 data utility and NFT marketplace built on the symbiosis of two main components: SynesisDAO and Kanon Exchange.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.synesis.one/overview">SynesisDAO</a> serves as the backbone of the platform, operating as a decentralized autonomous organization where contributors, data traders, and consumers come together around ontologies. The DAO&#8217;s primary function is to crowdsource ontologies in natural language format, which are then immutably stored as a permissionless public data utility, securing their authenticity, traceability, and accessibility.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.kanon.synesis.one/">The second pillar of the ecosystem is Kanon Exchange</a>, a specialized NFT marketplace where users can trade unique ontology primitives known as Kanons.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-106895" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/kanon.jpg" alt="" width="1000" height="700" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/kanon.jpg 1000w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/kanon-300x210.jpg 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/kanon-768x538.jpg 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/kanon-50x35.jpg 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/kanon-150x105.jpg 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/kanon-450x315.jpg 450w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" /></p>
<p>These are particularly interesting because of their ability to be used as collateral and converted into DeFi assets, opening up possibilities for lending, borrowing, insurance, and other sophisticated financial operations. In a world where data is often called &#8220;the new oil&#8221; yet those producing it see little benefit, Kanons finally gives data its true value by making it a tradeable, verifiable asset that directly rewards its creators.</p>
<p>Technologically, Synesis One has taken a pragmatic approach to blockchain integration. The platform&#8217;s initial deployment (V1) runs on the Solana blockchain, chosen specifically for its low gas costs and high performance.</p>
<p>This choice ensures that the ecosystem’s three key stakeholder groups can interact seamlessly, without the prohibitive transaction fees that are often associated with other blockchains. The stakeholders are the Contributors who mine ontologies for rewards, Traders who participate in the marketplace, and Consumers who utilize the AI training data.</p>
<p>This tripartite structure ensures that each participant has a clear role and incentive within the ecosystem, creating a self-sustaining cycle of data generation, validation, and utilization.</p>
<p>Once the Synesis Onie team implements its plans for cross-chain expansion, all of these elements will come together to further ensure that the platform can scale effectively as the adoption of AI and Blockchain technologies grows.</p>
<hr />
<h2>The Technology Behind Synesis One</h2>
<p>Synesis One&#8217;s architecture combines cutting-edge blockchain technology with a focus on scalability and user efficiency. The ecosystem is designed in such a way that anyone with the necessary expertise can provide data to train models with no knowledge of web3 programming or blockchain while being rewarded. <a href="https://www.train.synesis.one/">Synesis has called this approach Train2Earn,</a> which promises to become a driving force in AI development in the near future.</p>
<h3>Ontology Mining Framework</h3>
<p>Synesis One organizes ontology mining into distinct roles: Builders, Validators, and Architects. Builders generate domain-specific datasets, Validators ensure compliance and accuracy, and Architects curate and manage the integration of ontologies for AI systems. This structured workflow establishes a high standard of quality control, enabling AI models to access validated, application-specific data.</p>
<h3>Kanon as NFTs</h3>
<p>After being generated and validated, Ontologies are converted into unique, blockchain-registered digital assets termed Kanons. Beyond their function as data units, Kanons are designed for financial integration. They can be traded, fractionalized into fungible tokens through Atomic Splits, or leveraged as collateral in decentralized financial operations. These mechanisms ensure the monetization of data is both practical and transparent.</p>
<h3>Blockchain and Interoperability</h3>
<p>Synesis One’s decision to build on Solana was not merely a choice of convenience but a strategic alignment with the platform’s goals for scalability, accessibility, and cost efficiency. Solana’s high transaction throughput and low fees create a conducive environment for frequent interactions, whether minting NFTs, validating data, or distributing rewards.</p>
<p>This ensures that contributors, regardless of scale or frequency of activity, can participate without incurring prohibitive costs&#8230; a common barrier in many blockchain ecosystems.</p>
<p>However, the Synesis One team recognizes the limitations of relying on a single blockchain. As such, the roadmap includes cross-chain expansion to enhance flexibility, interoperability, and resilience. Cross-chain functionality will enable the platform to integrate with complementary ecosystems, facilitating interoperability with other blockchains and AI ecosystems.</p>
<h3>Synesis Relevance Index (SRI)</h3>
<p>The Synesis Relevance Index (SRI) is a dynamic ranking system that serves as a cornerstone for how Synesis One evaluates and rewards contributions. By analyzing the frequency and context of keyword usage within the platform, SRI offers a real-time snapshot of demand trends for specific ontologies.</p>
<p>This system not only ensures the relevance and utility of the ontologies but also provides contributors with actionable insights to maximize their impact while also balancing the supply and demand for Ontologies.</p>
<p>Each Kanon, representing a unique ontology primitive<a href="https://jup.ag/swap/USDC-SNS">, entitles its holder to claim network rewards in $SNS tokens.</a> The total claimable amount during each distribution period is determined by the Synesis Relevancy Index Score (SRIS), which measures the usage and importance of a specific ontology.</p>
<hr />
<h2>The Synesis One Team</h2>
<p>The Synesis One team reflects the very ethos of the platform: bringing together experts from diverse fields to shape the future of decentralized AI. With backgrounds spanning AI, blockchain, healthcare, and entrepreneurship, the team’s collective experience mirrors the platform’s interdisciplinary approach.</p>
<p>Joshua Hong, Co-Founder and CSO, is a serial entrepreneur and venture capitalist whose experience spans technology consulting at Accenture and leadership in transformative educational programs like YPO’s Singularity University Seminar.</p>
<p>Co-Founder Paul Lee brings a unique blend of scientific rigor and entrepreneurial acumen as a clinician, AI founder, and Oxford-trained biochemist. Their combined leadership ensures a balance of visionary strategy and technical grounding.</p>
<p>CEO Isaac Bang, a seasoned technologist, bridges blockchain, AI, and gaming, having led NFT product development at IMVU. His expertise aligns seamlessly with Synesis One’s mission to fuse innovation and accessibility.</p>
<p>Together, the team represents the very principles Synesis One champions: harnessing collective intelligence and diverse perspectives to build a decentralized platform capable of revolutionizing AI data ecosystems. This reflection of the platform’s ethos reinforces its capacity to lead the AI-driven Web3 transformation.</p>
<hr />
<h2>Conclusion</h2>
<p><a href="https://www.synesis.one/">Synesis One</a> represents a pivotal shift in how AI training data is sourced, validated, and monetized. By combining blockchain transparency with AI utility, the platform doesn&#8217;t just solve the pressing issues of data quality and compensation but creates an entirely new ecosystem where contributors are finally recognized and rewarded for their role in AI development.</p>
<p>Platforms like Synesis One become increasingly crucial in ensuring that the transition to an AI-driven world happens transparently and with fair compensation for all participants. Synesis One is leading the way to a world in which anyone can contribute to training the AI models of the future without the barriers of centralized control or lack of accountability.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/synesis-one/">Synesis One: Transforming AI Data Sourcing and Monetization</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">106749</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Pera: The Zero Trust Interoperability Platform for Creating Zero Trust Protocols (ZTPs)</title>
		<link>https://blockonomi.com/pera/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nicholas Say]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2024 09:17:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Guides]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blockonomi.com/?p=104366</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Pera has some new ideas about bringing the blockchain world together. People everywhere are waking up to the fact that blockchain is the future – and Pera makes it possible. As more blockchain developers and projects choose to focus on seamless interoperability, cross-chain bridges have become the Achilles&#8217; heel of the crypto ecosystem. In 2022 [...]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/pera/">Pera: The Zero Trust Interoperability Platform for Creating Zero Trust Protocols (ZTPs)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://pera.io/">Pera</a> has some new ideas about bringing the blockchain world together. People everywhere are waking up to the fact that blockchain is the future – and Pera makes it possible.</p>
<p>As more blockchain developers and projects choose to focus on seamless interoperability, cross-chain bridges have become the Achilles&#8217; heel of the crypto ecosystem. In 2022 alone, an estimated $2 billion was lost in 13 hacks and exploits involving these bridges.</p>
<p>While many approaches have been taken to solving these vulnerabilities, no definitive solution exists so far as the arms race continues.</p>
<p>This trend highlights a critical vulnerability in the current blockchain landscape. Cross-chain bridges, while essential for facilitating communication and asset transfer between different blockchain networks, have become prime targets for malicious actors. The reason is that these bridges often act as centralized points of failure, concentrating vast amounts of locked assets in smart contracts.</p>
<p>The ramifications of these deposits being compromised go beyond the catastrophic financial losses for users and projects alike.</p>
<p>Not only do they erode trust in the broader cryptocurrency ecosystem but they also deter individual users, institutional investors, and regulators from fully embracing blockchain technology. This makes projects like Pera, <a href="https://pera.io/blog/introducing-pera">formerly known as dWallet Network</a>, key players in the future growth of the blockchain ecosystem.</p>
<hr />
<h2>What is Pera?</h2>
<p>Pera describes itself as a “zero trust interoperability platform”, offering web3 and crypto projects and developers the chance to operate across multiple blockchain networks in a truly secure way.</p>
<p>This is achieved through Zero Trust Protocols (ZTPs) a new type of protocol that prioritizes the verification of every digital transaction, effectively “eliminating inherent trust”.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-large wp-image-104707" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/pera-1400x785.png" alt="" width="814" height="456" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/pera-1400x785.png 1400w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/pera-300x168.png 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/pera-768x431.png 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/pera-50x28.png 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/pera-150x84.png 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/pera-450x252.png 450w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/pera-1200x673.png 1200w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/pera.png 1459w" sizes="(max-width: 814px) 100vw, 814px" /></p>
<p><a href="https://docs.dwallet.io/">dWallet sits at the heart of Pera’s approach to interoperability</a>. This cross-chain wallet allows developers to build their own ZTPs to operate, offering cryptographic verification, non-custodial asset storage, and total control over their assets to their users.</p>
<p>According to Pera, not only does dWallet solve the old Sovereignty and Honeypot Problems but it is also highly compatible with other state-of-the-art web3 solutions.</p>
<p>dWallet is not a wallet app or interface but a type of infrastructure. This means they are meant for developers looking to build their own ZTPs. This makes Pera useful for applications like decentralized custody, native staking, native atomic swaps, native multi-chain lending, AI agents guardrails, and much more.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-104709" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/dwallet.png" alt="" width="1332" height="681" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/dwallet.png 1332w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/dwallet-300x153.png 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/dwallet-768x393.png 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/dwallet-50x26.png 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/dwallet-150x77.png 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/dwallet-450x230.png 450w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/dwallet-1200x614.png 1200w" sizes="(max-width: 1332px) 100vw, 1332px" /></p>
<hr />
<h2>What are ZTPs?</h2>
<p><a href="https://pera.io/blog/zero-trust-protocols-ztps">Zero Trust Protocols (ZTPs</a>) are what Pera is all about. They represent a fundamentally different approach to blockchain interoperability, which usually relies on solutions that require users to trust vulnerable methods like bridges or wrapped tokens. ZTPs seek to remove intermediaries altogether, bringing the “trustless” philosophy of cryptocurrency back to the ecosystem.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-104708" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/ztps.png" alt="" width="1027" height="835" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/ztps.png 1027w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/ztps-300x244.png 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/ztps-768x624.png 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/ztps-50x41.png 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/ztps-150x122.png 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/ztps-450x366.png 450w" sizes="(max-width: 1027px) 100vw, 1027px" /></p>
<p>At their core, ZTPs leverage sophisticated cryptography to ensure that every cross-chain interaction maintains the same security guarantees as native blockchain transactions. This is achieved through Pera&#8217;s innovative 2PC-MPC protocol, which requires both user participation and network verification for any (and every) operation.</p>
<p>In simpler terms, users don&#8217;t need to trust anyone but the math behind their transactions, just as they would if they were operating natively in each network involved in a transaction.</p>
<p>This means that with ZTPs, developers can build applications that were previously impossible. For example, projects can now let users stake native Bitcoin in their protocols, create truly trustless cross-chain lending platforms, or enable direct chain-to-chain interactions without relying on wrapped tokens or bridges.</p>
<p>This opens the door to a new generation of Web3 not limited by the security constraints that have plagued interoperable projects until now.</p>
<hr />
<h2>The Network Behind it All</h2>
<p>Pera&#8217;s infrastructure was originally built on a modified version of Sui&#8217;s blockchain. This was transformed into what the team called a &#8220;composable modular signature network&#8221; by removing smart contract capabilities and implementing their 2PC-MPC protocol. The result was a specialized network focused solely on secure cross-chain signing operations and powered by DWLT, its native token used for gas fees and authority delegation.</p>
<p>This approach allows Pera to achieve something unique in the blockchain space: true permissionless decentralization without sacrificing security or usability.</p>
<p>By requiring both user participation and network consensus for every operation, dWallet ensures that no single party, not even the network itself, can act maliciously. This makes it an ideal foundation for developers looking to build secure, cross-chain applications without compromising on Web3&#8217;s core principles.</p>
<p>The Alpha testnet release of Pera’s dWallet was made available to developers through its official GitHub, allowing anyone to audit the code to create a more secure platform. The alpha testnet could also be used for testing, providing developers with a sneak peak on its capabilities, which resulted in many important partnerships emerging.</p>
<hr />
<h2>A Budding Ecosystem</h2>
<p>Pera has established important partnerships over the past couple of months with the intent to increase their reach and capabilities. Some notorious names include L1 blockchain network Aptos, Espresso Marketplace, Secret Network, and modular blockchain solution Avail, as well as being integrated with Sui, Monad, and Celo.</p>
<p>Other notable partnerships include Big Brain Holdings, Digital Currency Group, Amplify, Zero Knowledge, Token Bay Capital, L2 Ventures, Insignius Capital, and Cerulean Ventures. In fact, many of these partners participated in dWallet Lab’s pre seed funding round, which saw 21 investors participate in the raising of over $5 million,</p>
<p>As part of its mission to make blockchain more interoperable, Pera also pays special attention to community building. The team regularly connects with its community through channels like Twitter, Discord, Telegram, Discourse, and Youtube, while also attending and speaking at events such as Encrypt Brussels, SecureFi Brussels, and Encrypt London.</p>
<hr />
<h2>Technical Capabilities</h2>
<p>Pera’s unique approach and proprietary technology allow it to operate at an efficiency few platforms can match. According to the team, Pera can process up to 10000 transactions per second (TPs) with sub-second latency.</p>
<p>This is much more efficient than major competitors, including top-notch blockchain networks like BNB, Polygon, Tron, and even Bitcoin. This allows the team to go as far as to claim to be “the fastest MPC solution in the web3 space”.</p>
<p>Pera can also scale to support up to thousands of signer nodes at any given time. Not only does this capability increase Pera’s performance but it also does so without compromising performance. This increase in security is only boosted by its zero-trust architecture, which eliminates single points of failure.</p>
<hr />
<h2>Conclusion</h2>
<p>Building upon the technical and ecosystem analysis, <a href="https://pera.io/">Pera’s approach and bet on ZTP</a> could very well be the turning point in blockchain&#8217;s evolution.</p>
<p>While previous interoperability solutions treated security as a feature to be balanced against convenience, Pera&#8217;s zero-trust approach fundamentally restructures this paradigm. By making security the foundational layer through its ZTPs, rather than an add-on, Pera could certainly reshape how developers approach cross-chain applications.</p>
<p>The platform&#8217;s ability to maintain high performance while scaling security through its distributed signing network suggests that the traditional trade-offs between security, decentralization, and scalability might be more flexible than previously thought.</p>
<p>An architectural breakthrough, combined with growing institutional backing and a rapidly expanding partnership network, positions Pera to potentially address the $2 billion elephant in the room: the persistent vulnerability of cross-chain bridges.</p>
<p>As blockchain technology continues to fight its way against security vulnerabilities, regulatory uncertainty, and fluctuating market cycles toward mainstream adoption, Pera&#8217;s innovation in trustless infrastructure could prove to be the missing piece that finally allows truly secure cross-chain applications to flourish.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/pera/">Pera: The Zero Trust Interoperability Platform for Creating Zero Trust Protocols (ZTPs)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">104366</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Orbitt: Revolutionizing Trading &#038; Project Development on Solana With AI</title>
		<link>https://blockonomi.com/orbitt/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nicholas Say]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 07:06:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blockonomi.com/?p=104010</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Navigating the cryptocurrency space can feel like walking through a minefield of complexity, volatility, and disinformation, especially in rapidly expanding ecosystems like the Solana blockchain. Both traders and developers face an uphill battle to keep up with the increasing number of projects and competition, which makes it difficult to reach the projects or investors they [...]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/orbitt/">Orbitt: Revolutionizing Trading &#038; Project Development on Solana With AI</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Navigating the cryptocurrency space can feel like walking through a minefield of complexity, volatility, and disinformation, especially in rapidly expanding ecosystems like the Solana blockchain.</p>
<p>Both traders and developers face an uphill battle to keep up with the increasing number of projects and competition, which makes it difficult to reach the projects or investors they are interested in.</p>
<p>With the pace of Solana innovation increasing by the day, these challenges are more apparent than ever. The lack of sophisticated, integrated tools tailored specifically for this high-speed environment leaves many participants feeling like they&#8217;re always a step behind, missing crucial opportunities or falling victim to market whiplash.</p>
<p>To developers, this means a lack of liquidity as their promising projects get lost in an inescapable noise. For traders, the absence of reliable analysis tools able to adapt to changing market conditions means that countless hours of “manual” analysis must be done regularly.</p>
<p>In a space in which decision paralysis, impulsive moves, FOMO, and lack of understanding can spell disaster, a better decision is needed.</p>
<p>AI-driven market analysis tools have emerged as one of the most promising solutions, bringing real-time analysis capabilities to a fragmented and often overwhelming market.</p>
<p><a href="https://orbitt.pro/en">One such tool is Orbitt</a>, a comprehensive ecosystem designed to revolutionize trading and project development on Solana through powerful and groundbreaking artificial intelligence (AI) analytics.</p>
<p>Let&#8217;s learn more about Orbitt!</p>
<hr />
<h2>What is Orbitt?</h2>
<p>Orbitt was created with the mission to democratize cryptocurrency by shedding its layers of complexity through AI, accessible design, and innovative blockchain solutions.</p>
<p>The ecosystem is formed by Orbitt PRO and Orbitt MM each designed to serve different segments of the crypto community in different ways.</p>
<p>Powered by the $ORBT token, Orbitt aims to become more than just another set of crypto tools in the ever-growing sea of blockchain-based solutions.</p>
<p>By bringing together the existing transparency, top-notch security, efficiency, scalability, and accessibility of the Solana network with unique AI-based capabilities, Orbitt seeks to empower traders and developers alike to create a vibrant community.</p>
<p>At this time, the Orbitt ecosystem is formed by two tools designed to serve different user bases: Orbitt Pro and Orbit MM.</p>
<p>These products, combined with the $ORBT token, allow traders and developers to gain important insights into the crypto market, amplifying project visibility, boosting trading volumes, offering access to innovative projects, and creating a collaborative community of like-minded crypto enthusiasts.</p>
<hr />
<h2>Orbitt Features</h2>
<h3>Orbitt PRO</h3>
<p><a href="https://orbitt.pro/en/chrome">Orbitt PRO stands at the center of the Orbitt ecosystem.</a> This AI-powered trading companion revolutionizes how traders interact with the cryptocurrency market by offering its users real-time analysis and insights based on their trading activities. Orbitt Pro seamlessly integrates into traders&#8217; existing workflows, using advanced machine learning algorithms trained on vast datasets of crypto market behavior to identify trends and patterns.</p>
<figure id="attachment_104265" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-104265" style="width: 1000px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-104265" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/10/pro.jpg" alt="Orbitt PRO Chrome Extension" width="1000" height="700" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/10/pro.jpg 1000w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/10/pro-300x210.jpg 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/10/pro-768x538.jpg 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/10/pro-50x35.jpg 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/10/pro-150x105.jpg 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/10/pro-450x315.jpg 450w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-104265" class="wp-caption-text">Orbitt PRO <a href="https://chromewebstore.google.com/detail/orbitt-pro-ai/gdflafpepcpbfijbpgkmncfjbkbleeel?hl=en&amp;authuser=0">Chrome Extension</a></figcaption></figure>
<p>Users can use prompts to interact with Orbitt PRO in the same way they do with major generative AI tools like ChatGPT Claude, making it accessible to virtually any trader. The use of readable language instead of complex charts and numbers also makes the information more easy to digest and learn from. Developed as a Chrome Extension. Orbitt PRO is accessible to users from major internet browsers like Google Chrome, Opera, Brave, and other Chromium-based browsers.</p>
<hr />
<h3>Orbitt MM</h3>
<p>The chances of success of any crypto project are only as high as its trading volume and liquidity allow. <a href="https://orbitt.pro/en/mm">Orbitt MM is designed to boost liquidity and trading volume</a> for Solana-based projects, using an innovative Telegram Bot to amplify project visibility. By helping projects reach their audiences and investors to find projects that suit their needs and strategies, Orbitt MM helps stakeholders connect more effectively.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-104267" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/10/mm.jpg" alt="" width="1000" height="700" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/10/mm.jpg 1000w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/10/mm-300x210.jpg 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/10/mm-768x538.jpg 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/10/mm-50x35.jpg 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/10/mm-150x105.jpg 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/10/mm-450x315.jpg 450w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" /></p>
<p>Orbitt MM offers different packages to blockchain projects, providing flexibility and effectiveness that suits their needs at any given time. These packages vary in duration, reach, volume gained, and other results. Projects can estimate the volume they stand to earn beforehand, helping them make the best decision to increase effectiveness.</p>
<h3>The $ORBT Token</h3>
<p>With a total supply of 20 million tokens, <a href="https://orbitt.pro/en/token">the $ORBT token</a> serves as the blood of the Orbitt Ecosystem by powering every transaction. A total of 19.9 million tokens exist, with 12.3 million being in circulation and gaining around 11.1% in value over the past week at the time of writing. A total of 7.7 million $ORBT tokens were vested and will be released over the next 2 years, helping manage supply.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-104266" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/10/token.jpg" alt="" width="1000" height="700" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/10/token.jpg 1000w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/10/token-300x210.jpg 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/10/token-768x538.jpg 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/10/token-50x35.jpg 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/10/token-150x105.jpg 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/10/token-450x315.jpg 450w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" /></p>
<p>The ORBT token is used to access all the advanced features of Orbitt PRO, participate in Orbitt MM, stake and receive rewards, and incentivize community engagement. The entirety of fees collected by the ecosystem will be used to reinvest in the ecosystem, with 50% going to ORBT buybacks and the remaining 50% creating volume.</p>
<p>The Orbitt team believes that this economic model will facilitate long-term sustainability, ensuring the rapid growth of the ecosystem and benefitting all parties. This is especially true when considering the efforts the team plans to make in terms of community engagement, which include the creation of educational content and resources, regular AMA sessions, a community rewards program, and beta testing.</p>
<hr />
<h2>Conclusion</h2>
<p>Orbitt represents a unique opportunity for the Solana network and blockchain ecosystem as a whole. By bringing together two of the most disruptive technologies of our times to democratize the cryptocurrency market, it could solve one of the biggest challenges the crypto space faces today: accessibility.</p>
<p>What sets Orbitt apart is its three-pronged approach to market challenges. While other platforms might focus solely on trading tools or launchpads, Orbitt&#8217;s ecosystem creates a symbiotic relationship between traders, developers, and projects.</p>
<p>The $ORBT tokenomics also show thoughtful design, with the 50/50 split between buybacks and volume creation ensuring that the ecosystem remains both sustainable and dynamic. This approach would help Orbitt avoid the common pitfall of utility tokens that struggle to maintain value beyond initial hype.</p>
<p>With Solana continuing to grow as one of the biggest blockchains and potential Ethereum-killers, Orbitt could become a dominant player in the space very soon.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/orbitt/">Orbitt: Revolutionizing Trading &#038; Project Development on Solana With AI</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">104010</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Meet IO.net: Unleashing the Internet of GPUs to Fuel the AI Revolution</title>
		<link>https://blockonomi.com/io-net-guide/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nicholas Say]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 06:40:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Guides]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blockonomi.com/?p=103121</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The AI gold rush is in full swing as 65% of organizations now report regularly using generative AI in some capacity. Small problem, no matter how much some want AI to be everywhere or even become your clone, there&#8217;s a critical shortage of the very thing needed to keep this AI revolution going: raw computing [...]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/io-net-guide/">Meet IO.net: Unleashing the Internet of GPUs to Fuel the AI Revolution</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The AI gold rush is in full swing as 65% of organizations now report regularly using generative AI in some capacity.</p>
<p>Small problem, no matter how much some want AI to be everywhere or even become your clone, there&#8217;s a critical shortage of the very thing needed to keep this AI revolution going: raw computing power. As tech giants hoard GPUs like greedy dragons guarding treasure, countless AI projects are left out in the cold.</p>
<p><a href="https://io.net/">IO.net</a> aims to fix this shortfall by offering a decentralized physical infrastructure network (DePIN) which aggregates GPUs from underutilized sources.</p>
<p>By tapping into independent data centers, repurposed crypto mining equipment, and other hardware networks, IO.net is looking to unlock an estimated 200 exaFLOPS of additional GPU capacity, the equivalent of 13 times what&#8217;s currently available from major cloud providers. Let’s take a look at what an “Internet of GPUs” looks like.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-103175" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/io.jpg" alt="" width="1000" height="700" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/io.jpg 1000w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/io-300x210.jpg 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/io-768x538.jpg 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/io-50x35.jpg 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/io-150x105.jpg 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/io-450x315.jpg 450w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" /></p>
<p>The current GPU shortage is more severe than most people, both experts and everyday users, realize. Major cloud providers only have about 10-15 exaFLOPS of GPU compute capacity to offer, while potential demand could be as high as 20-25 exaFLOPS.</p>
<p>The need for processing power will only increase over the years, given the increasing popularity of AI, gaming, and other GPU-intensive technologies. This 5-10 exaFLOPS shortfall creates significant challenges for AI and ML projects worldwide, such as long wait times to acquire hardware, lack of choice, and high costs.</p>
<p>The industry’s answer to this problem has been pretty basic so far: Just build more chips!</p>
<p>However, what if the solution isn&#8217;t creating more chips, but using the ones we already have more smartly? That&#8217;s what blockchain project IO.net is trying to accomplish, implementing an audacious plan that might just save the AI revolution by turning the world&#8217;s idle GPUs into the backbone of AI&#8217;s future.</p>
<hr />
<h2>What is IO.net</h2>
<p>At its core, <a href="https://io.net/">IO.net is a decentralized network</a> that connects idle GPUs worldwide, creating a massive, distributed supercomputer accessible to machine learning engineers or anyone who requires more GPU capacity. This means instant access to high-powered computing power, not only at a fraction of what big cloud providers charge but also more easily and faster than with traditional providers.</p>
<p>More than a service, however, IO.net is building an ecosystem with computer power at its heart. Their goal? To make advanced AI development possible for anyone, not just tech giants with deep pockets. By tapping into underused resources, IO.net aims to solve the GPU shortage and democratize the future of artificial intelligence in a more sustainable, accessible, and efficient way.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-103179" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/features.jpg" alt="" width="1000" height="700" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/features.jpg 1000w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/features-300x210.jpg 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/features-768x538.jpg 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/features-50x35.jpg 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/features-150x105.jpg 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/features-450x315.jpg 450w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" /></p>
<p>As a result, users also get to enjoy increased control and flexibility over the different resources and features of the network thanks to its modularity and use of decentralized infrastructure. This greatly differentiates IO.net from traditional providers like Amazon Web Services (AWS), Google Cloud, and other alternative cloud computing platforms.</p>
<hr />
<h2>IO.net Products</h2>
<p>The IO.net ecosystem is composed of various products and features designed to provide a comprehensive experience without sacrificing flexibility. These features also interact with the IO coin ($IO), creating a self-sustainable and trustless ecosystem that doesn’t require middlemen and operates more efficiently.</p>
<h3>IO Cloud</h3>
<p><a href="https://cloud.io.net/cloud/home">IO Cloud</a> is the platform&#8217;s flagship offering, allowing users to deploy and manage on-demand decentralized GPU clusters such as Ray, Mega-Ray, and Kubernetes. Some of its key features include seamless integration with IO SDK for distributed computing, native support for the RAY distributed computing frameworks, global distribution of GPU resources functioning like a CDN for ML serving and inference, and future access to the IO Models Store.</p>
<h3>IO Worker</h3>
<p><a href="https://worker.io.net/worker/devices">IO Worker</a> is a web application that enables individuals and businesses operating as suppliers to rent out their computing power. It offers them the opportunity for higher earnings compared to traditional cloud services, real-time performance monitoring, secure resource sharing, and global accessibility. In exchange, users of IO Worker are rewarded based on their block rewards, jobs processed, active time, blocks earned, and much more.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-103180" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/gpu.jpg" alt="" width="1000" height="700" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/gpu.jpg 1000w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/gpu-300x210.jpg 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/gpu-768x538.jpg 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/gpu-50x35.jpg 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/gpu-150x105.jpg 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/gpu-450x315.jpg 450w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" /></p>
<h3>IO Explorer</h3>
<p>Similar to other blockchain explorers,<a href="https://explorer.io.net/explorer/home"> IO Explorer</a> provides transparency into the network&#8217;s operations. This is achieved by offering comprehensive statistics on network activity and real-time metrics on cluster bookings, deployments, and network devices. Some of the information available to users includes total GPUs/CPUs, verified GPUs/CPUs, cluster-ready GPUs/CPUs, supply insights, Geo Distribution, activity trends, etc.</p>
<h3>IO ID</h3>
<p><a href="https://id.io.net/">IO ID</a> serves as the central hub for tracking earnings and expenses within the network, facilitating easy withdrawal of funds in cryptocurrency. This control panel allows users to interact with all the different IO.net elements, personalize their experience, connect their Solana/Aptos wallet, delete their account, and perform any other changes to their account.</p>
<h3>IO Coin ($IO)</h3>
<p><a href="https://docs.iog.net/docs/what-is-io-coin">IO Coin</a> is the native cryptocurrency of the IOG Network. $IO plays a crucial role in facilitating economic incentives within the ecosystem, balancing the needs of GPU renters/owners, and providing network security through staking mechanisms. Every transaction taking place in the IO ecosystem makes use of the IO token, independently of the currency users are interacting with fiat, USDC, or any other token in the front end.</p>
<p>IO Coin’s tokenomics were developed around having a fixed maximum supply of 800 million coins, hourly rewards to suppliers and their stakers, and the use of an $IO burning mechanism. 500 million of these $IO were distributed when the project launched while the remaining 300 million will be emitted and paid to suppliers as rewards every hour.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-103181" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/earnings.jpg" alt="" width="1000" height="700" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/earnings.jpg 1000w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/earnings-300x210.jpg 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/earnings-768x538.jpg 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/earnings-50x35.jpg 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/earnings-150x105.jpg 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/earnings-450x315.jpg 450w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" /></p>
<h2>Recent Developments</h2>
<p>IO.net has recently undergone significant leadership changes to drive its next phase of growth. Tory Green, formerly the COO, has stepped into the role of CEO with an ambitious vision for expansion. This transition marks a pivotal moment as IO.net aims to solidify its position and change the game in the world of cloud computing.</p>
<p>The company has launched a highly anticipated staking program, building on the success of its Ignition Reward Program. This new initiative allows participants to stake their devices in the IO Network, turning their computing power into a source of income. The strong community engagement is evident as over $1 million was staked shortly after the program&#8217;s launch.</p>
<p>IO.net has also formed strategic partnerships to enhance its offerings. A notable collaboration is with FLock.io to introduce Proof-of-AI (PoAI), an innovative consensus mechanism designed to ensure integrity and scalability in decentralized AI networks. This mechanism aims to verify genuine contribution of computing resources, deterring simulated participation and ensuring fair compensation for honest contributors.</p>
<p>The project&#8217;s potential has not gone unnoticed by investors so far. IO Research, the parent company behind io.net, recently raised <a href="https://www.reuters.com/technology/ai-focused-blockchain-startup-io-research-raises-30-mln-series-funding-round-2024-03-05/">$30 million</a> in a Series A funding round. This significant investment was backed by web3 powerhouses like Hack VC, Solana Labs, and OKX, ensuring the future plans of the project can be implemented.</p>
<h2>Conclusion</h2>
<p>IO.net is a bold step forward in the world of decentralized GPU computing for AI and machine learning applications, offering a real alternative in a seemingly saturated market.</p>
<p>By addressing the critical issues of availability, choice, and cost that plague traditional cloud providers, IO.net could soon become a key player in the development and growth of the AI ecosystem.</p>
<p>The platform&#8217;s innovative approach to aggregating underutilized GPU resources, combined with its robust feature set and thoughtful tokenomic model, offers a compelling solution to the current GPU shortage.</p>
<p>As AI and ML continue to drive technological advancement across industries, the demand for accessible, scalable, and cost-effective computing power will only grow.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/io-net-guide/">Meet IO.net: Unleashing the Internet of GPUs to Fuel the AI Revolution</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">103121</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Best YouTube Alternatives: The Future Decentralized Video Platforms</title>
		<link>https://blockonomi.com/youtube-alternative/</link>
					<comments>https://blockonomi.com/youtube-alternative/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Daniel Dob]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 06 Oct 2024 03:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[alternatives to youtube]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blockchain video]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[decentralized video]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Video]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video sharing platforms]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[youtube]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[youtube alternative]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[youtube alternatives]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blockonomi.com/?p=40996</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Video hosting or sharing platforms represent services that facilitate the upload, viewing, sharing, and streaming of video-based content on the Internet. At this point in time, Google’s YouTube represents the world’s largest video sharing platform, with over 1.9 billion monthly logged users, one billion hours-worth of video watched daily, and 500+ hours of content uploaded [...]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/youtube-alternative/">Best YouTube Alternatives: The Future Decentralized Video Platforms</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Video hosting or sharing platforms represent services that facilitate the upload, viewing, sharing, and streaming of video-based content on the Internet.</p>
<p>At this point in time, Google’s YouTube represents <a href="https://moneycheck.com/how-much-do-youtubers-make/">the world’s largest video sharing platform</a>, with over 1.9 billion monthly logged users, one billion hours-worth of video watched daily, and 500+ hours of content uploaded every minute of the day.</p>
<p>Despite these impressive numbers, YouTube isn’t without flaws. In fact, the video-sharing platform has many disadvantages and has been involved in numerous controversies that spawn from its very nature &#8211; centralization.</p>
<p>These issues include, but are not limited to strict video monetisation policies, unfair video promotion algorithms, lack of a personalized support service, vague terms &amp; conditions, data collection controversies, and privacy concerns.</p>
<p>Because of these pressing challenges, numerous YouTube viewers and content creators are actively considering the idea of migrating to an alternative platform.</p>
<p>The rise of blockchain technology has led to the appearance of several innovative video sharing platforms that are definitely worth anyone’s consideration.</p>
<p>While these platforms are considerably less widespread when compared to YouTube, some provide decentralization, open-source development, transparent terms &amp; conditions, improved search algorithms, privacy-focused approaches, alternative payment systems for content creators (cryptocurrencies), and more.</p>
<p>Others provide blockchain-based decentralized infrastructures that are needed to obtain these benefits through existing platform integration.</p>
<h2>Best blockchain-based YouTube alternatives</h2>
<p>Without further ado, here is an overview of the market’s best blockchain-based alternatives to YouTube, alongside several options that are bound to improve the current video streaming solutions.</p>
<hr />
<h2>LBRY</h2>
<p><a href="https://lbry.com/">LBRY</a> does not refer to itself as a video sharing service, but rather as a marketplace for all types of digital content, with a focus being placed on video.</p>
<p>The platform aims to create a protocol-based association between users and their digital content- could be movies, games, book, or pictures.</p>
<p>The company markets its service towards those who are privacy-conscious, freedom lovers, artists, content producers, computer geeks, and many more.</p>
<p>Read our interview with <a href="https://blockonomi.com/lbry-ceo-talks-youtube-censorship-online-free-speech-blockchain/">the LBRY Ceo here</a>.</p>
<figure id="attachment_41001" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-41001" style="width: 808px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-41001" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/04/lbry.jpg" alt="LBRY" width="808" height="633" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/04/lbry.jpg 808w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/04/lbry-300x235.jpg 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/04/lbry-768x602.jpg 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/04/lbry-50x39.jpg 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/04/lbry-87x67.jpg 87w" sizes="(max-width: 808px) 100vw, 808px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-41001" class="wp-caption-text">LBRY.tv</figcaption></figure>
<h3>Features</h3>
<p>To understand LBRY, it is important to consider it as both a protocol and a service. With this in mind, the protocol provides the technical infrastructure required to run the decentralized and blockchain-based peer-to-peer network where users are free to share, purchase and download content.</p>
<p>The service itself is quite straight-forward – it simply allows users to browse, host, share, upload, purchase, and download all types of <a href="https://blockonomi.com/siteground-coupon-code/">digital content</a>. Thus, services such as content discovery, content distribution, and transaction settlement are all integrated within the technical infrastructure of the service, thereby providing users with a seamless experience.</p>
<p>The platform relies on LBRY credits which can be used to purchase digital content. The tokens can then be exchanged to other cryptocurrencies on supporting exchanges.</p>
<p>Copyright protection is ensured through the public ledger, where each upload and purchase is recorded, thus making it easier for content rights owners to carry out infringement actions against those who unlawfully republish their content.</p>
<p>In the long run, LBRY has the potential of becoming a fully-fledged ecosystem meant to facilitate the purchase, storage, sale, and security of all types of digital content, including but not limited to videos, music, apps, e-books, articles, code, and more.</p>
<h3>User Interface</h3>
<p>LBRY aims to make its platform as easy to use and straightforward as possible. From a video sharing standpoint, LBRY.TV offers a UI that’s skilfully-designed, and similar to other platforms such as YouTube.</p>
<p>Both free and paid videos can be found – watching free does not require taking extra steps such as creating an account, whereas paid videos do require crypto-based payments and registration.</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><a class="infobutton" href="https://lbry.com/">Visit</a></p>
<hr />
<h2>D.Tube</h2>
<p>According to the platform’s website, <a href="https://d.tube/">D.Tube</a> represents the world’s first crypto-based video platform that’s decentralized and built using the infrastructure provided by the STEEM blockchain, alongside the <a href="https://blockonomi.com/interplanetary-file-system/">IPFS</a> P2P network.</p>
<h3>Features</h3>
<p>First of all, D.Tube offers a state-of-the-art video streaming service, where users can find and upload all types of content.</p>
<p>It has an integrated cryptocurrency incentive, as watching, uploading, sharing, and commenting on videos via the immutable STEEM blockchain helps users earn coin.</p>
<figure id="attachment_41002" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-41002" style="width: 808px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-41002" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/04/dtube.jpg" alt="DTube Homepage" width="808" height="633" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/04/dtube.jpg 808w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/04/dtube-300x235.jpg 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/04/dtube-768x602.jpg 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/04/dtube-50x39.jpg 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/04/dtube-87x67.jpg 87w" sizes="(max-width: 808px) 100vw, 808px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-41002" class="wp-caption-text">DTube Homepage</figcaption></figure>
<p>Additionally, the platform was designed to be censorship-resistant – from a technical standpoint, the company has no actual means to censor videos or enforce specific content guidelines. Censorship powers are placed in users’ hands, who decide which videos to censor or promote via upvotes and downvotes.</p>
<p>Users can also reward content creators with cryptocurrency, thus leading to a fully-fledged incentive program that provides a win-win situation to both users and uploaders.</p>
<p>Unlike YouTube and other video sharing services, D.Tube was designed to be fair to all users. With this in mind, the platform does not rely on hidden algorithms that decide which videos make the front page, and which ones can be monetized.</p>
<p>In fact, all service-related data is publicly-available. Last but not least, the service is ad-free. Users can decide to advertise by themselves within the videos they upload.</p>
<h3>User interface</h3>
<p>From a user interface standpoint, the platform is quite similar when compared to YouTube, in the sense that the UX shares a very similar design language.</p>
<p>As such, browsing D.Tube is bound to be a seamless experience, whereas watching content is always a pleasure. Browsing and discovering new videos is quite easy, as the service offers several sections, including hot videos, trending videos, new videos, watch later, watch again, and leading videos/users.</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><a class="infobutton" href="https://d.tube/">Visit</a></p>
<hr />
<h2>Dlive</h2>
<p>This company was founded by a group of video content creators and consumers who grew tired of having to deal with the challenges put forth by the industry.</p>
<p>These include unfair content promotion, rising platform fees, censorship, and high monetization bars. Thus, this led to the creation of Dlive, which aims to act as a live streaming service that’s based on value-sharing, and strives to empower both viewers and <a href="https://blockonomi.com/shopify-coupon-code/">creators</a> through an innovative incentive system.</p>
<p>We covered DLive before when the biggest YouTuber, Pewdiepie, <a href="https://blockonomi.com/pewdiepie-blockchain-dlive-sponsorship/">mentioned them</a> on his channel, exposing the service to millions of his followers.</p>
<h3>Features</h3>
<p>As such, Dlive represents a blockchain-based and decentralized live streaming platform that’s based on three revolutionary features: Lemon, LINO and LINO Stake.</p>
<p>With this in mind, Dlive is built on top of a blockchain network where Lemon acts as a token that can be transacted within the platform, for the purpose of donating and subscribing to content creators.</p>
<figure id="attachment_41003" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-41003" style="width: 808px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-41003" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/04/dlive.jpg" alt="DLive Homepage" width="808" height="713" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/04/dlive.jpg 808w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/04/dlive-300x265.jpg 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/04/dlive-768x678.jpg 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/04/dlive-50x44.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 808px) 100vw, 808px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-41003" class="wp-caption-text">DLive Homepage</figcaption></figure>
<p>LINO is an actual cryptocurrency that’s tradable outside the live streaming service – the coin can be earnt by both creators and viewers through content and voting rewards. Lastly, LINO holders can stake their tokens in order to receive a stake in the company.</p>
<p>This stake can then be used to elect validators, receive rewards, and cast votes on the future updates of the platform.</p>
<p>The platform’s blockchain-based infrastructure is censorship-resistant and employs an algorithm that fairly promotes all streamers. Thus, it has gained a considerable amount of popularity over the last few months.</p>
<h3>User interface</h3>
<p>From a live streaming standpoint, Dlive grants users and content creators access to a series of standard features that are offered by most other competitors in the industry.</p>
<p>These include easy access to hundreds of on-going live streams, a user chat service, the ability to subscribe to streamers, notifications, replays, highlights, and much more. The UX design employs a cool dark theme, whereas browsing for live streams is a seamless and fun experience.</p>
<p>Dlive also provides users with a series of knowledge pages, where they can learn more about the technicalities of Dlive, alongside the blockchain-based features that viewers and streamers can take advantage of. A professional customer support team is readily available to answer all questions.</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><a class="infobutton" href="https://lbry.com/">Visit</a></p>
<hr />
<h2>BitChute</h2>
<p>The company behind <a href="https://www.bitchute.com/">BitChute</a> has a simple goal – resisting against internet censorship. To achieve this, the video-sharing platform is decentralized and community-funded, while employing a set of rules that help avoid censorship.</p>
<h3>Features</h3>
<p>In terms of BitChute’s features, it works similarly to most video sharing platforms available on the web. To upload content, users must create an account, whereas streaming is easily done without registration.</p>
<figure id="attachment_41004" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-41004" style="width: 808px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-41004" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/04/bitchute.jpg" alt="Bitchute" width="808" height="713" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/04/bitchute.jpg 808w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/04/bitchute-300x265.jpg 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/04/bitchute-768x678.jpg 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/04/bitchute-50x44.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 808px) 100vw, 808px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-41004" class="wp-caption-text">Bitchute Homepage</figcaption></figure>
<p>Video uploads are placed in a series of categories, including anime, arts, auto, beauty, business, cuisine, DIY, education, entertainment, health, music, news, family, etc. The service also features content for increased visibility.</p>
<p>While still in its infancy, BitChute has attracted a good number of users and a series of interesting uploads that aren’t available anywhere else on the internet.</p>
<h3>User interface</h3>
<p>The platform’s user interface is basic and strives to ensure simplicity. Some may say that it’s a bit old-school and lacking in some regards, but the service skilfully does its main job. Watching and uploading is bound to be a seamless experience.</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><a class="infobutton" href="https://www.bitchute.com/">Visit</a></p>
<hr />
<h2>THETA</h2>
<p><a href="https://www.thetatoken.org/">Theta</a> was started after an in-depth analysis of the current challenges, controversies, and issues surrounding the video streaming industry of today.</p>
<p>Its founders quickly figured out that the standard content delivery networks are unreliable while leading to high operational costs that are mostly absorbed by publishers, rather than operators. Similarly, traditional video streaming services are centralized and inefficient, thus leading to censorship and unfair promotional algorithms.</p>
<p>The THETA platform aims to provide users with a decentralized next-gen video delivery service.</p>
<figure id="attachment_41005" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-41005" style="width: 808px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-41005" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/04/theta.jpg" alt="Theta.tv" width="808" height="713" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/04/theta.jpg 808w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/04/theta-300x265.jpg 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/04/theta-768x678.jpg 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/04/theta-50x44.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 808px) 100vw, 808px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-41005" class="wp-caption-text">Theta.tv</figcaption></figure>
<h3>Features</h3>
<p>As a <a href="https://blockonomi.com/best-torrent-sites/">peer-to-peer</a> (P2P) platform, THETA ensures high quality and smooth video streaming, as videos are hosted on servers throughout the world and instantly made available to viewers on demand.</p>
<p>The P2P business model means that platform operators do not directly invest into hosting infrastructure – rather, this responsibility is put in the hands of thousands of incentivised hosts, thus significantly reducing platform operation costs. This leads to a higher earning potential for content creators, thus ensuring better-quality streams.</p>
<p>However, it’s important to keep in mind that it isn’t only content creators who are incentivised on THETA. Rather, viewers earn THETA Fuel rewards for sharing their bandwidth and computer resources. The THETA token can then be exchanged for other cryptocurrencies, or used to reward content creators.</p>
<p>THETA employs an open-source approach for both its network and protocol, thus facilitating a significant degree of transparency. Furthermore, content providers and video platforms are free to use the existing API to build specialized decentralized applications (Dapps) for their audience.</p>
<h3>User interface</h3>
<p>The user interface is being designed to provide a beautiful interface that ensures ease-of-use. Browsing through movies, TV shows, e-sports, music, live streams and other content forms will be a seamless experience.</p>
<p>Do keep in mind that at the time of writing, the THETA Token end-to-end video streaming platform is still under development – current plans suggest that the service will go live later this year.</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><a class="infobutton" href="https://www.thetatoken.org/">Visit</a></p>
<hr />
<h2>Verasity</h2>
<p><a href="https://verasity.io/">Verasity</a> was designed with the purpose of building the infrastructure that publishers require to serve different types of attention-rewarded video content to billions of users worldwide.</p>
<p>According to the company, the video streaming and advertising industries are currently dealing with a number of challenges including low engagement for ads, low publisher revenue, low viewership, intrusive ads, the prevalence of ad blocking software and more.</p>
<figure id="attachment_41006" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-41006" style="width: 808px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-41006" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/04/verasity.jpg" alt="Verasity" width="808" height="573" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/04/verasity.jpg 808w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/04/verasity-300x213.jpg 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/04/verasity-768x545.jpg 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/04/verasity-50x35.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 808px) 100vw, 808px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-41006" class="wp-caption-text">Verasity Homepage</figcaption></figure>
<h3>Features</h3>
<p>The challenges that have been mentioned above can be dealt with via VERASITY, which provides in-video rewards, alongside a number of loyalty schemes that are based on four components.</p>
<p>To kick things off, the platform provides a HTML5 and full HD video player that’s supported on most devices. The second component is an integrated SDK reward module into the market’s most popular video streaming platforms, which provides users with VRA token rewards based on their actions without negatively influencing the workflow of publishers or the way viewers interact with online video.</p>
<p><iframe class="youtube-player" width="814" height="458" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/QBMGUbdHxdY?version=3&#038;rel=1&#038;showsearch=0&#038;showinfo=1&#038;iv_load_policy=1&#038;fs=1&#038;hl=en-US&#038;autohide=2&#038;wmode=transparent" allowfullscreen="true" style="border:0;" sandbox="allow-scripts allow-same-origin allow-popups allow-presentation allow-popups-to-escape-sandbox"></iframe></p>
<p>Thirdly, the VeraWallet app works in-video, and allows content viewers to earn, spend, and stake the VRA token as they please. Lastly, blockchain technology will be used to carry out verification and analytics of video interactions, and ad effectiveness.</p>
<p>Thus, the company aims to create a VRA-based virtuous cycle that provides incentives to advertisers, content publishers and viewers. With this in mind, VERASITY does not represent a video streaming platform, but rather an add-on that can be integrated within existing platforms to fix some of the challenges they’re currently dealing with.</p>
<h3>User interface</h3>
<p>The platform’s user interface is easy to operate, yet a good understanding of how the platform works is required to facilitate efficient usage of the provided tools.</p>
<p>Currently, VERASITY can be integrated within numerous video streaming services, including but not limited to YouTube, Vimeo, Twitch, VideoJS, Kaltura, FlowPlayer, JWPLAYER, BrightCove, iVideoSmart, and more.</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><a class="infobutton" href="https://verasity.io/">Visit</a></p>
<hr />
<h2>LivePeer</h2>
<p><a href="https://livepeer.org/">LivePeer</a> represents an open-source video infrastructure service that’s built directly on top of the <a href="https://blockonomi.com/ethereum/">Ethereum blockchain</a>, serving the purpose of providing video engineers with reliable and cost-effective video encoding.</p>
<p>The platform leverages blockchain particularities such as decentralization, in order to create innovative video streaming business models that are highly-scalable and low-cost.</p>
<h3>Features</h3>
<p>To put things better into perspective, LivePeer is currently creating a ‘platform as a service’ designed for project developers who require on-demand and live video capabilities. While videos can be embedded into websites with ease, this platform is attempting to increase the reliability of video workflow, while leading to great scalability and reduced costs, through a blockchain-based peer-to-peer infrastructure.</p>
<figure id="attachment_41007" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-41007" style="width: 808px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-41007" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/04/livepeer.jpg" alt="Livepeer Homepage" width="808" height="579" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/04/livepeer.jpg 808w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/04/livepeer-300x215.jpg 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/04/livepeer-768x550.jpg 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/04/livepeer-50x36.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 808px) 100vw, 808px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-41007" class="wp-caption-text">Livepeer Homepage</figcaption></figure>
<p>The platform can be leveraged by developers, users, and broadcasters, thanks to the variety of features that are being built for each user group. Thus, developers can utilize the platform for the purpose of powering video functionality.</p>
<p>Viewers will soon be able to stream video using applications that are built via LivePeer, whereas broadcasters with large audiences will take advantage of the platform’s tools in order to decrease infrastructure overhead.</p>
<p>Incentives are also offered to encourage the usage of LivePeer. As such, those who run the platform’s software can earn tokens by contributing with bandwidth and processing power.</p>
<p>The LPT token works via Ethereum, and is the exclusive payment methods supported by LivePeer. The token can be exchanged into other coins or fiat-based currencies via supporting exchanges.</p>
<h3>User interface</h3>
<p>Since this isn’t a video streaming service like some of the other platform’s highlighted in this article, it’s important to keep in mind that a solid technical understanding is required to ensure efficient usage of LivePeer’s tools and services.</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><a class="infobutton" href="https://lbry.com/">Visit</a></p>
<hr />
<h2>Bottom Line</h2>
<p>Based on everything that has been highlighted so far, the present and future of video streaming services is bright.</p>
<p>Blockchain integration, decentralization and user incentive protocols will power better, faster, <a href="https://blockonomi.com/online-censorship-decentralized-content-distribution/">censorship-resistant</a>, and more profitable video streaming services that are much better alternatives when compared to traditional platforms.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/youtube-alternative/">Best YouTube Alternatives: The Future Decentralized Video Platforms</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://blockonomi.com/youtube-alternative/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">40996</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>What is Mythical Marketplace? Platform for Trading In-Game NFT Assets</title>
		<link>https://blockonomi.com/mythical-marketplace/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Oliver Dale]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2024 08:24:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Gaming]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Guides]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blockonomi.com/?p=101617</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Mythical Marketplace is a digital platform designed for trading NFTs (non-fungible tokens) in the gaming world. Developed by Mythical Games, the studio behind titles like Blankos Block Party, this marketplace aims to bridge the gap between traditional gaming and blockchain technology. The Mythical Marketplace allows players to buy, sell, and trade in-game items as [...]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/mythical-marketplace/">What is Mythical Marketplace? Platform for Trading In-Game NFT Assets</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The <a href="https://mythical.market/">Mythical Marketplace</a> is a digital platform designed for trading NFTs (non-fungible tokens) in the gaming world. Developed by Mythical Games, the studio behind titles like Blankos Block Party, this marketplace aims to bridge the gap between traditional gaming and blockchain technology.</p>
<p>The Mythical Marketplace allows players to buy, sell, and trade in-game items as NFTs. This means that players can potentially monetize their time and effort spent in games, turning rare collectibles or achievements into tradable assets.</p>
<p>Mythical Marketplace focuses on user experience, particularly for gamers who may be new to blockchain technology. The platform offers features like &#8220;quick trades&#8221; for multiple assets and accepts both traditional and cryptocurrency payment methods.</p>
<p>The marketplace currently supports games such as NFL Rivals and Nitro Nation World Tour, with plans to expand its ecosystem.</p>
<figure id="attachment_101618" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-101618" style="width: 1000px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-101618" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/NFL.jpg" alt="NFL Rivals " width="1000" height="700" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/NFL.jpg 1000w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/NFL-300x210.jpg 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/NFL-768x538.jpg 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/NFL-50x35.jpg 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/NFL-150x105.jpg 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/NFL-450x315.jpg 450w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-101618" class="wp-caption-text">NFL Rivals</figcaption></figure>
<hr />
<h2>The Mythical Platform</h2>
<p>The Mythical Platform forms the technological foundation of the Mythical Marketplace. This underlying infrastructure manages crucial aspects of the marketplace ecosystem, including trades, payments, user accounts, and blockchain inventory.</p>
<p>Mythical Platform Features:</p>
<ul>
<li>Seamless integration with game inventories, allowing for smooth transfer of in-game items to the marketplace</li>
<li>Fraud protection measures to ensure secure transactions</li>
<li>Fee optimization to keep costs reasonable for users</li>
<li>Pricing recommendations for both buyers and sellers</li>
<li>Support for both fiat and cryptocurrency transactions</li>
</ul>
<p>The platform&#8217;s design prioritizes scalability and flexibility. It can handle a high volume of transactions and adapts to the specific needs of different games and partners.</p>
<p>For game developers, the Mythical Platform offers tools to easily incorporate blockchain technology into their games, including the option to create private-label marketplaces branded to their specifications.</p>
<figure id="attachment_101619" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-101619" style="width: 1000px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-101619" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/Nitro.jpg" alt="Nitro Nation: World Tour " width="1000" height="700" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/Nitro.jpg 1000w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/Nitro-300x210.jpg 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/Nitro-768x538.jpg 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/Nitro-50x35.jpg 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/Nitro-150x105.jpg 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/Nitro-450x315.jpg 450w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-101619" class="wp-caption-text">Nitro Nation: World Tour</figcaption></figure>
<p>An important aspect of the Mythical Platform is its approach to blockchain technology. While it leverages the benefits of blockchain for security and ownership verification, it aims to abstract much of the complexity away from the end-user.</p>
<p>This design philosophy aligns with the marketplace&#8217;s goal of making NFT trading accessible to a broad gaming audience, not just crypto enthusiasts.</p>
<hr />
<div>
<div>
<div>
<h2>User-Friendly Features for Gamers</h2>
<p>The Mythical Marketplace stands out for its commitment to creating a user-friendly experience, especially for gamers who may be new to NFTs and blockchain technology:</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Easy Account Creation:</strong> Users can simply log in with their Mythical account, eliminating the need for separate crypto wallets or complex setup processes. This significantly lowers the barrier to entry for newcomers to the NFT space.</li>
<li><strong>Quick Trades:</strong> The marketplace offers a &#8220;quick trades&#8221; feature, allowing users to trade multiple assets at once. This streamlines the process for gamers who want to manage their in-game inventories efficiently.</li>
<li><strong>Familiar Payment Methods:</strong> While the platform supports cryptocurrency, it also accepts traditional Web2 payment methods like credit cards. This flexibility makes the marketplace more accessible to a wider audience.</li>
<li><strong>Intuitive Interface:</strong> The marketplace is designed with gamers in mind, featuring an easy-to-navigate layout that displays important information about each NFT, such as its rarity, level, and power rating.</li>
<li><strong>In-Game Integration:</strong> Purchased NFTs are automatically added to users&#8217; in-game inventories, creating a seamless connection between the marketplace and supported games.</li>
<li><strong>Seller-Friendly Policies:</strong> Sellers can list their items on the marketplace while still using them in-game, offering flexibility in how they manage their digital assets.</li>
</ul>
<p>By prioritizing these user-friendly features, the Mythical Marketplace aims to make NFT trading as intuitive and accessible as possible for the average gamer.</p>
<figure id="attachment_101620" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-101620" style="width: 1000px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-101620" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/buy.jpg" alt="Buying an Item" width="1000" height="700" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/buy.jpg 1000w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/buy-300x210.jpg 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/buy-768x538.jpg 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/buy-50x35.jpg 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/buy-150x105.jpg 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/buy-450x315.jpg 450w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-101620" class="wp-caption-text">Buying an Item</figcaption></figure>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div>
<div>
<div>
<div>
<hr />
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<h2>Lowering the Barrier to Entry in NFT Gaming</h2>
<p>The Mythical Marketplace has made significant strides in reducing the complexity often associated with NFT and blockchain technology, making it more accessible to mainstream gamers. Here&#8217;s how:</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>No Crypto Wallet Required:</strong> Unlike many NFT platforms, users don&#8217;t need to set up a separate cryptocurrency wallet to participate. They can simply use their Mythical account, eliminating a common stumbling block for newcomers.</li>
<li><strong>Simplified Onboarding:</strong> The marketplace doesn&#8217;t require users to backup seed phrases or use cryptocurrency exchanges. This streamlined approach allows gamers to start trading quickly without navigating complex crypto processes.</li>
<li><strong>Familiar Payment Options:</strong> By accepting traditional payment methods alongside cryptocurrencies, the marketplace caters to users who may not be comfortable with or have access to digital currencies.</li>
<li><strong>In-Game Currency Integration:</strong> Some supported games use an in-game currency that can be easily purchased and used within the Mythical ecosystem, further simplifying the transaction process.</li>
<li><strong>Educational Approach:</strong> The platform provides clear, gamer-friendly explanations of NFTs and their value, helping users understand the technology without overwhelming them with technical jargon.</li>
</ul>
<hr />
<h2>Supported Games and Ecosystem</h2>
<p>The Mythical Marketplace hosts a growing ecosystem of games, featuring both first-party titles developed by Mythical Games and third-party games that utilize the Mythical Platform. This diverse lineup offers various experiences for players and collectors. Here are some key games in the Mythical ecosystem:</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>NFL Rivals:</strong> This officially licensed game allows players to collect and trade digital NFL player cards as NFTs. Users can build their dream lineups, compete against others, and climb leaderboards. The integration with the Mythical Marketplace enables players to buy and sell these digital athletes using the $MYTH token.</li>
<li><strong>Nitro Nation World Tour:</strong> A racing game where players can own and trade fully-licensed digital cars as NFTs. The game introduces an innovative feature where players can collect &#8220;Spark Plugs&#8221; of the same rarity and combine them to create a new vehicle within the game.</li>
<li>Blankos Block Party: While no longer directly integrated with the main Mythical Marketplace, this party game featuring unique digital vinyl toys called Blankos was one of the first to showcase Mythical&#8217;s NFT technology.</li>
</ul>
<p>The ecosystem is designed to cater to various gaming preferences, from sports management to racing, ensuring a broad appeal. Each game leverages the Mythical Platform&#8217;s technology to enable true ownership of in-game assets, allowing players to trade their items on the marketplace.</p>
<figure id="attachment_101621" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-101621" style="width: 1000px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-101621" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/blankos.jpg" alt="Blankos Block Party" width="1000" height="668" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/blankos.jpg 1000w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/blankos-300x200.jpg 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/blankos-768x513.jpg 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/blankos-50x33.jpg 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/blankos-150x100.jpg 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/blankos-450x301.jpg 450w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-101621" class="wp-caption-text">Blankos Block Party</figcaption></figure>
<p>Mythical Games continues to expand this ecosystem, working on new first-party titles and partnering with third-party developers.</p>
<hr />
<h2>Security and Trust Measures</h2>
<p>The Mythical Marketplace prioritizes security and trust, implementing several measures to protect users and their digital assets:</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Blockchain Technology:</strong> The marketplace utilizes blockchain to ensure the authenticity and ownership of NFTs. Each transaction is recorded on the blockchain, providing a transparent and immutable record of ownership.</li>
<li><strong>Fraud Protection:</strong> Advanced fraud detection and prevention systems are in place to safeguard users against potential scams or unauthorized transactions.</li>
<li><strong>Secure Payment Processing:</strong> Whether using cryptocurrency or traditional payment methods, the platform employs industry-standard security protocols to protect financial information.</li>
<li><strong>Smart Contract Audits: T</strong>he smart contracts underlying the NFT transactions are regularly audited to ensure they function as intended and are free from vulnerabilities.</li>
<li><strong>Account Security:</strong> Users are encouraged to enable two-factor authentication for added account protection. The platform also employs standard security practices like encrypted passwords and secure session management.</li>
<li><strong>Verified Game Integration:</strong> Only verified games can integrate with the Mythical Marketplace, ensuring that all NFTs traded on the platform are legitimate in-game assets.</li>
<li><strong>Transparent Pricing and Fees:</strong> The marketplace provides clear information about pricing and fees, helping users make informed decisions and building trust in the platform.</li>
<li><strong>Customer Support:</strong> A dedicated support team is available to assist users with any issues or concerns, further enhancing trust in the platform.</li>
<li><strong>Regular Updates and Maintenance:</strong> The platform undergoes regular updates to address any emerging security concerns and to improve overall performance.</li>
</ul>
<p>By implementing these security and trust measures, the Mythical Marketplace aims to create a safe environment for NFT trading, addressing common concerns associated with digital asset transactions and blockchain technology.</p>
<hr />
<h2>Conclusion</h2>
<p><a href="https://mythical.market">The Mythical Marketplace</a> represents a step forward in the integration of blockchain technology and traditional gaming. By focusing on user-friendly design, lowering barriers to entry, and prioritizing security, it&#8217;s making NFT trading accessible to a broader audience of gamers.</p>
<p>Key takeaways:</p>
<ul>
<li>The platform bridges the gap between conventional gaming and blockchain technology.</li>
<li>It offers a user-friendly experience, catering to both crypto-savvy users and newcomers.</li>
<li>The growing ecosystem of supported games provides diverse opportunities for players to engage with NFTs.</li>
<li>Strong security measures and transparency build trust in the platform.</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/mythical-marketplace/">What is Mythical Marketplace? Platform for Trading In-Game NFT Assets</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">101617</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Meet Orderly Network: The Decentralized Liquidity Layer for Web3 Trading</title>
		<link>https://blockonomi.com/orderly-network/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Oliver Dale]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 07:07:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[DeFi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Guides]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blockonomi.com/?p=101169</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Orderly Network is a DeFi platform that combines an orderbook-based trading infrastructure with a robust liquidity layer. Unlike traditional exchanges, Orderly operates as a backend infrastructure, enabling developers and businesses to build powerful trading applications without starting from scratch. Its key innovation lies in merging the high performance of centralized exchanges with the principles of [...]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/orderly-network/">Meet Orderly Network: The Decentralized Liquidity Layer for Web3 Trading</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://orderly.network/">Orderly Network</a> is a DeFi platform that combines an orderbook-based trading infrastructure with a robust liquidity layer.</p>
<p>Unlike traditional exchanges, Orderly operates as a backend infrastructure, enabling developers and businesses to build powerful trading applications without starting from scratch. Its key innovation lies in merging the high performance of centralized exchanges with the principles of decentralization, offering on-chain settlements and self-custody of assets.</p>
<p>Orderly&#8217;s DEX white-label solution allows builders to create trading platforms efficiently, accessing pre-established liquidity and professional-grade infrastructure.</p>
<p>The platform&#8217;s vision extends to creating an omnichain protocol, aiming to seamlessly connect traders across different blockchain networks within a single orderbook.</p>
<hr />
<h1>Orderly Network&#8217;s Core Components</h1>
<p>Orderly Network&#8217;s architecture is built on three fundamental components that work in harmony to create a powerful and efficient trading environment.</p>
<p>The first is its unified trading infrastructure, which ingeniously combines the benefits of centralized and decentralized exchanges. This infrastructure enables high-performance trading across different blockchain networks while maintaining the principles of decentralization, setting a new standard for cross-chain interactions.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-101172" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/orderly-1.jpg" alt="" width="1000" height="700" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/orderly-1.jpg 1000w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/orderly-1-300x210.jpg 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/orderly-1-768x538.jpg 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/orderly-1-50x35.jpg 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/orderly-1-150x105.jpg 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/orderly-1-450x315.jpg 450w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" /></p>
<p>The second core component is Orderly Network&#8217;s robust liquidity layer for both spot and perpetual futures markets. By aggregating liquidity from various sources, including professional market makers, this layer ensures efficient trade execution with minimal slippage.</p>
<p>The support for both spot and perpetual futures markets within the same ecosystem allows traders to implement more sophisticated strategies and manage their risk more effectively.</p>
<p>The third pillar of Orderly Network&#8217;s architecture is its orderbook-based system. Unlike many decentralized exchanges that use automated market makers, Orderly Network opts for a more traditional orderbook model, offering greater transparency and enabling advanced order types such as limit orders and stop-loss orders.</p>
<p>What sets this system apart is its implementation in a decentralized context: while the orderbook is maintained off-chain for performance reasons, all settlements occur on-chain, ensuring both speed and security.</p>
<hr />
<h1>Getting Started with Orderly Network</h1>
<p>Getting started with Orderly Network involves a few key steps, tailored to your role in the DeFi ecosystem.</p>
<p><a href="https://app.orderly.network/">For end-users</a>, the journey begins by connecting with one of Orderly&#8217;s partner platforms or applications that have integrated Orderly&#8217;s infrastructure.</p>
<p>These could be decentralized exchanges, wallets, or trading applications built on top of Orderly. You&#8217;ll typically need to connect your Web3 wallet, such as MetaMask, to the chosen platform.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-101173" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/connect.jpg" alt="" width="1000" height="700" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/connect.jpg 1000w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/connect-300x210.jpg 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/connect-768x538.jpg 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/connect-50x35.jpg 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/connect-150x105.jpg 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/connect-450x315.jpg 450w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" /></p>
<p>Once connected, you can start trading or using the services offered by that particular application, benefiting from Orderly&#8217;s deep liquidity and efficient orderbook system.</p>
<p>For developers and businesses looking to build on Orderly, the process involves engaging with Orderly&#8217;s documentation and development tools. Orderly provides comprehensive APIs and SDKs that allow for seamless integration of its trading infrastructure into new or existing applications.</p>
<p>This might involve setting up a developer account, obtaining necessary API keys, and familiarizing yourself with Orderly&#8217;s architecture and protocols. It&#8217;s important to note that Orderly Network itself doesn&#8217;t have a direct user interface; instead, it powers the trading experiences on partner platforms.</p>
<hr />
<h1>The $ORDER Token</h1>
<p><a href="https://airdrop.orderly.network/">The $ORDER token</a> is the lifeblood of the Orderly Network ecosystem, designed to align the interests of various stakeholders and drive the platform&#8217;s growth and decentralization.</p>
<p>As an ERC-20 token on Ethereum and an Omnichain Fungible Token (OFT) on other chains, $ORDER serves multiple crucial functions within the network.</p>
<p>Primarily, it acts as a governance token, allowing holders to participate in key decisions about the platform&#8217;s future through a decentralized governance process.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-101174" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/token.jpg" alt="" width="1000" height="700" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/token.jpg 1000w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/token-300x210.jpg 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/token-768x538.jpg 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/token-50x35.jpg 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/token-150x105.jpg 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/token-450x315.jpg 450w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" /></p>
<p>Staking $ORDER tokens generates VALOR, which represents a user&#8217;s stake in terms of amount and duration, entitling them to a share of the protocol treasury.</p>
<p>For traders, staking $ORDER boosts their trading rewards, while market makers can increase their share of market-making rewards through staking.</p>
<p>The token&#8217;s utility extends to various aspects of the Orderly ecosystem, including potential use in upcoming products and third-party DeFi protocols.</p>
<p>With a maximum supply of 1 billion tokens, $ORDER&#8217;s distribution is carefully structured to support long-term growth, with allocations for community incentives, strategic investors, team members, and ecosystem development.</p>
<p>Users can acquire $ORDER through various means, including participation in trading activities on Orderly-powered platforms, contribution to liquidity provision, or through secondary markets once the token is publicly traded.</p>
<hr />
<h1>Trading on Orderly Network</h1>
<p><a href="https://app.orderly.network/">Trading on Orderly Network</a> offers a unique blend of centralized exchange performance with decentralized finance principles. At the heart of Orderly&#8217;s trading system is its orderbook, which aggregates liquidity from various sources to ensure deep markets and efficient price discovery.</p>
<p>Unlike many DeFi platforms that use automated market makers, Orderly&#8217;s orderbook allows for limit orders, market orders, and even advanced order types like stop-loss and take-profit orders, giving traders greater control over their positions.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-101175" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/connect-1.jpg" alt="" width="1000" height="700" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/connect-1.jpg 1000w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/connect-1-300x210.jpg 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/connect-1-768x538.jpg 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/connect-1-50x35.jpg 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/connect-1-150x105.jpg 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/connect-1-450x315.jpg 450w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" /></p>
<p>The platform supports both spot trading for direct asset exchanges and perpetual futures for leveraged trading, catering to a wide range of trading strategies.</p>
<p>One of Orderly&#8217;s standout features is its gasless trading mechanism, where users can execute trades without paying blockchain transaction fees for each order, significantly reducing costs for active traders.</p>
<p>This is achieved through a layer-2 solution that batches transactions off-chain while ensuring final settlements occur on-chain for security.</p>
<p>Orderly also introduces cross-chain trading capabilities, allowing users to trade assets across different blockchain networks seamlessly within the same orderbook.</p>
<p>When it comes to fees, Orderly employs a maker-taker fee model, often offering rebates to market makers to encourage liquidity provision. Traders can potentially reduce their fees by staking $ORDER tokens, adding another layer of utility to the native token.</p>
<hr />
<h1>Rewards and Incentives</h1>
<p>Orderly Network has implemented a comprehensive rewards and incentives program to encourage participation and foster ecosystem growth.</p>
<p>At the forefront is the trading rewards program, which allocates 15% of the total $ORDER token supply to users trading on Orderly-powered platforms.</p>
<p>This program operates on an epoch basis, with rewards distributed over approximately 200 epochs, each lasting 14 days. The reward structure is designed to incentivize long-term engagement, with higher rewards in the initial bootstrapping phase gradually tapering off in later epochs.</p>
<p>Alongside trading rewards, Orderly offers a market making rewards program, allocating 10% of the total $ORDER supply to liquidity providers.</p>
<p>This program aims to ensure deep, consistent liquidity across all trading pairs. Both trading and market making rewards are calculated based on a combination of trading volume and $ORDER token staking, encouraging users to not only actively trade but also hold and stake the platform&#8217;s native token.</p>
<p>In recognition of early supporters, <a href="https://airdrop.orderly.network/">Orderly has allocated 13.3% of the total $ORDER supply for a retroactive airdrop.</a></p>
<p>This airdrop rewards early adopters on both EVM and NEAR chains, as well as participants in social campaigns and long-term incentive programs.</p>
<p>The rewards system extends beyond token distribution, with fee discounts offered to high-volume traders and enhanced rewards for those staking larger amounts of $ORDER.</p>
<hr />
<h1>Security and Self-Custody</h1>
<p>Security and self-custody are paramount principles in Orderly Network&#8217;s architecture, blending the robustness of decentralized systems with the performance of centralized exchanges.</p>
<p>At its core, Orderly Network upholds the ethos of &#8220;not your keys, not your coins&#8221; by ensuring that users retain full custody of their assets at all times. This is achieved through a sophisticated system where users&#8217; funds remain in their own wallets or smart contracts, only moving to trading contracts when actively participating in trades.</p>
<p>The platform utilizes advanced cryptographic techniques and secure multi-party computation to enable fast, off-chain order matching while maintaining on-chain settlement for all transactions. This hybrid approach allows for high-speed trading without compromising on security.</p>
<p>Orderly Network also implements a comprehensive set of security measures, including regular smart contract audits, bug bounty programs, and multi-signature wallets for protocol-owned assets.</p>
<p>To enhance user security, the platform offers features like customizable trading limits and optional two-factor authentication for critical operations. In the event of any security breaches, Orderly has established incident response protocols and maintains insurance coverage to protect users&#8217; assets.</p>
<hr />
<h1>Future Developments</h1>
<p>Orderly Network&#8217;s vision extends far beyond its current capabilities, with ambitious plans to revolutionize the decentralized finance landscape.</p>
<p>At the forefront of these developments is the platform&#8217;s push towards becoming a true omnichain protocol. This initiative aims to seamlessly connect traders from both EVM (Ethereum Virtual Machine) and non-EVM chains within a single, unified orderbook.</p>
<p>Such integration would eliminate the need for complex bridging processes, allowing users to deposit funds from any supported chain and trade effortlessly across multiple networks.</p>
<p>Orderly is also focusing on expanding its suite of financial products, with plans to introduce more sophisticated trading instruments like options and structured products. These additions will cater to advanced traders and institutions, potentially attracting more liquidity to the platform.</p>
<p>On the technical front, Orderly is continuously working on improving its layer-2 scaling solutions to enhance transaction speeds and reduce costs further.</p>
<p>The team is exploring cutting-edge technologies like zero-knowledge proofs to bolster privacy and security while maintaining transparency. Community engagement remains a priority, with plans to introduce more governance features and incentives for long-term token holders.</p>
<hr />
<h1>Conclusion</h1>
<p>Orderly Network represents a significant leap forward in decentralized finance, bridging the gap between centralized exchange performance and decentralized principles.</p>
<p>Its unified trading infrastructure, deep liquidity pool, and orderbook-based system cater to a wide range of market participants, from individual traders to institutions.</p>
<p>Key features like gasless trading, cross-chain functionality, and the $ORDER token ecosystem set Orderly apart in the DeFi landscape.</p>
<p>The platform&#8217;s commitment to security, self-custody, and community governance ensures a truly decentralized experience.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/orderly-network/">Meet Orderly Network: The Decentralized Liquidity Layer for Web3 Trading</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">101169</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Best Cryptocurrency Loyalty Programs: Top 5 Options for 2024</title>
		<link>https://blockonomi.com/cryptocurrency-loyalty-programs/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Oliver Dale]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 17:09:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Guides]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blockonomi.com/?p=99865</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Crypto loyalty programs are starting to become more popular to retain users and have also become more sophisticated, offering a lots of different rewards and ways to earn extra crypto in the hope of sparking customer loyalty in an increasingly crowded market. From NFT-based incentives to tiered reward systems, crypto platforms are pulling out all [...]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/cryptocurrency-loyalty-programs/">Best Cryptocurrency Loyalty Programs: Top 5 Options for 2024</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Crypto loyalty programs are starting to become more popular to retain users and have also become more sophisticated, offering a lots of different rewards and ways to earn extra crypto in the hope of sparking customer loyalty in an increasingly crowded market.</p>
<p>From NFT-based incentives to tiered reward systems, crypto platforms are pulling out all the stops to create engaging, value-driven experiences for their users.</p>
<p>In this guide we look at the top crypto loyalty programs available currently, and see what sets them apart in terms of innovation, user engagement, rewards, and accessibility.</p>
<p>Whether you&#8217;re a daily trader, a long-term hodler, or simply crypto-curious, understanding these programs could help you save money, make money and more.</p>
<p>Let&#8217;s take a look&#8230;.</p>
<hr />
<h2>What are Cryptocurrency Loyalty Programs?</h2>
<p>Cryptocurrency loyalty programs are incentive schemes designed by digital asset platforms to reward and retain their users. These programs aim to encourage ongoing engagement, increase platform usage, and foster a sense of community among participants.</p>
<p>Unlike traditional loyalty programs that might offer points or cash back, crypto loyalty programs often leverage blockchain technology and digital assets to provide unique, crypto-centric rewards.</p>
<p>These programs typically feature token rewards, tiered membership systems, and exclusive access to platform features or events. Many offer fee discounts for regular users and incorporate staking mechanisms to earn additional rewards.</p>
<p>Gamification elements are often included to make participation more engaging, while some programs focus on education, rewarding users for learning about cryptocurrencies and blockchain technology.</p>
<p>Increasingly, platforms are integrating NFTs into their loyalty schemes and offering community governance features. Referral bonuses are common, incentivizing users to bring new members to the platform.</p>
<p>For users, these programs provide additional value beyond basic cryptocurrency trading or holding.</p>
<p>For platforms, they help increase user retention, boost trading volumes, and create a more engaged user base. As the cryptocurrency market matures, these loyalty programs continue to evolve, becoming more sophisticated and tailored to user preferences, playing a crucial role in differentiating platforms in a crowded market.</p>
<hr />
<h2>Our Criteria for Choosing</h2>
<p>When selecting the best crypto loyalty programs, we looked at four key criteria to ensure we are showcasing the most innovative and user-friendly programs in the market:</p>
<ol>
<li><strong>Innovation and uniqueness:</strong> We assessed how each program stands out from the competition and offers unique rewards or benefits to its users.</li>
<li><strong>User engagement and community feedback: </strong>We considered the level of engagement within the community and how satisfied users are with the program.</li>
<li><strong>Rewards and benefits offered: </strong>We evaluated the types of rewards and benefits users can earn through the loyalty program.</li>
<li><strong>Ease of participation and accessibility:</strong> We looked at how easy it is for users to participate in the program and access their rewards.</li>
</ol>
<hr />
<h2>Top 5 Cryptocurrency Loyalty Programs</h2>
<h3>1. <a href="https://swapspace.co/invaders?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=blockonomi&amp;utm_campaign=backlinks">SwapSpace Invaders Club</a> NFT Loyalty Program</h3>
<figure id="attachment_99866" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-99866" style="width: 1000px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-99866" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/swapspace.jpg" alt="SwapSpace Invaders Club" width="1000" height="598" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/swapspace.jpg 1000w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/swapspace-300x179.jpg 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/swapspace-768x459.jpg 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/swapspace-50x30.jpg 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/swapspace-150x90.jpg 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/swapspace-450x269.jpg 450w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-99866" class="wp-caption-text">SwapSpace Invaders Club</figcaption></figure>
<ul>
<li><strong>Innovative feature:</strong> SwapSpace offers an enticing loyalty program centered around NFTs. By using the Invader NFT during exchanges, users can easily receive cashback from RevShare. Customizable NFTs allow users to find their Invader&#8217;s unique style using scenes, skins, and exclusive accessories from the store.</li>
<li><strong>User engagement:</strong> SwapSpace boasts a dedicated fan base that actively participates in the loyalty program and utilizes the platform&#8217;s services. In total, more than 4,300 NFTs were minted. Within two weeks of the launch, over 500 active users are actively participating in the loyalty program.</li>
<li><strong>Rewards:</strong> Users can enjoy up to 50% cashback and level up by making exchanges and completing tasks.</li>
<li><strong>Accessibility:</strong> The Personal Account feature allows users to track their exchange history and request payments at any time with 24/7 support.</li>
</ul>
<p style="text-align: center;"><a class="infobutton" href="https://swapspace.co/invaders?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=blockonomi&amp;utm_campaign=backlinks">Visit</a></p>
<hr />
<h3>2. Binance Rewards Program</h3>
<figure id="attachment_99867" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-99867" style="width: 1000px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-99867" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/binance.jpg" alt="Binance Rewards Hub" width="1000" height="598" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/binance.jpg 1000w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/binance-300x179.jpg 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/binance-768x459.jpg 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/binance-50x30.jpg 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/binance-150x90.jpg 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/binance-450x269.jpg 450w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-99867" class="wp-caption-text">Binance Rewards Hub</figcaption></figure>
<ul>
<li><strong>Innovative feature</strong>: Binance offers a tiered loyalty program based on Binance Points.</li>
<li><strong>User engagement:</strong> The Binance community is highly engaged, with users actively participating in trading competitions and other events.</li>
<li><strong>Rewards:</strong> Users can accumulate Points through tasks, campaigns, games, and point-based activities in the Rewards Hub. Points can be redeemed for rewards like Binance Vouchers, Gift Cards, game turns, non-profit donations, and more.</li>
<li><strong>Accessibility:</strong> Participation in the Binance loyalty program is seamless for existing platform users.</li>
</ul>
<p style="text-align: center;"><a class="infobutton" href="https://www.binance.com/rewards-hub">Visit</a></p>
<hr />
<h3>3. Coinbase Earn</h3>
<figure id="attachment_99868" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-99868" style="width: 1000px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-99868" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/earn-2.jpg" alt="Coinbase Earn" width="1000" height="598" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/earn-2.jpg 1000w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/earn-2-300x179.jpg 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/earn-2-768x459.jpg 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/earn-2-50x30.jpg 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/earn-2-150x90.jpg 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/earn-2-450x269.jpg 450w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-99868" class="wp-caption-text">Coinbase Earn</figcaption></figure>
<ul>
<li><strong>Innovative feature:</strong> Earn up to 9% APY (annual percentage yield) on your crypto assets and put them to work to earn rewards.</li>
<li><strong>User engagement:</strong> Coinbase has a large user base, and the Earn program has received positive feedback.</li>
<li><strong>Rewards:</strong> Users get rewarded for helping blockchain networks verify routine transactions in exchange for a small tradeoff in liquidity.</li>
<li><strong>Accessibility:</strong> Participation in Coinbase is open to all exchange users, making it easy for beginners to get started.</li>
</ul>
<p style="text-align: center;"><a class="infobutton" href="https://blockonomi.com/out/coinbase">Visit</a></p>
<hr />
<h3>4. Crypto.com Rewards+</h3>
<figure id="attachment_99869" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-99869" style="width: 1000px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-99869" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/crypto.jpg" alt="Crypto.com Rewards" width="1000" height="598" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/crypto.jpg 1000w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/crypto-300x179.jpg 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/crypto-768x459.jpg 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/crypto-50x30.jpg 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/crypto-150x90.jpg 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/crypto-450x269.jpg 450w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-99869" class="wp-caption-text">Crypto.com Rewards</figcaption></figure>
<ul>
<li><strong>Innovative feature:</strong> crypto.com offers a multi-tiered loyalty program, allowing users to get up to 8% back in CRON when using the Crypto.com Visa Card.</li>
<li><strong>User engagement:</strong> crypto.com has a dedicated fan base that actively participates in the loyalty program and uses the platform&#8217;s services.</li>
<li><strong>Rewards:</strong> Users can earn up to 10% p.a. on stablecoins, up to 8% back in CRON with Visa Card, and up to a US$200 bonus for each referral, with no limits.</li>
<li><strong>Accessibility:</strong> Participation in the Crypto.com loyalty program is open to all platform users, with clear guidelines on tier progression.</li>
</ul>
<p style="text-align: center;"><a class="infobutton" href="https://crypto.com/us/rewardsplus">Visit</a></p>
<hr />
<h3>5. KuCoin Rewards Hub</h3>
<figure id="attachment_99870" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-99870" style="width: 1000px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-99870" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/kucoin.jpg" alt="KuCoin Rewards" width="1000" height="700" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/kucoin.jpg 1000w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/kucoin-300x210.jpg 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/kucoin-768x538.jpg 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/kucoin-50x35.jpg 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/kucoin-150x105.jpg 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/kucoin-450x315.jpg 450w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-99870" class="wp-caption-text">KuCoin Rewards</figcaption></figure>
<ul>
<li><strong>Innovative feature:</strong> First Trade Reward offers users USDT rewards for completing their first trade in any amount, including spot, futures, margin, and bot trades.</li>
<li><strong>User engagement:</strong> KuCoin has a vibrant community actively providing liquidity to various token pairs.</li>
<li><strong>Rewards:</strong> Completing the Getting Started tasks earns users cryptocurrency rewards and coupons, which can be claimed upon signing up. Cryptocurrency rewards can be withdrawn once all tasks are completed, subject to platform approval and a processing time of 15 business days.</li>
<li><strong>Accessibility:</strong> KuCoin&#8217;s user-friendly interface and transparent bonus system have made it popular among active traders and investors.</li>
</ul>
<p style="text-align: center;"><a class="infobutton" href="https://www.kucoin.com/land/KuRewards">Visit</a></p>
<hr />
<h2>Comparative analysis of the programs</h2>
<p>Each of the programs on our list offers unique features and benefits to users, catering to a wide range of preferences and interests.</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>SwapSpace Invaders Club</strong> is distinguished by its focus on rewards and community engagement, providing users with a new way to earn and collect digital assets.</li>
<li><strong>Binance Rewards program</strong> is notable for offering a wide range of benefits, discounts, and privileges to users who own Binance Points, which attracts traders and investors who are looking for incentives to remain loyal to the platform.</li>
<li><strong>Coinbase Earn program</strong> allows users to generate passive income through an Annual Percentage Yield (APY), providing a straightforward way for users to grow their crypto assets over time.</li>
<li><strong>Crypto.com&#8217;s Rewards+</strong> set itself apart by offering exclusive investment opportunities and cashback rewards, appealing to users looking for diverse avenues to earn and expand their crypto holdings.</li>
<li><strong>KuCoin Rewards Hub</strong> is particularly attractive to active traders, thanks to its enticing offerings and bonuses tailored to meet the needs and preferences of this specific user group.</li>
</ul>
<hr />
<h2>Conclusion</h2>
<p>The cryptocurrency landscape in 2024 offers a diverse array of loyalty programs, each with its own unique appeal.</p>
<p>From <a href="https://swapspace.co/invaders?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=blockonomi&amp;utm_campaign=backlinks">SwapSpace&#8217;s innovative NFT-based rewards</a> to <a href="https://www.binance.com/rewards-hub">Binance&#8217;s comprehensive points system</a>, <a href="https://blockonomi.com/out/coinbase">Coinbase&#8217;s  earning approach</a>, <a href="https://crypto.com/us/rewardsplus">Crypto.com&#8217;s tiered benefits</a>, and <a href="https://www.kucoin.com/land/KuRewards">KuCoin&#8217;s trader-focused incentives</a>, there&#8217;s something for every type of crypto user.</p>
<p>These programs demonstrate the industry&#8217;s commitment to user engagement and retention through innovative reward structures. They not only incentivize platform usage but also educate users and foster community growth.</p>
<p>As crypto matures, we can expect these loyalty programs to evolve further as companies battle to gain and retain loyal users.</p>
<hr />
<h2>FAQs</h2>
<h3>What are cryptocurrency loyalty programs?</h3>
<p>Cryptocurrency loyalty programs are incentive schemes offered by crypto platforms to reward users for their engagement, loyalty, and participation in various activities. These programs typically offer benefits such as token rewards, discounted fees, exclusive promotions, and enhanced user experiences.</p>
<h3>How do I join a cryptocurrency loyalty program?</h3>
<p>Most loyalty programs are automatically available to users of the respective platforms. To join, you typically need to create an account on the platform and start participating in its activities. Some programs may require you to opt-in or meet certain criteria to access higher tiers of rewards.</p>
<h3>Are these loyalty programs free to join?</h3>
<p>Generally, joining these loyalty programs is free. However, some higher-tier rewards may require maintaining a certain balance or trading volume on the platform.</p>
<h3>Can I participate in multiple loyalty programs simultaneously?</h3>
<p>Yes, you can participate in multiple loyalty programs across different platforms. There are no restrictions on being a member of various programs at the same time.</p>
<h3>How safe are these loyalty programs?</h3>
<p>While the programs themselves are generally safe, it&#8217;s important to remember that they are tied to cryptocurrency platforms, which carry inherent risks. Always practice good security habits, such as using strong passwords and two-factor authentication.</p>
<h3>Do I need to pay taxes on rewards earned from these programs?</h3>
<p>Tax implications can vary depending on your country and the specific nature of the rewards. In many jurisdictions, rewards earned may be considered taxable income. It&#8217;s advisable to consult with a tax professional for guidance specific to your situation.</p>
<h3>Can the rewards earned be withdrawn or transferred to other platforms?</h3>
<p>This depends on the specific program and the type of rewards. Some rewards, like tokens or cryptocurrencies, can often be withdrawn or transferred. Others, like platform-specific points or discounts, may only be usable within the platform that issued them.</p>
<h3>How often do these loyalty programs update their offerings?</h3>
<p>Cryptocurrency platforms frequently update their loyalty programs to remain competitive and attractive to users. It&#8217;s a good idea to regularly check the terms and conditions of the programs you&#8217;re participating in to stay informed about any changes or new opportunities.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/cryptocurrency-loyalty-programs/">Best Cryptocurrency Loyalty Programs: Top 5 Options for 2024</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">99865</post-id>	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
