<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	
	xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
	xmlns:geo="http://www.w3.org/2003/01/geo/wgs84_pos#"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Cryptocurrency Trading News &amp; Updates: Latest Info from Blockonomi</title>
	<atom:link href="https://blockonomi.com/trading/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://blockonomi.com/trading/</link>
	<description>Cryptocurrency News &#38; Your Guide to the Blockchain Economy</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2024 08:06:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.7.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/fav-50x50.png</url>
	<title>Cryptocurrency Trading News &amp; Updates: Latest Info from Blockonomi</title>
	<link>https://blockonomi.com/trading/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
<site xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">134176212</site>	<item>
		<title>Hidden fees in Crypto Trading and How They’re Hurting your Portfolio</title>
		<link>https://blockonomi.com/hidden-fees-in-crypto-trading-and-how-theyre-hurting-your-portfolio/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Oliver Dale]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2024 08:06:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blockonomi.com/?p=107559</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Hidden fees often go unnoticed in crypto trading. But they can really affect your returns. With volatile markets and frequent trades, the costs can silently rack up and eat into your bottom line. Being aware of hidden fees and how to address them is crucial if you want to have success as a trader. The [...]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/hidden-fees-in-crypto-trading-and-how-theyre-hurting-your-portfolio/">Hidden fees in Crypto Trading and How They’re Hurting your Portfolio</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Hidden fees often go unnoticed in crypto trading. But they can really affect your returns. With volatile markets and frequent trades, the costs can silently rack up and eat into your bottom line. Being aware of hidden fees and how to address them is crucial if you want to have success as a trader.</p>
<h2><strong>The hidden fees dilemma</strong></h2>
<p>Crypto has seen explosive growth over the last decade. This growth has brought with it a wide variety of trading platforms. Each platform has its own fee structure, but the level of transparency can vary pretty drastically.</p>
<p>While some platforms provide clear fee breakdowns, others incorporate sneaky costs, like fees hidden within the bid-ask spread or additional charges on market orders.</p>
<p>What might seem like a small percentage fee can quickly compound for frequent traders. Over time, these seemingly minor costs add up. They eat into profits and hurt the returns of even the most well-thought-out strategies.</p>
<h2><strong>Why transparency matters in crypto trading</strong></h2>
<p>Fee transparency is more than just knowing what you’re paying &#8211; it means being able to make informed decisions. Because of varying and often complex fee structures, comparing fees across platforms can be confusing. Some platforms charge fees on both sides of a trade. Others include fluctuating spreads that aren’t always immediately clear.</p>
<p>The impact of hidden fees is felt even more by active traders. Frequent trading means taking an even bigger hit on high or hidden fees. This makes it extra-difficult to keep gains consistent in volatile markets like crypto.</p>
<h2><strong>Mitigating the impact of hidden fees</strong></h2>
<p>For traders, tackling the problem of hidden fees starts with understanding how different platforms structure their charges. This involves reading the small print. Look beyond headline rates and examine bid-ask spreads, maker/taker fees, and any other costs associated with transactions. It won’t take long to identify which platforms are being transparent, and which ones are keeping things intentionally opaque.</p>
<p>Platforms that prioritize fee transparency are your friend. They help traders take more control over their strategies. By providing clear breakdowns of costs upfront, transparent platforms allow you to trade with more confidence and precision.</p>
<h2><strong>Tradu Crypto stands out</strong></h2>
<p><a href="https://www.tradu.com/en/buy-crypto/?utm_source=blockonomi&amp;utm_medium=article">Tradu Crypto</a> is one example of a platform that offers a transparent fee structure. It’s set up to make trading costs clear and manageable. With options like zero commissions and raw spreads with minimal maker/taker fees, you can see the exact cost of their transactions upfront.</p>
<p>For high-volume traders, Tradu Crypto has additional benefits like instant rebates of up to 50%. This refreshing approach really helps to minimize costs.</p>
<p>Hidden fees are a big challenge, especially in crypto trading. Doing your homework &#8211; and choosing platforms with transparent pricing &#8211; can make a massive difference. By focusing on clear, predictable costs, you can protect profits and navigate the market more effectively.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/hidden-fees-in-crypto-trading-and-how-theyre-hurting-your-portfolio/">Hidden fees in Crypto Trading and How They’re Hurting your Portfolio</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">107559</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Where to Buy Klaytn (KLAY) Crypto Coin: Complete Guide</title>
		<link>https://blockonomi.com/buy-klaytn/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Oliver Dale]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2024 07:27:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Buying]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blockonomi.com/?p=67917</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Klaytn runs as a high-performance public blockchain and decentralized ecosystem. The protocol was created to enable companies and businesses to develop and apply blockchain technologies. As a result, the network offers many beneficial features that are intended to remove obstacles to blockchain adoption while speeding up the onboarding process. In this guide, we&#8217;ll discuss what [...]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/buy-klaytn/">Where to Buy Klaytn (KLAY) Crypto Coin: Complete Guide</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Klaytn runs as a high-performance public blockchain and decentralized ecosystem. The protocol was created to enable companies and businesses to develop and apply blockchain technologies.</p>
<p>As a result, the network offers many beneficial features that are intended to remove obstacles to blockchain adoption while speeding up the onboarding process.</p>
<p>In this guide, we&#8217;ll discuss what Klaytn is, why investors should invest in the digital asset KLAY, and the best wallets to store the token.</p>
<div class="callout">
<h2 style="text-align: center;">Where to Buy Klaytn KLAY</h2>
<p>This section is our top picks of where and how to buy the Klaytn KLAY Crypto token. We chose these based on our experience of using them and considered fees, security, payment options and reputation.</p>
<ul>
<li><strong><a href="/out/binance">Binance:</a> </strong>Largest Crypto Exchange with Low Fees</li>
<li><strong><a href="https://blockonomi.com/out/kucoin">Kucoin:</a></strong> Long Established Exchange With Lots of Listings</li>
<li><a href="https://blockonomi.com/out/gate"><strong>Gate:</strong></a> Solid Platform With Lots of Coins</li>
</ul>
<div class="verdict">
<h4 style="text-align: center;">Visit The Top Pick</h4>
<p style="text-align: center;"><a class="infobutton" href="/out/binance">Visit Binance</a></p>
</div>
</div>
<div class="callout">
<h3><img decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-1579 alignright" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/11/binance.gif" alt="Binance Review" width="150" height="150" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/11/binance.gif 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/11/binance-65x65.gif 65w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/11/binance-50x50.gif 50w" sizes="(max-width: 150px) 100vw, 150px" />Binance: Reputable Exchange with High Liquidity</h3>
<p><a href="/out/binance">Binance</a> is the largest cryptocurrency trading exchange in daily trade volumes. The exchange offers investors full access to trade over 600 crypto assets.</p>
<p>The renowned platform also features a well-detailed learning curve and advanced trading tools that support well-experienced traders and investors looking to learn how to buy different cryptos. Although Binance features a user-friendly interface that facilitates a great user experience, it is more suited for well-experienced traders.</p>
<p><strong>Read: <a href="https://blockonomi.com/binance-review/">Our Full Binance Review Here</a></strong></p>
<p>Binance has a minimum deposit of $10. This enables investors to kickstart their investing journey with low fees. Investors can also initiate deposits through seamless payment methods like wire transfers, credit/debit cards, peer-to-peer (P2P) payments, and other e-wallet solutions.</p>
<figure id="attachment_66588" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-66588" style="width: 785px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-66588" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/binance.jpg" alt="Binance Website" width="785" height="520" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/binance.jpg 785w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/binance-300x199.jpg 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/binance-768x509.jpg 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/binance-50x33.jpg 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/binance-270x180.jpg 270w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/binance-370x245.jpg 370w" sizes="(max-width: 785px) 100vw, 785px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-66588" class="wp-caption-text">Binance Website</figcaption></figure>
<p>Binance deposits come with a fee that varies based on the payment method used. For instance, the global exchange charges a standard fee of up to 4.50% for all deposits made with a debit/credit card.</p>
<p>All investors enjoy very low fees when trading on Binance, as it charges a standard trading fee of 0.1%. For investors that buy using Binance token (BNB), a discount of 25% on trading fees will be applied.</p>
<p>In addition, investors can rest assured that their funds and data are well protected whenever they trade on Binance. The broker features top-notch security measures like two-factor authentication (2FA), cold storage to keep most coins, whitelisting, and advanced data encryption to protect funds and data. Binance functions effectively in over 100 countries and has a spin-off regulated platform (Binance.US) that tends to US-based traders and investors.</p>
<p><strong>Pros</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Trading fees at 0.01%</li>
<li>High liquidity</li>
<li>Wide range of payment methods</li>
<li>600+ crypto assets in library</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Cons</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Interface is suited for advanced traders</li>
<li>US-based customers cannot trade most coins via its subsidiary</li>
</ul>
<div class="verdict">
<p style="text-align: center;"><a class="infobutton" href="/out/binance">Visit Binance</a></p>
</div>
</div>
<div class="callout">
<h3><img decoding="async" class="size-thumbnail wp-image-42275 alignright" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/kucoin-150x150.png" alt="" width="150" height="150" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/kucoin-150x150.png 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/kucoin-300x300.png 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/kucoin-50x50.png 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/kucoin-370x370.png 370w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/kucoin.png 400w" sizes="(max-width: 150px) 100vw, 150px" />KuCoin: Exchange With Lots of Listings</h3>
<p><a href="/out/kucoin">KuCoin</a> is one of the world's oldest and most popular crypto exchanges. The Seychelles-based broker is one of the most notable names in the market for traders who desire access to derivatives products to speculate in the market.</p>
<p>Currently, KuCoin provides access to over 600 cryptocurrencies. Besides trading and investing, the exchange allows investors to save, stake crypto, and even participate in Initial Exchange Offerings. With KuCoin, investors have an all-encompassing crypto hub.</p>
<p><strong>Read: <a href="https://blockonomi.com/kucoin-review/">Our Full Kucoin Review Here</a></strong></p>
<p>Like many brokers in its class, KuCoin could appear too overwhelming for beginners. The exchange is more suited for advanced traders who want to speculate and trade sophisticated products. So beginners might have some difficulty making use of it.</p>
<p>Despite this, investors could gain many benefits from trading with KuCoin. The broker has a low minimum balance of $5, with deposits available via major fiat currencies, peer-to-peer (P2P) transfers, and a few credit card options.</p>
<figure id="attachment_42262" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-42262" style="width: 808px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="wp-image-42262 size-full" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/kucoin.jpg" alt="Kucoin Homepage" width="808" height="585" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/kucoin.jpg 808w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/kucoin-300x217.jpg 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/kucoin-768x556.jpg 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/kucoin-50x36.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 808px) 100vw, 808px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-42262" class="wp-caption-text">Kucoin Homepage</figcaption></figure>
<p>As for trading fees, KuCoin users pay 0.1% in fees. But the fees could decrease based on an investor's 30-day trading volume and ownership of the company’s KCS token.</p>
<p>Security on KuCoin is also impressive. The system uses bank-level encryption and security infrastructures to protect users’ coins and data. KuCoin also has a specialized risk control department to enforce strict data usage policies.</p>
<p><strong>Pros</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Discounts available on trading fees</li>
<li>Extensive staking functionalities</li>
<li>Quick P2P trading system</li>
<li>Anonymous trading available</li>
<li>Low minimum balance</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Cons</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>No bank deposit option</li>
</ul>
<div class="verdict">
<p style="text-align: center;"><a class="infobutton" href="/out/kucoin">Visit Kucoin</a></p>
</div>
</div>
<div class="callout">
<h3><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="wp-image-5607 size-full alignright" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/03/gate-review.gif" alt="Gate Review" width="150" height="150" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/03/gate-review.gif 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/03/gate-review-65x65.gif 65w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/03/gate-review-50x50.gif 50w" sizes="(max-width: 150px) 100vw, 150px" />Gate.io: Solid Platform With Lots of Coins</h3>
<p><a href="https://blockonomi.com/out/gate">Gate.io </a>is a cryptocurrency trading site that aims to offer its members an alternative to the exchanges currently dominating the market.</p>
<p>The site has been in operation since 2017 and aims to capture a portion of the cryptocurrency trading market by offering its users hassle free access to a number of hard to find coins and up and coming projects.</p>
<p>The site is also designed to help investors find specific information related to both their preferred coins and overall market trends.</p>
<p><strong>Read: <a href="https://blockonomi.com/gate-io-review/">Our Full Gate.io Review Here</a></strong></p>
<p>Trading mostly takes place on a web-based trading platform that is similar to most cryptocurrency exchanges. The site incorporates a number of functional features such as an order book, trading history, and charting.</p>
<figure id="attachment_66924" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-66924" style="width: 785px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="wp-image-66924 size-full" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/gate-website.jpg" alt="Gate Website" width="785" height="548" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/gate-website.jpg 785w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/gate-website-300x209.jpg 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/gate-website-768x536.jpg 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/gate-website-50x35.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 785px) 100vw, 785px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-66924" class="wp-caption-text">Gate Website</figcaption></figure>
<p><strong>Pros</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>A wide range of currencies</li>
<li>A low fee structure</li>
<li>Simple registration process</li>
<li>Functional platform with a mobile app available</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Cons</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Unregulated</li>
<li>The team is not very transparent</li>
<li>No fiat currency transfers</li>
</ul>
<div class="verdict">
<p style="text-align: center;"><a class="infobutton" href="/out/gate">Visit Gate</a></p>
</div>
</div>
<hr />
<h2><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-68070" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/klaytn-logo.png" alt="" width="200" height="200" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/klaytn-logo.png 200w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/klaytn-logo-150x150.png 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/klaytn-logo-50x50.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 200px) 100vw, 200px" />What is Klaytn?</h2>
<p><a href="https://www.klaytn.foundation/">Klaytn</a> is an open-source blockchain focused on the creator economy, gamefi, and <a href="https://beanstalk.io/what-is-the-metaverse/">the metaverse</a>.</p>
<p>The platform, which was launched in June 2019, currently holds the lead in South Korea and is expanding its global business from its international base in Singapore.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-68065" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/klay.png" alt="" width="1328" height="636" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/klay.png 1328w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/klay-300x144.png 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/klay-1024x490.png 1024w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/klay-768x368.png 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/klay-50x24.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1328px) 100vw, 1328px" /></p>
<p>Klaytn focuses on innovative transformation that will empower people in the Web3 era of technology and business. In place of proof of work or proof of stake consensus, the platform employs the Practical Byzantine Fault Tolerance (PBFT) method.</p>
<p>There are no message exchanges between nodes in the PoW and POS algorithms, despite each node getting and validating blocks. However, with PBFT, each node interacts with other participating nodes to form a consensus, and the block&#8217;s finality may be ensured as soon as nodes succeed.</p>
<p>There are three different node types in Klaytn: CN (Consensus Node), PN (Proxy Node), and EN (Endpoint Node). Block generation is overseen by CCOs (Core Cell Operators), who also handle CNs. Every node in the network verifies these blocks.</p>
<p>In order to establish what the firm claims are the best environment for blockchain applications to flourish in their ecosystem, the Klaytn (KLAY) ecosystem offers a range of intriguing characteristics. These include transaction fee subsidisation for end users, robust transaction throughput, scalability facilitated by the service chain, and low latency network responsiveness.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-68066" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/meta.png" alt="" width="1326" height="564" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/meta.png 1326w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/meta-300x128.png 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/meta-1024x436.png 1024w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/meta-768x327.png 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/meta-50x21.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1326px) 100vw, 1326px" /></p>
<p>The interoperability of Klaytn with legacy technologies is another important element. According to the company&#8217;s official documentation, businesses can quickly switch to adopting the Klaytn blockchain technology.</p>
<p>The network&#8217;s utility and governance token is called KLAY. In the ecosystem, this cryptocurrency has several different functions. Investors can pay their transaction fees using KLAY. Additionally, it is a very quick and effective medium of trade. The token can be staked to ensure passive rewards and can even be used as secondary token collateral. 10 billion KLAY coins were issued at the time of Klaytn&#8217;s introduction, and there are currently <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/klaytn/">2.9 billion</a> KLAY coins in circulation.</p>
<hr />
<h3>Use Cases</h3>
<p><strong>Games</strong>: Wemade&#8217;s Klaytn-based P2E ( play to earn) game, MIR4, drew more than 1.3 million active players in less than three months after being available in 170 countries.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-68067" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/games.png" alt="" width="1325" height="574" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/games.png 1325w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/games-300x130.png 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/games-1024x444.png 1024w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/games-768x333.png 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/games-50x22.png 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/games-1170x508.png 1170w" sizes="(max-width: 1325px) 100vw, 1325px" /></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Exchanges/Defi</strong>: KLAY has a lot of global liquidity and is listed on several significant international exchanges, including Binance. With about $415.95M TVL (Total Value Locked), the DeFi ecosystem on Klaytn has likewise experienced exponential growth.</p>
<p><strong>Wallets</strong>: The Klaytn network is officially supported by Metamask, which is also easy to integrate into its ecosystem applications. Also, the Kakaotalk chat app has a wallet called Klip that links its 1.67 million KYC users to several DApps in the Klaytn ecosystem.</p>
<p><strong>Layer 2</strong>: WeMade&#8217;s Klaytn sidechain, WEMIX, is where the popular MMORPG MIR4 is hosted. WeMade has disclosed its intention to add 100 games to its platform. Also, BORA efficiently migrated to the Klaytn sidechain after its acquisition by Kakao Games. BORA has a stack of exciting projects revolving around NFTs and games in store for the future.</p>
<p><strong>Klaytn 2.0</strong>: With the announcement of further strategic agreements as part of its Klaytn 2.0 roadmap, Klaytn is set up for global growth.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-68068" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/roadmap.png" alt="" width="1336" height="577" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/roadmap.png 1336w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/roadmap-300x130.png 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/roadmap-1024x442.png 1024w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/roadmap-768x332.png 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/roadmap-50x22.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1336px) 100vw, 1336px" /></p>
<p>Here are some upgrades and changes that Klaytn has planned:</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Support for Ethereum Equivalence</strong>: By providing an Ethereum equivalent, Klaytn enhances the Ethereum environment while also using its unique advantages. Because Klaytn uses the same technology stack as Ethereum, projects based in the metaverse that find it difficult to work on Ethereum owing to its technical restrictions can do so more quickly and easily.</li>
<li><strong>Scale-Up Via Service Chains</strong>: As a scaling solution, Klaytn uses a hub-and-spoke design to preserve performance as the project ecosystem expands. Like in previous L2 solutions, the &#8220;spokes&#8221;, referred to as &#8220;Service Chains&#8221;, can be customised for specific dApp requirements and anchored to the main chain for increased security.</li>
<li><strong>Consensus Optimisation</strong>: TPS (Transaction Per Second) improvements operate as a performance multiplier in a &#8220;hub and spoke&#8221; design. Thus, the developers will simultaneously focus on optimising the consensus process to increase their chains&#8217; TPS.</li>
<li><strong>A Free and Friendly Environment for Developers</strong>: In line with its origins as an open-source, public blockchain project, Klaytn&#8217;s developers will devote efforts towards developing an end-to-end package for blockchain and metaverse developers to facilitate onboarding and a stack of open-source tools and platforms.</li>
<li><strong>Step Towards Centralisation</strong>: A fundamental principle of the metaverse and the coming economy is decentralisation. As part of the progressive transition towards decentralisation, Klaytn, which firmly believes in this shared global goal, will be revised using key components of the governance plan.</li>
</ul>
<hr />
<h2>Is Klaytn a Good Investment?</h2>
<p>Potentially, Klaytn has what it takes to deliver gains, especially considering its roadmap. However, always remember that the cryptocurrency market is volatile.</p>
<p>For investors seeking to invest in digital assets and exploring how to buy Klaytn, here are some unique features that make the digital asset worthwhile.</p>
<h3>A Complete Development Bundle for the Metaverse</h3>
<p>Klaytn provides an end-to-end metaverse package that includes tailored L2 solutions, chain explorers, SDKs and smart contract libraries, IPFS solutions, wallets, oracles and bridges, and an ecosystem of supporting services like stablecoin integration, NFT marketplaces, and tradefi interfaces.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-68069" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/metaverse.png" alt="" width="1306" height="507" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/metaverse.png 1306w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/metaverse-300x116.png 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/metaverse-1024x398.png 1024w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/metaverse-768x298.png 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/metaverse-50x19.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1306px) 100vw, 1306px" /></p>
<p>This bundle makes it easier to build for the metaverse.</p>
<h3>1-Second Deterministic Finality</h3>
<p>Klaytn uses an optimised version of Istanbul BFT to enable transactions to reach absolute finality in less than one second, allowing use cases where near-instant and irreversible finality is required, such as real-time minting of in-game item drops. This allows for responsive user experiences.</p>
<h3>Klaytn&#8217;s Data Guarantee</h3>
<p>Blockchains that use Proof-of-Work or Proof-of-Stake display probabilistic finality, meaning there is a minimal possibility that a transaction can be undone once it has been added to the chain. Due to this, many blockchains are inappropriate for mission-critical applications, especially when used at scale. Klaytn&#8217;s IBFT consensus algorithm provides the dependability and data consistency required for large-scale applications by ensuring that data stored on the blockchain is accurate and cannot be reversed.</p>
<h3>Access to Ethereum Equivalence</h3>
<p>Klaytn will adopt the EVM(Ethereum Virtual Machine) requirement through:</p>
<ul>
<li>Making the technological architecture of Klaytn comparable to the architecture of Ethereum in terms of execution and interface.</li>
<li>Building on top of the open-source codebases of the current Ethereum clients and interface libraries to inherit any upgrades made to them. Klaytn supports EVM as one of the developing standards for the metaverse and Web3.</li>
<li>Enabling contributions to both ecosystems from Klaytn Improvement Proposals (KIPs) and Ethereum Improvement Proposals (EIPs).</li>
</ul>
<h3>A Distinct Governance Framework</h3>
<p>The Governance Council (GC) of Klaytn is the cornerstone of their innovative approach to decentralisation. These GC members, which include top global companies and DAOs (Decentralised Autonomous Organisations) from various regions and industries, create a small validator network that may provide the advantages of a decentralised public blockchain while keeping the functionality of a permissioned blockchain. Furthermore, by adding more DAOs to its GC in the future to create a &#8220;DAO of DAOs&#8221;, Klaytn hopes to decentralise the system further.</p>
<h3>Integrated Scalability Through Service Chains</h3>
<p>The hub-and-spoke architecture, which is regarded as one of the best scalability solutions, is used by Klaytn. The spokes, or service chains, of Klaytn can be modified to meet particular DApp needs like high throughput, unique node configurations, or personalised security settings. Additionally, the inclusion of stacked service chains will offer the exponential scalability required for widespread adoption in the metaverse.</p>
<h3>Protocol-Level Ecosystem Fund of $1 Billion</h3>
<p>Klaytn has set aside a total of $1 billion to encourage ecosystem growth through a mix of the first issued reserve KLAY and on-chain tokenomics that re-invest 66% of newly-minted KLAY. The funds are dispersed among a variety of grant and incentive programmes:</p>
<ul>
<li>The Klaytn Improvement Reserve (KIR) for infrastructure, tools, and services that enhance the calibre of the Klaytn network.</li>
<li>The Klaytn Growth Fund (KGF) for projects in their early stages with a high likelihood of having a positive impact on Klaytn.</li>
<li>The Proof of Contribution (PoC) initiative rewards smart contract developers who help expand Klaytn&#8217;s on-chain operations.</li>
</ul>
<h3>The Preferred Business-Level Blockchain</h3>
<p>The leading mobile gaming companies, Netmarble and WeMade, as well as industry titans like the GMO Internet Group in Japan and the Salim Group in Indonesia, are partners with Klaytn, making Klaytn the blockchain of choice for corporations and enterprise-level use cases. Also, the Bank of Korea&#8217;s CBDC project, which utilises a private, ĺcustomised version of Klaytn, has chosen Klaytn as its official blockchain partner.</p>
<p>Klaytn maintains its integrity. However, for the digital asset to surge in the crypto market, clients must place their trust in it.</p>
<hr />
<h2>Klaytn Wallets</h2>
<p>Investors learning how to buy Klaytn have to also learn the best wallets to store the Klaytn crypto. A cryptocurrency wallet functions like a regular wallet and a bank account. It gives traders a place to save their coins and an easy way to spend and receive them.</p>
<h3>Software Wallet</h3>
<p>Hot wallets, also called software wallets, are one of the most popular cryptocurrency storage options. They are always online, hence the affiliation with the ‘hot’ tag. Investors can easily get a hot wallet once they open an account with a crypto exchange. This allows them to store and manage their private keys, which prove their ownership of their assets to the blockchain network. Hot wallets are usually more convenient for everyday crypto transactions and can be custodial or non-custodial.</p>
<figure id="attachment_66606" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-66606" style="width: 705px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-66606" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/hot-wallet.png" alt="Hot wallet" width="705" height="535" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/hot-wallet.png 705w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/hot-wallet-300x228.png 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/hot-wallet-50x38.png 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/hot-wallet-87x67.png 87w" sizes="(max-width: 705px) 100vw, 705px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-66606" class="wp-caption-text">Hot wallet</figcaption></figure>
<p>A custody wallet is responsible for storing assets to an exchange or a third-party platform. The user only places an order for a transfer or receipt, and the exchange signs off on the transaction, much like the traditional banking system. Meanwhile, a non-custodial or self-custody wallet gives the full responsibility to the end-user.</p>
<p>Hot wallets are usually free, but they are largely considered less secure due to their constant internet connectivity. An instance of a hot wallet is the Binance Wallet.</p>
<h3>Hardware Wallet</h3>
<p>A Hardware wallet is a device which has been created to provide an extra layer of security when interacting with your various cryptocurrency wallets.</p>
<p>Normally you would use your private key to move funds, the problem is though, if your computer has been compromised with malware or a virus, it is possible for your private keys to be captured and used to steal your funds.</p>
<figure id="attachment_66607" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-66607" style="width: 838px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-66607" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/cold-wallet.png" alt="Cold wallet" width="838" height="455" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/cold-wallet.png 838w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/cold-wallet-300x163.png 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/cold-wallet-768x417.png 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/cold-wallet-50x27.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 838px) 100vw, 838px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-66607" class="wp-caption-text">Hardware wallet</figcaption></figure>
<p>With a hardware wallet, the private keys are stored on the device and never exposed to your computer, which means even if you are infected with such a program your private keys will remain safe. These options are safest way to store your crypto if you have more than a small amount.</p>
<p>Popular examples of cold storage offerings are the Ledger and Trezor line of hardware wallet solutions, read our reviews:</p>
<ul>
<li><a href="https://blockonomi.com/ledger-nano-s-review/">Ledger Nano S Review</a></li>
<li><a href="https://blockonomi.com/ledger-nano-x-review/">Ledger Nano X Review</a></li>
<li><a href="https://blockonomi.com/trezor-vs-ledger/">Trezor vs. Ledger Review</a></li>
</ul>
<h3>Mobile wallet</h3>
<p>A mobile wallet is essentially a hot wallet on a smartphone device. They offer users an even more convenient way to use their coins for daily activities. Mobile wallets store and manage users' private keys while enabling them to pay for things they love with their digital assets.</p>
<figure id="attachment_66608" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-66608" style="width: 751px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-66608" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/mobile-wallet.png" alt="Mobile wallet" width="751" height="429" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/mobile-wallet.png 751w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/mobile-wallet-300x171.png 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/mobile-wallet-50x29.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 751px) 100vw, 751px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-66608" class="wp-caption-text">Mobile wallet</figcaption></figure>
<p>These wallets are usually free and always online for transactions to be processed. Popular mobile wallets are eToro Money Wallet and Coinbase Wallet.</p>
<h3>Desktop wallet</h3>
<p>A desktop wallet is a PC version of a hot wallet. It is essentially software that an investor downloads into their personal computer or laptop for easy interaction with their digital coins. They also offer a browser extension which allows users to interact using an extension instead of downloading the entire software. Desktop wallets are also hack-prone due to their online nature. A popular example is the Exodus Wallet.</p>
<h3>Paper Wallet</h3>
<p>The paper wallet is arguably the oldest form of crypto wallet. They are no longer common in the modern crypto industry. It contains users' public and private keys. The paper wallet is the least secure type of wallet as it can easily be lost, stolen, or torched.</p>
<hr />
<h2>Conclusion</h2>
<p>The Klaytn strategy is straightforward: make it simpler for companies to use blockchain services without it being a huge crisis. In particular, the network&#8217;s compatibility with legacy systems is a crucial draw for significant businesses prepared to make the switch. For the time being, Klaytn leads the field of enterprise-grade decentralised service providers. As more users become aware of the network&#8217;s beneficial qualities, we expect it to broaden its positioning.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/buy-klaytn/">Where to Buy Klaytn (KLAY) Crypto Coin: Complete Guide</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">67917</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Where to Buy API3 (API3) Crypto: Complete Beginner&#8217;s Guide</title>
		<link>https://blockonomi.com/buy-api3/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Oliver Dale]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2024 06:18:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Buying]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blockonomi.com/?p=67946</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Decentralized Autonomous Organizations DAOs provide hands-off governance for blockchain projects. One of the more recent projects disrupting this space is API3. The project aims to tackle the &#8216;Oracle problem&#8217; acting as a solution to connect APIs from data providers. Building the decentralized API network (dAPI) drew plenty of attention during the project development. Crypto enthusiasts [...]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/buy-api3/">Where to Buy API3 (API3) Crypto: Complete Beginner&#8217;s Guide</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Decentralized Autonomous Organizations DAOs provide hands-off governance for blockchain projects. One of the more recent projects disrupting this space is API3. The project aims to tackle the &#8216;Oracle problem&#8217; acting as a solution to connect APIs from data providers.</p>
<p>Building the decentralized API network (dAPI) drew plenty of attention during the project development. Crypto enthusiasts dub it &#8216;The Chainlink Killer&#8217; but is it?</p>
<p>This review looks at the API3 project in detail and how to buy the native API3 token. Does it offer value to the ecosystem? We&#8217;ll discuss how it works and how it solves these Oracle problems.</p>
<div class="callout">
<h2 style="text-align: center;">Where to Buy API3</h2>
<p>This section is our top picks of where and how to buy the API3 Crypto token. We chose these based on our experience of using them and considered fees, security, payment options and reputation.</p>
<ul>
<li><strong><a href="/out/binance">Binance:</a> </strong>Largest Crypto Exchange with Low Fees</li>
<li><strong><a href="/out/coinbase">Coinbase:</a> </strong>Highly Regarded and Easy to Use for Beginners</li>
<li><strong><a href="https://blockonomi.com/out/ftx">Kraken:</a></strong> Top Platform With High Liquidity</li>
</ul>
<div class="verdict">
<h4 style="text-align: center;">Visit The Top Pick</h4>
<p style="text-align: center;"><a class="infobutton" href="/out/etoro">Visit eToro</a></p>
</div>
</div>
<div class="callout">
<h3><img decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-1579 alignright" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/11/binance.gif" alt="Binance Review" width="150" height="150" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/11/binance.gif 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/11/binance-65x65.gif 65w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/11/binance-50x50.gif 50w" sizes="(max-width: 150px) 100vw, 150px" />Binance: Reputable Exchange with High Liquidity</h3>
<p><a href="/out/binance">Binance</a> is the largest cryptocurrency trading exchange in daily trade volumes. The exchange offers investors full access to trade over 600 crypto assets.</p>
<p>The renowned platform also features a well-detailed learning curve and advanced trading tools that support well-experienced traders and investors looking to learn how to buy different cryptos. Although Binance features a user-friendly interface that facilitates a great user experience, it is more suited for well-experienced traders.</p>
<p><strong>Read: <a href="https://blockonomi.com/binance-review/">Our Full Binance Review Here</a></strong></p>
<p>Binance has a minimum deposit of $10. This enables investors to kickstart their investing journey with low fees. Investors can also initiate deposits through seamless payment methods like wire transfers, credit/debit cards, peer-to-peer (P2P) payments, and other e-wallet solutions.</p>
<figure id="attachment_66588" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-66588" style="width: 785px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-66588" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/binance.jpg" alt="Binance Website" width="785" height="520" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/binance.jpg 785w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/binance-300x199.jpg 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/binance-768x509.jpg 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/binance-50x33.jpg 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/binance-270x180.jpg 270w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/binance-370x245.jpg 370w" sizes="(max-width: 785px) 100vw, 785px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-66588" class="wp-caption-text">Binance Website</figcaption></figure>
<p>Binance deposits come with a fee that varies based on the payment method used. For instance, the global exchange charges a standard fee of up to 4.50% for all deposits made with a debit/credit card.</p>
<p>All investors enjoy very low fees when trading on Binance, as it charges a standard trading fee of 0.1%. For investors that buy using Binance token (BNB), a discount of 25% on trading fees will be applied.</p>
<p>In addition, investors can rest assured that their funds and data are well protected whenever they trade on Binance. The broker features top-notch security measures like two-factor authentication (2FA), cold storage to keep most coins, whitelisting, and advanced data encryption to protect funds and data. Binance functions effectively in over 100 countries and has a spin-off regulated platform (Binance.US) that tends to US-based traders and investors.</p>
<p><strong>Pros</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Trading fees at 0.01%</li>
<li>High liquidity</li>
<li>Wide range of payment methods</li>
<li>600+ crypto assets in library</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Cons</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Interface is suited for advanced traders</li>
<li>US-based customers cannot trade most coins via its subsidiary</li>
</ul>
<div class="verdict">
<p style="text-align: center;"><a class="infobutton" href="/out/binance">Visit Binance</a></p>
</div>
</div>
<div class="callout">
<h3><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-37984 alignright" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/coinbase-review.gif" alt="Coinbase Review" width="150" height="150" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/coinbase-review.gif 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/coinbase-review-50x50.gif 50w" sizes="(max-width: 150px) 100vw, 150px" />Coinbase: Simple &amp; Easy to Use Exchange</h3>
<p><a href="/out/coinbase">Coinbase</a> is also a great option for investors looking for how to buy the crypto seamlessly. The US-based crypto trading platform enables users to buy, sell, and stake cryptocurrencies with zero complexity.</p>
<p>Coinbase integrates a user-friendly interface that simplifies crypto trading. The crypto trading platform supports well over 10,000 blockchain-based assets.</p>
<p><strong>Read: <a href="https://blockonomi.com/coinbase-review/">Our Full Coinbase Review Here</a></strong></p>
<p>The exchange’s signup and verification process take less than 10 minutes. For traders looking to invest easily, Coinbase is a great alternative to Binance.</p>
<p>Coinbase has a minimum deposit of $2, the lowest minimum deposit in the market presently This exchange also offers a wide range of deposit methods like automated clearing house (ACH), Wire transfer, debit card, and e-wallet solutions, as well as cashouts in local currencies like USD, GBP, and EUR. Coinbase charges up to 3.99% for debit card deposits.</p>
<figure id="attachment_66587" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-66587" style="width: 770px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-large wp-image-66587" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/coinbase-1024x490.png" alt="Coinbase Website" width="770" height="368" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/coinbase-1024x490.png 1024w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/coinbase-300x144.png 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/coinbase-768x367.png 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/coinbase-50x24.png 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/coinbase.png 1348w" sizes="(max-width: 770px) 100vw, 770px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-66587" class="wp-caption-text">Coinbase Website</figcaption></figure>
<p>Investors enjoy a 4% cash back reward whenever a Coinbase debit card is used for crypto purchases.</p>
<p>For fees, Coinbase charges a competitive fee of 0.5% - 4.5% depending on the payment method, cryptocurrency type, and transaction sizes.</p>
<p>Coinbase has evolved from a traditional exchange to a versatile platform with great services dedicated to retail and institutional investors, such as an in-built exchange wallet, self-issued cash back visa card, staking, derivatives, asset hubs, ventures, and many more.</p>
<p>Furthermore, Coinbase has in-built security practices like 2FA verification as an added security layer to investors’ usernames and passwords, crime insurance that secures digital assets from theft and fraud, and many more.</p>
<p>Also, Coinbase is licensed by the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) and regulated by top financial authorities like Financial Conduct Authority (FCA), Financial Crimes and Enforcement Network (FinCEN), and the New York State Department of Financial Services (NYSDFS).</p>
<p><strong>Pros</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Beginner-focused</li>
<li>Licensed and reputable platform</li>
<li>Insurance in case of hacks</li>
<li>Low minimum deposit</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Cons</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>High fee compared to competitors</li>
<li>No credit card deposits for US customers</li>
</ul>
<div class="verdict">
<p style="text-align: center;"><a class="infobutton" href="/out/coinbase">Visit Coinbase</a></p>
</div>
</div>
<div class="callout">
<h3><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-3084 alignright" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/01/kraken-review.gif" alt="Kraken Review" width="150" height="150" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/01/kraken-review.gif 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/01/kraken-review-65x65.gif 65w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/01/kraken-review-50x50.gif 50w" sizes="(max-width: 150px) 100vw, 150px" />Kraken: Top Crypto Platform with High Liquidity</h3>
<p>Founded in 2011, <a href="/out/kraken">Kraken</a> is one of the oldest and most popular <a href="https://blockonomi.com/cryptocurrency-exchanges/">cryptocurrency exchanges</a> currently in operation.</p>
<p>The exchange has built a reputation as being a secure destination for anyone interested in trading cryptocurrencies and it is also a popular choice for both traders and institutions across a variety of locations.</p>
<p><strong>Read: <a href="https://blockonomi.com/kraken-review/">Our Full Kraken Review Here</a></strong></p>
<p>Kraken retains an international appeal and provides efficient trading opportunities in numerous fiat currencies. Kraken is also the current world leader in terms of Bitcoin to Euro trading volumes.</p>
<figure id="attachment_42155" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-42155" style="width: 808px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-42155" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/kraken.jpg" alt="Kraken Homepage" width="808" height="683" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/kraken.jpg 808w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/kraken-300x254.jpg 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/kraken-768x649.jpg 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/kraken-50x42.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 808px) 100vw, 808px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-42155" class="wp-caption-text">Kraken Homepage</figcaption></figure>
<p>Kraken is most well known for its Bitcoin and Ethereum to cash (EUR and USD) markets; however a wide range of both fiat and cryptocurrencies are tradable on the platform</p>
<h4>Pros</h4>
<ul>
<li>Dedicated service for institutions</li>
<li>Great for beginners to use</li>
<li>High trading liquidity</li>
</ul>
<h4>Cons</h4>
<ul>
<li>The lengthy ID verification process</li>
</ul>
<div class="verdict">
<p style="text-align: center;"><a class="infobutton" href="/out/kraken">Visit Kraken</a></p>
</div>
</div>
<hr />
<h2>What is API3?</h2>
<p>To grasp the concept of the <a href="https://api3.org/">API3 project</a>, we must understand how it works. API stands for &#8216;Application Programming Interface.&#8217; It&#8217;s a well-documented protocol enabling the transfer of services and data. APIs are commonplace in the app development community, with most programmers being familiar with the technology.</p>
<p>An example of a functional API is the protocol designed to provide pricing data to cryptocurrency exchanges and aggregators, such as Coinmarketcap.com. The API has many useful applications, and it can monetize data in scenarios where data providers allow access to that data by developers for a fee.</p>
<figure id="attachment_67948" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-67948" style="width: 785px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-67948" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/web3-1.jpg" alt="Create trustless applications that interact with Web APIs" width="785" height="598" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/web3-1.jpg 785w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/web3-1-300x229.jpg 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/web3-1-768x585.jpg 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/web3-1-50x38.jpg 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/web3-1-87x67.jpg 87w" sizes="(max-width: 785px) 100vw, 785px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-67948" class="wp-caption-text">Create trustless applications that interact with Web APIs</figcaption></figure>
<p>This structure allows developers to build apps efficiently without creating everything themselves. We could think of APIs as a set of Lego blocks. Developers choose what they require from the API and connect it to their applications. The reality is that many apps would fail to launch or function without API.</p>
<p>This concept sounds like a dream for developers. However, the evolution of the space to dApps and Web 3.0 presents a few problems. The issue is that API infrastructure isn&#8217;t compatible with this new technology.</p>
<p>This stage is where API3 promises to make it possible for older API data providers and users to connect data sources to smart contracts. This functionality is possible without connecting to third-party intermediaries. API3 accomplishes this through the decentralized API network.</p>
<hr />
<h2>What Is the Value in dAPI?</h2>
<p>Oracle technology was supposed to act as the data provider to smart contracts before the creation of API3. One of the leading technologies in this space is the Chainlink project. Chainlink has a node sitting between its API provider and smart contract.</p>
<p>The issue with this infrastructure is it adds a new intermediary, completing the function of removing the third-party solution in the process. The problem with the design is Oracle networks are typically rent-seeking. This issue means the cost of the process continues to rise.</p>
<p>Since the Chainlink project is a dominant oracle network, it&#8217;s gaining a sole monopoly over all related data feeds. Unfortunately, this process creates a type of centralization. There&#8217;s also no means to govern data provided to Oracles.</p>
<p>Unfortunately, the nodes are neglected and chastised for providing incorrect or corrupt data. However, there are no penalties enforced on the provider.</p>
<hr />
<h2>What Is the Chainlink?</h2>
<p><a href="https://blockonomi.com/chainlink-guide/">Chainlink</a> distributes requests across data sources and oracles. API3 thinks the solution to the issue is allowing API providers to operate their nodes themselves. This model institutes competition, lowering the inflationary mechanism in the system while promoting decentralization. This structure gives the influence to govern the data provider.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-24162" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/11/chainlink-1.jpg" alt="Chainlink Guide" width="1400" height="933" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/11/chainlink-1.jpg 1400w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/11/chainlink-1-300x200.jpg 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/11/chainlink-1-768x512.jpg 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/11/chainlink-1-1024x682.jpg 1024w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/11/chainlink-1-50x33.jpg 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/11/chainlink-1-610x407.jpg 610w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/11/chainlink-1-450x300.jpg 450w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/11/chainlink-1-1300x866.jpg 1300w" sizes="(max-width: 1400px) 100vw, 1400px" /></p>
<p>The huge growth of the DeFi economy means it&#8217;s critical for apps to source reliable and trustworthy data. It also ensures the process is completely transparent. With the API3 system, oracles will own the services provided and the data turning them into &#8216;first-party&#8217; Oracles.</p>
<p>This design increases decentralization and allows transparent curation of the data feed, which is critical in all DeFi applications.</p>
<hr />
<h2>The Oracle Problem</h2>
<p><a href="https://blockonomi.com/oracles-guide/">The Oracle problem</a> is one of the central issues facing the implementation of smart contracts. The problem becomes apparent when on-chain smart contracts have enforceable rules and functions. However, this goes out the window when you realize it&#8217;s only useful for data already on the Ethereum network.</p>
<p>Unfortunately, there&#8217;s no way to build a smart contract around asset prices like stocks or precious metals when the data source is off-chain. This issue is the core of the Oracle problem. The challenge is to place this data on-chain and execute it in a trustless, decentralized manner.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-14397" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/oracles-guide.jpg" alt="What are Oracles?" width="1400" height="933" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/oracles-guide.jpg 1400w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/oracles-guide-300x200.jpg 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/oracles-guide-768x512.jpg 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/oracles-guide-1024x682.jpg 1024w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/oracles-guide-450x300.jpg 450w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/09/oracles-guide-1300x866.jpg 1300w" sizes="(max-width: 1400px) 100vw, 1400px" /></p>
<p>In addition, there must be protocols in place to verify the data and its source. When we rely on Oracles, we increase the vulnerable attack vectors in the smart contract and the Oracle provider. Blockchain engineers have looked for a solution to this issue since the development of smart contracts.</p>
<p>Some solutions, like Gnosis and Augur, implement the approach of prediction markets. However, the preferred strategy is an Oracle provider delivering data cost-effectively and anonymously without third-party interventions. This design formed the basis for the development of Chainlink.</p>
<hr />
<h2>Chainlink On-chain Oracles</h2>
<p>If we consider the state of these Oracle-based solutions, Chainlink takes center stage. It&#8217;s the preferred Oracle solution, making huge strides in the blockchain development community in recent years. The LINK project has a robust community, with the LINK token positioned as a blue-chip token with plenty of utility.</p>
<p>However, it&#8217;s important to note that while LINK does solve many issues, it does have problems. That&#8217;s where API3 steps in to provide the best solution. API3 presents the best solution to the Oracle problem, making it indispensable to devs.</p>
<hr />
<h2>The API Problem</h2>
<p>So, the Oracle problem is merely a simple oversight in smart contract development on the ETH network. Oracle development neglected to consider node decentralization when collecting and distributing Oracle data.</p>
<p>The reality is the issues Oracles solve aren&#8217;t as challenging and complex as you might assume. Essentially, what the Oracles are attempting to solve using a complex method, pulling off-chain data to on-chain contracts.</p>
<p>In this respect, Oracles compare with APIs in mobile and web applications. They achieve this since the solutions are required to deliver data to end users.</p>
<hr />
<h2>The API3 Solution</h2>
<p>Let&#8217;s look at how API3 resolves these issues. We know there are several issues with delivering accurate and secure data on-chain to smart contracts. Can API3 solve the problems effectively compared to the current Oracle solutions?</p>
<figure id="attachment_67949" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-67949" style="width: 785px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-67949" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/beacons.jpg" alt="Beacons allow smart contract developers to connect Web3 applications" width="785" height="598" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/beacons.jpg 785w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/beacons-300x229.jpg 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/beacons-768x585.jpg 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/beacons-50x38.jpg 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/beacons-87x67.jpg 87w" sizes="(max-width: 785px) 100vw, 785px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-67949" class="wp-caption-text">Beacons allow smart contract developers to connect Web3 applications</figcaption></figure>
<p>Essentially, API3 takes the value passed on to the nodes in Chainlink, delivering it to the data providers. As a result, the process removes the middleware, optimizing it. Instead of placing nodes between data providers and smart contracts, API3 simply turns the data providers into nodes.</p>
<p>This strategy removes unneeded, additional, and redundant layers, solving several problems that Chainlink is working on. It also presents a viable solution to Chainlink&#8217;s scaling issues as the protocol grows.</p>
<hr />
<h2>API3 Token Use Cases</h2>
<p>The API3 technology intends to use its decentralized autonomous organization (DAO) for governance protocols. This strategy means participants in the Chainlink ecosystem have a say in network security and development.</p>
<p>The API3 ecosystem relies on the API3 token for the following functions.</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Collateral</strong> – The API3 staking pool acts as collateral for on-chain insurance.</li>
<li><strong>Staking</strong> – API3 holders stake API3 to participate in on-chain governance and earn rewards.</li>
<li><strong>Governance</strong> – The API3 token provides a direct incentive for governance, like voting. Users that stake API3 receive a portion of the dAPI revenue. Their staked API3 tokens provide collateral for on-chain insurance.</li>
<li><strong>Disputes</strong> – dApps can open disputes and raise insurance claims in the case of lost revenue due to downtime, malfunction, or incorrect data. The dev team intends to use this functionality to resolve insurance claims.</li>
<li><strong>Payments</strong> – The dev team intends to charge a subscription fee for those dApps utilizing the dAPI network. Data providers will receive rewards in API3 tokens.</li>
</ul>
<hr />
<h2>API3 Governance</h2>
<p>Decentralized governance is a requirement for most blockchain projects in the modern era of web 3.0. API3 plans to cover this issue by incorporating a DAO governance protocol.</p>
<p>This structure adds value to the tokens beyond a simple monetary specification. It means holders of API3 tokens and those staking them get a say in the governance of the blockchain and the execution of any changes that occur.</p>
<p>Those users holding or staking API3 tokens decide on updates to governance changes, such as the fee structure. This structure allows no single point of failure in the direction and governance of the project&#8217;s development and operations.</p>
<p>Considering that API3 will operate as a data marketplace, this functionality will be incredibly powerful, making for a bullish sentiment on the API3 project and its future.</p>
<hr />
<h2>The API3 DAO</h2>
<p>The governance of the API3 protocol includes a staking mechanism. Staking allows for governance and voting. However, it also provides an incentive for users to stake their API3 tokens as insurance against malfunctions or data errors in the system.</p>
<figure id="attachment_67950" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-67950" style="width: 785px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-67950" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/dao.jpg" alt="API3 DAO" width="785" height="598" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/dao.jpg 785w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/dao-300x229.jpg 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/dao-768x585.jpg 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/dao-50x38.jpg 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/dao-87x67.jpg 87w" sizes="(max-width: 785px) 100vw, 785px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-67950" class="wp-caption-text">API3 DAO</figcaption></figure>
<p>While it might be somewhat naïve to assume these issues won&#8217;t occur, the model insinuates that these occurrences are minimal. We&#8217;ve seen similar data errors occur on other API platforms. So, it&#8217;s good to see that API3 acknowledges a solution for altering the possibility of this occurring.</p>
<p>The deflationary effect is another benefit API3 offers to users that choose to stake their tokens. This structure allows the community to maintain a stable market price, reducing volatility in the API3 price action in the market.</p>
<hr />
<h2>The API3 Token</h2>
<p>In November 2020, API3 conducted its private funding round, raising $3 million for the project. A public sale of <a href="https://api3.org/dao#token">API3 tokens</a> in December 2020 was a success, giving the ecosystem the funding it needs to develop and execute the protocol and network.</p>
<p>The public sale raised a staggering $23 million for the project, showing the interest in the utility API3 offers the dApp community. The API3 tokens went on sale using a bonding curve, beginning at $0.30 and eventually reaching $2.00.</p>
<p>The project experienced widespread adoption in the dApp market, experiencing a 1,300% increase in price during the mania of 2021. Despite losing much of that value in the crypto winter of 2022, it remains a viable project.</p>
<figure id="attachment_67952" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-67952" style="width: 785px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-67952" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/API3-Token.jpg" alt="API3 Token" width="785" height="598" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/API3-Token.jpg 785w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/API3-Token-300x229.jpg 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/API3-Token-768x585.jpg 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/API3-Token-50x38.jpg 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/API3-Token-87x67.jpg 87w" sizes="(max-width: 785px) 100vw, 785px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-67952" class="wp-caption-text">API3 Token</figcaption></figure>
<p>API3 tokens have a total circulating supply of 100,000,000 API3 tokens. The team sold 30 million API3 tokens in both sales, with ten million going to the private sale and twenty million going to the public sale.</p>
<p>It&#8217;s important to note the public tokens are unlocked, but the tokens sold in the private sale are subject to a vesting schedule of two or three years for the lock-up period. Early investors in the project stake their API3 tokens to receive incentive rewards for supporting the API3 ecosystem.</p>
<hr />
<h2>API3 Token Allocation</h2>
<p>The API3 tokens started trading on exchanges on December 1, 2020. The initial price was set at $1.30, and it steadily rose in value as the hours passed. Within a week, the API3 token was trading at $2 each, producing a 30%+ return in just 14 days.</p>
<p>While there was a dip under $2 by the end of 2020, the 2021 mania saw the price moon to $964 before experiencing a slow decline to a less volatile price, holding a range between $1.05 to $2.00 in H2 2022.</p>
<hr />
<h2>How to Buy API3 on eToro</h2>
<p>This broker offers low fees, high liquidity, a wide range of crypto offerings, top-notch security, and in-built wallet functionality. To get started seamlessly, follow these detailed steps:</p>
<p class="disclaimer">eToro USA LLC; Investments are subject to market risk, including the possible loss of principal.</p>
<h3>1. Sign Up</h3>
<p><a href="/out/etoro">Visit eToro</a> and click on the ‘Start Investing’ visible in the middle of the home page. This will redirect the investor to a registration page where they must enter a username, email address, and a strong password.</p>
<figure id="attachment_66610" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-66610" style="width: 770px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-large wp-image-66610" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/signup-1024x470.png" alt="Signup for eToro" width="770" height="353" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/signup-1024x470.png 1024w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/signup-300x138.png 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/signup-768x353.png 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/signup-50x23.png 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/signup.png 1359w" sizes="(max-width: 770px) 100vw, 770px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-66610" class="wp-caption-text">Signup for eToro</figcaption></figure>
<p>They can skip this process and sign up by connecting to a Google or Facebook account.</p>
<h3>2. Verify ID</h3>
<p>As a regulated broker, eToro requires that investors complete a know-your-customer (KYC) process on eToro. This process enables them to unlock this broker's full trading features and functionalities. To get started, click on the newly created profile icon and proceed to select the ‘Verification’ icon. Once done, upload a valid ID card. This could be in the form of a driver’s license or any government-issued identity card.</p>
<figure id="attachment_66611" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-66611" style="width: 687px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-66611" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/verify.png" alt="Verify your ID" width="687" height="456" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/verify.png 687w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/verify-300x199.png 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/verify-50x33.png 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/verify-270x180.png 270w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/verify-370x245.png 370w" sizes="(max-width: 687px) 100vw, 687px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-66611" class="wp-caption-text">Verify your ID</figcaption></figure>
<p>Investors will also be asked to submit a recent utility bill or bank statement to validate their addresses.</p>
<h3>3. Deposit Funds</h3>
<p>Once the verification process is complete, investors can proceed to initiate a deposit on their newly created eToro account. Click on the action tab, select ‘Deposit Funds’, choose a payment channel, and input the investment amount.</p>
<figure id="attachment_66612" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-66612" style="width: 497px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-66612" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/deposit-1.png" alt="Deposit Funds" width="497" height="527" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/deposit-1.png 497w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/deposit-1-283x300.png 283w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/deposit-1-47x50.png 47w" sizes="(max-width: 497px) 100vw, 497px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-66612" class="wp-caption-text">Deposit Funds</figcaption></figure>
<p>Investors in the UK and US can invest with a minimum deposit of $10 with cards and a minimum deposit of $500 for bank transfers. Once done, tap on the ‘Deposit’ icon to place an order.</p>
<hr />
<h2>API3 Wallets</h2>
<h3>Software Wallet</h3>
<p>Hot wallets, also called software wallets, are one of the most popular cryptocurrency storage options. They are always online, hence the affiliation with the ‘hot’ tag. Investors can easily get a hot wallet once they open an account with a crypto exchange. This allows them to store and manage their private keys, which prove their ownership of their assets to the blockchain network. Hot wallets are usually more convenient for everyday crypto transactions and can be custodial or non-custodial.</p>
<figure id="attachment_66606" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-66606" style="width: 705px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-66606" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/hot-wallet.png" alt="Hot wallet" width="705" height="535" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/hot-wallet.png 705w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/hot-wallet-300x228.png 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/hot-wallet-50x38.png 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/hot-wallet-87x67.png 87w" sizes="(max-width: 705px) 100vw, 705px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-66606" class="wp-caption-text">Hot wallet</figcaption></figure>
<p>A custody wallet is responsible for storing assets to an exchange or a third-party platform. The user only places an order for a transfer or receipt, and the exchange signs off on the transaction, much like the traditional banking system. Meanwhile, a non-custodial or self-custody wallet gives the full responsibility to the end-user.</p>
<p>Hot wallets are usually free, but they are largely considered less secure due to their constant internet connectivity. An instance of a hot wallet is the Binance Wallet.</p>
<h3>Hardware Wallet</h3>
<p>A Hardware wallet is a device which has been created to provide an extra layer of security when interacting with your various cryptocurrency wallets.</p>
<p>Normally you would use your private key to move funds, the problem is though, if your computer has been compromised with malware or a virus, it is possible for your private keys to be captured and used to steal your funds.</p>
<figure id="attachment_66607" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-66607" style="width: 838px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-66607" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/cold-wallet.png" alt="Cold wallet" width="838" height="455" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/cold-wallet.png 838w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/cold-wallet-300x163.png 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/cold-wallet-768x417.png 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/cold-wallet-50x27.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 838px) 100vw, 838px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-66607" class="wp-caption-text">Hardware wallet</figcaption></figure>
<p>With a hardware wallet, the private keys are stored on the device and never exposed to your computer, which means even if you are infected with such a program your private keys will remain safe. These options are safest way to store your crypto if you have more than a small amount.</p>
<p>Popular examples of cold storage offerings are the Ledger and Trezor line of hardware wallet solutions, read our reviews:</p>
<ul>
<li><a href="https://blockonomi.com/ledger-nano-s-review/">Ledger Nano S Review</a></li>
<li><a href="https://blockonomi.com/ledger-nano-x-review/">Ledger Nano X Review</a></li>
<li><a href="https://blockonomi.com/trezor-vs-ledger/">Trezor vs. Ledger Review</a></li>
</ul>
<h3>Mobile wallet</h3>
<p>A mobile wallet is essentially a hot wallet on a smartphone device. They offer users an even more convenient way to use their coins for daily activities. Mobile wallets store and manage users' private keys while enabling them to pay for things they love with their digital assets.</p>
<figure id="attachment_66608" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-66608" style="width: 751px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-66608" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/mobile-wallet.png" alt="Mobile wallet" width="751" height="429" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/mobile-wallet.png 751w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/mobile-wallet-300x171.png 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/mobile-wallet-50x29.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 751px) 100vw, 751px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-66608" class="wp-caption-text">Mobile wallet</figcaption></figure>
<p>These wallets are usually free and always online for transactions to be processed. Popular mobile wallets are eToro Money Wallet and Coinbase Wallet.</p>
<h3>Desktop wallet</h3>
<p>A desktop wallet is a PC version of a hot wallet. It is essentially software that an investor downloads into their personal computer or laptop for easy interaction with their digital coins. They also offer a browser extension which allows users to interact using an extension instead of downloading the entire software. Desktop wallets are also hack-prone due to their online nature. A popular example is the Exodus Wallet.</p>
<h3>Paper Wallet</h3>
<p>The paper wallet is arguably the oldest form of crypto wallet. They are no longer common in the modern crypto industry. It contains users' public and private keys. The paper wallet is the least secure type of wallet as it can easily be lost, stolen, or torched.</p>
<hr />
<h2>API3 – Conclusion</h2>
<p>Undoubtedly, API3 presents tremendous value to the DeFi space as blockchain adoption grows.</p>
<p>Devs can create complex, novel use cases, and those dApps created using the tech require better means of interfacing with third-party data providers.</p>
<ul>
<li>While existing oracle solutions are somewhat functional, several design compromises lead to severe problems as solutions scale. As a result, we could experience compromised data sets and an increase in costs that make the ecosystem exclusionary.</li>
<li>In the case of data corruption and compromise impact could be massive. The highly automated design of dApps and smart contracts will experience any data corruption spread throughout the network. The API3 solution enables API providers to operate Airnode oracles, giving interoperability with all third-party providers in a decentralized process.</li>
<li>It ensures the API providers have the required incentive to produce high-quality, trusted data. When we consider the potential for significant returns offered to node operators in oracle systems, API providers will likely capitalize on the ability to provide services and data via the easy-to-implement Airnodes.</li>
</ul>
<p>Unless we see something superior, it appears API3 brings a powerful solution to the Oracle problem by connecting conventional API services and decentralized blockchain tech. While it&#8217;s too early to assume API3 is the solution to the Oracle problem, it certainly looks promising.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/buy-api3/">Where to Buy API3 (API3) Crypto: Complete Beginner&#8217;s Guide</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">67946</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Where To Buy BitTorrent Coin (BTT) Crypto: Beginner’s Guide</title>
		<link>https://blockonomi.com/buy-bittorrent/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jimmy Aki]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2024 05:48:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Buying]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blockonomi.com/?p=67060</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Before the Tron Network acquisition, BitTorrent was one of the most successful decentralized platforms. The protocol allows users to share files directly without the interference of a central entity. The project&#8217;s eventual integration with Tron has further heightened interests, and investors are keen to learn how to buy BitTorrent for its potential growth. This guide [...]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/buy-bittorrent/">Where To Buy BitTorrent Coin (BTT) Crypto: Beginner’s Guide</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Before the Tron Network acquisition, BitTorrent was one of the most successful decentralized platforms. The protocol allows users to share files directly without the interference of a central entity.</p>
<p>The project&#8217;s eventual integration with Tron has further heightened interests, and investors are keen to learn how to buy BitTorrent for its potential growth.</p>
<p>This guide will provide a tutorial on how to buy BitTorrent in minutes and why this thriving and rapidly developing TRON-based cryptocurrency is so popular.</p>
<div class="callout">
<h2 style="text-align: center;">Where to Buy BitTorrent BTT</h2>
<p>This section is our top picks of where and how to buy the BitTorrent BTT Crypto token. We chose these based on our experience of using them and considered fees, security, payment options and reputation.</p>
<ul>
<li><strong><a href="/out/binance">Binance:</a> </strong>Largest Crypto Exchange with Low Fees</li>
<li><strong><a href="https://blockonomi.com/out/kraken">Kraken:</a></strong> Great Exchange for Newbies &amp; Advanced Users</li>
<li><a href="https://blockonomi.com/out/gate"><strong>Gate:</strong></a> Solid Platform With Lots of Coins</li>
</ul>
<div class="verdict">
<h4 style="text-align: center;">Visit The Top Pick</h4>
<p style="text-align: center;"><a class="infobutton" href="/out/binance">Visit Binance</a></p>
</div>
</div>
<div class="callout">
<h3><img decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-1579 alignright" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/11/binance.gif" alt="Binance Review" width="150" height="150" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/11/binance.gif 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/11/binance-65x65.gif 65w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/11/binance-50x50.gif 50w" sizes="(max-width: 150px) 100vw, 150px" />Binance: Reputable Exchange with High Liquidity</h3>
<p><a href="/out/binance">Binance</a> is the largest cryptocurrency trading exchange in daily trade volumes. The exchange offers investors full access to trade over 600 crypto assets.</p>
<p>The renowned platform also features a well-detailed learning curve and advanced trading tools that support well-experienced traders and investors looking to learn how to buy different cryptos. Although Binance features a user-friendly interface that facilitates a great user experience, it is more suited for well-experienced traders.</p>
<p><strong>Read: <a href="https://blockonomi.com/binance-review/">Our Full Binance Review Here</a></strong></p>
<p>Binance has a minimum deposit of $10. This enables investors to kickstart their investing journey with low fees. Investors can also initiate deposits through seamless payment methods like wire transfers, credit/debit cards, peer-to-peer (P2P) payments, and other e-wallet solutions.</p>
<figure id="attachment_66588" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-66588" style="width: 785px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-66588" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/binance.jpg" alt="Binance Website" width="785" height="520" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/binance.jpg 785w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/binance-300x199.jpg 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/binance-768x509.jpg 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/binance-50x33.jpg 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/binance-270x180.jpg 270w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/binance-370x245.jpg 370w" sizes="(max-width: 785px) 100vw, 785px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-66588" class="wp-caption-text">Binance Website</figcaption></figure>
<p>Binance deposits come with a fee that varies based on the payment method used. For instance, the global exchange charges a standard fee of up to 4.50% for all deposits made with a debit/credit card.</p>
<p>All investors enjoy very low fees when trading on Binance, as it charges a standard trading fee of 0.1%. For investors that buy using Binance token (BNB), a discount of 25% on trading fees will be applied.</p>
<p>In addition, investors can rest assured that their funds and data are well protected whenever they trade on Binance. The broker features top-notch security measures like two-factor authentication (2FA), cold storage to keep most coins, whitelisting, and advanced data encryption to protect funds and data. Binance functions effectively in over 100 countries and has a spin-off regulated platform (Binance.US) that tends to US-based traders and investors.</p>
<p><strong>Pros</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Trading fees at 0.01%</li>
<li>High liquidity</li>
<li>Wide range of payment methods</li>
<li>600+ crypto assets in library</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Cons</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Interface is suited for advanced traders</li>
<li>US-based customers cannot trade most coins via its subsidiary</li>
</ul>
<div class="verdict">
<p style="text-align: center;"><a class="infobutton" href="/out/binance">Visit Binance</a></p>
</div>
</div>
<div class="callout">
<h3><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-3084 alignright" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/01/kraken-review.gif" alt="Kraken Review" width="150" height="150" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/01/kraken-review.gif 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/01/kraken-review-65x65.gif 65w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/01/kraken-review-50x50.gif 50w" sizes="(max-width: 150px) 100vw, 150px" />Kraken: Top Crypto Platform with High Liquidity</h3>
<p>Founded in 2011, <a href="/out/kraken">Kraken</a> is one of the oldest and most popular <a href="https://blockonomi.com/cryptocurrency-exchanges/">cryptocurrency exchanges</a> currently in operation.</p>
<p>The exchange has built a reputation as being a secure destination for anyone interested in trading cryptocurrencies and it is also a popular choice for both traders and institutions across a variety of locations.</p>
<p><strong>Read: <a href="https://blockonomi.com/kraken-review/">Our Full Kraken Review Here</a></strong></p>
<p>Kraken retains an international appeal and provides efficient trading opportunities in numerous fiat currencies. Kraken is also the current world leader in terms of Bitcoin to Euro trading volumes.</p>
<figure id="attachment_42155" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-42155" style="width: 808px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-42155" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/kraken.jpg" alt="Kraken Homepage" width="808" height="683" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/kraken.jpg 808w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/kraken-300x254.jpg 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/kraken-768x649.jpg 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/kraken-50x42.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 808px) 100vw, 808px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-42155" class="wp-caption-text">Kraken Homepage</figcaption></figure>
<p>Kraken is most well known for its Bitcoin and Ethereum to cash (EUR and USD) markets; however a wide range of both fiat and cryptocurrencies are tradable on the platform</p>
<h4>Pros</h4>
<ul>
<li>Dedicated service for institutions</li>
<li>Great for beginners to use</li>
<li>High trading liquidity</li>
</ul>
<h4>Cons</h4>
<ul>
<li>The lengthy ID verification process</li>
</ul>
<div class="verdict">
<p style="text-align: center;"><a class="infobutton" href="/out/kraken">Visit Kraken</a></p>
</div>
</div>
<div class="callout">
<h3><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="wp-image-5607 size-full alignright" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/03/gate-review.gif" alt="Gate Review" width="150" height="150" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/03/gate-review.gif 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/03/gate-review-65x65.gif 65w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/03/gate-review-50x50.gif 50w" sizes="(max-width: 150px) 100vw, 150px" />Gate.io: Solid Platform With Lots of Coins</h3>
<p><a href="https://blockonomi.com/out/gate">Gate.io </a>is a cryptocurrency trading site that aims to offer its members an alternative to the exchanges currently dominating the market.</p>
<p>The site has been in operation since 2017 and aims to capture a portion of the cryptocurrency trading market by offering its users hassle free access to a number of hard to find coins and up and coming projects.</p>
<p>The site is also designed to help investors find specific information related to both their preferred coins and overall market trends.</p>
<p><strong>Read: <a href="https://blockonomi.com/gate-io-review/">Our Full Gate.io Review Here</a></strong></p>
<p>Trading mostly takes place on a web-based trading platform that is similar to most cryptocurrency exchanges. The site incorporates a number of functional features such as an order book, trading history, and charting.</p>
<figure id="attachment_66924" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-66924" style="width: 785px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="wp-image-66924 size-full" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/gate-website.jpg" alt="Gate Website" width="785" height="548" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/gate-website.jpg 785w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/gate-website-300x209.jpg 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/gate-website-768x536.jpg 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/gate-website-50x35.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 785px) 100vw, 785px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-66924" class="wp-caption-text">Gate Website</figcaption></figure>
<p><strong>Pros</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>A wide range of currencies</li>
<li>A low fee structure</li>
<li>Simple registration process</li>
<li>Functional platform with a mobile app available</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Cons</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Unregulated</li>
<li>The team is not very transparent</li>
<li>No fiat currency transfers</li>
</ul>
<div class="verdict">
<p style="text-align: center;"><a class="infobutton" href="/out/gate">Visit Gate</a></p>
</div>
</div>
<hr />
<h2>What Is BitTorrent-New (BTT)?</h2>
<p>BitTorrent (BTT) is a utility token deployed on <img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="alignright wp-image-67068" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Screenshot-2022-08-24-at-15.44.50.png" alt="" width="225" height="86" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Screenshot-2022-08-24-at-15.44.50.png 136w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Screenshot-2022-08-24-at-15.44.50-50x19.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 225px) 100vw, 225px" />TRON’s blockchain. It powers popular decentralised applications and protocols &#8212; BitTorrent File System, BitTorrent Speed, and DLive.</p>
<p>These DApps use the BitTorrent protocol to share and transfer data and files swiftly. As a result, BTT became the largest file-sharing protocol in the year 2019.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-67069 aligncenter" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Screenshot-2022-08-24-at-15.44.58.png" alt="" width="1168" height="517" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Screenshot-2022-08-24-at-15.44.58.png 1168w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Screenshot-2022-08-24-at-15.44.58-300x133.png 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Screenshot-2022-08-24-at-15.44.58-1024x453.png 1024w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Screenshot-2022-08-24-at-15.44.58-768x340.png 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Screenshot-2022-08-24-at-15.44.58-50x22.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1168px) 100vw, 1168px" />By incorporating a hybrid consensus mechanism, BitTorrent has eliminated the accessibility problems.</p>
<p>BitTorrent also relies on a cryptographic method that is based on zero disclosure and mathematical consistency on a blockchain-enabled transaction; this cross-checks data seamlessly without revealing data or third parties involved in the transaction. This has provided solutions to the issues of security.</p>
<p>All these wouldn’t have been possible without the advent of the Zyro protocol. This protocol acts as the mainstream of the entire decentralised finance ecosystem.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-67072" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Screenshot-2022-08-24-at-15.51.35.png" alt="" width="1272" height="278" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Screenshot-2022-08-24-at-15.51.35.png 1272w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Screenshot-2022-08-24-at-15.51.35-300x66.png 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Screenshot-2022-08-24-at-15.51.35-1024x224.png 1024w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Screenshot-2022-08-24-at-15.51.35-768x168.png 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Screenshot-2022-08-24-at-15.51.35-50x11.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1272px) 100vw, 1272px" />BitTorrent also acts as a unique protocol for peer-to-peer exchange, and its entrance into the crypto industry via its native token, BTT, has boosted power, utility, and usability by users among several platforms.</p>
<p>A distinguishing feature that makes BitTorrent stand out among its peers is its high liquidity and the lightning speed of transactions on the BTT ecosystem. This feature gives it an advantage that can be compared to other Ethereum-based decentralised finance protocols and enables several mining avenues for all users. This shows that the BTT token is a catalyst that implements smart contracts and processes all transfer funds.</p>
<p>In general, the BitTorrent protocol is trusted. It is the first choice regarding file sharing and faster downloads. Launched in 2001 by Bram Cohen, the protocol offers seamless interoperability with other chains like TRON and Binance Smart Chain.</p>
<p>Its most recent project is the DLive protocol, the first-ever decentralised live streaming platform powered by BTT. With more progressions likely to occur, crypto enthusiasts are eager to learn how to buy BitTorrent.</p>
<hr />
<h2>What Can You Do With BitTorrent (BTT)?</h2>
<p>BitTorrent (BTT) is experiencing exponential growth through its unique real-life use cases:</p>
<h3>Fast Download Speed</h3>
<p>BitTorrent lightning-speed is the primary use case of the BTT tokens. Users who are downloading content can pay BTT tokens to uploaders for swift download speeds. As a result, BTT tokens can be received and used swiftly by both uploaders and downloaders.</p>
<p>BitTorrent automatically boosts the number of files available and the demand for those files by allowing users to optimise their overall experience through the &#8216;faster downloads&#8217; integration and providing economic rewards for those uploading files.</p>
<h3>Decentralised Live Streaming</h3>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-67071" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Screenshot-2022-08-24-at-15.46.51.png" alt="" width="1252" height="454" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Screenshot-2022-08-24-at-15.46.51.png 1252w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Screenshot-2022-08-24-at-15.46.51-300x109.png 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Screenshot-2022-08-24-at-15.46.51-1024x371.png 1024w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Screenshot-2022-08-24-at-15.46.51-768x278.png 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Screenshot-2022-08-24-at-15.46.51-50x18.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1252px) 100vw, 1252px" />DLive is a decentralised streaming network powered by the TRON network. BitTorrent acquired it in 2019. DLive uses BTT to reward content creators, viewers, and those who stake tokens on the platform. Viewers can seamlessly subscribe to channels and donate to their favourite streamers using BTT. Creators can also reward users economically by paying small rewards of BTT whenever a challenge is completed.</p>
<h3>Investment</h3>
<p>Just like most crypto assets, one of the primary use cases of BTT is speculating on the price of the token growing exponentially in the future. BTT has inherent worth and will never approach the zero-value mark because BitTorrent has proven itself as a network with real-life utilities sought by active users who rely on BTT to function properly. BTT is an option for investors who want to hedge risk while gaining a lot.</p>
<hr />
<h2>How Does the BitTorrent-New Work?</h2>
<p>Since BitTorrent is a peer-to-peer protocol, computers in a BitTorrent swarm (a group of computers used to download and upload the same file/torrent ) can transfer data seamlessly without needing a central server.</p>
<p>BitTorrent multi-peers systems facilitate faster downloads. Instead of connecting to only one source, users can connect to several sources. This has enabled people with lower bandwidth to join in with file-sharing activities and realise the idea of increasing data distribution by breaking up very large files into smaller bits.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-67070" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Screenshot-2022-08-24-at-15.45.17.png" alt="" width="588" height="458" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Screenshot-2022-08-24-at-15.45.17.png 588w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Screenshot-2022-08-24-at-15.45.17-300x234.png 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Screenshot-2022-08-24-at-15.45.17-50x39.png 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Screenshot-2022-08-24-at-15.45.17-87x67.png 87w" sizes="(max-width: 588px) 100vw, 588px" />On the BitTorrent platform, the first uploader of a file (often regarded as a torrent) is the ‘seed’; those who download the file are known as ‘peers’. When the download is complete, they also become a seed. Each seed has a piece of the file (the downloaded file) which is encrypted by a cryptographic hash (a digital key code) embedded in the file descriptor. The more seeds created in the BitTorrent network, the faster it becomes to download the file seamlessly. If a file doesn’t have a seeder, it won’t be possible to download as there is no connected user with the complete file.</p>
<hr />
<h2>Is BitTorrent Crypto a Good Investment?</h2>
<p>Many crypto enthusiasts and experts believe BTT to be a fairly underrated token given that it is based on the TRON foundation, has great utility, and is priced under a dollar. Here are major reasons this digital asset is considered a great investment option:</p>
<h3>BitTorrent is a TRC-20 Token</h3>
<p>BitTorrent (BTT) is deployed on TRON, a reputable blockchain project. The successes recorded by the TRON chain will continue to rub off on BitTorrent&#8217;s entire ecosystem. This is likely to generate massive gains in the future. In addition, TRON Foundation will continue to create integrations capable of improving BitTorrent, and BTT will enjoy the benefits of its acquisition.</p>
<h3>BTT Is Relatively Cheap</h3>
<p>BitTorrent native coin, BTT, is one of the fastest-rising cryptocurrencies in the market today, with its price pegged at less than a dollar. This means that investors can buy BTT tokens with little funds and generate massive gains once a bullish run sets in.</p>
<h3>BTT Is Attractive to Long-Term Investors</h3>
<p>Long-term investors are often the best earners in the crypto market. HODLING a crypto token is a rewarding investment strategy. It involves purchasing a token and waiting for a long period (after it has generated interest/growth in value) before selling. As earlier stated, BTT is a cheap crypto token but might grow over a long time. Investors ready to wait for months/years will surely stand a good chance of seeing their investments become great fortunes in the future.</p>
<h3>Ethereum Virtual Machine (EVM) Compatibility</h3>
<p>BitTorrent is compatible with all Ethereum-based smart contracts. The BitTorrent Chain enables developers to migrate and build decentralised applications (DApps) easily.</p>
<p>Ethereum is currently the largest hub for dApps and boasts of 3000 plus blockchain-focused applications. BiTorrent is compatible with the foremost smart contract network, meaning developers on the Tron Network can simultaneously launch dApps on both blockchain protocols with ease.</p>
<p>Even more impressive is the fact that Solidity-based smart contracts can run on BitTorrent seamlessly. This gives developers easy access to the robust ecosystem of both Ethereum and Tron networks, as all blockchain services can be executed cross-chain.</p>
<hr />
<h2>How to Buy BitTorrent-New on Binance</h2>
<p>Investors can easily buy BitTorrent-New (BTT) with very low fees and enjoy high liquidity, a wide range of payment channels, and top-notch security anywhere Binance is available.</p>
<p>The following is an in-depth guide designed to assist investors in getting started:</p>
<h3>Step 1. Create a Binance Account</h3>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-66790" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/binance-register--scaled.jpg" alt="" width="2560" height="1381" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/binance-register--scaled.jpg 2560w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/binance-register--300x162.jpg 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/binance-register--1024x552.jpg 1024w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/binance-register--768x414.jpg 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/binance-register--1536x828.jpg 1536w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/binance-register--2048x1105.jpg 2048w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/binance-register--50x27.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px" />Creating an account is the first step to buying BitTorrent (BTT) tokens on Binance. Simply select ‘Create a Personal Account’ to register for an individualised trading account.</p>
<p>Investors must submit a valid email address and input a strong password they can always remember. The password can consist of symbols, numbers, and alphabets. To verify a phone line and an email address, users will need to input a cellphone number after tapping the &#8216;Next&#8217; button to move to the next screen page.</p>
<h3>Step 2. Verify Account</h3>
<p>Binance, just like all regulated exchanges, requires users to provide KYC (Know-Your-Customer) information and complete some verifications to access the platform’s full features. This ranges from government-issued identity card(s) to driver’s licenses. Proceed to complete the face verification process.</p>
<h3>Step 3. Deposit Funds</h3>
<figure id="attachment_66584" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-66584" style="width: 675px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-66584" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/deposit.png" alt="Deposit on Binance" width="675" height="434" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/deposit.png 675w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/deposit-300x193.png 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/deposit-50x32.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 675px) 100vw, 675px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-66584" class="wp-caption-text">Deposit on Binance</figcaption></figure>
<p>The next step is the deposit. Binance features many payment options, from bank transfer and credit/debit cards to peer-to-peer (P2P) and e-wallet solutions like PayPal. Click on the ‘Deposit’ icon, type in the amount to invest, choose a payment channel, and tap on ‘Deposit’ to fund the newly created account.</p>
<h3>Step 4. Buy BTT</h3>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-67073" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Screenshot-2022-08-24-at-15.52.59.png" alt="" width="453" height="429" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Screenshot-2022-08-24-at-15.52.59.png 453w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Screenshot-2022-08-24-at-15.52.59-300x284.png 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Screenshot-2022-08-24-at-15.52.59-50x47.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 453px) 100vw, 453px" />After a successful payment using the chosen payment method, proceed to the search bar menu, type ‘BTT’, and click on relevant results. Investors can now place a buy order, so Binance knows they wish to buy BTT. Once investors have successfully placed a buy order, the BTT tokens will be added to their wallets once the transaction has been processed and finished.</p>
<hr />
<h2>BitTorrent BTT Wallets</h2>
<h3>Software Wallet</h3>
<p>Hot wallets, also called software wallets, are one of the most popular cryptocurrency storage options. They are always online, hence the affiliation with the ‘hot’ tag. Investors can easily get a hot wallet once they open an account with a crypto exchange. This allows them to store and manage their private keys, which prove their ownership of their assets to the blockchain network. Hot wallets are usually more convenient for everyday crypto transactions and can be custodial or non-custodial.</p>
<figure id="attachment_66606" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-66606" style="width: 705px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-66606" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/hot-wallet.png" alt="Hot wallet" width="705" height="535" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/hot-wallet.png 705w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/hot-wallet-300x228.png 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/hot-wallet-50x38.png 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/hot-wallet-87x67.png 87w" sizes="(max-width: 705px) 100vw, 705px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-66606" class="wp-caption-text">Hot wallet</figcaption></figure>
<p>A custody wallet is responsible for storing assets to an exchange or a third-party platform. The user only places an order for a transfer or receipt, and the exchange signs off on the transaction, much like the traditional banking system. Meanwhile, a non-custodial or self-custody wallet gives the full responsibility to the end-user.</p>
<p>Hot wallets are usually free, but they are largely considered less secure due to their constant internet connectivity. An instance of a hot wallet is the Binance Wallet.</p>
<h3>Hardware Wallet</h3>
<p>A Hardware wallet is a device which has been created to provide an extra layer of security when interacting with your various cryptocurrency wallets.</p>
<p>Normally you would use your private key to move funds, the problem is though, if your computer has been compromised with malware or a virus, it is possible for your private keys to be captured and used to steal your funds.</p>
<figure id="attachment_66607" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-66607" style="width: 838px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-66607" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/cold-wallet.png" alt="Cold wallet" width="838" height="455" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/cold-wallet.png 838w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/cold-wallet-300x163.png 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/cold-wallet-768x417.png 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/cold-wallet-50x27.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 838px) 100vw, 838px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-66607" class="wp-caption-text">Hardware wallet</figcaption></figure>
<p>With a hardware wallet, the private keys are stored on the device and never exposed to your computer, which means even if you are infected with such a program your private keys will remain safe. These options are safest way to store your crypto if you have more than a small amount.</p>
<p>Popular examples of cold storage offerings are the Ledger and Trezor line of hardware wallet solutions, read our reviews:</p>
<ul>
<li><a href="https://blockonomi.com/ledger-nano-s-review/">Ledger Nano S Review</a></li>
<li><a href="https://blockonomi.com/ledger-nano-x-review/">Ledger Nano X Review</a></li>
<li><a href="https://blockonomi.com/trezor-vs-ledger/">Trezor vs. Ledger Review</a></li>
</ul>
<h3>Mobile wallet</h3>
<p>A mobile wallet is essentially a hot wallet on a smartphone device. They offer users an even more convenient way to use their coins for daily activities. Mobile wallets store and manage users' private keys while enabling them to pay for things they love with their digital assets.</p>
<figure id="attachment_66608" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-66608" style="width: 751px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-66608" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/mobile-wallet.png" alt="Mobile wallet" width="751" height="429" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/mobile-wallet.png 751w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/mobile-wallet-300x171.png 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/mobile-wallet-50x29.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 751px) 100vw, 751px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-66608" class="wp-caption-text">Mobile wallet</figcaption></figure>
<p>These wallets are usually free and always online for transactions to be processed. Popular mobile wallets are eToro Money Wallet and Coinbase Wallet.</p>
<h3>Desktop wallet</h3>
<p>A desktop wallet is a PC version of a hot wallet. It is essentially software that an investor downloads into their personal computer or laptop for easy interaction with their digital coins. They also offer a browser extension which allows users to interact using an extension instead of downloading the entire software. Desktop wallets are also hack-prone due to their online nature. A popular example is the Exodus Wallet.</p>
<h3>Paper Wallet</h3>
<p>The paper wallet is arguably the oldest form of crypto wallet. They are no longer common in the modern crypto industry. It contains users' public and private keys. The paper wallet is the least secure type of wallet as it can easily be lost, stolen, or torched.</p>
<hr />
<h2>BitTorrent BTT FAQs</h2>
<h3>Where can I buy BitTorrent tokens?</h3>
<p>BitTorrent (BTT) is a fast-rising crypto project. Its real-life utility has seen it listed on varieties of top crypto exchanges. However, if an investor wants to buy BitTorrent (BTT) with low fees on a regulated and trusted platform, Binance is the best exchange to get started. This exchange features seamless trading services and top security to make a trading journey great!</p>
<h3>How do I purchase BitTorrent?</h3>
<p>Investing in cryptocurrencies can sometimes be complex, leaving investors unsure of how to buy BitTorrent. It is easy to buy BTT. All investors have to do is choose an exchange (we recommend Binance for a low-fee trading experience) and proceed to select how to buy BitTorrent, either with fiat or crypto. With fiat, Binance gives investors options like bank transfer, credit/debit card, peer-to-peer (P2P) market, and e-wallet solutions like PayPal. If an investor decides to buy BTT via crypto, they have to select the crypto to trade for BTT. For instance, BTC/BTT.</p>
<h3>Where is BitTorrent traded?</h3>
<p>As earlier stated, BitTorrent is listed and supported by several exchanges. These exchanges differ as they are decentralised and centralised. Exchanges like Uniswap and Sushiswap are decentralised, while the likes of Binance and Coinbase are centralised exchanges. Both decentralised and centralised exchanges can be used to purchase BitTorrent (BTT). However, for top-notch security and ease of use, we recommend centralised exchanges, like Binance.</p>
<h3>Is BitTorrent on Coinbase?</h3>
<p>Unfortunately, BitTorrent (BTT) is not supported by Coinbase. This means that investors cannot buy, sell, trade, or stake BTT on Coinbase. Not to worry, investors can buy BTT easily via Binance in less than 10 minutes. Investors can also leverage and earn interest whenever they stake their BTT tokens via the BinanceEarn feature.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/buy-bittorrent/">Where To Buy BitTorrent Coin (BTT) Crypto: Beginner’s Guide</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">67060</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Where to Buy Terra Classic (LUNC) Crypto: Beginner’s Guide</title>
		<link>https://blockonomi.com/buy-terra-classic/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jimmy Aki]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2024 05:40:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Buying]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blockonomi.com/?p=67558</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Volatility is a major issue in the cryptocurrency space. The price of Bitcoin, the most important crypto asset, frequently rises and falls. The Terra blockchain was designed to improve this situation. Terra&#8217;s goal is to achieve the price stability found in fiat currencies while ensuring that the cryptocurrency is resistant to censorship. Even though Terra [...]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/buy-terra-classic/">Where to Buy Terra Classic (LUNC) Crypto: Beginner’s Guide</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Volatility is a major issue in the cryptocurrency space. The price of Bitcoin, the most important crypto asset, frequently rises and falls. The Terra blockchain was designed to improve this situation. Terra&#8217;s goal is to achieve the price stability found in fiat currencies while ensuring that the cryptocurrency is resistant to censorship.</p>
<p>Even though Terra blockchain has since been renamed Terra Classic, investors remain enthusiastic about the protocol&#8217;s vision. This guide will explore how to buy Terra Classic and how the project maintains price and censorship stability.</p>
<div class="callout">
<h2 style="text-align: center;">Where to Buy Terra Classic LUNC</h2>
<p>This section is our top picks of where and how to buy the Terra Classic LUNC Crypto coin. We chose these based on our experience of using them and considered fees, security, payment options and reputation.</p>
<ul>
<li><strong><a href="/out/binance">Binance:</a> </strong>Largest Crypto Exchange with Low Fees</li>
<li><strong><a href="https://blockonomi.com/out/kucoin">Kucoin:</a> </strong>Highly Regarded and Easy to Use for Beginners</li>
<li><a href="https://blockonomi.com/out/gate"><strong>Gate:</strong></a> Solid Platform With Lots of Coins</li>
</ul>
<div class="verdict">
<h4 style="text-align: center;">Visit The Top Pick</h4>
<p style="text-align: center;"><a class="infobutton" href="/out/binance">VisitBinance</a></p>
</div>
</div>
<div class="callout">
<h3><img decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-1579 alignright" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/11/binance.gif" alt="Binance Review" width="150" height="150" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/11/binance.gif 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/11/binance-65x65.gif 65w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/11/binance-50x50.gif 50w" sizes="(max-width: 150px) 100vw, 150px" />Binance: Reputable Exchange with High Liquidity</h3>
<p><a href="/out/binance">Binance</a> is the largest cryptocurrency trading exchange in daily trade volumes. The exchange offers investors full access to trade over 600 crypto assets.</p>
<p>The renowned platform also features a well-detailed learning curve and advanced trading tools that support well-experienced traders and investors looking to learn how to buy different cryptos. Although Binance features a user-friendly interface that facilitates a great user experience, it is more suited for well-experienced traders.</p>
<p><strong>Read: <a href="https://blockonomi.com/binance-review/">Our Full Binance Review Here</a></strong></p>
<p>Binance has a minimum deposit of $10. This enables investors to kickstart their investing journey with low fees. Investors can also initiate deposits through seamless payment methods like wire transfers, credit/debit cards, peer-to-peer (P2P) payments, and other e-wallet solutions.</p>
<figure id="attachment_66588" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-66588" style="width: 785px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-66588" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/binance.jpg" alt="Binance Website" width="785" height="520" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/binance.jpg 785w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/binance-300x199.jpg 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/binance-768x509.jpg 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/binance-50x33.jpg 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/binance-270x180.jpg 270w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/binance-370x245.jpg 370w" sizes="(max-width: 785px) 100vw, 785px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-66588" class="wp-caption-text">Binance Website</figcaption></figure>
<p>Binance deposits come with a fee that varies based on the payment method used. For instance, the global exchange charges a standard fee of up to 4.50% for all deposits made with a debit/credit card.</p>
<p>All investors enjoy very low fees when trading on Binance, as it charges a standard trading fee of 0.1%. For investors that buy using Binance token (BNB), a discount of 25% on trading fees will be applied.</p>
<p>In addition, investors can rest assured that their funds and data are well protected whenever they trade on Binance. The broker features top-notch security measures like two-factor authentication (2FA), cold storage to keep most coins, whitelisting, and advanced data encryption to protect funds and data. Binance functions effectively in over 100 countries and has a spin-off regulated platform (Binance.US) that tends to US-based traders and investors.</p>
<p><strong>Pros</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Trading fees at 0.01%</li>
<li>High liquidity</li>
<li>Wide range of payment methods</li>
<li>600+ crypto assets in library</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Cons</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Interface is suited for advanced traders</li>
<li>US-based customers cannot trade most coins via its subsidiary</li>
</ul>
<div class="verdict">
<p style="text-align: center;"><a class="infobutton" href="/out/binance">Visit Binance</a></p>
</div>
</div>
<div class="callout">
<h3><img decoding="async" class="size-thumbnail wp-image-42275 alignright" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/kucoin-150x150.png" alt="" width="150" height="150" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/kucoin-150x150.png 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/kucoin-300x300.png 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/kucoin-50x50.png 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/kucoin-370x370.png 370w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/kucoin.png 400w" sizes="(max-width: 150px) 100vw, 150px" />KuCoin: Exchange With Lots of Listings</h3>
<p><a href="/out/kucoin">KuCoin</a> is one of the world's oldest and most popular crypto exchanges. The Seychelles-based broker is one of the most notable names in the market for traders who desire access to derivatives products to speculate in the market.</p>
<p>Currently, KuCoin provides access to over 600 cryptocurrencies. Besides trading and investing, the exchange allows investors to save, stake crypto, and even participate in Initial Exchange Offerings. With KuCoin, investors have an all-encompassing crypto hub.</p>
<p><strong>Read: <a href="https://blockonomi.com/kucoin-review/">Our Full Kucoin Review Here</a></strong></p>
<p>Like many brokers in its class, KuCoin could appear too overwhelming for beginners. The exchange is more suited for advanced traders who want to speculate and trade sophisticated products. So beginners might have some difficulty making use of it.</p>
<p>Despite this, investors could gain many benefits from trading with KuCoin. The broker has a low minimum balance of $5, with deposits available via major fiat currencies, peer-to-peer (P2P) transfers, and a few credit card options.</p>
<figure id="attachment_42262" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-42262" style="width: 808px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="wp-image-42262 size-full" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/kucoin.jpg" alt="Kucoin Homepage" width="808" height="585" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/kucoin.jpg 808w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/kucoin-300x217.jpg 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/kucoin-768x556.jpg 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/kucoin-50x36.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 808px) 100vw, 808px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-42262" class="wp-caption-text">Kucoin Homepage</figcaption></figure>
<p>As for trading fees, KuCoin users pay 0.1% in fees. But the fees could decrease based on an investor's 30-day trading volume and ownership of the company’s KCS token.</p>
<p>Security on KuCoin is also impressive. The system uses bank-level encryption and security infrastructures to protect users’ coins and data. KuCoin also has a specialized risk control department to enforce strict data usage policies.</p>
<p><strong>Pros</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Discounts available on trading fees</li>
<li>Extensive staking functionalities</li>
<li>Quick P2P trading system</li>
<li>Anonymous trading available</li>
<li>Low minimum balance</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Cons</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>No bank deposit option</li>
</ul>
<div class="verdict">
<p style="text-align: center;"><a class="infobutton" href="/out/kucoin">Visit Kucoin</a></p>
</div>
</div>
<div class="callout">
<h3><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="wp-image-5607 size-full alignright" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/03/gate-review.gif" alt="Gate Review" width="150" height="150" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/03/gate-review.gif 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/03/gate-review-65x65.gif 65w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/03/gate-review-50x50.gif 50w" sizes="(max-width: 150px) 100vw, 150px" />Gate.io: Solid Platform With Lots of Coins</h3>
<p><a href="https://blockonomi.com/out/gate">Gate.io </a>is a cryptocurrency trading site that aims to offer its members an alternative to the exchanges currently dominating the market.</p>
<p>The site has been in operation since 2017 and aims to capture a portion of the cryptocurrency trading market by offering its users hassle free access to a number of hard to find coins and up and coming projects.</p>
<p>The site is also designed to help investors find specific information related to both their preferred coins and overall market trends.</p>
<p><strong>Read: <a href="https://blockonomi.com/gate-io-review/">Our Full Gate.io Review Here</a></strong></p>
<p>Trading mostly takes place on a web-based trading platform that is similar to most cryptocurrency exchanges. The site incorporates a number of functional features such as an order book, trading history, and charting.</p>
<figure id="attachment_66924" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-66924" style="width: 785px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="wp-image-66924 size-full" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/gate-website.jpg" alt="Gate Website" width="785" height="548" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/gate-website.jpg 785w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/gate-website-300x209.jpg 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/gate-website-768x536.jpg 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/gate-website-50x35.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 785px) 100vw, 785px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-66924" class="wp-caption-text">Gate Website</figcaption></figure>
<p><strong>Pros</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>A wide range of currencies</li>
<li>A low fee structure</li>
<li>Simple registration process</li>
<li>Functional platform with a mobile app available</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Cons</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Unregulated</li>
<li>The team is not very transparent</li>
<li>No fiat currency transfers</li>
</ul>
<div class="verdict">
<p style="text-align: center;"><a class="infobutton" href="/out/gate">Visit Gate</a></p>
</div>
</div>
<hr />
<h2>What Is Terra Classic? <img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="alignright wp-image-67573" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/Terra-Classic-logo.png" alt="Terra Classic logo" width="120" height="120" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/Terra-Classic-logo.png 200w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/Terra-Classic-logo-150x150.png 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/Terra-Classic-logo-50x50.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 120px) 100vw, 120px" /></h2>
<p><a href="https://www.terra.money/">Terra Classic</a> is a blockchain protocol founded in 2018 by Daniel Shin and Do Kwon of Terraform Labs. The project aimed to speed up the adoption of blockchain technology and cryptocurrency by addressing volatility.</p>
<p>To achieve this price stability vision, the Terraform Labs team launched UST, the industry&#8217;s first algorithmic stablecoin. Other algorithmic stablecoins created include the South Korean Won, Mongolian Turik, and the International Monetary Fund&#8217;s Special Drawing Rights (SDR).</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-67579 aligncenter" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/screenshot-www.terra_.money-2022.09.08-13_16_54.png" alt="how to buy Terra Classic" width="1236" height="497" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/screenshot-www.terra_.money-2022.09.08-13_16_54.png 1236w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/screenshot-www.terra_.money-2022.09.08-13_16_54-300x121.png 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/screenshot-www.terra_.money-2022.09.08-13_16_54-1024x412.png 1024w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/screenshot-www.terra_.money-2022.09.08-13_16_54-768x309.png 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/screenshot-www.terra_.money-2022.09.08-13_16_54-50x20.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1236px) 100vw, 1236px" />UST was designed to be pegged, one-to-one, to the US dollar. The Terra blockchain also created the infamous network token, LUNA, to keep its peg. When UST prices fall below one dollar, a certain amount of LUNA is minted to ensure it repegs.</p>
<hr />
<h3>The Avalanche of Troubles</h3>
<p>Terra&#8217;s innovative price stability mantra could only last so long&#8230;.</p>
<p>Everything came down to TerraUSD, an algorithmic stablecoin (UST). Because there is no physical fiat reserve backing UST, it is unlike any other stablecoin on the market.</p>
<p>To maintain its stability, it relies on arbitrage mechanisms. When it depegs or loses its dollar valuation, a certain amount of its LUNA token is sold, resulting in a demand contraction for the UST peg.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-67578 aligncenter" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/screenshot-www.terra_.money-2022.09.08-13_14_35.png" alt="how to buy Terra Classic" width="1287" height="608" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/screenshot-www.terra_.money-2022.09.08-13_14_35.png 1287w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/screenshot-www.terra_.money-2022.09.08-13_14_35-300x142.png 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/screenshot-www.terra_.money-2022.09.08-13_14_35-1024x484.png 1024w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/screenshot-www.terra_.money-2022.09.08-13_14_35-768x363.png 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/screenshot-www.terra_.money-2022.09.08-13_14_35-50x24.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1287px) 100vw, 1287px" />The blockchain began to fall in May 2021, when the UST stablecoin&#8217;s value dropped from $1 to $0.96 in a one-week period, providing traders with a lucrative arbitrage opportunity.</p>
<p>Terraform Labs launched the Luna Foundation Guard to prevent a future occurrence (LFG). As a reserve for its UST stablecoin, LFG purchased a then-record amount of $3.5 billion in Bitcoin <a href="https://blockonomi.com/buy-avalanche/">and the AVAX token</a>.</p>
<p>However, during the May 2022 bear market, the UST token and LUNA fell significantly.</p>
<p>After learning that its yield-generating protocol, Anchor, was reversing its promised 20% annual percentage yield (APY), UST depegged from $1. To stanch the fall, billions of LUNA tokens were minted, resulting in hyperinflation and market saturation. Furthermore, the LFG liquidated all of its crypto holdings, precipitating a much steeper decline in the emerging industry.</p>
<p>Terra blockchain decided to create a hardfork similar to the infamous Ethereum split due to the shortfall. Terra 2.0 would be the name of the new smart contract network, while Terra Classic and Luna Classic would be the names of the failed experiments.</p>
<hr />
<h3>Use Cases</h3>
<p>Does Terra Classic&#8217;s tumultuous history make it any less useful? Absolutely not. Terra Classic maintains its position as a smart contract network while also resisting censorship. Developers can use it to create decentralised applications (dApps) to meet the market&#8217;s rising demand.</p>
<p>While its stablecoin is nowhere near its $1 peg, the LUNC remains one of the market&#8217;s most well-known cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p>The native token still has a market cap of more than $3 billion.</p>
<hr />
<h3>Partnerships</h3>
<p>Terra Classic was once a cryptocurrency darling. Several traditional tech companies and crypto companies were collaborating on projects.</p>
<p>Terra announced a partnership with Chia, a South Korean mobile payments company, in July 2019. In the same year, Terra announced that its Terra Alliance group of companies was working to seize a significant share of the rapidly expanding cryptocurrency market. The alliance included ten major corporations with a combined net worth of $25 billion.</p>
<hr />
<h2>How Does Terra Classic Work?</h2>
<p>Terra Classic is not different from its split second. It is primarily a smart contract network platform that serves as a testing ground for dApps and other decentralised ecosystems.</p>
<p>How do its stablecoin and native token interact with one another? As previously stated, TerraUSD is an algorithmic stablecoin that requires a secondary token to keep its peg. This is accomplished by minting and burning LUNA tokens using arbitrage mechanisms.</p>
<p>To purchase one UST, an investor must mint it, and the purchase rate is then added to the LUNA token. The Terra Classic blockchain then burns or permanently removes the addition from circulation. This repeated burning of LUNA reduces the amount of it available on the open market, causing its price to rise.</p>
<p>To purchase or mint LUNA, a user must first convert the UST stablecoin. This creates a counter-balance for both digital assets.</p>
<p>Arbitrageurs, or traders who profit from small price changes, are essential to the Terra Classic network&#8217;s operation. They ensure that the equilibrium is maintained. If the price of UST falls below $1, they sell LUNA for the stablecoin, and if it rises above $1, they buy UST for LUNA. They introduce a kind of forced scarcity of cryptocurrencies by doing so.</p>
<hr />
<h2>Is Terra Classic a Good Investment?</h2>
<p>So much has happened in the Terra ecosystem. Is Terra Classic still a good buy?</p>
<h3>Code is law</h3>
<p>The current standoff between Terra Classic and Terra blockchain is reminiscent of the <a href="https://blockonomi.com/ethereum-vs-ethereum-classic/">2016 Ethereum split</a>. Since then, a few die-hard code maximalists have kept the Ethereum Classic running; it still commands a significant percentage of the crypto market.</p>
<p>Investing in Terra Classic may be a viable way for users who believe in the code&#8217;s supremacy to ensure its continued survival.</p>
<h3>Potential Supply Reduction</h3>
<p>Since the debacle in May 2022, the Terra Classic community has not been idle. While Do Kwon has left Terra Classic to focus on Terra 2.0, the Terra Classic community has remained strong.</p>
<p>There is a growing belief that Terra Classic&#8217;s LUNC will reclaim some of its former glory. This comes in response to a <a href="https://classic-agora.terra.money/t/proposal-for-the-1-2-tax-parameter-change/46319">community proposal</a> submitted on September 1. The author advocates for a 1.2% tax parameter change in it.</p>
<p>The plan is to reduce the number of LUNC tokens in circulation to create a supply crunch and increase the token&#8217;s value. If this passes the community vote, investors may be in possession of a crypto gem.</p>
<hr />
<h2>How to Buy Terra Classic on eToro</h2>
<p>We recommend that traders <a href="/out/etoro/">invest in Terra Classic through the eToro platform</a>. Why? The multi-asset brokerage firm has a communal nature. eToro was founded in 2007 to promote investment in stocks, bonds, commodities, FX currency pairs, and various other assets.</p>
<p>Since then, the broker has shifted its focus to the crypto space, commanding a sizable library of 75+ cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-67577" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/screenshot-www.etoro_.com-2022.09.08-13_17_50.png" alt="eToro" width="1228" height="549" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/screenshot-www.etoro_.com-2022.09.08-13_17_50.png 1228w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/screenshot-www.etoro_.com-2022.09.08-13_17_50-300x134.png 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/screenshot-www.etoro_.com-2022.09.08-13_17_50-1024x458.png 1024w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/screenshot-www.etoro_.com-2022.09.08-13_17_50-768x343.png 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/screenshot-www.etoro_.com-2022.09.08-13_17_50-50x22.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1228px) 100vw, 1228px" />Its social climate has helped it become one of the top destinations for its 23.3 million users. Because eToro is a social trading platform, investors can communicate, interact, and learn from one another. CopyTrader is also available on eToro. This means that users can mimic their counterparts&#8217; trading strategies and positions while only paying a small fee. This enables inexperienced investors to learn about the underlying asset and financial market while still making a reasonable profit.</p>
<p>eToro also has a <a href="https://blockonomi.com/etoro-copy-trading-guide/">CopyPortfolio</a> feature. This allows users to spread their investments among top-performing companies. This feature automatically balances the investor&#8217;s investment portfolio.</p>
<p>eToro has one of the lowest fees in the crypto space, charging users only a 1% bid-ask spread. All of its payment channels have no deposit fees. On the other hand, withdrawals are charged $5 across all payment methods.</p>
<p>eToro offers the well-known two-factor authentication (2FA) and masking technology to protect users&#8217; funds. The Financial Conduct Authority (FCA), Cyprus Securities and Exchange Commission (CySEC), Australian Securities and Investment Commission (ASIC), and the Financial Industry Regulatory Authority (FINRA) all regulate eToro.</p>
<p>Because Binance has announced the discontinuation of the <a href="https://www.binance.com/en/support/announcement/f14b7fc184b74237a9e68796a2939dec">Shuttle Bridge</a> between the Ethereum network and the Binance Smart Chain (BSC), only a few exchanges support the LUNC token. As a result, eToro is a viable option for those interested in investing in LUNC.</p>
<p>Traders seeking how to buy Terra Classic can follow these detailed steps to purchase Terra Classic on eToro:</p>
<h3>Register on eToro</h3>
<p>First, open an eToro account. Go to the official eToro website and click the &#8216;Start Investing&#8217; button on the homepage. Insert the necessary information: full name, email address, and password.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-67576" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/screenshot-www.etoro_.com-2022.09.08-13_18_47.png" alt="Sign up on eToro" width="1360" height="541" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/screenshot-www.etoro_.com-2022.09.08-13_18_47.png 1360w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/screenshot-www.etoro_.com-2022.09.08-13_18_47-300x119.png 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/screenshot-www.etoro_.com-2022.09.08-13_18_47-1024x407.png 1024w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/screenshot-www.etoro_.com-2022.09.08-13_18_47-768x306.png 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/screenshot-www.etoro_.com-2022.09.08-13_18_47-50x20.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1360px) 100vw, 1360px" />eToro allows users to sign up using their Google, Apple, or Facebook accounts for a more streamlined sign-up process.</p>
<h3>Verify ID</h3>
<p>Because eToro is regulated, all new accounts must verify their identity before trading on the platform. To verify, tap the profile icon and select &#8216;Verify&#8217;. Submit or upload a copy of a recent driver&#8217;s license that includes the full name as it appears on the eToro platform, or upload an official passport. <span style="font-size: 19px;">A document containing a residential address should also be uploaded. This can be a bank statement or a recent utility bill that includes the address. This is referred to as proof of address.</span></p>
<h3>Deposit</h3>
<p>The following step is to fund the new eToro account. Tap the action tab and select &#8216;Deposit Funds&#8217; from the list of functions. Then, choose a payment method. eToro does not charge fees for deposits made through any of its payment channels, and users can fund their accounts via bank wire transfer, credit/debit cards, PayPal, Skrill, Neteller, and various other methods.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-67575" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/screenshot-www.etoro_.com-2022.09.08-13_19_21.png" alt="Deposit on eToro" width="634" height="353" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/screenshot-www.etoro_.com-2022.09.08-13_19_21.png 634w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/screenshot-www.etoro_.com-2022.09.08-13_19_21-300x167.png 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/screenshot-www.etoro_.com-2022.09.08-13_19_21-50x28.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 634px) 100vw, 634px" />Enter the amount to invest. eToro has a regional minimum deposit requirement. eToro allows investors in the United States and the United Kingdom to get started with as little as $20.</p>
<h3>Buy Terra Classic</h3>
<p>The last step is to buy Terra Classic. The quickest way is to type &#8216;LUNC&#8217; into the search bar at the top of the dashboard and click on the appropriate result.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-67574" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/screenshot-www.etoro_.com-2022.09.08-13_19_43.png" alt="Buy Terra Classic on eToro" width="1020" height="261" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/screenshot-www.etoro_.com-2022.09.08-13_19_43.png 1020w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/screenshot-www.etoro_.com-2022.09.08-13_19_43-300x77.png 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/screenshot-www.etoro_.com-2022.09.08-13_19_43-768x197.png 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/screenshot-www.etoro_.com-2022.09.08-13_19_43-50x13.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1020px) 100vw, 1020px" />Tap &#8216;Trade&#8217; in the upper right-hand corner and enter the amount of the token to buy. Then, click &#8216;Open Trade&#8217; to finish the process.</p>
<hr />
<h2>Conclusion</h2>
<p>Terra Classic remains one of the top crypto dogs despite its historical decline. Investors who are code maximalists can still buy Terra Classic to preserve its code base. Investors looking for an undervalued crypto gem can also buy the asset.</p>
<p>We recommend that investors seeking how to buy Terra Classic use eToro. The social trading platform provides mirror trading capabilities, allowing investors to mimic the trades of more experienced traders. The CopyPortfolio functionality, which automatically diversifies one&#8217;s investment, is even more unique. With a competitive trading fee of 1% and a zero deposit fee structure, eToro is a popular choice for many.</p>
<hr />
<h2>Luna Classic FAQs</h2>
<h3>Where can I buy Terra Crypto?</h3>
<p>Terra crypto is available on several cryptocurrency exchanges. Binance, Coinbase, and eToro are some popular examples. To get started, newly opened accounts must verify their ID and fund with the stipulated minimum amount.</p>
<h3>Can you buy Terra Classic on Binance?</h3>
<p>Binance accepts LUNC purchases on its platform. However, investors who rely on the Shuttle Bridge can no longer access Terra Classic on Binance.</p>
<h3>Can I buy Luna on Coinbase?</h3>
<p>Yes, the Terra 2.0 token, LUNA, is available to trade on Coinbase. New users need to verify their Coinbase account by uploading either a driver’s license or a government-issued ID card. A small minimum deposit of $2 is required to get started on the Coinbase platform.</p>
<h3>How do I get LUNC Crypto?</h3>
<p>Investors must create a new account on the chosen platform. Then they must verify their driver&#8217;s license or official passport and fund their account with a predetermined amount. After that, investors can trade the LUNC cryptocurrency.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/buy-terra-classic/">Where to Buy Terra Classic (LUNC) Crypto: Beginner’s Guide</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">67558</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Where to Buy Injective Protocol (INJ) Crypto Coin: Complete Guide</title>
		<link>https://blockonomi.com/buy-injective/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Oliver Dale]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2024 05:24:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Buying]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blockonomi.com/?p=67954</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>One of the biggest issues with decentralized exchanges is price and order manipulation. The Injective Protocol promises to eliminate these problems with its decentralized layer-2 platform for derivatives trading. With Injective, users receive a decentralized trade execution coordinator and order book, preventing frontrunning on the exchange. The protocol leverages its layer-2 blockchain tech for compiling [...]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/buy-injective/">Where to Buy Injective Protocol (INJ) Crypto Coin: Complete Guide</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>One of the biggest issues with decentralized exchanges is price and order manipulation. The Injective Protocol promises to eliminate these problems with its decentralized layer-2 platform for derivatives trading.</p>
<p>With<a href="https://injective.com/"> Injective</a>, users receive a decentralized trade execution coordinator and order book, preventing frontrunning on the exchange. The protocol leverages its layer-2 blockchain tech for compiling transfers on-chain through an EVM-compatible environment.</p>
<p>The Interjection protocol builds the EVM on the Cosmos-SDK, which is a side chain allowing scaling on the Ethereum Network.</p>
<p>This guide will take an indepth look at how the Injective platform works and where &amp; how to buy the project&#8217;s native INJ token.</p>
<div class="callout">
<h2 style="text-align: center;">Where to Buy Injective INJ</h2>
<p>This section is our top picks of where and how to buy the Injective INJ Crypto token. We chose these based on our experience of using them and considered fees, security, payment options and reputation.</p>
<ul>
<li><strong><a href="/out/binance">Binance:</a> </strong>Largest Crypto Exchange with Low Fees</li>
<li><strong><a href="/out/coinbase">Coinbase:</a> </strong>Highly Regarded and Easy to Use for Beginners</li>
<li><strong><a href="https://blockonomi.com/out/ftx">Kraken:</a></strong> Top Platform With High Liquidity</li>
<li><strong><a href="https://blockonomi.com/out/kucoin">Kucoin:</a></strong> Long Established Exchange With Lots of Listings</li>
</ul>
<div class="verdict">
<h4 style="text-align: center;">Visit The Top Pick</h4>
<p style="text-align: center;"><a class="infobutton" href="/out/binance">Visit Binance</a></p>
</div>
</div>
<div class="callout">
<h3><img decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-1579 alignright" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/11/binance.gif" alt="Binance Review" width="150" height="150" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/11/binance.gif 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/11/binance-65x65.gif 65w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/11/binance-50x50.gif 50w" sizes="(max-width: 150px) 100vw, 150px" />Binance: Reputable Exchange with High Liquidity</h3>
<p><a href="/out/binance">Binance</a> is the largest cryptocurrency trading exchange in daily trade volumes. The exchange offers investors full access to trade over 600 crypto assets.</p>
<p>The renowned platform also features a well-detailed learning curve and advanced trading tools that support well-experienced traders and investors looking to learn how to buy different cryptos. Although Binance features a user-friendly interface that facilitates a great user experience, it is more suited for well-experienced traders.</p>
<p><strong>Read: <a href="https://blockonomi.com/binance-review/">Our Full Binance Review Here</a></strong></p>
<p>Binance has a minimum deposit of $10. This enables investors to kickstart their investing journey with low fees. Investors can also initiate deposits through seamless payment methods like wire transfers, credit/debit cards, peer-to-peer (P2P) payments, and other e-wallet solutions.</p>
<figure id="attachment_66588" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-66588" style="width: 785px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-66588" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/binance.jpg" alt="Binance Website" width="785" height="520" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/binance.jpg 785w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/binance-300x199.jpg 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/binance-768x509.jpg 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/binance-50x33.jpg 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/binance-270x180.jpg 270w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/binance-370x245.jpg 370w" sizes="(max-width: 785px) 100vw, 785px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-66588" class="wp-caption-text">Binance Website</figcaption></figure>
<p>Binance deposits come with a fee that varies based on the payment method used. For instance, the global exchange charges a standard fee of up to 4.50% for all deposits made with a debit/credit card.</p>
<p>All investors enjoy very low fees when trading on Binance, as it charges a standard trading fee of 0.1%. For investors that buy using Binance token (BNB), a discount of 25% on trading fees will be applied.</p>
<p>In addition, investors can rest assured that their funds and data are well protected whenever they trade on Binance. The broker features top-notch security measures like two-factor authentication (2FA), cold storage to keep most coins, whitelisting, and advanced data encryption to protect funds and data. Binance functions effectively in over 100 countries and has a spin-off regulated platform (Binance.US) that tends to US-based traders and investors.</p>
<p><strong>Pros</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Trading fees at 0.01%</li>
<li>High liquidity</li>
<li>Wide range of payment methods</li>
<li>600+ crypto assets in library</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Cons</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Interface is suited for advanced traders</li>
<li>US-based customers cannot trade most coins via its subsidiary</li>
</ul>
<div class="verdict">
<p style="text-align: center;"><a class="infobutton" href="/out/binance">Visit Binance</a></p>
</div>
</div>
<div class="callout">
<h3><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-37984 alignright" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/coinbase-review.gif" alt="Coinbase Review" width="150" height="150" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/coinbase-review.gif 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/coinbase-review-50x50.gif 50w" sizes="(max-width: 150px) 100vw, 150px" />Coinbase: Simple &amp; Easy to Use Exchange</h3>
<p><a href="/out/coinbase">Coinbase</a> is also a great option for investors looking for how to buy the crypto seamlessly. The US-based crypto trading platform enables users to buy, sell, and stake cryptocurrencies with zero complexity.</p>
<p>Coinbase integrates a user-friendly interface that simplifies crypto trading. The crypto trading platform supports well over 10,000 blockchain-based assets.</p>
<p><strong>Read: <a href="https://blockonomi.com/coinbase-review/">Our Full Coinbase Review Here</a></strong></p>
<p>The exchange’s signup and verification process take less than 10 minutes. For traders looking to invest easily, Coinbase is a great alternative to Binance.</p>
<p>Coinbase has a minimum deposit of $2, the lowest minimum deposit in the market presently This exchange also offers a wide range of deposit methods like automated clearing house (ACH), Wire transfer, debit card, and e-wallet solutions, as well as cashouts in local currencies like USD, GBP, and EUR. Coinbase charges up to 3.99% for debit card deposits.</p>
<figure id="attachment_66587" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-66587" style="width: 770px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-large wp-image-66587" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/coinbase-1024x490.png" alt="Coinbase Website" width="770" height="368" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/coinbase-1024x490.png 1024w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/coinbase-300x144.png 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/coinbase-768x367.png 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/coinbase-50x24.png 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/coinbase.png 1348w" sizes="(max-width: 770px) 100vw, 770px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-66587" class="wp-caption-text">Coinbase Website</figcaption></figure>
<p>Investors enjoy a 4% cash back reward whenever a Coinbase debit card is used for crypto purchases.</p>
<p>For fees, Coinbase charges a competitive fee of 0.5% - 4.5% depending on the payment method, cryptocurrency type, and transaction sizes.</p>
<p>Coinbase has evolved from a traditional exchange to a versatile platform with great services dedicated to retail and institutional investors, such as an in-built exchange wallet, self-issued cash back visa card, staking, derivatives, asset hubs, ventures, and many more.</p>
<p>Furthermore, Coinbase has in-built security practices like 2FA verification as an added security layer to investors’ usernames and passwords, crime insurance that secures digital assets from theft and fraud, and many more.</p>
<p>Also, Coinbase is licensed by the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) and regulated by top financial authorities like Financial Conduct Authority (FCA), Financial Crimes and Enforcement Network (FinCEN), and the New York State Department of Financial Services (NYSDFS).</p>
<p><strong>Pros</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Beginner-focused</li>
<li>Licensed and reputable platform</li>
<li>Insurance in case of hacks</li>
<li>Low minimum deposit</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Cons</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>High fee compared to competitors</li>
<li>No credit card deposits for US customers</li>
</ul>
<div class="verdict">
<p style="text-align: center;"><a class="infobutton" href="/out/coinbase">Visit Coinbase</a></p>
</div>
</div>
<div class="callout">
<h3><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-3084 alignright" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/01/kraken-review.gif" alt="Kraken Review" width="150" height="150" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/01/kraken-review.gif 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/01/kraken-review-65x65.gif 65w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/01/kraken-review-50x50.gif 50w" sizes="(max-width: 150px) 100vw, 150px" />Kraken: Top Crypto Platform with High Liquidity</h3>
<p>Founded in 2011, <a href="/out/kraken">Kraken</a> is one of the oldest and most popular <a href="https://blockonomi.com/cryptocurrency-exchanges/">cryptocurrency exchanges</a> currently in operation.</p>
<p>The exchange has built a reputation as being a secure destination for anyone interested in trading cryptocurrencies and it is also a popular choice for both traders and institutions across a variety of locations.</p>
<p><strong>Read: <a href="https://blockonomi.com/kraken-review/">Our Full Kraken Review Here</a></strong></p>
<p>Kraken retains an international appeal and provides efficient trading opportunities in numerous fiat currencies. Kraken is also the current world leader in terms of Bitcoin to Euro trading volumes.</p>
<figure id="attachment_42155" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-42155" style="width: 808px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-42155" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/kraken.jpg" alt="Kraken Homepage" width="808" height="683" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/kraken.jpg 808w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/kraken-300x254.jpg 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/kraken-768x649.jpg 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/kraken-50x42.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 808px) 100vw, 808px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-42155" class="wp-caption-text">Kraken Homepage</figcaption></figure>
<p>Kraken is most well known for its Bitcoin and Ethereum to cash (EUR and USD) markets; however a wide range of both fiat and cryptocurrencies are tradable on the platform</p>
<h4>Pros</h4>
<ul>
<li>Dedicated service for institutions</li>
<li>Great for beginners to use</li>
<li>High trading liquidity</li>
</ul>
<h4>Cons</h4>
<ul>
<li>The lengthy ID verification process</li>
</ul>
<div class="verdict">
<p style="text-align: center;"><a class="infobutton" href="/out/kraken">Visit Kraken</a></p>
</div>
</div>
<div class="callout">
<h3><img decoding="async" class="size-thumbnail wp-image-42275 alignright" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/kucoin-150x150.png" alt="" width="150" height="150" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/kucoin-150x150.png 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/kucoin-300x300.png 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/kucoin-50x50.png 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/kucoin-370x370.png 370w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/kucoin.png 400w" sizes="(max-width: 150px) 100vw, 150px" />KuCoin: Exchange With Lots of Listings</h3>
<p><a href="/out/kucoin">KuCoin</a> is one of the world's oldest and most popular crypto exchanges. The Seychelles-based broker is one of the most notable names in the market for traders who desire access to derivatives products to speculate in the market.</p>
<p>Currently, KuCoin provides access to over 600 cryptocurrencies. Besides trading and investing, the exchange allows investors to save, stake crypto, and even participate in Initial Exchange Offerings. With KuCoin, investors have an all-encompassing crypto hub.</p>
<p><strong>Read: <a href="https://blockonomi.com/kucoin-review/">Our Full Kucoin Review Here</a></strong></p>
<p>Like many brokers in its class, KuCoin could appear too overwhelming for beginners. The exchange is more suited for advanced traders who want to speculate and trade sophisticated products. So beginners might have some difficulty making use of it.</p>
<p>Despite this, investors could gain many benefits from trading with KuCoin. The broker has a low minimum balance of $5, with deposits available via major fiat currencies, peer-to-peer (P2P) transfers, and a few credit card options.</p>
<figure id="attachment_42262" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-42262" style="width: 808px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="wp-image-42262 size-full" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/kucoin.jpg" alt="Kucoin Homepage" width="808" height="585" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/kucoin.jpg 808w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/kucoin-300x217.jpg 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/kucoin-768x556.jpg 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/kucoin-50x36.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 808px) 100vw, 808px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-42262" class="wp-caption-text">Kucoin Homepage</figcaption></figure>
<p>As for trading fees, KuCoin users pay 0.1% in fees. But the fees could decrease based on an investor's 30-day trading volume and ownership of the company’s KCS token.</p>
<p>Security on KuCoin is also impressive. The system uses bank-level encryption and security infrastructures to protect users’ coins and data. KuCoin also has a specialized risk control department to enforce strict data usage policies.</p>
<p><strong>Pros</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Discounts available on trading fees</li>
<li>Extensive staking functionalities</li>
<li>Quick P2P trading system</li>
<li>Anonymous trading available</li>
<li>Low minimum balance</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Cons</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>No bank deposit option</li>
</ul>
<div class="verdict">
<p style="text-align: center;"><a class="infobutton" href="/out/kucoin">Visit Kucoin</a></p>
</div>
</div>
<hr />
<h2>Injective Protocol Derivative Dex</h2>
<p>There are dozens of blockchain projects launched every week. However, establishing the testnet for <a href="https://injective.com/">Injective Protocol</a> created waves in the blockchain development community. The project can potentially change the digital landscape for crypto trading on decentralized exchanges.</p>
<hr />
<h2>Injective Protocol</h2>
<p>The Injective Protocol emerged in a whitepaper released in December 2018. It consists of a development team experienced in implementing large-scale blockchain and tech projects. Understandably, the industry seems excited about what the Injective Protocol can bring to the space.</p>
<p>The Injective Protocol is a decentralized derivatives exchange (DEX). The project aims to bridge differences in decentralized and centralized exchanges while including the booming decentralized finance ecosystem.</p>
<figure id="attachment_67962" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-67962" style="width: 785px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-67962" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/home.jpg" alt="Injective is an open interoperable smart contracts platform optimized for decentralized finance applications. " width="785" height="598" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/home.jpg 785w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/home-300x229.jpg 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/home-768x585.jpg 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/home-50x38.jpg 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/home-87x67.jpg 87w" sizes="(max-width: 785px) 100vw, 785px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-67962" class="wp-caption-text">Injective is an open interoperable smart contracts platform optimized for decentralized finance applications.</figcaption></figure>
<p>In the past, a DEX represents a logical solution to the regulatory and security issues affecting CEXs. However, it&#8217;s important to note that DEXs have several obstacles to making them efficient and effective. One of the core problems with current DEX systems is an inability to provide the same levels of liquidity and convenience supplied by CEX.</p>
<p>Despite the DEX providing the true spirit of the blockchain and crypto movement, these core issues with the system hindered its adoption in the market. The DEX hopes to bring its enhanced functionality to the DeFi sector, providing the same kind of liquidity similar to a CEX.</p>
<p>Let&#8217;s take a deep dive into the design of the Injective Protocol to understand what makes the DEX a revolution in the DeFi space.</p>
<hr />
<h2>Decentralized Exchanges Explained</h2>
<p>When we discuss crypto exchanges, we can separate them into centralized exchanges (CEX) and decentralized exchanges (DEX). A centralized exchange is a system like Coinbase and Binance. These protocols host the private keys of digital assets traded on the platform.</p>
<p>Decentralized exchanges, like Uniswap, do not host digital assets&#8217; private keys. They remain in the custody of the owners, not the platform. The core selling point of a centralized exchange is its user-friendly operation, making it easy for platform users to buy and sell assets without any issues.</p>
<p>The CEX is a great way to increase cryptocurrency adoption by bringing new users into the system, but they present a range of problems to the user. The DEX attempts to resolve these issues. We&#8217;ve all heard the phrase &#8216;not your keys, not your coins.&#8217; It&#8217;s a popular meme on Reddit and other message boards.</p>
<p>The phrase means that the person holding the digital assets&#8217; private keys is its rightful owner. This is a big issue with CEX platforms. To use the CEX, you have to give them your private keys, essentially giving up ownership of your assets.</p>
<hr />
<h2>Injective Protocol Features</h2>
<p>The Injective Protocol is a completely universal DeFi protocol enabling cross-chain trading of derivatives across several financial products like spot trading, perpetual swaps, and futures. The Injective Chain implements itself as a Cosmos SDK module, built on Ethermint.</p>
<p>The protocol uses a Tendermint-based Proof-of-Stake (POS) consensus protocol for facilitating cross-chain trading of derivatives across the Ethereum, Cosmos, and other layer-1 protocols. The Injective Protocol utilizes the Verifiable Delay Function (VDF), making it collision resistant and able to prevent order frontrunning.</p>
<figure id="attachment_67963" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-67963" style="width: 785px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-67963" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/features.jpg" alt="Injective Protocol Features" width="785" height="598" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/features.jpg 785w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/features-300x229.jpg 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/features-768x585.jpg 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/features-50x38.jpg 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/features-87x67.jpg 87w" sizes="(max-width: 785px) 100vw, 785px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-67963" class="wp-caption-text">Injective Protocol Features</figcaption></figure>
<p>The native token running the Injective Protocol is INJ. The token has a range of functions on the platform, such as protocol governance, derivative collateralization, staking, liquidity mining, and exchange fee value capturing.</p>
<p>With the Injective platform, users can contribute and implement decentralized cross-chain derivatives trading without paying gas fees. Users get access to cross-chain yield generation for several digital assets.</p>
<p>Users can create and trade derivative markets with a price feed, opening more opportunities for trading on markets not available on other CEXs.</p>
<hr />
<h2>Injective Protocol Improves DEX User Functionality</h2>
<p>Recent versions of DEX protocols apply innovation to move them in the direction of being as decentralized as possible. The Injective Protocol is an example, with the project utilized as a stepping stone to creating a platform that&#8217;s diverse and flexible.</p>
<p>The Injective Protocol promises users improved liquidity, more market diversity, faster order execution, and zero gas fees for trading. These features of the Injective Protocol make it the first truly decentralized exchange.</p>
<hr />
<h2>The Advantages of the Injective Exchange</h2>
<p>We can expect the Injective Protocol to change the face of decentralized finance thanks to the innovations and improvements it brings to the DeFi market. The infrastructure in the Injective Chain enables it to host several DeFi applications (Dapps), including the order execution on the platform.</p>
<p>The Injection Protocol provides seamless functionality in order execution. Users also get superior order matching technology and a decentralized order book, making frontrunning of orders by high-frequency systems impossible.</p>
<p>When forming these systems into a single protocol, these dApps create a peer-to-peer decentralized exchange. While this isn&#8217;t exactly a new technology, the tools added to the ecosystem distinguish the characteristics and features of the Injective Protocol, distinguishing it from other DEX platforms.</p>
<figure id="attachment_67964" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-67964" style="width: 785px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-67964" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/hub.jpg" alt="The Injective Hub" width="785" height="598" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/hub.jpg 785w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/hub-300x229.jpg 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/hub-768x585.jpg 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/hub-50x38.jpg 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/hub-87x67.jpg 87w" sizes="(max-width: 785px) 100vw, 785px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-67964" class="wp-caption-text">The <a href="https://hub.injective.network/">Injective Hub</a></figcaption></figure>
<p>The Injection Protocol relies on its consensus system built on the Tendermint-based Proof-of-Stake (PoS) protocol, assisting with cross-chain trading of derivatives the Ethereum, Cosmos, and similar layer-1 protocols. The design allows for effective staking, delegating, and earning rewards.</p>
<p>The Injective Exchange is open-source software, allowing for comprehensive protocol auditing to remove vulnerabilities and bugs. The highly flexible infrastructure of the exchange eliminates the typical barriers to entry experienced by other DEXs.</p>
<p>Since exchange users can create and trade any market that offers a price feed, users can access markets through the protocol that isn&#8217;t available on the exchanges.</p>
<p>Core products available on the testnet for the Injective Protocol are validated and tested by the largest institutional market makers, traders, and investment funds utilizing the blockchain. As a result of this design, the team experienced no hitches when launching the mainnet in 2021.</p>
<hr />
<h2>How Does the Injective Protocol Work?</h2>
<p>The Injective chain provides the backbone for the DEX. It plays a vital role in ensuring the functionality of all four elements of the Injective Protocol. The chain bridges the gap in order books. The 0x-based order books utilized on the exchange provide the platform for full decentralization and assist with optimizing transaction efficiency.</p>
<p>This protocol is possible because orders enable a side-chain relay with settlement completed on-chain. The order book also hosts censorship-resistant INJ nodes, adding to its decentralized nature. The Trade Execution Coordinator (TEC) removes the possibility of frontrunning the order book.</p>
<p>Frontrunning is the practice that high-frequency algorithmic traders use to monitor the order book and place orders in front of others, executing them for arbitrage purposes. As a result, the average trader receives slippage on their trade execution, or partial or no fill, depending on the order type they use.</p>
<figure id="attachment_67965" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-67965" style="width: 785px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-67965" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/developers.jpg" alt="Injective for Developers" width="785" height="598" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/developers.jpg 785w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/developers-300x229.jpg 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/developers-768x585.jpg 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/developers-50x38.jpg 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/developers-87x67.jpg 87w" sizes="(max-width: 785px) 100vw, 785px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-67965" class="wp-caption-text">Injective for Developers</figcaption></figure>
<p>Institutional traders claim this practice adds liquidity to the market, while traders claim it&#8217;s nothing more than stealing from orders because they have a technological advantage. For instance, many stock trading firms use a &#8216;Payment for Order Flow&#8217; model where they don&#8217;t charge the trader any commissions on trades.</p>
<p>However, in this model, the trader ends up paying for it through more slippage and no-fills or partial fills. Many traders claim this practice is unethical, while others don&#8217;t care, as long as they don&#8217;t have to pay commissions.</p>
<p>The Injective Protocol utilizes verifiable delay, acting as a &#8216;speed bump&#8217; ensuring new orders don&#8217;t get filled ahead of existing orders. The Bi-directional Token Bridge allows the transfer of ERC-20 tokens on the INJ chain. The bridge created in the Cosmos network is known as the &#8220;peg zone.&#8221;</p>
<p>These peg zones feature account-based blockchain bridges between zones in the Cosmos ecosystem and exterior blockchains, such as Ethereum, in this case. The Peg Zone Injective operates in the following stages from an Ethereum address.</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Via the INJ Peg zone smart contract.</strong></li>
<li><strong>Via the relay to the ETH bridge modules.</strong></li>
<li><strong>Via an oracle to the Banking Module on the Cosmos address.</strong></li>
<li><strong>The procedure reverses in Cosmos to Ethereum trades.</strong></li>
</ul>
<p>The EVM Execution Environment functionality enables the execution of Ethereum smart contracts while utilizing the Injective Chain. This structure allows developers to create dApps through the Ethereum network. However, the protocol offers a scalable environment using a Proof of Stake consensus model.</p>
<p>The dApp development process offers a similar approach when using the Injective EVM. This protocol provides additional benefits like improved smart contract byte code size limits. The smart contracts functionality performed in the EVM environment include the following.</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Trade Execution Coordinators.</strong></li>
<li><strong>Bi-directional token bridges.</strong></li>
<li><strong>Staking.</strong></li>
<li><strong>Futures contracts trading.</strong></li>
<li><strong>ERC20 contracts.</strong></li>
</ul>
<hr />
<h2>INJ Tokenomics</h2>
<p>The INJ token is the dedicated crypto token of the Injective Protocol. The INJ token serves several functions, bringing real utility to the platform. Its core purpose is to act as the governance token for regulating and managing the Injective Protocol.</p>
<p>The INJ token offers holders governance rights to propose changes to the protocol and vote on implementing these changes. The second use of the INJ token is to act as collateral for loans. It works like a stablecoin, providing collateral in DeFi applications where users can end INJ tokens as a margin in derivative markets created on the DEX.</p>
<p>The INJ tokens may also provide insurance pool staking or collateral to generate passive income through interest generated on loans. The token may also act as an incentive for operators of relay nodes and market makers.</p>
<figure id="attachment_67966" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-67966" style="width: 785px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-67966" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/staking.jpg" alt="Injective Staking" width="785" height="598" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/staking.jpg 785w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/staking-300x229.jpg 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/staking-768x585.jpg 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/staking-50x38.jpg 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/staking-87x67.jpg 87w" sizes="(max-width: 785px) 100vw, 785px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-67966" class="wp-caption-text">Injective Staking</figcaption></figure>
<p>The platform operates through a model, with market makers paying 0.1% exchange fees while takers pay a 0.2% commission. This structure allows market makers to maintain a net positive payment model in their rebates, which, in turn, incentivizes the provisioning of liquidity on the DEX.</p>
<p>After creating liquidity, markets enjoy tighter spreads on asset pairs while providing excellent market depth for traders. On top, the validators and nodes can improve their interface and API catering to trades while being rewarded for the transaction and providing liquidity to the market.</p>
<p>The protocol uses the remaining fees to buy back INJ tokens, burning them to create a deflationary ecosystem. This model adds further value to the remaining circulating supply of INJ tokens by creating scarcity. A portion of the INJ tokens available undergoes distribution to users of the DEX based on the notional profits accumulated.</p>
<p>Users with the largest amount of notional profits receive the most benefit from the protocol and the biggest INJ rewards. This system rewards those users who utilize the platform frequently. The protocol calculates these rewards based on daily snapshots.</p>
<hr />
<h2>INJ – Mainnet Launch</h2>
<p>The Injective Protocol launched its mainnet in November 2021. The team released a $120 million incentive pool alongside the mainnet launch, &#8216;Injective Astro&#8217; assists with promoting liquidity on the exchange and encourages higher trading volumes.</p>
<p>To help put this in perspective, $120 Million makes the Injective Astro program the largest liquidity incentive program in the DEX space and the Cosmos ecosystem. The mainnet and Astro incentive program launch follows the Injective Bridge, supporting seamless Ethereum and Cosmos-based token transfers.</p>
<p>The Injective protocol touts fast withdrawal times to Ethereum in under ten minutes. That&#8217;s far faster than other layer-2 solutions that take up to a week to process transactions. Eric Chen from the INJ team states the following surrounding the Injective protocol.</p>
<figure id="attachment_67967" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-67967" style="width: 785px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-67967" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/backers.jpg" alt="Some large funds &amp; Institutions back Injective" width="785" height="598" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/backers.jpg 785w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/backers-300x229.jpg 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/backers-768x585.jpg 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/backers-50x38.jpg 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/backers-87x67.jpg 87w" sizes="(max-width: 785px) 100vw, 785px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-67967" class="wp-caption-text">Some large funds &amp; Institutions back Injective</figcaption></figure>
<p>&#8220;Our mission at Injective has always been to build the most powerful cross-chain protocol for completely decentralized derivatives trading. As Injective interconnects new chains, the ecosystem will continue to serve as a DeFi gateway for trading across the multi-chain universe.</p>
<p>Injective&#8217;s Ethereum-native tooling allows users to create and trade new cross-chain markets without the typical roadblocks associated with making transactions across distinct blockchain networks.&#8221;</p>
<p>Binance Labs chose the Injective protocol as one of the first projects to benefit from its incubator program. The company raised $10 million in an investment seeding round from Pantera Capital and Mark Cuban.</p>
<hr />
<h2>How to Buy INJ Token on Binance</h2>
<p>After exploring where to buy and the coin’s use cases, the next thing is to explore how to buy it for your portfolio. Binance is our recommended exchange, so we'll explore how to purchase the asset using Binance.</p>
<h3>Step 1: Sign Up</h3>
<p>Go to the <a href="/out/binance">Binance home page</a> and click on “Register”.</p>
<figure id="attachment_66583" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-66583" style="width: 1342px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="wp-image-66583 size-full" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/welcome.png" alt="Binance signup" width="1342" height="488" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/welcome.png 1342w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/welcome-300x109.png 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/welcome-1024x372.png 1024w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/welcome-768x279.png 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/welcome-50x18.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1342px) 100vw, 1342px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-66583" class="wp-caption-text">Binance signup</figcaption></figure>
<p>Binance allows investors to register using their mobile phone, email address, or Google account. Most users choose the first two options and provide their phone numbers, emails, and desired passwords. A link will be sent to their registration channel of choice, and investors can click on it to authenticate their accounts.</p>
<h3>Step 2: Verify Your Identity</h3>
<p>Like many other regulated brokers, Binance requires that investors verify their identity before commencing their purchase.</p>
<p>To complete the process, visit the “Identification” tab. Investors will have to share personal information, their proof of residence, and a government-verified means of identification. This process should take no more than a few minutes to complete.</p>
<h3>Step 3: Deposit Your Funds</h3>
<p>Next, investors will have to deposit into their Binance wallets. The exchange makes deposits possible using payment processors, wire transfers, bank deposits, and direct crypto transfers. And its required minimum deposit is $10.</p>
<figure id="attachment_66584" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-66584" style="width: 675px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="wp-image-66584 size-full" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/deposit.png" alt="Deposit on Binance" width="675" height="434" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/deposit.png 675w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/deposit-300x193.png 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/deposit-50x32.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 675px) 100vw, 675px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-66584" class="wp-caption-text">Deposit on Binance</figcaption></figure>
<p>To make a deposit, go to the “Payment” section and click “Add a new payment method” to enter payment details. Alternatively, investors can click the “Buy Crypto” button to select a payment method and complete their transfer.</p>
<h3>Step 4: Buy</h3>
<p>With a funded wallet, investors are ready to make a your purchase. Head to the “Buy Crypto” section and enter the desired amount. Click on “Continue” after reviewing the terms, and the wallet should be updated immediately.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/buy-injective/">Where to Buy Injective Protocol (INJ) Crypto Coin: Complete Guide</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">67954</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Where to Buy Solana (SOL) Crypto Coin: Beginner’s Guide</title>
		<link>https://blockonomi.com/buy-solana/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nicholas Say]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2024 02:58:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Buying]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Solana]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blockonomi.com/?p=34775</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Solana is a high-performance blockchain for creating scalable decentralized applications. Solana has some innovative solutions to some of the most common challenges that blockchain faces. One of the biggest ones isn’t new. Scalability has been a hot topic in the blockchain community, and one of the biggest reasons why many people doubt that a decentralized blockchain [...]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/buy-solana/">Where to Buy Solana (SOL) Crypto Coin: Beginner’s Guide</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Solana is a high-performance blockchain for creating scalable decentralized applications.</p>
<p><a href="https://solana.com/">Solana</a> has some innovative solutions to some of the most common challenges that blockchain faces. One of the biggest ones isn’t new. Scalability has been a hot topic in the blockchain community, and one of the biggest reasons why many people doubt that a decentralized blockchain could replace centralized payment systems like Visa.</p>
<p>Bitcoin was one of the biggest breakthroughs in bridging trust and the creation of new money, but it probably isn’t going to be the platform that creates a decentralized global settlement system. Like many of the blockchains that exist, it simply can’t settle transactions fast enough to be practical as a global platform.</p>
<p>Solana has a good solution to the scalability dilemma, and it also has some other great ideas that could help blockchain enter its next phase of development.</p>
<p>Learn more about Solana below and find out where and how to buy Solana&#8217;s native token SOL in our complete guide.</p>
<div class="callout">
<h2 style="text-align: center;">Where to Buy Solana SOL Token</h2>
<p>This section is our top picks of where and how to buy the Solana <a href="https://blockonomi.com/best-solana-casino/">SOL Crypto token</a>. We chose these based on our experience of using them and considered fees, security, payment options and reputation.</p>
<ul>
<li><strong><a href="/out/binance">Binance:</a> </strong>Largest Crypto Exchange with Low Fees</li>
<li><strong><a href="/out/coinbase">Coinbase:</a> </strong>Highly Regarded and Easy to Use for Beginners</li>
<li><strong><a href="/out/kucoin">Kucoin:</a></strong> A Top Pick &amp; Easy to Use Platform</li>
</ul>
<div class="verdict">
<h4 style="text-align: center;">Visit The Top Pick</h4>
<p style="text-align: center;"><a class="infobutton" href="/out/binance">Visit Binance</a></p>
</div>
</div>
<div class="callout">
<h3><img decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-1579 alignright" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/11/binance.gif" alt="Binance Review" width="150" height="150" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/11/binance.gif 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/11/binance-65x65.gif 65w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/11/binance-50x50.gif 50w" sizes="(max-width: 150px) 100vw, 150px" />Binance: Reputable Exchange with High Liquidity</h3>
<p><a href="/out/binance">Binance</a> is the largest cryptocurrency trading exchange in daily trade volumes. The exchange offers investors full access to trade over 600 crypto assets.</p>
<p>The renowned platform also features a well-detailed learning curve and advanced trading tools that support well-experienced traders and investors looking to learn how to buy different cryptos. Although Binance features a user-friendly interface that facilitates a great user experience, it is more suited for well-experienced traders.</p>
<p><strong>Read: <a href="https://blockonomi.com/binance-review/">Our Full Binance Review Here</a></strong></p>
<p>Binance has a minimum deposit of $10. This enables investors to kickstart their investing journey with low fees. Investors can also initiate deposits through seamless payment methods like wire transfers, credit/debit cards, peer-to-peer (P2P) payments, and other e-wallet solutions.</p>
<figure id="attachment_66588" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-66588" style="width: 785px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-66588" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/binance.jpg" alt="Binance Website" width="785" height="520" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/binance.jpg 785w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/binance-300x199.jpg 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/binance-768x509.jpg 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/binance-50x33.jpg 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/binance-270x180.jpg 270w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/binance-370x245.jpg 370w" sizes="(max-width: 785px) 100vw, 785px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-66588" class="wp-caption-text">Binance Website</figcaption></figure>
<p>Binance deposits come with a fee that varies based on the payment method used. For instance, the global exchange charges a standard fee of up to 4.50% for all deposits made with a debit/credit card.</p>
<p>All investors enjoy very low fees when trading on Binance, as it charges a standard trading fee of 0.1%. For investors that buy using Binance token (BNB), a discount of 25% on trading fees will be applied.</p>
<p>In addition, investors can rest assured that their funds and data are well protected whenever they trade on Binance. The broker features top-notch security measures like two-factor authentication (2FA), cold storage to keep most coins, whitelisting, and advanced data encryption to protect funds and data. Binance functions effectively in over 100 countries and has a spin-off regulated platform (Binance.US) that tends to US-based traders and investors.</p>
<p><strong>Pros</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Trading fees at 0.01%</li>
<li>High liquidity</li>
<li>Wide range of payment methods</li>
<li>600+ crypto assets in library</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Cons</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Interface is suited for advanced traders</li>
<li>US-based customers cannot trade most coins via its subsidiary</li>
</ul>
<div class="verdict">
<p style="text-align: center;"><a class="infobutton" href="/out/binance">Visit Binance</a></p>
</div>
</div>
<div class="callout">
<h3><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-37984 alignright" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/coinbase-review.gif" alt="Coinbase Review" width="150" height="150" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/coinbase-review.gif 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/coinbase-review-50x50.gif 50w" sizes="(max-width: 150px) 100vw, 150px" />Coinbase: Simple &amp; Easy to Use Exchange</h3>
<p><a href="/out/coinbase">Coinbase</a> is also a great option for investors looking for how to buy the crypto seamlessly. The US-based crypto trading platform enables users to buy, sell, and stake cryptocurrencies with zero complexity.</p>
<p>Coinbase integrates a user-friendly interface that simplifies crypto trading. The crypto trading platform supports well over 10,000 blockchain-based assets.</p>
<p><strong>Read: <a href="https://blockonomi.com/coinbase-review/">Our Full Coinbase Review Here</a></strong></p>
<p>The exchange’s signup and verification process take less than 10 minutes. For traders looking to invest easily, Coinbase is a great alternative to Binance.</p>
<p>Coinbase has a minimum deposit of $2, the lowest minimum deposit in the market presently This exchange also offers a wide range of deposit methods like automated clearing house (ACH), Wire transfer, debit card, and e-wallet solutions, as well as cashouts in local currencies like USD, GBP, and EUR. Coinbase charges up to 3.99% for debit card deposits.</p>
<figure id="attachment_66587" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-66587" style="width: 770px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-large wp-image-66587" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/coinbase-1024x490.png" alt="Coinbase Website" width="770" height="368" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/coinbase-1024x490.png 1024w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/coinbase-300x144.png 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/coinbase-768x367.png 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/coinbase-50x24.png 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/coinbase.png 1348w" sizes="(max-width: 770px) 100vw, 770px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-66587" class="wp-caption-text">Coinbase Website</figcaption></figure>
<p>Investors enjoy a 4% cash back reward whenever a Coinbase debit card is used for crypto purchases.</p>
<p>For fees, Coinbase charges a competitive fee of 0.5% - 4.5% depending on the payment method, cryptocurrency type, and transaction sizes.</p>
<p>Coinbase has evolved from a traditional exchange to a versatile platform with great services dedicated to retail and institutional investors, such as an in-built exchange wallet, self-issued cash back visa card, staking, derivatives, asset hubs, ventures, and many more.</p>
<p>Furthermore, Coinbase has in-built security practices like 2FA verification as an added security layer to investors’ usernames and passwords, crime insurance that secures digital assets from theft and fraud, and many more.</p>
<p>Also, Coinbase is licensed by the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) and regulated by top financial authorities like Financial Conduct Authority (FCA), Financial Crimes and Enforcement Network (FinCEN), and the New York State Department of Financial Services (NYSDFS).</p>
<p><strong>Pros</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Beginner-focused</li>
<li>Licensed and reputable platform</li>
<li>Insurance in case of hacks</li>
<li>Low minimum deposit</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Cons</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>High fee compared to competitors</li>
<li>No credit card deposits for US customers</li>
</ul>
<div class="verdict">
<p style="text-align: center;"><a class="infobutton" href="/out/coinbase">Visit Coinbase</a></p>
</div>
</div>
<div class="callout">
<h3><img decoding="async" class="size-thumbnail wp-image-42275 alignright" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/kucoin-150x150.png" alt="" width="150" height="150" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/kucoin-150x150.png 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/kucoin-300x300.png 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/kucoin-50x50.png 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/kucoin-370x370.png 370w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/kucoin.png 400w" sizes="(max-width: 150px) 100vw, 150px" />KuCoin: Exchange With Lots of Listings</h3>
<p><a href="/out/kucoin">KuCoin</a> is one of the world's oldest and most popular crypto exchanges. The Seychelles-based broker is one of the most notable names in the market for traders who desire access to derivatives products to speculate in the market.</p>
<p>Currently, KuCoin provides access to over 600 cryptocurrencies. Besides trading and investing, the exchange allows investors to save, stake crypto, and even participate in Initial Exchange Offerings. With KuCoin, investors have an all-encompassing crypto hub.</p>
<p><strong>Read: <a href="https://blockonomi.com/kucoin-review/">Our Full Kucoin Review Here</a></strong></p>
<p>Like many brokers in its class, KuCoin could appear too overwhelming for beginners. The exchange is more suited for advanced traders who want to speculate and trade sophisticated products. So beginners might have some difficulty making use of it.</p>
<p>Despite this, investors could gain many benefits from trading with KuCoin. The broker has a low minimum balance of $5, with deposits available via major fiat currencies, peer-to-peer (P2P) transfers, and a few credit card options.</p>
<figure id="attachment_42262" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-42262" style="width: 808px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="wp-image-42262 size-full" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/kucoin.jpg" alt="Kucoin Homepage" width="808" height="585" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/kucoin.jpg 808w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/kucoin-300x217.jpg 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/kucoin-768x556.jpg 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/kucoin-50x36.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 808px) 100vw, 808px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-42262" class="wp-caption-text">Kucoin Homepage</figcaption></figure>
<p>As for trading fees, KuCoin users pay 0.1% in fees. But the fees could decrease based on an investor's 30-day trading volume and ownership of the company’s KCS token.</p>
<p>Security on KuCoin is also impressive. The system uses bank-level encryption and security infrastructures to protect users’ coins and data. KuCoin also has a specialized risk control department to enforce strict data usage policies.</p>
<p><strong>Pros</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Discounts available on trading fees</li>
<li>Extensive staking functionalities</li>
<li>Quick P2P trading system</li>
<li>Anonymous trading available</li>
<li>Low minimum balance</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Cons</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>No bank deposit option</li>
</ul>
<div class="verdict">
<p style="text-align: center;"><a class="infobutton" href="/out/kucoin">Visit Kucoin</a></p>
</div>
</div>
<hr />
<h2>What is Solana?</h2>
<p><a href="https://solana.com/">Solana</a> was founded in 2017 by <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/anatoly-yakovenko/">Anatoly Yakovenko</a>, a former executive at Qualcomm with vast experience working with decentralized and distributed systems, alongside working on compression algorithms for Dropbox.</p>
<p>Anatoly joined forces with CTO Greg Fitzgerald and Chief Scientist Eric Williams to create a trustless and distributed protocol that encodes the passage of time within the data structure and allows higher scalability than common layer 1 blockchains.</p>
<figure id="attachment_66934" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-66934" style="width: 785px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-66934" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/solana.jpg" alt="Solana" width="785" height="548" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/solana.jpg 785w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/solana-300x209.jpg 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/solana-768x536.jpg 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/solana-50x35.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 785px) 100vw, 785px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-66934" class="wp-caption-text">Solana</figcaption></figure>
<hr />
<h2>Solana Features</h2>
<p>Solana has created eight key innovations that may change how blockchain is implemented as a decentralized system. It has implemented Proof of History (PoH), a protocol to embed passage of time into the blockchain data structure, and integrated it with TowerBFT the system’s Proof-of-Staked based consensus mechanism.</p>
<p>By using PoH, which is a high frequency <a href="https://blog.trailofbits.com/2018/10/12/introduction-to-verifiable-delay-functions-vdfs/">Verifiable Delay Function</a> (VDF), Solana hopes to eliminate the issues which have given rise to other potential solutions, such as sharding.</p>
<p>A Verifiable Delay Function is a function that requires more computational time to evaluate than to verify. Solana uses a serialized, recursive SHA256, periodically sampling the count and hash, as an effective VDF. This data structure takes real time to generate given the specific SHA256 instructions included on CPUs and can be verified in parallel by splitting the hash chain across multiple GPU cores. <i>According to the company:</i></p>
<p>“Solana’s specific implementation uses a sequential preimage resistant hash that runs over itself continuously with the previous output used as the next input. Periodically the count and the current output are recorded.</p>
<p>For a SHA256 hash function (also Bitcoin’s hash algorithm), this process is impossible to parallelize without a brute force attack using 2¹²⁸ cores.</p>
<p>We can then be certain that real time has passed between each counter as it was generated, and that the recorded order of each counter is the same as it was in real time.”</p>
<figure id="attachment_58771" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-58771" style="width: 1400px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-58771" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/solana.jpg" alt="Solana NFTs are Now Live on Opensea" width="1400" height="933" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/solana.jpg 1400w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/solana-300x200.jpg 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/solana-1024x682.jpg 1024w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/solana-768x512.jpg 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/solana-50x33.jpg 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/solana-270x180.jpg 270w" sizes="(max-width: 1400px) 100vw, 1400px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-58771" class="wp-caption-text"><a href="https://blockonomi.com/solana-nfts-are-now-live-on-opensea/">Solana NFTs</a> are Now Live <a href="https://beanstalk.io/how-to-buy-nft-on-opensea/">on Opensea</a></figcaption></figure>
<hr />
<h2>Integration With TowerBFT</h2>
<p>The use of the PoH ledger allows a user to compute the state of all the nodes with a fraction of the messaging overhead of most PoS systems. It also works with Solana’s version of PBFT (Practical Byzantine Fault Tolerance)  as the network’s clock, allowing the protocol to encode vote lock-outs in the ledger.These lock-outs are used to ensure that Validators (block producing nodes) aren’t able to vote on two separate forks of the blockchain at the same time. If an attempt is detected, the malicious Validator will be penalized and have his stake slashed.</p>
<blockquote><p>Practically, each time a validator votes for a specific version of the ledger at a specified PoH height, there is a lockout that is associated with that vote. That validator is restricted from voting on a future version of the ledger that doesn’t contain that vote for a specified amount of PoH time (w/out the risk of slashing). Each additional vote on a ledger increases (doubles) the vote lockouts of each previous vote, creating an exponentially growing commitment to safety (consistency) on the given branch.</p></blockquote>
<hr />
<h2>Proof of Stake</h2>
<p>TowerBFT thereby provides the slashing rules that underlie Solana’s Proof of Stake consensus architecture. In this design, validators’ ledger votes are weighted by the amount of capital (SOL) they have locked at stake while validating.</p>
<p>Valiators can also receive tokens from non-validating token holders and stake those tokens on their behalf. Rewards are distributed to validators in proportion to their stake, so non-validating token holders can earn rewards by delegating to a validator and receiving the associated rewards, minus a commission fee taken by the validator.</p>
<p>Solana’s block production is determined by a randomly generated leader schedule, which is set according to his proportion of the total stake at the start of an epoch. That is to say, a validator is expected to be elected leader with a frequency that is commiserate with their proportion of total stake (e.g. a validator with 20% of total stake will represent roughly 20% of the leader schedule)</p>
<p>Rewards for block production will be paid by both inflation, that is expected to reduce over time, and by transaction fees.</p>
<hr />
<h2>Ideas that Matter</h2>
<p>The novel use of PoH, TowerBFT and PoS aren’t the only innovations that Solana is bringing to the table. The company has also created other viable systems that address some of the shortcomings in the first generation of decentralized blockchains.</p>
<h2>Archivers</h2>
<p>At full capacity, Solana estimates that its blockchain would generate roughly 4 petabytes of data on an annual basis. If it were a requirement that a full node store this data, it would introduce a huge barrier to entry for participation in the protocol.</p>
<p>To address this, Solana is able to leverage PoH to stripe and store the growing ledger across storage light-clients (Archivers). This means that the ledger can be split up and distributed across many network participants with no single participant needing to store the entirety of the ledger while the network can ensure multiple redundancy of the global ledger. Additionally, this provides a low barrier to entry to become involved with Solana as a network participant. All is needed is some extra storage space and an internet connection and it is possible to begin earning Solana tokens are rewards for participating as an Archiver on the network.</p>
<p>Solana plans to incentivize full nodes with an estimated 3% of SOL inflation (yearly), which is a clear benefit over Bitcoin. Although Bitcoin is the most valuable blockchain in the world when measured by market cap, full nodes aren’t incentivized.</p>
<h2>Turbine</h2>
<p>The amount of time it requires to propagate all blockchain data to all nodes can be a major hindrance to scalability, because of the lack of bandwidth.</p>
<p>Solana thinks that the answer is to break the data down into packets, which is how BitTorrent distributes huge files with relatively small amounts of bandwidth. Turbine leverages the entire network to move data and allows nodes to do more with less.</p>
<h2>Sealevel</h2>
<p>Solana thinks that parallel validation can be applied to smart contracts, and that the entire network can benefit from gains in efficiency.</p>
<p>According to Solana:</p>
<blockquote><p>“Solana’s runtime can process tens of thousands of contracts in parallel, using as many cores as are available to the Validator. This is because Solana transactions describe all the states a transaction will read or write while executing. This not only allows for non-overlapping transactions to execute concurrently, but also for transactions that are only reading the same state to execute concurrently as well.”</p></blockquote>
<p>It is clear that Solana has created an integrated blockchain platform that offers up well thought out solutions to some of the biggest issues that decentralized blockchains face as they grow in popularity.</p>
<hr />
<h2>The SOL Token</h2>
<p>Solana also has a token, called SOL, which can be passed to nodes on the Solana blockchain for running an on-chain program or validating its output. Solana says that:</p>
<p>“…a SOL may be split as many as 34 times. The fractional SOL is called a lamport. It is named in honor of Solana’s biggest technical influence, Leslie Lamport. A lamport has a value of approximately 0.0000000000582 sol (2^-34).”</p>
<hr />
<h2>Solana Wallets</h2>
<h3>Software Wallet</h3>
<p>Hot wallets, also called software wallets, are one of the most popular cryptocurrency storage options. They are always online, hence the affiliation with the ‘hot’ tag. Investors can easily get a hot wallet once they open an account with a crypto exchange. This allows them to store and manage their private keys, which prove their ownership of their assets to the blockchain network. Hot wallets are usually more convenient for everyday crypto transactions and can be custodial or non-custodial.</p>
<figure id="attachment_66606" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-66606" style="width: 705px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-66606" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/hot-wallet.png" alt="Hot wallet" width="705" height="535" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/hot-wallet.png 705w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/hot-wallet-300x228.png 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/hot-wallet-50x38.png 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/hot-wallet-87x67.png 87w" sizes="(max-width: 705px) 100vw, 705px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-66606" class="wp-caption-text">Hot wallet</figcaption></figure>
<p>A custody wallet is responsible for storing assets to an exchange or a third-party platform. The user only places an order for a transfer or receipt, and the exchange signs off on the transaction, much like the traditional banking system. Meanwhile, a non-custodial or self-custody wallet gives the full responsibility to the end-user.</p>
<p>Hot wallets are usually free, but they are largely considered less secure due to their constant internet connectivity. An instance of a hot wallet is the Binance Wallet.</p>
<h3>Hardware Wallet</h3>
<p>A Hardware wallet is a device which has been created to provide an extra layer of security when interacting with your various cryptocurrency wallets.</p>
<p>Normally you would use your private key to move funds, the problem is though, if your computer has been compromised with malware or a virus, it is possible for your private keys to be captured and used to steal your funds.</p>
<figure id="attachment_66607" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-66607" style="width: 838px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-66607" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/cold-wallet.png" alt="Cold wallet" width="838" height="455" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/cold-wallet.png 838w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/cold-wallet-300x163.png 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/cold-wallet-768x417.png 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/cold-wallet-50x27.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 838px) 100vw, 838px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-66607" class="wp-caption-text">Hardware wallet</figcaption></figure>
<p>With a hardware wallet, the private keys are stored on the device and never exposed to your computer, which means even if you are infected with such a program your private keys will remain safe. These options are safest way to store your crypto if you have more than a small amount.</p>
<p>Popular examples of cold storage offerings are the Ledger and Trezor line of hardware wallet solutions, read our reviews:</p>
<ul>
<li><a href="https://blockonomi.com/ledger-nano-s-review/">Ledger Nano S Review</a></li>
<li><a href="https://blockonomi.com/ledger-nano-x-review/">Ledger Nano X Review</a></li>
<li><a href="https://blockonomi.com/trezor-vs-ledger/">Trezor vs. Ledger Review</a></li>
</ul>
<h3>Mobile wallet</h3>
<p>A mobile wallet is essentially a hot wallet on a smartphone device. They offer users an even more convenient way to use their coins for daily activities. Mobile wallets store and manage users' private keys while enabling them to pay for things they love with their digital assets.</p>
<figure id="attachment_66608" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-66608" style="width: 751px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-66608" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/mobile-wallet.png" alt="Mobile wallet" width="751" height="429" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/mobile-wallet.png 751w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/mobile-wallet-300x171.png 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/mobile-wallet-50x29.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 751px) 100vw, 751px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-66608" class="wp-caption-text">Mobile wallet</figcaption></figure>
<p>These wallets are usually free and always online for transactions to be processed. Popular mobile wallets are eToro Money Wallet and Coinbase Wallet.</p>
<h3>Desktop wallet</h3>
<p>A desktop wallet is a PC version of a hot wallet. It is essentially software that an investor downloads into their personal computer or laptop for easy interaction with their digital coins. They also offer a browser extension which allows users to interact using an extension instead of downloading the entire software. Desktop wallets are also hack-prone due to their online nature. A popular example is the Exodus Wallet.</p>
<h3>Paper Wallet</h3>
<p>The paper wallet is arguably the oldest form of crypto wallet. They are no longer common in the modern crypto industry. It contains users' public and private keys. The paper wallet is the least secure type of wallet as it can easily be lost, stolen, or torched.</p>
<hr />
<h2>How to Buy Solana on Binance</h2>
<p>After exploring where to buy and the coin’s use cases, the next thing is to explore how to buy it for your portfolio. Binance is our recommended exchange, so we'll explore how to purchase the asset using Binance.</p>
<h3>Step 1: Sign Up</h3>
<p>Go to the <a href="/out/binance">Binance home page</a> and click on “Register”.</p>
<figure id="attachment_66583" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-66583" style="width: 1342px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="wp-image-66583 size-full" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/welcome.png" alt="Binance signup" width="1342" height="488" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/welcome.png 1342w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/welcome-300x109.png 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/welcome-1024x372.png 1024w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/welcome-768x279.png 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/welcome-50x18.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1342px) 100vw, 1342px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-66583" class="wp-caption-text">Binance signup</figcaption></figure>
<p>Binance allows investors to register using their mobile phone, email address, or Google account. Most users choose the first two options and provide their phone numbers, emails, and desired passwords. A link will be sent to their registration channel of choice, and investors can click on it to authenticate their accounts.</p>
<h3>Step 2: Verify Your Identity</h3>
<p>Like many other regulated brokers, Binance requires that investors verify their identity before commencing their purchase.</p>
<p>To complete the process, visit the “Identification” tab. Investors will have to share personal information, their proof of residence, and a government-verified means of identification. This process should take no more than a few minutes to complete.</p>
<h3>Step 3: Deposit Your Funds</h3>
<p>Next, investors will have to deposit into their Binance wallets. The exchange makes deposits possible using payment processors, wire transfers, bank deposits, and direct crypto transfers. And its required minimum deposit is $10.</p>
<figure id="attachment_66584" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-66584" style="width: 675px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="wp-image-66584 size-full" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/deposit.png" alt="Deposit on Binance" width="675" height="434" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/deposit.png 675w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/deposit-300x193.png 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/deposit-50x32.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 675px) 100vw, 675px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-66584" class="wp-caption-text">Deposit on Binance</figcaption></figure>
<p>To make a deposit, go to the “Payment” section and click “Add a new payment method” to enter payment details. Alternatively, investors can click the “Buy Crypto” button to select a payment method and complete their transfer.</p>
<h3>Step 4: Buy</h3>
<p>With a funded wallet, investors are ready to make a your purchase. Head to the “Buy Crypto” section and enter the desired amount. Click on “Continue” after reviewing the terms, and the wallet should be updated immediately.</p>
<hr />
<h2>Conclusion</h2>
<p>Solana is working to create scalability solutions for decentralized blockchain systems, and it has addressed some of the biggest issues that decentralized platforms face. By removing sharding from its design, Solana makes network-wide validation faster, and potentially more secure in the long-run.</p>
<p>The Solana blockchain has the potential to match a platform like Visa, without any sort of centralized system. The non-linear architecture that Solana employs may force other blockchain developers to rethink linear blockchain systems, due to their inherent limitations.</p>
<p>Proof of History (PoH) protocol is an interesting way to remove the problem of time from a blockchain, and the system that Solana may be successful in creating a global relative time standard for decentralized blockchain operations.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/buy-solana/">Where to Buy Solana (SOL) Crypto Coin: Beginner’s Guide</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">34775</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Where to Buy Theta Token (THETA) Crypto: Complete Guide</title>
		<link>https://blockonomi.com/buy-theta/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jimmy Aki]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2024 02:28:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Buying]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blockonomi.com/?p=66775</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A significant portion of internet traffic is generated by streaming and video-sharing websites. The majority of the income, however, goes to businesses and platforms like YouTube rather than the content creators responsible for the growth of streaming services. Theta proposes a decentralized video streaming network to address this issue. The platform rewards all content producers, [...]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/buy-theta/">Where to Buy Theta Token (THETA) Crypto: Complete Guide</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A significant portion of internet traffic is generated by streaming and video-sharing websites. The majority of the income, however, goes to businesses and platforms like YouTube rather than the content creators responsible for the growth of streaming services.</p>
<p>Theta proposes a <a href="https://blockonomi.com/youtube-alternative/">decentralized video</a> streaming network to address this issue. The platform rewards all content producers, viewers, and users who contribute to decentralizing the online video market through its native coin.</p>
<p>This article will examine how to buy Theta tokens, how the digital asset works, and where to buy it.</p>
<div class="callout">
<h2 style="text-align: center;">Where to Buy Theta Network THETA</h2>
<p>This section is our top picks of where and how to buy the Theta Crypto token. We chose these based on our experience of using them and considered fees, security, payment options and reputation.</p>
<ul>
<li><strong><a href="/out/binance">Binance:</a> </strong>Largest Crypto Exchange with Low Fees</li>
<li><strong><a href="/out/coinbase">Coinbase:</a> </strong>Highly Regarded and Easy to Use for Beginners</li>
<li><strong><a href="https://blockonomi.com/out/ftx">Kraken:</a></strong> Top Platform With High Liquidity</li>
<li><strong><a href="https://blockonomi.com/out/kucoin">Kucoin:</a></strong> Long Established Exchange With Lots of Listings</li>
</ul>
<div class="verdict">
<h4 style="text-align: center;">Visit The Top Pick</h4>
<p style="text-align: center;"><a class="infobutton" href="/out/binance">Visit Binance</a></p>
</div>
</div>
<div class="callout">
<h3><img decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-1579 alignright" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/11/binance.gif" alt="Binance Review" width="150" height="150" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/11/binance.gif 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/11/binance-65x65.gif 65w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/11/binance-50x50.gif 50w" sizes="(max-width: 150px) 100vw, 150px" />Binance: Reputable Exchange with High Liquidity</h3>
<p><a href="/out/binance">Binance</a> is the largest cryptocurrency trading exchange in daily trade volumes. The exchange offers investors full access to trade over 600 crypto assets.</p>
<p>The renowned platform also features a well-detailed learning curve and advanced trading tools that support well-experienced traders and investors looking to learn how to buy different cryptos. Although Binance features a user-friendly interface that facilitates a great user experience, it is more suited for well-experienced traders.</p>
<p><strong>Read: <a href="https://blockonomi.com/binance-review/">Our Full Binance Review Here</a></strong></p>
<p>Binance has a minimum deposit of $10. This enables investors to kickstart their investing journey with low fees. Investors can also initiate deposits through seamless payment methods like wire transfers, credit/debit cards, peer-to-peer (P2P) payments, and other e-wallet solutions.</p>
<figure id="attachment_66588" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-66588" style="width: 785px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-66588" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/binance.jpg" alt="Binance Website" width="785" height="520" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/binance.jpg 785w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/binance-300x199.jpg 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/binance-768x509.jpg 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/binance-50x33.jpg 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/binance-270x180.jpg 270w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/binance-370x245.jpg 370w" sizes="(max-width: 785px) 100vw, 785px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-66588" class="wp-caption-text">Binance Website</figcaption></figure>
<p>Binance deposits come with a fee that varies based on the payment method used. For instance, the global exchange charges a standard fee of up to 4.50% for all deposits made with a debit/credit card.</p>
<p>All investors enjoy very low fees when trading on Binance, as it charges a standard trading fee of 0.1%. For investors that buy using Binance token (BNB), a discount of 25% on trading fees will be applied.</p>
<p>In addition, investors can rest assured that their funds and data are well protected whenever they trade on Binance. The broker features top-notch security measures like two-factor authentication (2FA), cold storage to keep most coins, whitelisting, and advanced data encryption to protect funds and data. Binance functions effectively in over 100 countries and has a spin-off regulated platform (Binance.US) that tends to US-based traders and investors.</p>
<p><strong>Pros</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Trading fees at 0.01%</li>
<li>High liquidity</li>
<li>Wide range of payment methods</li>
<li>600+ crypto assets in library</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Cons</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Interface is suited for advanced traders</li>
<li>US-based customers cannot trade most coins via its subsidiary</li>
</ul>
<div class="verdict">
<p style="text-align: center;"><a class="infobutton" href="/out/binance">Visit Binance</a></p>
</div>
</div>
<div class="callout">
<h3><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-37984 alignright" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/coinbase-review.gif" alt="Coinbase Review" width="150" height="150" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/coinbase-review.gif 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/coinbase-review-50x50.gif 50w" sizes="(max-width: 150px) 100vw, 150px" />Coinbase: Simple &amp; Easy to Use Exchange</h3>
<p><a href="/out/coinbase">Coinbase</a> is also a great option for investors looking for how to buy the crypto seamlessly. The US-based crypto trading platform enables users to buy, sell, and stake cryptocurrencies with zero complexity.</p>
<p>Coinbase integrates a user-friendly interface that simplifies crypto trading. The crypto trading platform supports well over 10,000 blockchain-based assets.</p>
<p><strong>Read: <a href="https://blockonomi.com/coinbase-review/">Our Full Coinbase Review Here</a></strong></p>
<p>The exchange’s signup and verification process take less than 10 minutes. For traders looking to invest easily, Coinbase is a great alternative to Binance.</p>
<p>Coinbase has a minimum deposit of $2, the lowest minimum deposit in the market presently This exchange also offers a wide range of deposit methods like automated clearing house (ACH), Wire transfer, debit card, and e-wallet solutions, as well as cashouts in local currencies like USD, GBP, and EUR. Coinbase charges up to 3.99% for debit card deposits.</p>
<figure id="attachment_66587" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-66587" style="width: 770px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-large wp-image-66587" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/coinbase-1024x490.png" alt="Coinbase Website" width="770" height="368" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/coinbase-1024x490.png 1024w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/coinbase-300x144.png 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/coinbase-768x367.png 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/coinbase-50x24.png 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/coinbase.png 1348w" sizes="(max-width: 770px) 100vw, 770px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-66587" class="wp-caption-text">Coinbase Website</figcaption></figure>
<p>Investors enjoy a 4% cash back reward whenever a Coinbase debit card is used for crypto purchases.</p>
<p>For fees, Coinbase charges a competitive fee of 0.5% - 4.5% depending on the payment method, cryptocurrency type, and transaction sizes.</p>
<p>Coinbase has evolved from a traditional exchange to a versatile platform with great services dedicated to retail and institutional investors, such as an in-built exchange wallet, self-issued cash back visa card, staking, derivatives, asset hubs, ventures, and many more.</p>
<p>Furthermore, Coinbase has in-built security practices like 2FA verification as an added security layer to investors’ usernames and passwords, crime insurance that secures digital assets from theft and fraud, and many more.</p>
<p>Also, Coinbase is licensed by the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) and regulated by top financial authorities like Financial Conduct Authority (FCA), Financial Crimes and Enforcement Network (FinCEN), and the New York State Department of Financial Services (NYSDFS).</p>
<p><strong>Pros</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Beginner-focused</li>
<li>Licensed and reputable platform</li>
<li>Insurance in case of hacks</li>
<li>Low minimum deposit</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Cons</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>High fee compared to competitors</li>
<li>No credit card deposits for US customers</li>
</ul>
<div class="verdict">
<p style="text-align: center;"><a class="infobutton" href="/out/coinbase">Visit Coinbase</a></p>
</div>
</div>
<div class="callout">
<h3><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-3084 alignright" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/01/kraken-review.gif" alt="Kraken Review" width="150" height="150" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/01/kraken-review.gif 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/01/kraken-review-65x65.gif 65w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/01/kraken-review-50x50.gif 50w" sizes="(max-width: 150px) 100vw, 150px" />Kraken: Top Crypto Platform with High Liquidity</h3>
<p>Founded in 2011, <a href="/out/kraken">Kraken</a> is one of the oldest and most popular <a href="https://blockonomi.com/cryptocurrency-exchanges/">cryptocurrency exchanges</a> currently in operation.</p>
<p>The exchange has built a reputation as being a secure destination for anyone interested in trading cryptocurrencies and it is also a popular choice for both traders and institutions across a variety of locations.</p>
<p><strong>Read: <a href="https://blockonomi.com/kraken-review/">Our Full Kraken Review Here</a></strong></p>
<p>Kraken retains an international appeal and provides efficient trading opportunities in numerous fiat currencies. Kraken is also the current world leader in terms of Bitcoin to Euro trading volumes.</p>
<figure id="attachment_42155" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-42155" style="width: 808px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-42155" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/kraken.jpg" alt="Kraken Homepage" width="808" height="683" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/kraken.jpg 808w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/kraken-300x254.jpg 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/kraken-768x649.jpg 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/kraken-50x42.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 808px) 100vw, 808px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-42155" class="wp-caption-text">Kraken Homepage</figcaption></figure>
<p>Kraken is most well known for its Bitcoin and Ethereum to cash (EUR and USD) markets; however a wide range of both fiat and cryptocurrencies are tradable on the platform</p>
<h4>Pros</h4>
<ul>
<li>Dedicated service for institutions</li>
<li>Great for beginners to use</li>
<li>High trading liquidity</li>
</ul>
<h4>Cons</h4>
<ul>
<li>The lengthy ID verification process</li>
</ul>
<div class="verdict">
<p style="text-align: center;"><a class="infobutton" href="/out/kraken">Visit Kraken</a></p>
</div>
</div>
<div class="callout">
<h3><img decoding="async" class="size-thumbnail wp-image-42275 alignright" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/kucoin-150x150.png" alt="" width="150" height="150" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/kucoin-150x150.png 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/kucoin-300x300.png 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/kucoin-50x50.png 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/kucoin-370x370.png 370w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/kucoin.png 400w" sizes="(max-width: 150px) 100vw, 150px" />KuCoin: Exchange With Lots of Listings</h3>
<p><a href="/out/kucoin">KuCoin</a> is one of the world's oldest and most popular crypto exchanges. The Seychelles-based broker is one of the most notable names in the market for traders who desire access to derivatives products to speculate in the market.</p>
<p>Currently, KuCoin provides access to over 600 cryptocurrencies. Besides trading and investing, the exchange allows investors to save, stake crypto, and even participate in Initial Exchange Offerings. With KuCoin, investors have an all-encompassing crypto hub.</p>
<p><strong>Read: <a href="https://blockonomi.com/kucoin-review/">Our Full Kucoin Review Here</a></strong></p>
<p>Like many brokers in its class, KuCoin could appear too overwhelming for beginners. The exchange is more suited for advanced traders who want to speculate and trade sophisticated products. So beginners might have some difficulty making use of it.</p>
<p>Despite this, investors could gain many benefits from trading with KuCoin. The broker has a low minimum balance of $5, with deposits available via major fiat currencies, peer-to-peer (P2P) transfers, and a few credit card options.</p>
<figure id="attachment_42262" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-42262" style="width: 808px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="wp-image-42262 size-full" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/kucoin.jpg" alt="Kucoin Homepage" width="808" height="585" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/kucoin.jpg 808w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/kucoin-300x217.jpg 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/kucoin-768x556.jpg 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/07/kucoin-50x36.jpg 50w" sizes="(max-width: 808px) 100vw, 808px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-42262" class="wp-caption-text">Kucoin Homepage</figcaption></figure>
<p>As for trading fees, KuCoin users pay 0.1% in fees. But the fees could decrease based on an investor's 30-day trading volume and ownership of the company’s KCS token.</p>
<p>Security on KuCoin is also impressive. The system uses bank-level encryption and security infrastructures to protect users’ coins and data. KuCoin also has a specialized risk control department to enforce strict data usage policies.</p>
<p><strong>Pros</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Discounts available on trading fees</li>
<li>Extensive staking functionalities</li>
<li>Quick P2P trading system</li>
<li>Anonymous trading available</li>
<li>Low minimum balance</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Cons</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>No bank deposit option</li>
</ul>
<div class="verdict">
<p style="text-align: center;"><a class="infobutton" href="/out/kucoin">Visit Kucoin</a></p>
</div>
</div>
<hr />
<h2>What Is Theta Coin?</h2>
<p><a href="https://www.thetatoken.org/">Theta Network</a>, whose utility token is <img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="alignright size-full wp-image-66793" style="font-size: 19px; font-family: ff-more-web-pro, 'PT Serif', Georgia, serif;" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Screenshot-2022-08-18-at-18.35.52.png" alt="" width="425" height="135" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Screenshot-2022-08-18-at-18.35.52.png 425w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Screenshot-2022-08-18-at-18.35.52-300x95.png 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Screenshot-2022-08-18-at-18.35.52-50x16.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 425px) 100vw, 425px" /><span style="font-size: 19px;">THETA, </span>aims to lead the way in streaming and entertainment technology. They intend to accomplish this by using P2P (peer-to-peer) bandwidth resource sharing.</p>
<p>Theta is a peer-to-peer video streaming network launched in 2019. Its users are primarily responsible for its functionality. The community-run &#8220;guardian&#8221; node network and users contribute to the decentralisation of the Theta platform.</p>
<p>Theta intends to provide a decentralised platform for content producers to address the issues with streaming services like YouTube and Twitch. Its blockchain, like that of Cardano and Ethereum, supports smart contracts. However, unlike many other smart contract-enabled blockchains, Theta has a functioning ecosystem and users on its platform. Moreover, Theta&#8217;s blockchain-based decentralised application (DApp), Theta.tv, enables users to stream content without requiring a centralised third-party network.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-66794" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Screenshot-2022-08-18-at-18.36.03.png" alt="" width="1297" height="347" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Screenshot-2022-08-18-at-18.36.03.png 1297w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Screenshot-2022-08-18-at-18.36.03-300x80.png 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Screenshot-2022-08-18-at-18.36.03-1024x274.png 1024w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Screenshot-2022-08-18-at-18.36.03-768x205.png 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Screenshot-2022-08-18-at-18.36.03-50x13.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1297px) 100vw, 1297px" />The open-source network has two tokens: THETA and Theta Fuel (TFUEL). <a href="https://blockonomi.com/buy-theta/">Theta token</a>, the platform&#8217;s native cryptocurrency, is employed for protocol governance. Because Theta is decentralised, token holders can vote with their tokens on network improvements. TFuel, used to pay network validators to process transactions on Theta&#8217;s blockchain, is comparable to Ethereum&#8217;s gas.</p>
<hr />
<h2>Theta Use Cases</h2>
<p>Theta Network is comparable to platforms like Twitch or YouTube in that content producers can link to various dApps to stream the content they want. The Theta network uses a dual token system using THETA and Theta Fuel tokens to provide services. So what are the use cases for the network and tokens?</p>
<h3>Governance</h3>
<p>Theta governance is one of the most important use cases of the Theta token. A crypto ecosystem&#8217;s governance entails internal network activity management. According to its white paper, holders of Theta tokens are tasked with voting for various ecosystem operations. The typical investor will also need to vote on other network-wide initiatives.</p>
<p>Holders will vote on the best project while formulating development plans. The token holders can cast a vote depending on how many tokens they own.</p>
<p><iframe class="youtube-player" width="814" height="458" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/OQR7GVoV-24?version=3&#038;rel=1&#038;showsearch=0&#038;showinfo=1&#038;iv_load_policy=1&#038;fs=1&#038;hl=en-US&#038;autohide=2&#038;wmode=transparent" allowfullscreen="true" style="border:0;" sandbox="allow-scripts allow-same-origin allow-popups allow-presentation allow-popups-to-escape-sandbox"></iframe></p>
<h3>Ethereum virtual machine (EVM)</h3>
<p>When creating Dapps, using the Ethereum and Theta chains will be feasible thanks to the EVM compatibility. Furthermore, Dapps can be moved to and from the Theta chain.</p>
<p>Theta Fuel token is the primary asset that aids gas payments to run the decentralised apps. Dapps on the Theta network need resources, namely processing power.</p>
<p>Blockchains frequently <a href="https://beanstalk.io/gas-in-crypto/">charge gas fees</a> for processing power. Therefore, developers must use Theta Fuel to pay the gas fee.</p>
<h3>Payments and Royalty Distribution</h3>
<p>Another use for this Theta network is ensuring the payment mechanism is streamlined. The network makes use of a pay-per-use or pay-as-you-go system. Investors only pay for what they consume. Such a system would enable content producers to profit directly from their work.</p>
<p>Theta features a resource-oriented micropayments pool that uses the available smart contracts to track micropayments and video clips. The distribution of royalties to the content providers will be equitable.</p>
<h3>Theta.tv Contents and Rewards</h3>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-66806" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Screenshot-2022-08-18-at-19.34.20.png" alt="" width="422" height="111" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Screenshot-2022-08-18-at-19.34.20.png 422w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Screenshot-2022-08-18-at-19.34.20-300x79.png 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Screenshot-2022-08-18-at-19.34.20-50x13.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 422px) 100vw, 422px" />Theta.tv is one of Theta Network&#8217;s most popular applications and a powerful example of the Network&#8217;s potential as a decentralised content distribution network. This is because it offers various channels of the highest quality and production, channels devoted to multiple interests and technologies, and the ability to stream very easily without giving up income generation in Theta Network&#8217;s tokenomics.</p>
<h3>Partnership</h3>
<p>Theta and Sony have <a href="https://twitter.com/mitchliu/status/1531495239197728768?s=20&amp;t=-b_UWsXbFk77DwH3bYz4nA">collaborated</a> to release 3D NFTs compatible with Sony&#8217;s Spatial Reality Device (SRD). A tablet-like gadget called the SRD shows 3D visuals in semi-augmented reality.</p>
<p>Users can view and interact with three-dimensional items without the aid of glasses or other attachments using Sony&#8217;s SRD. This tablet-like device displays three-dimensional graphics in a semi-physical augmented reality.</p>
<p>Thus, the Theta and Sony NFTs will be visible and operative on the SRD in mixed reality 3D without eye attachments.</p>
<hr />
<h2>How Does Theta Protocol Work?</h2>
<p>Theta is a decentralized video delivery network that complies with ERC-20. According to this classification, Theta users can utilise the Ethereum ecosystem to simplify their cryptocurrency experience.</p>
<p>ERC-20 currencies are supported by a vast selection of wallets, DEXs, and games, thanks to Ethereum having the largest Dapp ecosystem in the world.</p>
<p>Furthermore, to increase the calibre of stream delivery, Theta integrates several patented technologies with the efficiency and security of Ethereum.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-66807" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Screenshot-2022-08-18-at-19.36.31.png" alt="" width="726" height="404" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Screenshot-2022-08-18-at-19.36.31.png 726w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Screenshot-2022-08-18-at-19.36.31-300x167.png 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Screenshot-2022-08-18-at-19.36.31-50x28.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 726px) 100vw, 726px" /></p>
<h3>Theta Blockchain</h3>
<p>The foundation of the decentralised video sharing network is the Theta blockchain. Based on the Multi-level Byzantine Fault Tolerant consensus method, it enables smart contracts and NFTs and allows for 1,000 transactions per second.</p>
<p>The architecture of the blockchain enables optimum functionality. The system can, for instance, retrieve streams from peering caching nodes. By using this strategy, video platforms can drastically cut their content delivery network (CDN) expenses.</p>
<p>The network is supported by two primary node types that host videos and validate transactions:</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Enterprise Validators Nodes:</strong> Only 20–30 of these nodes exist, and they are managed by giants like Google, Binance, and Theta Labs. Transactions are organised into blocks and introduced to the network via Enterprise Validator Nodes.</li>
<li><strong>Guardian Nodes:</strong> This is the Theta blockchain&#8217;s second level of security. Guardian Nodes seal the blocks, validate them, and act as a regulator to spot defective nodes.</li>
</ul>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-66795" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Screenshot-2022-08-18-at-18.36.18.png" alt="" width="1280" height="491" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Screenshot-2022-08-18-at-18.36.18.png 1280w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Screenshot-2022-08-18-at-18.36.18-300x115.png 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Screenshot-2022-08-18-at-18.36.18-1024x393.png 1024w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Screenshot-2022-08-18-at-18.36.18-768x295.png 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Screenshot-2022-08-18-at-18.36.18-50x19.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1280px) 100vw, 1280px" />Additionally, Theta has 130,000 Edge Nodes that offer the platform&#8217;s <a href="https://community.theta.tv/theta-edgecast/"><strong>EdgeCast</strong></a> service: the computational power necessary to relay video broadcasts in exchange for TFUEL tokens. Because Theta is decentralised, no one can control or block films, like on centralised sites. Edge Nodes aid in keeping the network censorship-resistant.</p>
<h3>Consensus Mechanism</h3>
<p>Multi-Level Byzantine Fault Tolerance, a new variation of the Proof-of-Stake consensus process, is used by Theta. When compared to conventional Proof-of-work systems, this consensus method is substantially faster.</p>
<p>The consensus technique used by Theta differs from conventional PoS in that it involves both validator and guardian nodes, giving the protocol an additional layer of security.</p>
<p>These nodes must stake THETA tokens to create blocks, participate in voting, and power the blockchain. While Guardian Nodes only need to stake 100,000 THETA, Validator Nodes must stake a minimum of 10,000,000 THETA.</p>
<p>Also, the number of THETA staked determines voting power.</p>
<h3>Dual Token</h3>
<p>The dual token system Theta uses allows for the separation of the functions of each token. For example, Theta Token (THETA), the protocol&#8217;s governance token, is staked by the Validator and Guardian nodes. On the other hand, Theta Fuel (TFUEL) is the &#8220;gas&#8221; token utilised for network functions, like engaging with smart contracts.</p>
<hr />
<h2>Is Theta Coin a Good Investment?</h2>
<p>Theta is a serious contender in the market, where many blockchain initiatives are emerging, thanks to its history and functionality. Its coin, THETA, offers a solution for content consumption in addition to serving the growing blockchain ecosystem.</p>
<p>Let&#8217;s look at some benefits for investors wondering how to buy Theta coin and why they should invest.</p>
<h3>Access to Multiple Content</h3>
<p>Theta users have access to a global data delivery and video content base. This open-source project offers peer-to-peer streaming, esports, music, TV/movies, education, enterprise conferencing, and more.</p>
<h3>Interoperability</h3>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-66808" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Screenshot-2022-08-18-at-19.40.37.png" alt="" width="684" height="243" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Screenshot-2022-08-18-at-19.40.37.png 684w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Screenshot-2022-08-18-at-19.40.37-300x107.png 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Screenshot-2022-08-18-at-19.40.37-50x18.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 684px) 100vw, 684px" />The Theta network&#8217;s expandability and interoperability are two more key advantages. The network allows for the development of vertical decentralised applications (Dapp). These applications use the platform&#8217;s powerful technological toolkit and are built on top of it. SLIVER.tv was the first Dapp to debut on the network.</p>
<h3>Affordable Content Ownership and Revenue</h3>
<p>The main benefit of this project is that streaming through Theta Network is significantly less expensive than using other centralised networks. Also, because the incentive and storage payment systems are entirely decentralised, users can earn money from it directly into their wallets.</p>
<p>Theta Network provides tools for integrating its services into decentralised applications (dApps) and centralised applications, with the option to incorporate digital rights management (DRM) for content protection and even advertising to generate revenue.</p>
<h3>Multiple Streaming Choices</h3>
<p>Finally, the quality of streaming content can vary depending on requirements. 720p (HD), 1080p (Full HD), 2K, 4K, and VR/AR in real time are all possible resolutions. Because of its P2P-style CDN transmission and storage technology, Theta Network is unique in terms of streaming capabilities. All of this is kept up by its blockchain network&#8217;s tokenomics.</p>
<h3>Theta Token Utility</h3>
<p>The THETA token is valuable because of how it may be used in the dual-token Theta Network economy. For example, THETA is required for staking by Guardian and Validator nodes and serves as a crucial governance token.</p>
<h3>Top Collaboration</h3>
<p>Numerous investors have backed the platform, including major venture capital firms and leading IT firms like Sony and Samsung.</p>
<p>Theta has a distinguished board of advisors that includes industry leaders from Microsoft, Sony, Verizon, and Twitch. The co-founder of YouTube and most well-known Theta backer is Steve Chen. He believes the network will disrupt the video industry successfully because of the platform&#8217;s improved image quality and less expensive content delivery.</p>
<p>Theta also has many partners, including big names like NASA, Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer, and Katy Perry.</p>
<hr />
<h2>How to Buy Theta Coin on Binance</h2>
<p>Unsure about how to buy Theta coin? Learn how to purchase Theta Network (THETA) using <a href="/out/binance">the Binance app</a>:</p>
<p>After exploring where to buy and the coin’s use cases, the next thing is to explore how to buy it for your portfolio. Binance is our recommended exchange, so we'll explore how to purchase the asset using Binance.</p>
<h3>Step 1: Sign Up</h3>
<p>Go to the <a href="/out/binance">Binance home page</a> and click on “Register”.</p>
<figure id="attachment_66583" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-66583" style="width: 1342px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="wp-image-66583 size-full" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/welcome.png" alt="Binance signup" width="1342" height="488" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/welcome.png 1342w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/welcome-300x109.png 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/welcome-1024x372.png 1024w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/welcome-768x279.png 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/welcome-50x18.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 1342px) 100vw, 1342px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-66583" class="wp-caption-text">Binance signup</figcaption></figure>
<p>Binance allows investors to register using their mobile phone, email address, or Google account. Most users choose the first two options and provide their phone numbers, emails, and desired passwords. A link will be sent to their registration channel of choice, and investors can click on it to authenticate their accounts.</p>
<h3>Step 2: Verify Your Identity</h3>
<p>Like many other regulated brokers, Binance requires that investors verify their identity before commencing their purchase.</p>
<p>To complete the process, visit the “Identification” tab. Investors will have to share personal information, their proof of residence, and a government-verified means of identification. This process should take no more than a few minutes to complete.</p>
<h3>Step 3: Deposit Your Funds</h3>
<p>Next, investors will have to deposit into their Binance wallets. The exchange makes deposits possible using payment processors, wire transfers, bank deposits, and direct crypto transfers. And its required minimum deposit is $10.</p>
<figure id="attachment_66584" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-66584" style="width: 675px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="wp-image-66584 size-full" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/deposit.png" alt="Deposit on Binance" width="675" height="434" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/deposit.png 675w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/deposit-300x193.png 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/deposit-50x32.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 675px) 100vw, 675px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-66584" class="wp-caption-text">Deposit on Binance</figcaption></figure>
<p>To make a deposit, go to the “Payment” section and click “Add a new payment method” to enter payment details. Alternatively, investors can click the “Buy Crypto” button to select a payment method and complete their transfer.</p>
<h3>Step 4: Buy</h3>
<p>With a funded wallet, investors are ready to make a your purchase. Head to the “Buy Crypto” section and enter the desired amount. Click on “Continue” after reviewing the terms, and the wallet should be updated immediately.</p>
<h4>Buy THETA</h4>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-66792 aligncenter" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Screenshot-2022-08-18-at-18.31.29.png" alt="" width="495" height="391" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Screenshot-2022-08-18-at-18.31.29.png 495w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Screenshot-2022-08-18-at-18.31.29-300x237.png 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Screenshot-2022-08-18-at-18.31.29-50x39.png 50w" sizes="(max-width: 495px) 100vw, 495px" />Once deposited, enter &#8220;THETA&#8221; into the search bar and select &#8220;Spot&#8221; trading. When ready to purchase, enter the desired THETA amount and select &#8220;Buy THETA&#8221;.</p>
<hr />
<h2>Theta Network FAQs</h2>
<h3>Where can I buy THETA Crypto?</h3>
<p>After careful consideration, we&#8217;ve selected Binance as the ideal exchange, which makes purchasing THETA quick and safe. With access to more than 600 digital crypto assets, Binance is the largest cryptocurrency exchange in the world by daily trade volume, processing over $60 billion in everyday transactions. In contrast to its rivals, Binance offers its users competitively low trading fees. Users that pay with the Binance Coin (BNB) token can get a 25% reduction on trading fees, while the maximum trading charge is set at 0.1%. It is straightforward to use and user-friendly.</p>
<h3>What exchanges sell THETA?</h3>
<p>Buying THETA from an exchange is the recommended option, and while there are several exchanges that investors can purchase THETA from, we&#8217;ll name a few. Some cryptocurrency exchanges that sell THETA include Binance, eToro, Kucoin &amp; FTX.</p>
<h3>Can I buy THETA Crypto on Coinbase?</h3>
<p>Investors cannot buy THETA on Coinbase because the cryptocurrency exchange does not support the token.</p>
<h3>Is THETA coin worth buying?</h3>
<p>Theta coin is worth buying. Theta seems to fill a significant gap in the market. Theta also has significant backing and collaboration. Consequently, there is a rising market demand for its token.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/buy-theta/">Where to Buy Theta Token (THETA) Crypto: Complete Guide</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">66775</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Zignaly Founders Extend $ZIG Token Lock-Up for Another Year</title>
		<link>https://blockonomi.com/zignaly-founders-extend-zig-token-lock-up-for-another-year/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Oliver Dale]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 08:17:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blockonomi.com/?p=105111</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Zignaly, the premiere platform for connecting users with top digital asset managers, has announced that its founders have made the strategic decision to extend the lock-up on their $ZIG tokens until January 2026, a year later than originally planned. This decision underscores their unwavering commitment to ZIGChain, the Layer-1 blockchain designed to democratize wealth generation, [...]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/zignaly-founders-extend-zig-token-lock-up-for-another-year/">Zignaly Founders Extend $ZIG Token Lock-Up for Another Year</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://zignaly.com/about">Zignaly</a>, the premiere platform for connecting users with top digital asset managers, has announced that its founders have made the strategic decision to extend the lock-up on their $ZIG tokens until January 2026, a year later than originally planned.</p>
<p>This decision underscores their unwavering commitment to ZIGChain, the Layer-1 blockchain designed to democratize wealth generation, making investment opportunities accessible to everyone.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;By extending the lock-up on our $ZIG tokens, we emphasize our commitment to the community and the mission of ZIGChain,”</p></blockquote>
<p>said Bartolome R. Bordallo, Co-Founder and CEO of Zignaly.</p>
<blockquote><p>“This decision is about fostering equal investment opportunities and ensuring long-term sustainability for all stakeholders. Together, we are building a more inclusive financial future that benefits everyone.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>ZIGChain, Zignaly’s Layer 1 blockchain, represents the next evolution in democratizing wealth-generation opportunities. By offering an infrastructure for developers to build decentralized wealth-generation protocols and fund managers to deploy advanced strategies, ZIGChain is disrupting the way institutions and retail investors can invest. The Blockchain’s <a href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2024/04/17/zignaly-announces-cosmos-based-zigchain-100m-ecosystem-fund/">$100M Ecosystem Fund</a>, supported by DWFLabs and UDHC Finance, aims to drive further innovation within the WEB3 space.</p>
<p>The choice to maintain the lock-up also aligns with the company’s focus on creating equal financial opportunities for all participants within the ZIGChain ecosystem, ensuring that the project&#8217;s core values remain intact. It also significantly changes the company’s tokenomics, leading to lower supply in the market as founder tokens remain locked.</p>
<p>This extension excludes the founders&#8217; donation of 100 million $ZIG tokens to the ZIGChain Foundation. Starting January 2025, these tokens will continue to vest over a 30-month period, following a linear release schedule. The vesting plan aims to empower the ZIGChain ecosy</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/zignaly-founders-extend-zig-token-lock-up-for-another-year/">Zignaly Founders Extend $ZIG Token Lock-Up for Another Year</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">105111</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Orbitt: Revolutionizing Trading &#038; Project Development on Solana With AI</title>
		<link>https://blockonomi.com/orbitt/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nicholas Say]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 07:06:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trading]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blockonomi.com/?p=104010</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Navigating the cryptocurrency space can feel like walking through a minefield of complexity, volatility, and disinformation, especially in rapidly expanding ecosystems like the Solana blockchain. Both traders and developers face an uphill battle to keep up with the increasing number of projects and competition, which makes it difficult to reach the projects or investors they [...]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/orbitt/">Orbitt: Revolutionizing Trading &#038; Project Development on Solana With AI</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Navigating the cryptocurrency space can feel like walking through a minefield of complexity, volatility, and disinformation, especially in rapidly expanding ecosystems like the Solana blockchain.</p>
<p>Both traders and developers face an uphill battle to keep up with the increasing number of projects and competition, which makes it difficult to reach the projects or investors they are interested in.</p>
<p>With the pace of Solana innovation increasing by the day, these challenges are more apparent than ever. The lack of sophisticated, integrated tools tailored specifically for this high-speed environment leaves many participants feeling like they&#8217;re always a step behind, missing crucial opportunities or falling victim to market whiplash.</p>
<p>To developers, this means a lack of liquidity as their promising projects get lost in an inescapable noise. For traders, the absence of reliable analysis tools able to adapt to changing market conditions means that countless hours of “manual” analysis must be done regularly.</p>
<p>In a space in which decision paralysis, impulsive moves, FOMO, and lack of understanding can spell disaster, a better decision is needed.</p>
<p>AI-driven market analysis tools have emerged as one of the most promising solutions, bringing real-time analysis capabilities to a fragmented and often overwhelming market.</p>
<p><a href="https://orbitt.pro/en">One such tool is Orbitt</a>, a comprehensive ecosystem designed to revolutionize trading and project development on Solana through powerful and groundbreaking artificial intelligence (AI) analytics.</p>
<p>Let&#8217;s learn more about Orbitt!</p>
<hr />
<h2>What is Orbitt?</h2>
<p>Orbitt was created with the mission to democratize cryptocurrency by shedding its layers of complexity through AI, accessible design, and innovative blockchain solutions.</p>
<p>The ecosystem is formed by Orbitt PRO and Orbitt MM each designed to serve different segments of the crypto community in different ways.</p>
<p>Powered by the $ORBT token, Orbitt aims to become more than just another set of crypto tools in the ever-growing sea of blockchain-based solutions.</p>
<p>By bringing together the existing transparency, top-notch security, efficiency, scalability, and accessibility of the Solana network with unique AI-based capabilities, Orbitt seeks to empower traders and developers alike to create a vibrant community.</p>
<p>At this time, the Orbitt ecosystem is formed by two tools designed to serve different user bases: Orbitt Pro and Orbit MM.</p>
<p>These products, combined with the $ORBT token, allow traders and developers to gain important insights into the crypto market, amplifying project visibility, boosting trading volumes, offering access to innovative projects, and creating a collaborative community of like-minded crypto enthusiasts.</p>
<hr />
<h2>Orbitt Features</h2>
<h3>Orbitt PRO</h3>
<p><a href="https://orbitt.pro/en/chrome">Orbitt PRO stands at the center of the Orbitt ecosystem.</a> This AI-powered trading companion revolutionizes how traders interact with the cryptocurrency market by offering its users real-time analysis and insights based on their trading activities. Orbitt Pro seamlessly integrates into traders&#8217; existing workflows, using advanced machine learning algorithms trained on vast datasets of crypto market behavior to identify trends and patterns.</p>
<figure id="attachment_104265" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-104265" style="width: 1000px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-104265" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/10/pro.jpg" alt="Orbitt PRO Chrome Extension" width="1000" height="700" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/10/pro.jpg 1000w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/10/pro-300x210.jpg 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/10/pro-768x538.jpg 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/10/pro-50x35.jpg 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/10/pro-150x105.jpg 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/10/pro-450x315.jpg 450w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-104265" class="wp-caption-text">Orbitt PRO <a href="https://chromewebstore.google.com/detail/orbitt-pro-ai/gdflafpepcpbfijbpgkmncfjbkbleeel?hl=en&amp;authuser=0">Chrome Extension</a></figcaption></figure>
<p>Users can use prompts to interact with Orbitt PRO in the same way they do with major generative AI tools like ChatGPT Claude, making it accessible to virtually any trader. The use of readable language instead of complex charts and numbers also makes the information more easy to digest and learn from. Developed as a Chrome Extension. Orbitt PRO is accessible to users from major internet browsers like Google Chrome, Opera, Brave, and other Chromium-based browsers.</p>
<hr />
<h3>Orbitt MM</h3>
<p>The chances of success of any crypto project are only as high as its trading volume and liquidity allow. <a href="https://orbitt.pro/en/mm">Orbitt MM is designed to boost liquidity and trading volume</a> for Solana-based projects, using an innovative Telegram Bot to amplify project visibility. By helping projects reach their audiences and investors to find projects that suit their needs and strategies, Orbitt MM helps stakeholders connect more effectively.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-104267" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/10/mm.jpg" alt="" width="1000" height="700" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/10/mm.jpg 1000w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/10/mm-300x210.jpg 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/10/mm-768x538.jpg 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/10/mm-50x35.jpg 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/10/mm-150x105.jpg 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/10/mm-450x315.jpg 450w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" /></p>
<p>Orbitt MM offers different packages to blockchain projects, providing flexibility and effectiveness that suits their needs at any given time. These packages vary in duration, reach, volume gained, and other results. Projects can estimate the volume they stand to earn beforehand, helping them make the best decision to increase effectiveness.</p>
<h3>The $ORBT Token</h3>
<p>With a total supply of 20 million tokens, <a href="https://orbitt.pro/en/token">the $ORBT token</a> serves as the blood of the Orbitt Ecosystem by powering every transaction. A total of 19.9 million tokens exist, with 12.3 million being in circulation and gaining around 11.1% in value over the past week at the time of writing. A total of 7.7 million $ORBT tokens were vested and will be released over the next 2 years, helping manage supply.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-104266" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/10/token.jpg" alt="" width="1000" height="700" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/10/token.jpg 1000w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/10/token-300x210.jpg 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/10/token-768x538.jpg 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/10/token-50x35.jpg 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/10/token-150x105.jpg 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/10/token-450x315.jpg 450w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" /></p>
<p>The ORBT token is used to access all the advanced features of Orbitt PRO, participate in Orbitt MM, stake and receive rewards, and incentivize community engagement. The entirety of fees collected by the ecosystem will be used to reinvest in the ecosystem, with 50% going to ORBT buybacks and the remaining 50% creating volume.</p>
<p>The Orbitt team believes that this economic model will facilitate long-term sustainability, ensuring the rapid growth of the ecosystem and benefitting all parties. This is especially true when considering the efforts the team plans to make in terms of community engagement, which include the creation of educational content and resources, regular AMA sessions, a community rewards program, and beta testing.</p>
<hr />
<h2>Conclusion</h2>
<p>Orbitt represents a unique opportunity for the Solana network and blockchain ecosystem as a whole. By bringing together two of the most disruptive technologies of our times to democratize the cryptocurrency market, it could solve one of the biggest challenges the crypto space faces today: accessibility.</p>
<p>What sets Orbitt apart is its three-pronged approach to market challenges. While other platforms might focus solely on trading tools or launchpads, Orbitt&#8217;s ecosystem creates a symbiotic relationship between traders, developers, and projects.</p>
<p>The $ORBT tokenomics also show thoughtful design, with the 50/50 split between buybacks and volume creation ensuring that the ecosystem remains both sustainable and dynamic. This approach would help Orbitt avoid the common pitfall of utility tokens that struggle to maintain value beyond initial hype.</p>
<p>With Solana continuing to grow as one of the biggest blockchains and potential Ethereum-killers, Orbitt could become a dominant player in the space very soon.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/orbitt/">Orbitt: Revolutionizing Trading &#038; Project Development on Solana With AI</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">104010</post-id>	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
