<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	
	xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
	xmlns:geo="http://www.w3.org/2003/01/geo/wgs84_pos#"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Bitcoin News &amp; Updates: Latest Live Info about Bitcoin from Blockonomi</title>
	<atom:link href="https://blockonomi.com/bitcoin/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://blockonomi.com/bitcoin/</link>
	<description>Cryptocurrency News &#38; Your Guide to the Blockchain Economy</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 10:50:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.7.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/fav-50x50.png</url>
	<title>Bitcoin News &amp; Updates: Latest Live Info about Bitcoin from Blockonomi</title>
	<link>https://blockonomi.com/bitcoin/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
<site xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">134176212</site>	<item>
		<title>Riot Platforms Completes $525M Note Offering for Bitcoin Acquisition</title>
		<link>https://blockonomi.com/riot-platforms-completes-525m-note-offering-for-bitcoin-acquisition/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Oliver Dale]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 10:50:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regulation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blockonomi.com/?p=108025</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>TLDR Riot Platforms secured $525M through senior notes offering, netting $511.5M after expenses The notes will mature in 2030 with a 0.75% interest rate Company plans to use funds for Bitcoin purchases and operations Recently acquired 705 Bitcoin for $68.45M Currently holds 12,000 Bitcoin (~$1.2B), second only to Marathon Digital&#8217;s 40,000 BTC Riot Platforms, one [...]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/riot-platforms-completes-525m-note-offering-for-bitcoin-acquisition/">Riot Platforms Completes $525M Note Offering for Bitcoin Acquisition</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>TLDR</h2>
<ul>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Riot Platforms secured $525M through senior notes offering, netting $511.5M after expenses</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">The notes will mature in 2030 with a 0.75% interest rate</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Company plans to use funds for Bitcoin purchases and operations</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Recently acquired 705 Bitcoin for $68.45M</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Currently holds 12,000 Bitcoin (~$1.2B), second only to Marathon Digital&#8217;s 40,000 BTC</li>
</ul>
<hr />
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words"><a href="https://cryptobriefing.com/riot-platforms-525m-bitcoin-offering/">Riot Platforms, one of the largest Bitcoin mining companies in North America, has completed a $525 million senior note offering to expand its Bitcoin holdings</a> and support ongoing operations. The company announced the completion of the private offering through a <a href="https://www.sec.gov/Archives/edgar/data/1167419/000110465924127656/tm2430044d5_8k.htm">filing with the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC).</a></p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">After covering expenses related to the offering, Riot Platforms netted approximately $511.5 million. The senior notes come with a 0.75% interest rate and will reach maturity in 2030, providing the company with long-term financing at relatively low interest rates in the current market environment.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The terms of the offering include a provision that allows noteholders to convert their holdings into common stock starting in 2029. However, earlier conversion options may become available under certain conditions, giving both the company and investors some flexibility in managing their investments.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words"><a href="https://intel.arkm.com/explorer/entity/riot-platforms">Recent data from Arkham Intelligence</a> reveals that Riot Platforms currently holds approximately 12,000 Bitcoin in its treasury. At current market prices, this holding is valued at around $1.2 billion, placing Riot as the second-largest Bitcoin holder among mining companies.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The company&#8217;s position in the mining sector is notable but still trails behind industry leader Marathon Digital, which maintains a larger Bitcoin treasury of over 40,000 Bitcoin,<a href="https://treasuries.bitbo.io/miners/"> according to data from Bitbo.</a> This gap highlights the competitive nature of Bitcoin accumulation among major mining operations.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Riot has been actively growing its Bitcoin holdings through both mining operations and direct purchases. The company recently completed an acquisition of 705 Bitcoin for $68.45 million, demonstrating its commitment to expanding its cryptocurrency assets.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The senior note offering represents a strategic move by Riot to secure additional funding without immediately diluting shareholder value through stock offerings. The low interest rate of 0.75% suggests strong investor confidence in the company&#8217;s business model and future prospects.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The mining company&#8217;s decision to raise funds through notes rather than selling equity comes at a time when <a href="https://moneycheck.com/best-bitcoin-casinos/">Bitcoin</a> mining companies are seeking efficient ways to fund their operations and growth. This approach allows Riot to maintain its current ownership structure while accessing substantial capital.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The funds from the offering will serve multiple purposes, with Bitcoin acquisition being a primary focus. The company plans to use the proceeds for both direct Bitcoin purchases and general corporate purposes, giving it flexibility in how it deploys the capital.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Riot&#8217;s mining operations require substantial ongoing investment in equipment and infrastructure. The new funding will help support these operational needs while allowing the company to continue building its Bitcoin reserves.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The company&#8217;s strategy aligns with a broader trend among Bitcoin mining firms to maintain large Bitcoin holdings rather than immediately selling all mined coins. This approach allows miners to benefit from potential price appreciation while maintaining a strong asset base.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The conversion feature of the notes, beginning in 2029, provides future flexibility for both Riot and the noteholders. This structure allows the company to potentially reduce its debt burden while giving investors the option to participate in any future equity appreciation.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The successful completion of this offering comes during a period of renewed interest in Bitcoin mining operations. Rising Bitcoin prices have improved the profitability metrics for mining companies, making it easier to raise capital on favorable terms.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Riot&#8217;s position as the second-largest Bitcoin holder among mining companies reflects its success in executing its mining and accumulation strategy. The company has consistently worked to build its Bitcoin reserves while maintaining operational efficiency.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The timing of this offering coincides with a period of expansion in the Bitcoin mining sector, as companies seek to strengthen their positions in the market. Riot&#8217;s ability to secure funding at attractive rates indicates continued institutional interest in the Bitcoin mining industry.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/riot-platforms-completes-525m-note-offering-for-bitcoin-acquisition/">Riot Platforms Completes $525M Note Offering for Bitcoin Acquisition</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">108025</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Eric Trump Forecasts $1M Bitcoin Price at Abu Dhabi Crypto Conference</title>
		<link>https://blockonomi.com/eric-trump-forecasts-1m-bitcoin-price-at-abu-dhabi-crypto-conference/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Oliver Dale]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 10:41:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blockonomi.com/?p=108021</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>TLDR Eric Trump predicted Bitcoin will reach $1 million per coin during his speech at Bitcoin MENA conference in Abu Dhabi on December 9, 2024 He stated Donald Trump will be &#8220;the most pro-crypto president in the history of America&#8221; and plans to make the US the &#8220;crypto capital of the world&#8221; Eric Trump emphasized [...]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/eric-trump-forecasts-1m-bitcoin-price-at-abu-dhabi-crypto-conference/">Eric Trump Forecasts $1M Bitcoin Price at Abu Dhabi Crypto Conference</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>TLDR</h2>
<ul>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Eric Trump predicted Bitcoin will reach $1 million per coin during his speech at Bitcoin MENA conference in Abu Dhabi on December 9, 2024</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">He stated Donald Trump will be &#8220;the most pro-crypto president in the history of America&#8221; and plans to make the US the &#8220;crypto capital of the world&#8221;</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Eric Trump emphasized Bitcoin&#8217;s role as a global asset that doesn&#8217;t require intermediaries like banks or brokers</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">He highlighted Bitcoin&#8217;s fixed supply of 21 million coins and its potential to empower people in developing nations</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">The Trump family pledged continued support for cryptocurrency and its role in what Eric calls a &#8220;financial revolution&#8221;</li>
</ul>
<hr />
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words"><a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/news/eric-trumps-bold-call-bitcoin-to-soar-to-1-million-in-financial-revolution/">Eric Trump, Vice President of the Trump Organization and son of President-elect Donald Trump, made headlines at the Bitcoin MENA 2024 conference in Abu Dhabi</a> on December 9 with his prediction that Bitcoin will reach $1 million per coin. The announcement came as part of a broader discussion about cryptocurrency&#8217;s future under the incoming Trump administration.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">During his address to conference attendees, <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/eric-trump-predicts-1m-bitcoin-as-america-welcomes-most-pro-crypto-president-in-history/">Eric Trump expressed strong support for Bitcoin, describing it as a cornerstone of modern finance.</a> He highlighted his father&#8217;s recent statements in Nashville, where Donald Trump declared his intention to become &#8220;the bitcoin president&#8221; and &#8220;the crypto president.&#8221;</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The younger Trump emphasized the administration&#8217;s plans to implement what he called &#8220;smart regulation&#8221; of cryptocurrency. He contrasted this approach with that of the current Biden administration, specifically criticizing SEC Chair Gary Gensler&#8217;s regulatory stance. Trump praised Paul Atkins, appointed by Donald Trump, as &#8220;an unbelievable ally&#8221; to the cryptocurrency industry.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">In discussing Bitcoin&#8217;s value proposition, Eric Trump drew parallels between the digital currency and his family&#8217;s traditional interest in hard assets. He pointed to Bitcoin&#8217;s scarcity, noting its fixed supply of 21 million coins as a key factor in its value potential.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">COMMENT: Eric Trump is confident that Bitcoin will hit $1M. <a href="https://t.co/iFb5cmzpFz">https://t.co/iFb5cmzpFz</a></p>
<p>&mdash; BSCN (@BSCNews) <a href="https://twitter.com/BSCNews/status/1866502972827742577?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">December 10, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The Trump Organization executive highlighted Bitcoin&#8217;s accessibility as one of its main advantages over traditional investments. He compared it to real estate, noting that unlike property investments, Bitcoin isn&#8217;t tied to specific geographical locations and offers instant liquidity.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Trump addressed the global implications of cryptocurrency adoption, suggesting that Bitcoin could serve as a tool for financial inclusion in developing nations. He emphasized that Bitcoin allows worldwide participation regardless of wealth or location.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The conference speech included observations about institutional adoption of cryptocurrency. Trump referenced the market&#8217;s reaction when Bitcoin reached $100,000, suggesting that the $1 million milestone would attract even more attention from institutional investors.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">In discussing the regulatory landscape, Trump criticized what he characterized as an adversarial approach by current regulators. He promised that the incoming administration would take a more supportive stance toward the cryptocurrency industry.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Trump outlined his vision of <a href="https://moneycheck.com/best-bitcoin-casinos/">Bitcoin&#8217;s</a> role in modernizing the global financial system. He described how the cryptocurrency eliminates the need for traditional banking intermediaries and their associated fees.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The speech touched on Bitcoin&#8217;s potential as a hedge against traditional financial system inefficiencies. Trump pointed to the cryptocurrency&#8217;s decentralized nature as a key advantage in this context.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Addressing practical applications, Trump discussed how Bitcoin transactions can be conducted without the complexity often associated with traditional financial instruments. He used the example of being able to buy or sell Bitcoin &#8220;while having dinner with your spouse&#8221; to illustrate its convenience.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Trump emphasized his family&#8217;s commitment to supporting cryptocurrency development. He stated that they would &#8220;lead the charge in every single way&#8221; in promoting crypto adoption.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The conference appearance included discussion of the Trump administration&#8217;s planned approach to cryptocurrency regulation. Eric Trump indicated that his father&#8217;s administration would work to position the United States as the global leader in cryptocurrency innovation.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Trump concluded his remarks by predicting that governments and institutions embracing Bitcoin would emerge as the primary beneficiaries of what he termed a &#8220;digital revolution.&#8221;</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/eric-trump-forecasts-1m-bitcoin-price-at-abu-dhabi-crypto-conference/">Eric Trump Forecasts $1M Bitcoin Price at Abu Dhabi Crypto Conference</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">108021</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Vancouver City Council Approves Bitcoin Integration Study for 2025</title>
		<link>https://blockonomi.com/vancouver-city-council-approves-bitcoin-integration-study-for-2025/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Oliver Dale]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 10:37:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regulation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blockonomi.com/?p=108008</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>TLDR Vancouver City Council has approved a proposal to study Bitcoin integration into municipal operations Mayor Ken Sim pledged a personal donation of $10,000 in Bitcoin to the city The comprehensive study will be completed by Q1 2025, examining risks and benefits The Ministry of Housing states current laws don&#8217;t recognize crypto for municipal transactions [...]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/vancouver-city-council-approves-bitcoin-integration-study-for-2025/">Vancouver City Council Approves Bitcoin Integration Study for 2025</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>TLDR</h2>
<ul>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Vancouver City Council has approved a proposal to study Bitcoin integration into municipal operations</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Mayor Ken Sim pledged a personal donation of $10,000 in Bitcoin to the city</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">The comprehensive study will be completed by Q1 2025, examining risks and benefits</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">The Ministry of Housing states current laws don&#8217;t recognize crypto for municipal transactions</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Six council members supported the motion despite opposition from local experts</li>
</ul>
<hr />
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words"><a href="https://cryptobriefing.com/vancouver-approves-motion-bitcoin-reserve-asset/">Vancouver is moving toward potential cryptocurrency integration after the City Council approved a proposal to study Bitcoin&#8217;s role in municipal operations.</a> The motion, which passed with support from six council members, initiates a detailed examination of how the city might incorporate Bitcoin into its financial system.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words"><a href="https://coincu.com/296558-vancouver-bitcoin-proposal-has-now-been-approved/">Mayor Ken Sim, who introduced the proposal, aims to position Vancouver as a &#8220;Bitcoin-friendly city.&#8221;</a> To demonstrate his commitment, Sim announced a personal pledge of $10,000 worth of Bitcoin as a donation to the city. The mayor, who holds shares in Coinbase Global Inc., has been vocal about his belief in cryptocurrency&#8217;s potential benefits.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The approved study will examine several aspects of Bitcoin adoption, including its possible use as a reserve asset and its acceptance for municipal payments and fees. City staff must complete this comprehensive analysis by the end of the first quarter of 2025, providing detailed insights into the practical implications of such a move.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The proposal faces several hurdles, particularly regarding existing regulations. The Ministry of Housing and Municipal Affairs has pointed out that neither the Community Charter nor the Vancouver Charter currently recognizes cryptocurrency as a valid form of payment for municipal services or transactions. Additionally, the ministry clarified that local governments are not permitted to hold digital assets as financial reserves under current laws.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Opposition to the proposal has emerged from various quarters. Green Councilor Pete Fry voted against the motion, citing concerns about potential connections to illegal activities.</p>
<blockquote>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">&#8220;In the absence of any really specific acknowledgement of the very serious issues around money laundering and the history in this city, I don&#8217;t think this is a step in the right direction,&#8221; Fry stated during the council meeting.</p>
</blockquote>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The study will involve consultations with financial advisors, cryptocurrency experts, and community stakeholders. This broad approach aims to gather diverse perspectives on the potential impacts of Bitcoin adoption on municipal operations.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Mayor Sim has presented Bitcoin as a potential hedge against inflation and economic uncertainty. His personal involvement in cryptocurrency investments has influenced his advocacy for this initiative, though this has also raised questions about potential conflicts of interest.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The proposal&#8217;s timing coincides with increased interest in cryptocurrency following Donald Trump&#8217;s election victory. Trump has indicated plans to create a more supportive regulatory environment for the cryptocurrency industry, potentially influencing similar initiatives across North America.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The Vancouver proposal reflects a growing global trend. In Switzerland, the Canton of Bern recently passed a proposal to explore Bitcoin mining as a solution for excess energy usage and grid stabilization, indicating broader international interest in cryptocurrency integration.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">If implemented, Vancouver would become one of the first cities worldwide to incorporate Bitcoin into its municipal operations. The city&#8217;s approach to this initiative could serve as a model for other municipalities considering similar measures.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The approved study will examine various technical aspects of Bitcoin integration, including security protocols, transaction processing, and storage solutions. These technical considerations will play a crucial role in determining the feasibility of the proposal.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The council&#8217;s decision requires city staff to analyze both potential benefits and risks. This includes examining Bitcoin&#8217;s price volatility and its impact on municipal finances, as well as the technical infrastructure needed to support cryptocurrency transactions.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">City officials must also consider the practical aspects of implementing such a system, including staff training, software integration, and public education about cryptocurrency use for municipal services.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The timeline set for the study allows for thorough examination of these various aspects, with the Q1 2025 deadline providing adequate time for comprehensive analysis and stakeholder consultation.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The most recent development in this initiative is the formal approval of the study by the council, setting in motion the examination process that will determine Vancouver&#8217;s future relationship with cryptocurrency.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/vancouver-city-council-approves-bitcoin-integration-study-for-2025/">Vancouver City Council Approves Bitcoin Integration Study for 2025</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">108008</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Less than 1% of Microsoft Shareholders Support Bitcoin Investment Plan</title>
		<link>https://blockonomi.com/less-than-1-of-microsoft-shareholders-support-bitcoin-investment-plan/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Oliver Dale]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 10:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blockonomi.com/?p=108000</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>TLDR Only 0.55% of Microsoft shareholders (28.23 million votes) supported the Bitcoin investment proposal, while 5.148 billion votes were cast against it The National Center for Public Policy Research proposed Microsoft allocate 1% of total assets to Bitcoin as an inflation hedge Microsoft&#8217;s board recommended against the proposal, citing Bitcoin&#8217;s volatility as a key concern [...]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/less-than-1-of-microsoft-shareholders-support-bitcoin-investment-plan/">Less than 1% of Microsoft Shareholders Support Bitcoin Investment Plan</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>TLDR</h2>
<ul>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Only 0.55% of Microsoft shareholders (28.23 million votes) supported the Bitcoin investment proposal, while 5.148 billion votes were cast against it</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">The National Center for Public Policy Research proposed Microsoft allocate 1% of total assets to Bitcoin as an inflation hedge</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Microsoft&#8217;s board recommended against the proposal, citing Bitcoin&#8217;s volatility as a key concern</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">The vote occurred during the annual shareholder meeting on December 10, 2024, as Bitcoin traded above $100,000</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">MicroStrategy was highlighted as a contrasting example, having recently increased its Bitcoin holdings to 423,650 BTC valued at approximately $42 billion</li>
</ul>
<hr />
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">In a clear demonstration of corporate sentiment toward cryptocurrency investment, <a href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2024/12/12/less-than-1-of-microsoft-shareholders-voted-for-btc-proposal">Microsoft shareholders have decisively rejected a proposal to invest in Bitcoin.</a> The vote, which took place at the company&#8217;s annual shareholder meeting on December 10, 2024, saw only 0.55% of shareholders supporting the initiative to add the digital currency to Microsoft&#8217;s balance sheet.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The proposal, put forward by the <a href="https://decrypt.co/296145/less-than-1-of-microsoft-shareholders-voted-in-favor-of-investing-in-bitcoin">National Center for Public Policy Research, recommended that Microsoft allocate 1% of its total assets to Bitcoin as a hedge against inflation.</a> However, the final tally showed just 28.234 million votes in favor, compared to 5.148 billion against, with 22.6 million abstentions.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Microsoft&#8217;s board of directors had urged shareholders to vote against the proposal before the meeting, expressing concerns about Bitcoin&#8217;s price volatility. During the shareholder meeting, the company stated, &#8220;Bitcoin is a more volatile asset at the moment than corporate bonds, so companies should not risk shareholder value by holding too much of it.&#8221;</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The vote comes at a time when Bitcoin&#8217;s price has once again surpassed $100,000 per coin, highlighting both the potential rewards and risks associated with cryptocurrency investment. Despite recommending against the proposal, Microsoft acknowledged that companies should evaluate the benefits of holding at least 1% of their assets in Bitcoin.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The company&#8217;s Global Treasury and Investment Services team indicated they will continue monitoring trends related to Bitcoin and cryptocurrency to inform future decision-making. This stance suggests that while Microsoft isn&#8217;t ready to embrace Bitcoin investment now, they&#8217;re maintaining an open mind about future possibilities.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">In the broader corporate landscape, several companies have recently moved to add Bitcoin to their balance sheets. Healthcare technology company Semler Scientific added $30 million in Bitcoin to its holdings this month, while Amazon is currently considering a recommendation to convert 5% of its assets into Bitcoin, with a decision expected in spring 2025.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The shareholder vote discussion highlighted MicroStrategy&#8217;s experience as the largest private Bitcoin holder. The software development firm recently acquired an additional $1.5 billion in Bitcoin, bringing its total holdings to 423,650 BTC, valued at approximately $42 billion.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">According to the proxy statement,</p>
<blockquote>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">&#8220;MicroStrategy—which, like Microsoft, is a technology company, but unlike Microsoft, holds Bitcoin on its balance sheet—has had its stock outperform Microsoft stock this year by 313% despite doing only a fraction of the business that Microsoft has.&#8221;</p>
</blockquote>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The statement also noted that institutional adoption of<a href="https://moneycheck.com/best-bitcoin-casinos/"> Bitcoin</a> is becoming more common, pointing out that BlackRock, Microsoft&#8217;s second-largest shareholder, offers its clients a Bitcoin ETF.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Microsoft&#8217;s board emphasized that while they rejected the Bitcoin proposal, the company evaluates a wide range of assets for investment purposes. They specifically noted that volatility remains a key factor in evaluating cryptocurrency investments for corporate treasury applications.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The vote also included other proposed shareholder motions, including requests for reports on AI and misinformation/disinformation, as well as weapons development risks. These proposals also failed to pass.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Prediction markets had anticipated this outcome, with Polymarket bettors giving the motion only a 12-16% chance of being ratified.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The results align with Microsoft&#8217;s stated preference for stable and predictable investments that ensure liquidity and operational funding. The company maintains this position even as Bitcoin&#8217;s price has reached new highs and other corporations have embraced cryptocurrency investments.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">With 22.6 million abstentions recorded, the voting results demonstrate a clear preference among Microsoft shareholders for traditional corporate treasury management approaches over cryptocurrency investment at this time.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The voting breakdown shows this was one of the most decisive shareholder votes in recent Microsoft history, with the 0.55% support rate ranking among the lowest for any major proposal put before shareholders.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/less-than-1-of-microsoft-shareholders-support-bitcoin-investment-plan/">Less than 1% of Microsoft Shareholders Support Bitcoin Investment Plan</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">108000</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin (BTC) Price: Whale Accumulation Surges with 342 New Large Wallets Created</title>
		<link>https://blockonomi.com/bitcoin-btc-price-whale-accumulation-surges-with-342-new-large-wallets-created/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Oliver Dale]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 09:23:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blockonomi.com/?p=107986</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>TLDR Bitcoin recovered from a $94,500 dip and surged past $100,000 after US CPI data aligned with market expectations, with analysts predicting potential rises to $275,000 based on cup and handle pattern analysis Heavy whale accumulation occurred during consolidation, with 342 new wallets holding over 100 BTC created during the recent price drop from $104,000 [...]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/bitcoin-btc-price-whale-accumulation-surges-with-342-new-large-wallets-created/">Bitcoin (BTC) Price: Whale Accumulation Surges with 342 New Large Wallets Created</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>TLDR</h2>
<ul>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Bitcoin recovered from a $94,500 dip and surged past $100,000 after US CPI data aligned with market expectations, with analysts predicting potential rises to $275,000 based on cup and handle pattern analysis</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Heavy whale accumulation occurred during consolidation, with 342 new wallets holding over 100 BTC created during the recent price drop from $104,000 to $90,000</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Spot Bitcoin ETF inflows remain strong, with BlackRock&#8217;s IBIT reaching over $35 billion in net inflows since launch</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Analysts predict a 96-97% chance of a 25 basis point rate cut at next week&#8217;s FOMC meeting, potentially catalyzing further price movement</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Technical analysis suggests Bitcoin broke out of its $94,500-$98,000 trading range, with altcoins showing stronger relative performance</li>
</ul>
<hr />
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words"><a href="https://coingape.com/will-bitcoin-price-hit-new-all-time-high-heading-into-fomc/">Bitcoin has pushed past the $100,000 mark, recovering swiftly from yesterday&#8217;s dip to $94,500.</a> The rebound comes as new data reveals substantial whale accumulation and continued strong inflows into spot Bitcoin ETFs, painting a picture of robust institutional and high-net-worth investor interest.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The latest market movements follow the release of US Consumer Price Index (CPI) data, which aligned with market expectations. This development has strengthened predictions of a potential Federal Reserve rate cut at next week&#8217;s Federal Open Market Committee (FOMC) meeting, with analysts estimating a 96-97% probability of a 25 basis point reduction.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">During the recent consolidation period around $96,000, large investors demonstrated strong buying activity. Data from blockchain analytics reveals that 342 new wallets holding more than 100 BTC were created as Bitcoin&#8217;s price fluctuated between $104,000 and $90,000, indicating substantial accumulation by wealthy investors during the price dip.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The institutional adoption of Bitcoin continues to expand through spot ETF products. BlackRock&#8217;s IBIT has reached a new milestone, exceeding $35 billion in net inflows since its launch. The ETF sector has maintained positive inflows for nine consecutive trading sessions, highlighting sustained institutional interest in the asset class.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Technical analysis from crypto analyst Ali Martinez identifies a cup and handle pattern forming on Bitcoin&#8217;s weekly chart. This traditional bullish formation suggests a potential price target of $275,000, though Martinez advises traders to maintain caution and avoid excessive leverage.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Buy the dip, and don&#39;t overleverage! <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Bitcoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Bitcoin</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24BTC&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">$BTC</a> will reach $275,000, based on this cup and handle pattern! <a href="https://t.co/cqf99cBtmB">pic.twitter.com/cqf99cBtmB</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Ali (@ali_charts) <a href="https://twitter.com/ali_charts/status/1866517510268330035?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">December 10, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Market data from Coinglass shows over $478 million worth of contracts were liquidated in the past 24 hours during the recent price volatility. Interestingly, altcoin positions experienced higher liquidation volumes compared to Bitcoin positions, suggesting more stable holding patterns for BTC.</p>
<figure id="attachment_107987" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-107987" style="width: 847px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-107987" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-12-at-09-19-34-Bitcoin-Price-BTC-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko.png" alt="Bitcoin Price on CoinGecko" width="847" height="623" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-12-at-09-19-34-Bitcoin-Price-BTC-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko.png 847w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-12-at-09-19-34-Bitcoin-Price-BTC-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko-300x221.png 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-12-at-09-19-34-Bitcoin-Price-BTC-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko-768x565.png 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-12-at-09-19-34-Bitcoin-Price-BTC-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko-50x37.png 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-12-at-09-19-34-Bitcoin-Price-BTC-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko-150x110.png 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-12-at-09-19-34-Bitcoin-Price-BTC-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko-450x331.png 450w" sizes="(max-width: 847px) 100vw, 847px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-107987" class="wp-caption-text">Bitcoin Price on <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/bitcoin">CoinGecko</a></figcaption></figure>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The cryptocurrency&#8217;s price recovery appears supported by declining exchange reserves, which have reached multi-year lows. This trend typically indicates reduced selling pressure as fewer coins are available for immediate sale on exchanges.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Corporate adoption of <a href="https://moneycheck.com/best-bitcoin-casinos/">Bitcoin</a> continues to expand, with Canadian video-sharing platform Rumble becoming the latest company to announce a Bitcoin treasury strategy. This follows a broader trend of companies exploring cryptocurrency as a treasury asset, despite Microsoft shareholders recently rejecting a proposal to allocate 1% of the company&#8217;s assets to Bitcoin.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Former investment banker Anthony Scaramucci has suggested that China might establish its own Bitcoin reserve if the United States proceeds with strategic Bitcoin reserve plans. Such national adoption could further impact the supply-demand dynamics of the cryptocurrency.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The altcoin market has shown even stronger performance during this recovery period.<a href="https://moneycheck.com/best-ethereum-casinos/"> Ethereum</a> has registered a 7% increase, trading near $3,920, while other major cryptocurrencies like <a href="https://moneycheck.com/best-xrp-casinos/">XRP</a>, <a href="https://moneycheck.com/best-bnb-casinos/">BNB</a>, <a href="https://moneycheck.com/best-solana-casinos/">SOL</a>, and <a href="https://moneycheck.com/best-doge-casinos/">DOGE</a> have posted gains between 4-5%.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Analysis from 10x Research notes that Bitcoin&#8217;s price often rallies after declining ahead of inflation reports, particularly when the data meets market expectations and calms inflation concerns. The firm expects measured market movements through year-end as many investors typically close their positions following the FOMC meeting.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Looking at short-term price action, Bitcoin has broken out of its previous trading range between $94,500 and $98,000. The movement above $100,000 represents a clear break from this consolidation pattern, though traders remain watchful of key support levels around $90,000.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The overall market structure suggests continued strength, with Bitcoin maintaining prices above previous resistance levels. The combination of institutional inflow through ETFs, whale accumulation, and broader market adoption provides multiple support factors for current price levels.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Trading volume has remained robust, with daily volumes consistently supporting price action above $100,000. The market currently shows a healthy balance between spot and derivatives trading, indicating sustainable price discovery.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">At press time, Bitcoin trades at $100,453, representing a 4.1% increase over the past 24 hours.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/bitcoin-btc-price-whale-accumulation-surges-with-342-new-large-wallets-created/">Bitcoin (BTC) Price: Whale Accumulation Surges with 342 New Large Wallets Created</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">107986</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>MicroStrategy to Join Nasdaq 100 Index with $2.1B Expected ETF Investment</title>
		<link>https://blockonomi.com/microstrategy-to-join-nasdaq-100-index-with-2-1b-expected-etf-investment/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Oliver Dale]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2024 10:34:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blockonomi.com/?p=107903</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>TLDR MicroStrategy expected to join Nasdaq 100 on December 23, with official announcement due December 13 ETFs tracking Nasdaq 100 projected to purchase $2.1 billion in MicroStrategy shares Company expected to have 0.47% weight in index as 40th largest holding MicroStrategy just bought 21,550 BTC for $2.1 billion at $98,000 per coin Total Bitcoin holdings [...]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/microstrategy-to-join-nasdaq-100-index-with-2-1b-expected-etf-investment/">MicroStrategy to Join Nasdaq 100 Index with $2.1B Expected ETF Investment</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>TLDR</h2>
<ul>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">MicroStrategy expected to join Nasdaq 100 on December 23, with official announcement due December 13</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">ETFs tracking Nasdaq 100 projected to purchase $2.1 billion in MicroStrategy shares</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Company expected to have 0.47% weight in index as 40th largest holding</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">MicroStrategy just bought 21,550 BTC for $2.1 billion at $98,000 per coin</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Total Bitcoin holdings now at 423,650 BTC, worth approximately $42 billion</li>
</ul>
<hr />
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words"><a href="https://decrypt.co/295932/microstrategys-nasdaq-debut-could-trigger-etf-buying-spree">MicroStrategy is set to join the Nasdaq 100 Index on December 23, marking a key development for the company known for its large Bitcoin holdings.</a> The official announcement is expected this Friday, December 13, according to Bloomberg analysts.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The company&#8217;s addition to the prestigious index is projected to trigger $2.1 billion in ETF share purchases, as calculated by Bloomberg ETF analyst James Seyffart. This volume represents about 20% of the company&#8217;s daily trading activity.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Within the Nasdaq 100, MicroStrategy is expected to become the 40th largest holding with a 0.47% weight in the index, according to ETF analyst Eric Balchunas. The Nasdaq 100 indexes the hundred largest non-financial companies listed on the Nasdaq exchange.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr"><a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24MSTR&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">$MSTR</a> is likely to be added to <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24QQQ&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">$QQQ</a> on 12/23 (w/ announcement coming 12/13). Moderna likely to get boot (symbolic). Below is best guess of adds/drops via <a href="https://twitter.com/JSeyff?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@JSeyff</a>. Likely a 0.47% weight (40th biggest holding). There&#39;s $550b of ETFs tracking the index. S&amp;P 500 add next yr prob. <a href="https://t.co/rmTavtvWQL">pic.twitter.com/rmTavtvWQL</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Eric Balchunas (@EricBalchunas) <a href="https://twitter.com/EricBalchunas/status/1866595936983716168?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">December 10, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The timing of this index inclusion coincides with MicroStrategy&#8217;s continued Bitcoin acquisition strategy. The company just announced its fifth consecutive purchase, acquiring 21,550 BTC for $2.1 billion at an average price of $98,000 per Bitcoin.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">This latest purchase has increased MicroStrategy&#8217;s total Bitcoin holdings to 423,650 BTC, currently valued at approximately $42 billion at market prices. The company has established itself as the largest corporate holder of Bitcoin.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The market has responded positively to MicroStrategy&#8217;s strategy. The company&#8217;s shares have increased by over 450% this year, outpacing Bitcoin&#8217;s 110% rise during the same period. This growth has pushed MicroStrategy&#8217;s market value to $82 billion, up from $54.8 billion just a month ago.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The Nasdaq 100 serves as a key benchmark for sectors including technology, consumer services, and healthcare. Its composition directly influences market sentiment and investment flows, particularly in growth-focused areas of the U.S. economy.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The index underlies several investment products, with the Invesco QQQ Trust ETF being the most notable. Approximately $550 billion in ETF assets track the index, meaning membership changes can lead to substantial portfolio adjustments.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words"><a href="https://cryptobriefing.com/microstrategy-nasdaq-inclusion-etfs/">While MicroStrategy appears poised to join the Nasdaq 100, S</a>eyffart noted that inclusion in the S&amp;P 500 would be more challenging due to the company&#8217;s current profitability metrics. However, he suggested that upcoming changes in accounting rules related to Bitcoin valuations could make the company eligible for S&amp;P 500 inclusion by 2025.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Neither the Nasdaq nor MicroStrategy have provided official comments on the expected index inclusion. However, Bloomberg analyst Balchunas stated that based on their analysis, they saw no grounds for possible exclusion.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Traditional investors have increasingly looked to MicroStrategy&#8217;s stock as a way to gain exposure to cryptocurrency through familiar equity markets. This trend has contributed to the company&#8217;s strong market performance.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The company&#8217;s shares have become highly active in trading. Recent data from TradingView shows that MicroStrategy&#8217;s stock has seen more trading activity than popular stocks like Nvidia and Tesla by certain metrics.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">MicroStrategy&#8217;s potential inclusion represents a notable moment for crypto-focused companies entering mainstream finance. The move could increase the visibility of cryptocurrency-related investments within traditional market indexes.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The index addition process is scheduled to be implemented the week following the official announcement, allowing time for market participants to prepare for the associated portfolio adjustments.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">These developments come during a period of rising Bitcoin prices, which have supported both MicroStrategy&#8217;s Bitcoin holdings value and its stock price performance.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/microstrategy-to-join-nasdaq-100-index-with-2-1b-expected-etf-investment/">MicroStrategy to Join Nasdaq 100 Index with $2.1B Expected ETF Investment</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">107903</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitcoin (BTC) Price: Maintains $94K Support Level as Market Momentum Shifts</title>
		<link>https://blockonomi.com/bitcoin-btc-price-maintains-94k-support-level-as-market-momentum-shifts/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Oliver Dale]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2024 10:12:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blockonomi.com/?p=107897</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>TLDR Bitcoin currently trading below $98,000 after briefly touching $100,000 on Dec 5th Market liquidity inflow has slowed to $7 billion from previous $15 billion Price finding support above $94,200 with resistance at $98,000 Strong correlation (0.6) observed with NVIDIA stock performance Market leverage has normalized to healthier levels, potentially setting up for another push [...]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/bitcoin-btc-price-maintains-94k-support-level-as-market-momentum-shifts/">Bitcoin (BTC) Price: Maintains $94K Support Level as Market Momentum Shifts</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>TLDR</h2>
<ul>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Bitcoin currently trading below $98,000 after briefly touching $100,000 on Dec 5th</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Market liquidity inflow has slowed to $7 billion from previous $15 billion</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Price finding support above $94,200 with resistance at $98,000</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Strong correlation (0.6) observed with NVIDIA stock performance</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Market leverage has normalized to healthier levels, potentially setting up for another push toward $100,000</li>
</ul>
<hr />
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words"><a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/analysis/btc/bitcoin-price-holds-support-94250/">Bitcoin&#8217;s price movement has entered a consolidation phase, trading between $90,000 and $100,000 in December 2024.</a> After briefly touching the $100,000 mark on December 5th, the leading cryptocurrency has established support above $94,200, while facing resistance near the $98,000 level.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words"><a href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2024/12/11/bitcoin-s-100-k-breakout-pause-likely-due-to-liquidity-factors-and-nvidias-stalled-rally">Recent market data shows a notable decrease in liquidity inflows to the cryptocurrency market.</a> The weekly rate of change in the market liquidity impulse index, which tracks stablecoin mints, Bitcoin ETF inflows, and futures market changes, has dropped to $7 billion from previous highs above $15 billion recorded in November.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Technical analysis indicates the formation of a key bearish trend line with resistance at $97,800 on the hourly chart. The price currently trades below both $98,000 and the 100-hour Simple Moving Average, suggesting short-term overhead resistance at these levels.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The cryptocurrency has shown resilience by maintaining support above $94,200, with recent price action indicating a consolidation pattern. A recovery wave lifted the price above $96,650, reaching the 61.8% Fibonacci retracement level of the downward movement from $98,267 to $94,314.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Market structure analysis reveals multiple support levels, with immediate support near $96,500 and major support established at $95,000. The next critical support level sits at $94,250, with $92,000 serving as a backup support zone should selling pressure increase.</p>
<figure id="attachment_107898" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-107898" style="width: 847px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-107898" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-11-at-10-09-51-Bitcoin-Price-BTC-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko.png" alt="Bitcoin Price on CoinGecko" width="847" height="632" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-11-at-10-09-51-Bitcoin-Price-BTC-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko.png 847w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-11-at-10-09-51-Bitcoin-Price-BTC-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko-300x224.png 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-11-at-10-09-51-Bitcoin-Price-BTC-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko-768x573.png 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-11-at-10-09-51-Bitcoin-Price-BTC-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko-50x37.png 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-11-at-10-09-51-Bitcoin-Price-BTC-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko-150x112.png 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-11-at-10-09-51-Bitcoin-Price-BTC-Live-Price-Chart-Market-Cap-News-Today-CoinGecko-450x336.png 450w" sizes="(max-width: 847px) 100vw, 847px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-107898" class="wp-caption-text">Bitcoin Price on <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/coins/bitcoin">CoinGecko</a></figcaption></figure>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">An interesting correlation has emerged between Bitcoin and NVIDIA (NVDA) stock performance, with a three-month correlation coefficient of 0.6. This relationship highlights Bitcoin&#8217;s increasing connection to broader technology market trends and risk assets.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The year-to-date performance comparison shows<a href="https://moneycheck.com/best-bitcoin-casinos/"> Bitcoin</a> up 130%, while NVIDIA has gained 172%. This parallel movement suggests similar market psychology driving both assets, despite their different fundamental characteristics.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Trading volumes have remained steady during this consolidation period, indicating sustained market interest despite the pause in upward momentum. The market has seen a normalization of leverage levels, potentially creating healthier conditions for future price movements.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Looking at potential upside scenarios, a clear break above $98,000 could open the path to test $98,800. Should this level be breached, the next target would be the psychologically important $100,000 mark, followed by possible extension toward $102,000.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The stablecoin market, which plays a crucial role in crypto market liquidity, has shown slower mint rates compared to previous months. This reduction in new stablecoin creation has contributed to the overall slowdown in market liquidity.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">ETF flows, another key component of market liquidity, have also moderated from their early November peaks. This adjustment in institutional investment pace has impacted the market&#8217;s ability to sustain moves above $100,000.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Technical indicators present a mixed picture, with the hourly MACD losing momentum in the bearish zone, while the RSI hovers below the 50 level. These readings suggest neutral to slightly bearish short-term momentum.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The futures market has shown signs of normalization, with funding rates returning to more sustainable levels compared to the elevated rates seen during the November rally. This indicates a more balanced positioning between long and short traders.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Market data indicates that the $94,314 price point has served as a recent swing low, while $98,267 marked a local high, establishing the current trading range that Bitcoin has respected over the past week.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The latest price action shows Bitcoin trading at $96,800, representing a 2.3% decline from the December 5th peak above $100,000. Trading volume across major exchanges has averaged $42 billion daily during this consolidation period.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/bitcoin-btc-price-maintains-94k-support-level-as-market-momentum-shifts/">Bitcoin (BTC) Price: Maintains $94K Support Level as Market Momentum Shifts</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">107897</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitwise Report: Bitcoin, Ethereum, and Solana Expected to Reach New Highs in 2025</title>
		<link>https://blockonomi.com/bitwise-report-bitcoin-ethereum-and-solana-expected-to-reach-new-highs-in-2025/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Oliver Dale]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2024 09:39:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethereum]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blockonomi.com/?p=107887</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>TLDR Bitcoin hit new ATH of $104,000 in 2024, up 141.72% YTD, driven by spot ETF launches totaling $33.56B in assets Crypto-friendly Trump administration expected to establish Bitcoin strategic reserve and reform SEC policies Bitwise predicts Bitcoin could reach $200,000-$500,000, ETH $7,000, and SOL $750 by 2025 Major cryptocurrencies outperformed traditional assets in 2024: SOL [...]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/bitwise-report-bitcoin-ethereum-and-solana-expected-to-reach-new-highs-in-2025/">Bitwise Report: Bitcoin, Ethereum, and Solana Expected to Reach New Highs in 2025</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>TLDR</h2>
<ul>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Bitcoin hit new ATH of $104,000 in 2024, up 141.72% YTD, driven by spot ETF launches totaling $33.56B in assets</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Crypto-friendly Trump administration expected to establish Bitcoin strategic reserve and reform SEC policies</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Bitwise predicts Bitcoin could reach $200,000-$500,000, ETH $7,000, and SOL $750 by 2025</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Major cryptocurrencies outperformed traditional assets in 2024: SOL up 127.71%, XRP up 285.23%, ETH up 75.77%</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Crypto-related stocks showed strong performance: MicroStrategy up 525.39%, Coinbase up 97.57%</li>
</ul>
<hr />
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Cryptocurrency asset manager<a href="https://s3.us-east-1.amazonaws.com/static.bitwiseinvestments.com/Research/Bitwise-The-Year-Ahead-10-Crypto-Predictions-for-2025.pdf"> Bitwise has released a comprehensive report</a> predicting record-breaking valuations for major digital assets by 2025, backed by data showing strong institutional adoption and regulatory developments in 2024.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words"><a href="https://www.newsbtc.com/bitcoin-news/bitwise-forecast-bitcoin-ethereum-and-solana-poised-for-record-highs-in-2025/">The cryptocurrency market demonstrated robust growth in 2024, with Bitcoin reaching $104,000, marking a 141.72% increase year-to-date.</a> This surge coincided with the launch of spot Bitcoin ETFs in the United States, which accumulated $33.56 billion in assets.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Other cryptocurrencies showed similar upward momentum. Solana posted gains of 127.71%, while XRP experienced a 285.23% increase. Ethereum, despite lagging behind its peers, still achieved a 75.77% rise in value.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The cryptocurrency market&#8217;s strength extended beyond digital assets to crypto-related equities. MicroStrategy, a business intelligence company known for its Bitcoin holdings, saw its stock price surge by 525.39%. Cryptocurrency exchange Coinbase also performed well, with its shares rising 97.57%.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">These gains outpaced traditional financial markets, with the S&amp;P 500 returning 28.07%, gold increasing by 27.65%, and bonds yielding 3.40% during the same period.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The regulatory landscape showed marked improvement throughout 2024. The success of crypto-friendly candidates in U.S. elections created a more favorable environment for the industry. President-elect Donald Trump&#8217;s campaign embraced cryptocurrencies, including plans to establish a strategic Bitcoin reserve.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The appointment of Scott Bessent as Treasury Secretary further reinforced positive sentiment, given his previous statements supporting cryptocurrency as a vehicle for freedom. These developments contributed to the market&#8217;s upward trajectory.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Looking ahead to 2025, Bitwise&#8217;s research team describes the period as the &#8220;Golden Age of Crypto.&#8221; Their optimistic outlook stems from increasing institutional adoption, technological advances in blockchain, and expected stimulus measures from major central banks.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The report specifically focuses on Bitcoin, Ethereum, and Solana, which they term the &#8220;magnificent three.&#8221; These assets are expected to maintain their strong performance relative to traditional investments.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">For <a href="https://moneycheck.com/best-bitcoin-casinos/">Bitcoin</a>, Bitwise projects potential prices of $200,000 to $500,000. This forecast considers continued inflows into Bitcoin ETFs and the supply reduction from the April 2024 halving event. The proposed U.S. government strategic reserve of one million Bitcoins could further drive prices upward.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words"><a href="https://moneycheck.com/best-ethereum-casinos/">Ethereum</a> faced challenges in 2024 as investors focused on Bitcoin and faster networks. However, Bitwise expects a revival in 2025, projecting a new all-time high of $7,000. This outlook is based on growing activity on Layer 2 solutions like Base and Starknet, anticipated spot Ethereum ETF inflows, and increased stablecoin and tokenization projects.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words"><a href="https://moneycheck.com/best-solana-casinos/">Solana&#8217;s</a> recovery from the 2022 market downturn impressed investors, with its 2024 surge partly driven by memecoin activity. Bitwise predicts continued ecosystem growth beyond memecoins, forecasting a new high of $750 per SOL.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The cryptocurrency market&#8217;s current state shows consolidation, with Bitcoin trading at $96,000, Ethereum at $3,662, and Solana at $218.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The April 2024 Bitcoin halving event remains a key factor in these projections, as it will reduce the rate of new Bitcoin creation and potentially increase scarcity in the market.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">These forecasts align with broader market trends showing increased institutional participation and mainstream adoption of cryptocurrencies through regulated investment vehicles.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/bitwise-report-bitcoin-ethereum-and-solana-expected-to-reach-new-highs-in-2025/">Bitwise Report: Bitcoin, Ethereum, and Solana Expected to Reach New Highs in 2025</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">107887</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Altcoin Season Index Suggests Potential Bitcoin Rally Ahead</title>
		<link>https://blockonomi.com/altcoin-season-index-suggests-potential-bitcoin-rally-ahead/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Oliver Dale]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2024 09:29:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blockonomi.com/?p=107881</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>TLDR Altcoin Season Index above 60 historically indicates Bitcoin gains of 73% over 6 months Support level for Bitcoin remains strong at $95,000 with consistent buying activity Spot Bitcoin ETFs continue to see strong inflows, with $438.5 million added Tuesday Market analysts view recent altcoin pullback as healthy market correction Bitcoin currently trading at $97,700 [...]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/altcoin-season-index-suggests-potential-bitcoin-rally-ahead/">Altcoin Season Index Suggests Potential Bitcoin Rally Ahead</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>TLDR</h2>
<ul>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Altcoin Season Index above 60 historically indicates Bitcoin gains of 73% over 6 months</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Support level for Bitcoin remains strong at $95,000 with consistent buying activity</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Spot Bitcoin ETFs continue to see strong inflows, with $438.5 million added Tuesday</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Market analysts view recent altcoin pullback as healthy market correction</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Bitcoin currently trading at $97,700 with $1.933 trillion market cap</li>
</ul>
<hr />
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The cryptocurrency market is showing resilience as Bitcoin maintains support above $95,000, while institutional interest continues through spot Bitcoin ETFs. <a href="https://coingape.com/altcoin-season-index-suggest-btc-price-rally-can-resume-again/">According to recent data, these ETF products attracted another $438.5 million in inflows on Tuesday,</a> with BlackRock&#8217;s IBIT and Fidelity&#8217;s FBTC leading the charge.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Investment firm VanEck has identified a pattern in the cryptocurrency markets that could point to future Bitcoin price increases. Their analysis focuses on the Altcoin Season Index, which measures how many of the top 50 cryptocurrencies are outperforming Bitcoin over a 90-day period.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">When this index crosses above 60, indicating strong altcoin performance, Bitcoin has historically shown positive returns in the following months. VanEck&#8217;s data, analyzing 61 such instances, reveals average gains of 10% over one month, 30% over three months, and 73% over six months.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The current market structure shows Bitcoin trading at $97,700, with a market capitalization of $1.933 trillion. Trading patterns indicate strong buyer interest whenever the price approaches the $95,000 level, with quick recoveries from any dips below this threshold.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Crypto analyst IncomeSharks has documented seven distinct occasions where price movements below $95,000 were met with immediate buying pressure. This repeated pattern suggests robust market confidence at this price point, despite recent volatility in the broader cryptocurrency market.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The altcoin market recently experienced a pullback following a rally that coincided with Donald Trump&#8217;s victory. However, market analysts have characterized this correction as a healthy market development, noting that it helped remove excess speculation from the sector.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">BlackRock&#8217;s IBIT ETF continues to lead institutional interest, bringing in $295.6 million in new investments on Tuesday. Fidelity&#8217;s FBTC followed closely with $210.5 million in inflows, according to data from Farside Investors.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Blockchain analytics platform Santiment has noted increased bearish sentiment on social media, with some users predicting Bitcoin prices could fall to between $80,000 and $89,000. However, Santiment suggests this growing negative sentiment could actually be a bullish indicator for Bitcoin&#8217;s price.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The probability of positive returns based on the Altcoin Season Index crossing 60 stands at 56.5% over one month, 59.9% over three months, and 61.1% over six months, according to VanEck&#8217;s research. This data suggests the potential for Bitcoin to reach $160,000 by mid-2025.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Technical analysis from market observers shows no indicators pointing to a market top, despite the recent strong performance in altcoin markets. The consistent buying pressure at the $95,000 support level reinforces this view.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Recent market data indicates that the cryptocurrency market has maintained stability despite various external factors. The steady flow of institutional money through ETF products suggests continued mainstream adoption of digital assets.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Spot<a href="https://moneycheck.com/best-bitcoin-casinos/"> Bitcoin</a> ETFs have emerged as a key driver of market activity, providing traditional investors with regulated exposure to the cryptocurrency market. The sustained inflows indicate growing acceptance of Bitcoin as an investment asset among institutional players.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The market&#8217;s reaction to price dips has been notably consistent, with buyers stepping in quickly when Bitcoin approaches the $95,000 level. This behavior has established a clear support zone that has held up through multiple tests.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The altcoin market&#8217;s healthy correction following its recent rally has helped establish more sustainable price levels across the cryptocurrency sector. Market participants note that this cooling off period was necessary after the intense speculation during the previous upward movement.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The most recent data shows spot Bitcoin ETF inflows maintaining their momentum, with daily volumes remaining robust across all major providers. This continued institutional interest provides a foundation for market stability at current price levels.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/altcoin-season-index-suggests-potential-bitcoin-rally-ahead/">Altcoin Season Index Suggests Potential Bitcoin Rally Ahead</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">107881</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Microsoft Shareholders Decline $800M Bitcoin Investment Strategy</title>
		<link>https://blockonomi.com/microsoft-shareholders-decline-800m-bitcoin-investment-strategy/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Oliver Dale]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2024 09:10:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blockonomi.com/?p=107874</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>TLDR Microsoft shareholders rejected a proposal to invest 1% ($800M) of treasury in Bitcoin The proposal came from NCPPR and was supported by Michael Saylor of MicroStrategy Microsoft&#8217;s board cited Bitcoin&#8217;s volatility as a key concern Bitcoin price dropped 4% to $95,700 following the decision A similar proposal is pending for Amazon, suggesting 5% ($4.5B) [...]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/microsoft-shareholders-decline-800m-bitcoin-investment-strategy/">Microsoft Shareholders Decline $800M Bitcoin Investment Strategy</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>TLDR</h2>
<ul>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Microsoft shareholders rejected a proposal to invest 1% ($800M) of treasury in Bitcoin</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">The proposal came from NCPPR and was supported by Michael Saylor of MicroStrategy</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Microsoft&#8217;s board cited Bitcoin&#8217;s volatility as a key concern</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Bitcoin price dropped 4% to $95,700 following the decision</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">A similar proposal is pending for Amazon, suggesting 5% ($4.5B) allocation</li>
</ul>
<hr />
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words"><a href="https://fullycrypto.com/microsoft-rejects-bitcoin-treasury-proposal?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=microsoft-rejects-bitcoin-treasury-proposal">Microsoft shareholders have rejected a proposal to add Bitcoin to the company&#8217;s treasury holdings</a> during their annual meeting on December 10, 2024. The proposal, put forward by the National Center for Public Policy Research (NCPPR), suggested allocating 1% of Microsoft&#8217;s treasury to Bitcoin, which would have amounted to approximately $800 million based on the company&#8217;s current cash reserves and short-term investments.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words"><a href="https://cryptoslate.com/microsoft-shareholders-oppose-bitcoin-treasury-allocation-in-preliminary-vote/">The board of directors had previously recommended against the proposal on October 24, expressing concerns about Bitcoin&#8217;s volatility and its suitability for corporate treasury operations.</a> The company&#8217;s Global Treasury and Investment Services team, which regularly evaluates various investment options, determined that cryptocurrencies might not align with Microsoft&#8217;s need for stable and predictable investments.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Following the announcement of the decision, Bitcoin&#8217;s price experienced a 4% decline, dropping to around $95,700. The market reaction highlighted the cryptocurrency&#8217;s sensitivity to corporate adoption decisions, particularly from major technology companies.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">MicroStrategy&#8217;s Executive Chairman Michael Saylor had actively advocated for the proposal. In a three-minute presentation to Microsoft&#8217;s board of directors on December 1, Saylor argued that Bitcoin represented a fundamental component of future technological innovation. He suggested that incorporating Bitcoin into Microsoft&#8217;s treasury could help the company achieve a $5 trillion market cap by 2034.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Saylor&#8217;s company, MicroStrategy, currently holds 423,650 Bitcoin, and their stock has seen a 443% increase in 2024, reaching $371.98. The company&#8217;s shares hit an all-time high of $473.83 on November 20, surpassing previous records from the dotcom era.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The NCPPR&#8217;s proposal emphasized Bitcoin&#8217;s potential role as an inflation hedge and its possible positive impact on shareholder value. However, Microsoft&#8217;s board maintained that their existing investment evaluation processes were sufficient, making a public assessment of Bitcoin investment unnecessary.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Despite rejecting the proposal, Microsoft&#8217;s board stated they continue to monitor trends and developments in the cryptocurrency market. This approach reflects a cautious stance toward integrating digital assets into corporate financial strategies.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The decision comes at a time when corporate Bitcoin adoption remains a debated topic. While some companies have embraced cryptocurrency investments, others maintain traditional treasury management approaches focused on stability and liquidity.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">A similar proposal is currently under consideration at Amazon, where the NCPPR has suggested allocating 5% of the company&#8217;s assets to <a href="https://moneycheck.com/best-bitcoin-casinos/">Bitcoin.</a> With Amazon holding $88 billion in cash and short-term assets, this would represent a potential $4.5 billion investment in the cryptocurrency.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The Microsoft board&#8217;s primary concerns centered on Bitcoin&#8217;s price volatility and its implications for corporate treasury management. The company emphasized the importance of maintaining stable and predictable investments to ensure operational funding and liquidity.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">During the annual meeting, shareholders followed the board&#8217;s recommendation, demonstrating alignment with a more conservative approach to treasury management. The decision reflects the challenges that cryptocurrencies face in gaining acceptance as corporate treasury assets.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The voting process took place during Microsoft&#8217;s annual shareholder meeting, where various corporate governance and strategic matters were discussed. The Bitcoin proposal represented one of several items on the agenda requiring shareholder consideration.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Microsoft&#8217;s Global Treasury and Investment Services team maintains responsibility for evaluating potential investments and managing the company&#8217;s financial resources. Their assessment of Bitcoin and other cryptocurrencies factors into the broader strategy of maintaining financial stability and supporting corporate operations.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The impact of the decision extended beyond Microsoft, influencing market sentiment and potentially setting a precedent for other large corporations considering similar proposals. The cryptocurrency market&#8217;s reaction demonstrated the weight that corporate adoption decisions carry in the broader digital asset ecosystem.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">This development occurs against the backdrop of increasing institutional interest in cryptocurrencies, though companies remain divided on their approach to digital asset investment. The outcome of Amazon&#8217;s pending Bitcoin proposal may provide additional insight into corporate attitudes toward cryptocurrency treasury allocation.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/microsoft-shareholders-decline-800m-bitcoin-investment-strategy/">Microsoft Shareholders Decline $800M Bitcoin Investment Strategy</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">107874</post-id>	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
