<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	
	xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
	xmlns:geo="http://www.w3.org/2003/01/geo/wgs84_pos#"
	>

<channel>
	<title>NFTs Archives - Blockonomi</title>
	<atom:link href="https://blockonomi.com/nfts/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://blockonomi.com/nfts/</link>
	<description>Cryptocurrency News &#38; Your Guide to the Blockchain Economy</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 09:08:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.7.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/fav-50x50.png</url>
	<title>NFTs Archives - Blockonomi</title>
	<link>https://blockonomi.com/nfts/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
<site xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">134176212</site>	<item>
		<title>Pudgy Penguins NFT Collection Floor Price Hits 27 ETH as $PENGU Token Launch Approaches</title>
		<link>https://blockonomi.com/pudgy-penguins-nft-collection-floor-price-hits-27-eth-as-pengu-token-launch-approaches/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Oliver Dale]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 09:08:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NFTs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blockonomi.com/?p=107977</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>TLDR Pudgy Penguins NFT floor price has reached 27 ETH ($102,600), surpassing Bitcoin&#8217;s price of $101,000 for the first time in its history The project ranks second among NFT collections behind CryptoPunks (39.5 ETH floor price) The upcoming launch of $PENGU token on Solana in 2024 has driven increased interest, with NFT prices rising 194% [...]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/pudgy-penguins-nft-collection-floor-price-hits-27-eth-as-pengu-token-launch-approaches/">Pudgy Penguins NFT Collection Floor Price Hits 27 ETH as $PENGU Token Launch Approaches</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>TLDR</h2>
<ul>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Pudgy Penguins NFT floor price has reached 27 ETH ($102,600), surpassing Bitcoin&#8217;s price of $101,000 for the first time in its history</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">The project ranks second among NFT collections behind CryptoPunks (39.5 ETH floor price)</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">The upcoming launch of $PENGU token on Solana in 2024 has driven increased interest, with NFT prices rising 194% in the past month</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">NFT sales volume peaked at over $180M in early December with over 12,000 active wallets</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">The most expensive Pudgy Penguin is currently listed at 50.3093 ETH ($197,508.78) on OpenSea</li>
</ul>
<hr />
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The popular NFT collection <a href="https://cryptobriefing.com/pudgy-penguins-nfts-surge/">Pudgy Penguins has achieved a remarkable milestone in December 2024,</a> with its floor price surpassing $100,000 and exceeding the price of Bitcoin. The collection&#8217;s minimum entry price reached 27 ETH, equivalent to $102,600, marking a new all-time high for the project.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">This price breakthrough positions <a href="https://crypto.news/pudgypenguin-nft-price-exceeds-bitcoins-price-opensea/">Pudgy Penguins as the second-largest NFT collection in terms of floor price,</a> trailing only behind the legendary CryptoPunks collection, which maintains a floor price of 39.5 ETH ($150,000). The collection&#8217;s most expensive piece is currently listed at 50.3093 ETH, approximately $197,508.78 on the NFT marketplace OpenSea.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The surge in value comes amid heightened trading activity, with the project experiencing a 194% price increase over the past month according to data from CoinGecko. The collection has seen its market dominance rise to 21.88%, surpassing the previous market leader, Bored Ape Yacht Club, which now holds 16.31% of the market share.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The timing of this price rally coincides with the announcement of the project&#8217;s upcoming ecosystem token, $PENGU, scheduled for release on the Solana blockchain. While the exact launch date remains undisclosed, the team has confirmed the token will debut in 2024, with less than 20 days remaining in the current year.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The introduction of $PENGU represents a strategic cross-chain expansion for the project. Despite the NFT collection remaining on Ethereum, the decision to launch the token on Solana demonstrates the team&#8217;s approach to leveraging opportunities across multiple blockchain networks.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Introducing <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24PENGU&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">$PENGU</a>, the official coin of Pudgy Penguins.</p>
<p>Launching in 2024. Learn more below. <a href="https://t.co/J715bODcM6">pic.twitter.com/J715bODcM6</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Pudgy Penguins (@pudgypenguins) <a href="https://twitter.com/pudgypenguins/status/1864851993094664602?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">December 6, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The tokenomics structure for $PENGU has been carefully planned, with a total supply set at 88,888,888,888 tokens. The distribution allocates 25.9% to the existing Pudgy Penguins community, while 24.12% is reserved for other communities and new &#8220;Huddle&#8221; members.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Team allocation has been structured with long-term alignment in mind, with current and future team members receiving 17.8% of the supply. This portion is subject to a one-year cliff and three-year vesting period. The company will retain 11.48% under identical vesting conditions.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The project&#8217;s recent success is reflected in its trading volumes, with NFT sales reaching over $180 million in early December. The number of active market wallets exceeded 12,000, indicating strong market participation and investor interest.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Looking at the collection&#8217;s growth trajectory, Pudgy Penguins has seen its market dominance more than triple since October 2024, when it held just 9.5% of the market share. This increase aligns with a broader recovery in the NFT market, which saw total sales volumes rise 57.8% to $562 million in November, reaching the highest monthly figure since May.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The collection&#8217;s rise to prominence began in 2021, and it has since expanded beyond the digital realm through strategic retail partnerships with major brands including Walmart and Target. These real-world connections have helped establish Pudgy Penguins as more than just a digital art collection.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The project consists of 8,888 unique NFTs, each with distinct characteristics and varying levels of rarity. The current floor price of 27.65 ETH ($108,460) represents the minimum investment required to join the collection&#8217;s ownership group.</p>
<figure id="attachment_107981" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-107981" style="width: 847px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-107981" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-12-at-09-06-14-Pudgy-Penguins-NFT-Floor-Price-Chart-CoinGecko.png" alt="Pudgy Penguins Price on CoinGecko" width="847" height="635" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-12-at-09-06-14-Pudgy-Penguins-NFT-Floor-Price-Chart-CoinGecko.png 847w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-12-at-09-06-14-Pudgy-Penguins-NFT-Floor-Price-Chart-CoinGecko-300x225.png 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-12-at-09-06-14-Pudgy-Penguins-NFT-Floor-Price-Chart-CoinGecko-768x576.png 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-12-at-09-06-14-Pudgy-Penguins-NFT-Floor-Price-Chart-CoinGecko-50x37.png 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-12-at-09-06-14-Pudgy-Penguins-NFT-Floor-Price-Chart-CoinGecko-150x112.png 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-12-at-09-06-14-Pudgy-Penguins-NFT-Floor-Price-Chart-CoinGecko-450x337.png 450w" sizes="(max-width: 847px) 100vw, 847px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-107981" class="wp-caption-text">Pudgy Penguins Price on <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/nft/pudgy-penguins">CoinGecko</a></figcaption></figure>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Market data shows particular strength in blue-chip NFT collections, with both CryptoPunks and Pudgy Penguins leading the recent market recovery. The floor price for Pudgy Penguins demonstrated this momentum with a 262% increase during November, rising from 8.7 ETH to 13 ETH before its current levels.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Trading activity has remained robust through December, with daily volumes consistently showing strong market interest. The 21.88% market dominance achieved by Pudgy Penguins represents a major shift in the NFT landscape, particularly in displacing Bored Ape Yacht Club from its previous market-leading position.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The current floor price statistics show the collection maintaining steady value above the $100,000 mark, with Bitcoin prices hovering around $101,445 at the time of writing.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/pudgy-penguins-nft-collection-floor-price-hits-27-eth-as-pengu-token-launch-approaches/">Pudgy Penguins NFT Collection Floor Price Hits 27 ETH as $PENGU Token Launch Approaches</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">107977</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Pudgy Penguins Announces PENGU Token on Solana Blockchain</title>
		<link>https://blockonomi.com/pudgy-penguins-announces-pengu-token-on-solana-blockchain/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Oliver Dale]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 11:32:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Analysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NFTs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blockonomi.com/?p=107732</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>TLDR Pudgy Penguins NFT project announces PENGU token on Solana blockchain, launching December 2024 Total token supply will be 88.88 billion PENGU Project reaches new all-time high floor price of over $74,000 Token distribution includes NFT holders, public good, DEX liquidity, and team allocation Follows recent expansion including Pudgy Party mobile game and Walmart toy [...]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/pudgy-penguins-announces-pengu-token-on-solana-blockchain/">Pudgy Penguins Announces PENGU Token on Solana Blockchain</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>TLDR</h2>
<ul>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Pudgy Penguins NFT project announces PENGU token on Solana blockchain, launching December 2024</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Total token supply will be 88.88 billion PENGU</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Project reaches new all-time high floor price of over $74,000</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Token distribution includes NFT holders, public good, DEX liquidity, and team allocation</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Follows recent expansion including Pudgy Party mobile game and Walmart toy line</li>
</ul>
<hr />
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Pudgy Penguins, the popular NFT project,<a href="https://fullycrypto.com/pudgy-penguins-to-pengu-token-this-month?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pudgy-penguins-to-pengu-token-this-month"> announced plans to launch a new token called PENGU on the Solana blockchain this December.</a> The announcement comes as the project&#8217;s NFT floor price reaches a new all-time high of over $74,000.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The PENGU token will have a total supply of 88.88 billion tokens. The project team has outlined plans for broad distribution, including allocations to current NFT holders, public initiatives, and providing liquidity on decentralized exchanges (DEXs).</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">This token launch follows the project&#8217;s recent expansion into mobile gaming with Pudgy Party, announced just last month. The gaming venture represents one of several moves by the project to grow beyond its NFT roots.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The project&#8217;s reach already extends into traditional retail through a partnership with Walmart, where physical Pudgy Penguins toys are sold across stores in the United States. This retail presence, established a year ago, marked an early step in the project&#8217;s broader expansion strategy.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">In announcing PENGU, the project team emphasized their goal of uniting existing fans while opening doors for new participants who may not own their NFTs. They&#8217;ve dubbed the upcoming period as the start of &#8220;prophecy years,&#8221; though specific details about this concept remain unclear.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Introducing <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24PENGU&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">$PENGU</a>, the official coin of Pudgy Penguins.</p>
<p>Launching in 2024. Learn more below. <a href="https://t.co/J715bODcM6">pic.twitter.com/J715bODcM6</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Pudgy Penguins (@pudgypenguins) <a href="https://twitter.com/pudgypenguins/status/1864851993094664602?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">December 6, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Current Pudgy Penguins NFT holders will receive a portion of the token allocation, though exact distribution amounts haven&#8217;t been disclosed. The development team plans to retain a small percentage of the tokens for operational purposes.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Both Ethereum and Solana communities will receive token allocations, highlighting the project&#8217;s cross-chain approach despite choosing Solana for the token launch. This decision could help bridge communities across different blockchain platforms.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The project has positioned itself as &#8220;the face of crypto,&#8221; claiming presence &#8220;in millions of households worldwide.&#8221; While exact numbers aren&#8217;t independently verified, their Walmart partnership does provide substantial retail exposure.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Token allocations will include funds for &#8220;public good&#8221; initiatives, though specific details about these programs haven&#8217;t been announced. The team plans to provide liquidity on decentralized exchanges to ensure trading availability.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The timing of the token launch coincides with strong performance in the NFT collection&#8217;s trading prices. The floor price reaching over $74,000 represents the highest level in the project&#8217;s history.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The PENGU token launch marks another step in Pudgy Penguins&#8217; expansion from digital collectibles into broader applications. Their development timeline shows consistent growth from NFTs to physical toys, mobile gaming, and now tokens.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Project leaders have emphasized accessibility in their token launch plans, aiming to include both cryptocurrency veterans and newcomers. This approach aligns with their earlier moves into mainstream retail through Walmart.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The cross-chain nature of the token distribution, including both Ethereum and Solana communities, suggests an attempt to unite different blockchain user bases. This could create new opportunities for collaboration across platforms.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Technical details about the token, including smart contract specifications and security measures, are still forthcoming. The team hasn&#8217;t yet announced which decentralized exchanges will list PENGU at launch.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The December launch timeline places the token debut during a period of increased activity in digital asset markets. The project&#8217;s established brand recognition through retail presence and NFT success could influence initial token reception.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/pudgy-penguins-announces-pengu-token-on-solana-blockchain/">Pudgy Penguins Announces PENGU Token on Solana Blockchain</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">107732</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Pudgy Penguins Launches PENGU Token on Solana, NFT Floor Price Hits $62,000</title>
		<link>https://blockonomi.com/pudgy-penguins-launches-pengu-token-on-solana-nft-floor-price-hits-62000/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Oliver Dale]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 09:51:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[NFTs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blockonomi.com/?p=107588</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>TLDR Pudgy Penguins announces PENGU token launch on Solana blockchain with 88 billion total supply NFT collection hits new all-time high floor price of $62,000, up 40% this week Project to distribute tokens across NFT holders (23.5%) and crypto communities (22.02%) Company raised $11M for Ethereum Layer-2 network called Abstract Brand expanded beyond NFTs with [...]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/pudgy-penguins-launches-pengu-token-on-solana-nft-floor-price-hits-62000/">Pudgy Penguins Launches PENGU Token on Solana, NFT Floor Price Hits $62,000</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>TLDR</h2>
<ul>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Pudgy Penguins announces PENGU token launch on Solana blockchain with 88 billion total supply</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">NFT collection hits new all-time high floor price of $62,000, up 40% this week</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Project to distribute tokens across NFT holders (23.5%) and crypto communities (22.02%)</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Company raised $11M for Ethereum Layer-2 network called Abstract</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Brand expanded beyond NFTs with $10M+ in physical toy sales and upcoming mobile game</li>
</ul>
<hr />
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words"><a href="https://www.pudgypenguins.com/">Pudgy Penguins</a>, the third-largest NFT collection by market capitalization, announced plans to launch PENGU, a new token on the Solana blockchain, before the end of 2024. <a href="https://decrypt.co/295215/pudgy-penguins-to-hatch-a-master-coin-on-solana-as-nft-floor-prices-surge">The news comes as the project&#8217;s NFT floor price reached a record high of $62,000, marking a 40% increase this week.</a></p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The project team revealed plans to distribute 88 billion PENGU tokens, with 23.5% reserved for current Pudgy Penguins NFT holders and 22.02% allocated to the broader Solana and Ethereum communities. The distribution plan includes setting aside 12.32% of tokens to provide liquidity on decentralized exchanges.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">In the project&#8217;s announcement video, the PENGU token is presented as the &#8220;Master Coin,&#8221; which will be &#8220;hatched&#8221; from a golden egg by the core team of seven members. This metaphorical approach aligns with the project&#8217;s playful brand identity, which began in July 2021 with 8,888 NFT pieces.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Introducing <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24PENGU&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">$PENGU</a>, the official coin of Pudgy Penguins.</p>
<p>Launching in 2024. Learn more below. <a href="https://t.co/J715bODcM6">pic.twitter.com/J715bODcM6</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Pudgy Penguins (@pudgypenguins) <a href="https://twitter.com/pudgypenguins/status/1864851993094664602?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">December 6, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The collection&#8217;s market performance has been strong, with its floor price surpassing the previous peak of $57,000 recorded in February 2024. This price movement coincides with Bitcoin&#8217;s rise above $100,000 and reflects broader market momentum affecting major NFT collections.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Pudgy Penguins has maintained market stability despite NFT market fluctuations, achieving a total market capitalization of approximately $550 million. The brand&#8217;s success extends beyond digital assets, having generated over $10 million in revenue from physical toy sales through major retailers including Walmart, Target, and Walgreens.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The project&#8217;s expansion plans include a mobile game called Pudgy Party, developed in partnership with Mythical Games. Set to launch globally on iOS and Android platforms in 2025, the game emphasizes teamwork and shared rewards in an accessible environment, differentiating itself from typical knockout royale games.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Earlier this year, Igloo, Inc., the parent company of Pudgy Penguins, secured $11 million in funding to develop Abstract, a new Ethereum layer-2 scaling network. The funding round was led by Founders Fund, with participation from Fenbushi Capital, 1kx, Everest Ventures Group, and Selini Capital.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The PENGU token launch represents a strategic move as market attention shifts from NFTs to fungible tokens and meme coins. On social media platform X, formerly Twitter, the project acknowledged this shift, stating &#8220;Tides are shifting. A new beginning is upon us.&#8221;</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Tides are shifting, a new beginning is upon us. <a href="https://t.co/fYsAbWIvdL">pic.twitter.com/fYsAbWIvdL</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Pudgy Penguins (@pudgypenguins) <a href="https://twitter.com/pudgypenguins/status/1864068504258850960?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">December 3, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The project&#8217;s social media presence remains strong, with over 3 million followers across platforms and 32 billion views on Giphy. This engagement supports the brand&#8217;s expansion beyond its original NFT focus.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The broader NFT market has shown renewed activity, with the overall market capitalization reaching $8.6 billion according to <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/nft/pudgy-penguins">CoinGecko data</a>. Weekly Ethereum NFT trading volume has doubled, exceeding $101 million.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The project&#8217;s trajectory changed when Luca Netz acquired it in 2022, transforming it from a struggling NFT collection into a prominent crypto-native brand. In July, Netz shared optimistic projections for the project, suggesting a potential floor price target of 200 ETH (approximately $780,000 at current rates) during this market cycle.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">While the project plans future integration with the Abstract Ethereum Layer-2 solution, current efforts focus on establishing PENGU&#8217;s presence in the Solana ecosystem. The token launch adds a new dimension to Pudgy Penguins&#8217; expanding portfolio of digital and physical products.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The distribution model for PENGU tokens includes provisions for existing NFT holders across various collections, including Pudgy Penguins, Lil Pudgys, and Pudgy Rods. This approach aims to reward early supporters while expanding the project&#8217;s reach to new communities.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The project&#8217;s original collection featured penguin characters with various traits and accessories, establishing a recognizable brand that has since expanded into multiple product lines and digital experiences.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The decision to launch on Solana represents a cross-chain expansion for the traditionally Ethereum-based project, potentially opening new opportunities for growth and user engagement across different blockchain ecosystems.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/pudgy-penguins-launches-pengu-token-on-solana-nft-floor-price-hits-62000/">Pudgy Penguins Launches PENGU Token on Solana, NFT Floor Price Hits $62,000</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">107588</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Nifty Island&#8217;s ISLAND Token to Debut After 140,000-User Campaign</title>
		<link>https://blockonomi.com/nifty-islands-island-token-to-debut-after-140000-user-campaign/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Oliver Dale]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 09:34:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Gaming]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NFTs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blockonomi.com/?p=107409</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>TLDR: Nifty Island announces ISLAND token launch for December 17, 2024 Play-to-airdrop campaign ended November 1 with 140,000+ active wallets and 70,000 islands created Users from campaign will receive 12.5% of total token supply (25% increase from initial plan) One million ISLAND tokens set aside for new users who missed the campaign Launch comes amid [...]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/nifty-islands-island-token-to-debut-after-140000-user-campaign/">Nifty Island&#8217;s ISLAND Token to Debut After 140,000-User Campaign</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>TLDR:</h2>
<ul>
<li>Nifty Island announces ISLAND token launch for December 17, 2024</li>
<li>Play-to-airdrop campaign ended November 1 with 140,000+ active wallets and 70,000 islands created</li>
<li>Users from campaign will receive 12.5% of total token supply (25% increase from initial plan)</li>
<li>One million ISLAND tokens set aside for new users who missed the campaign</li>
<li>Launch comes amid surge in gaming tokens, with SAND and MANA up 150%+ in past month</li>
</ul>
<hr />
<p>Ethereum-based metaverse gaming platform <a href="https://www.niftyisland.com/">Nifty Island</a> has set December 17, 2024, as the launch date for its ISLAND token, marking a major milestone for the project. The announcement comes after nine months of community building through a play-to-airdrop campaign that drew over 140,000 active participants.</p>
<p>The platform&#8217;s recent play-to-airdrop campaign, which concluded on November 1, proved more successful than initially anticipated. Users created nearly 70,000 playable islands within the game&#8217;s ecosystem, showing strong engagement with the platform&#8217;s creative tools.</p>
<p>In response to the campaign&#8217;s success, Nifty Island has increased the token allocation for participating users. The project will now distribute 12.5% of the total ISLAND token supply to campaign participants, representing a 25% increase from the original distribution plan.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Every community. Infinite islands. One token. </p>
<p>The dream of an open game world powered by web3 will be fulfilled.</p>
<p>On 12.17 <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24ISLAND&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">$ISLAND</a> TGE arrives <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/15.0.3/72x72/1f3dd.png" alt="🏝" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> <a href="https://t.co/9K54xETGyX">pic.twitter.com/9K54xETGyX</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Nifty Island <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/15.0.3/72x72/1f3dd.png" alt="🏝" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> (@Nifty_Island) <a href="https://twitter.com/Nifty_Island/status/1863997033951981753?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">December 3, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>To maintain momentum and attract new users, Nifty Island has partnered with several Web3 communities. These partnerships have led to the creation of a special allocation of one million ISLAND tokens, which will be available for claiming on launch day by users who missed the initial campaign.</p>
<p>Charles Smith, co-founder of Nifty Island, shared his vision for the platform&#8217;s future in November. &#8220;We now have a rock-solid foundation on which we can build the future of Nifty,&#8221; he told Decrypt, hinting at major developments ahead.</p>
<p>The platform&#8217;s development roadmap includes several ambitious goals. Plans are underway to bring Nifty Island to mobile devices, making the game more accessible to a broader audience. The team is also working on enhancing in-game content creation tools to improve the platform&#8217;s viral potential.</p>
<p>Smith believes these upcoming changes will transform the platform dramatically. &#8220;What we&#8217;re working on will be a new paradigm for Web3 gaming—as fundamental a shift as the emergence of play-to-airdrop was,&#8221; he explained, suggesting that current users might find the platform &#8220;unrecognizable&#8221; after future updates.</p>
<p>The ISLAND token launch comes at an opportune time in the gaming token market. Several established metaverse tokens have seen notable price increases over the past month. The Sandbox&#8217;s SAND token and Decentraland&#8217;s MANA have both recorded gains exceeding 150% in the last 30 days.</p>
<p>The Sandbox has been particularly active, with its SAND token showing a 32.3% increase in just 24 hours, reaching approximately $0.8. The token has maintained strong momentum with a 26.2% rise over seven days, according to CoinGecko data.</p>
<p>Within the broader gaming token market, this surge represents a reversal of previous market conditions. The sector has experienced renewed interest from investors and users alike, suggesting a potential shift in market sentiment toward gaming and metaverse projects.</p>
<p>Nifty Island&#8217;s approach to token distribution reflects a focus on community engagement. The increased allocation for play-to-airdrop participants rewards early adopters while the additional token pool for newcomers helps maintain an open ecosystem.</p>
<p>The platform&#8217;s sandbox-style gameplay allows users to create and share their own game worlds, called Islands. This user-generated content model aims to ensure a steady stream of fresh experiences for players, potentially supporting long-term engagement.</p>
<p>Technical development continues alongside the token launch preparations. The team has emphasized their commitment to building robust infrastructure for the platform&#8217;s growing user base.</p>
<p>The December 17 launch will position ISLAND alongside other established metaverse tokens in the market. As the date approaches, the project team continues to focus on platform development and community growth.</p>
<p>The timing of the launch aligns with increased market activity in the gaming token sector, where several major players have seen substantial price movements in recent weeks.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/nifty-islands-island-token-to-debut-after-140000-user-campaign/">Nifty Island&#8217;s ISLAND Token to Debut After 140,000-User Campaign</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">107409</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>NFT Trading Volume Reaches 7-Month High as Market Rebounds</title>
		<link>https://blockonomi.com/nft-trading-volume-reaches-7-month-high-as-market-rebounds/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Oliver Dale]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2024 09:33:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[NFTs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blockonomi.com/?p=107216</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>TLDR NFT daily sales reached $40.4 million, highest in 7 months CryptoPunks leads with $5.6M in daily sales, maintains 40% market share Floor prices for top NFTs: CryptoPunks ($162,000), BAYC ($85,900), Pudgy Penguins ($54,500) Total NFT market cap hit $8.8 billion, up 17.3% in a week November sales volume reached $562 million, highest since May [...]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/nft-trading-volume-reaches-7-month-high-as-market-rebounds/">NFT Trading Volume Reaches 7-Month High as Market Rebounds</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>TLDR</h2>
<ul>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">NFT daily sales reached $40.4 million, highest in 7 months</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">CryptoPunks leads with $5.6M in daily sales, maintains 40% market share</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Floor prices for top NFTs: CryptoPunks ($162,000), BAYC ($85,900), Pudgy Penguins ($54,500)</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Total NFT market cap hit $8.8 billion, up 17.3% in a week</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">November sales volume reached $562 million, highest since May 2024</li>
</ul>
<hr />
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words"><a href="https://crypto.news/nft-sales-floor-prices-surge-cryptopunks-lead-the-charge/">The NFT market has demonstrated a robust recovery in late 2024</a>, with daily sales reaching $40.4 million, marking the highest trading volume in over seven months. <a href="https://www.cryptoslam.io/">According to data from CryptoSlam,</a> this represents a 28% increase in just 24 hours, indicating renewed interest in digital collectibles.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Ethereum continues to dominate the NFT ecosystem, generating $26.4 million in daily sales. Bitcoin and Solana follow with $6.3 million and $2.5 million in trading volume, respectively. The market has seen active participation from both buyers and sellers, with 41,000 buyers and approximately 30,000 sellers engaging in transactions.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">CryptoPunks, one of the oldest and most established NFT collections, maintains its position as the market leader with $5.6 million in daily sales. Despite a 4% dip in recent activity, the collection commands a 40% market share, demonstrating its enduring appeal among collectors.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The Bored Ape Yacht Club (BAYC) collection has shown strong performance as well, with a 15% increase in 24-hour volume to $3.2 million. According to CoinGecko data, the floor prices of major collections have seen notable increases, with CryptoPunks reaching $162,000, BAYC at $85,900, and Pudgy Penguins at $54,500.</p>
<figure id="attachment_107217" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-107217" style="width: 1358px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-107217" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-02-at-09-31-41-Top-NFT-Collections-by-Market-Cap-Floor-Price-Volume-CoinGecko.png" alt="NFT Collection Prices on CoinGecko" width="1358" height="839" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-02-at-09-31-41-Top-NFT-Collections-by-Market-Cap-Floor-Price-Volume-CoinGecko.png 1358w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-02-at-09-31-41-Top-NFT-Collections-by-Market-Cap-Floor-Price-Volume-CoinGecko-300x185.png 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-02-at-09-31-41-Top-NFT-Collections-by-Market-Cap-Floor-Price-Volume-CoinGecko-768x474.png 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-02-at-09-31-41-Top-NFT-Collections-by-Market-Cap-Floor-Price-Volume-CoinGecko-50x31.png 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-02-at-09-31-41-Top-NFT-Collections-by-Market-Cap-Floor-Price-Volume-CoinGecko-150x93.png 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-02-at-09-31-41-Top-NFT-Collections-by-Market-Cap-Floor-Price-Volume-CoinGecko-450x278.png 450w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Screenshot-2024-12-02-at-09-31-41-Top-NFT-Collections-by-Market-Cap-Floor-Price-Volume-CoinGecko-1200x741.png 1200w" sizes="(max-width: 1358px) 100vw, 1358px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-107217" class="wp-caption-text">NFT Collection Prices on <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/nft">CoinGecko</a></figcaption></figure>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The total market capitalization of NFTs has grown to $8.8 billion, representing a 17.3% increase over the past week. This growth coincides with broader positive trends in the cryptocurrency market, which recently reached an all-time high of $3.628 trillion in total market capitalization.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">November 2024 proved to be a pivotal month for the NFT market, with total sales volume reaching $562 million. This figure represents the highest monthly sales since May 2024, which recorded nearly $600 million in transactions. However, the number of unique buyers has decreased, with November seeing 662,000 buyers compared to over a million in May.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The marketplace landscape has evolved, with Blur leading in transaction volume at $271 million, followed closely by OpenSea with $161 million. OpenSea maintains a larger user base with approximately 188,000 active traders, while Blur operates with a smaller but more active group of around 38,000 traders.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Cardano&#8217;s NFT ecosystem has also shown notable activity, with the platform recording the most expensive single NFT sale of the day. An 8-bit Zombie #0388 collectible sold for over $388,000, contributing to Cardano&#8217;s total daily sales of $594,000.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The total number of NFT buyers has increased by 7%, indicating growing market participation. The surge in activity spans across multiple blockchain platforms, with each showing distinct patterns of growth and user engagement.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The market&#8217;s recovery extends beyond just the top collections. Pudgy Penguins has emerged as a serious contender in the blue-chip space, maintaining a floor price of approximately $55,758 with a 30% weekly appreciation. Azuki, another notable collection, has seen its floor price increase by 8.61% in a single day.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Three collections &#8211; CryptoPunks, BAYC, and Pudgy Penguins &#8211; now dominate the market, controlling 73% of all market activity. This concentration suggests a preference for established collections among traders and investors.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The CryptoSlam 500 NFT Index, currently at 1,135.04, shows a 53.77% decline from its all-time high of 2,494.74, providing context for the current market position relative to previous peaks.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Trading platforms have reported increased activity, with various marketplaces across EVM chains showing substantial volume. This growth in platform activity indicates broader market participation and liquidity.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The latest data from December 2024 shows the NFT market at its highest trading levels since late April, with global sales volumes continuing to climb across major blockchain networks.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/nft-trading-volume-reaches-7-month-high-as-market-rebounds/">NFT Trading Volume Reaches 7-Month High as Market Rebounds</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">107216</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>OpEd: NFTs Spike – The Metaverse Asset is Popular Again!</title>
		<link>https://blockonomi.com/oped-nfts-spike-the-metaverse-asset-is-popular-again/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nicholas Say]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 10:44:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Metaverse]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NFTs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blockonomi.com/?p=106764</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In the world of blockchain technology – there will always be hype – and underlying innovation. The McTrumper crypto rally is in full force. BTC is flirting with $100k! $1 Million USD is next! The long hated NFT complex sprung back to life – with some unique digital items blasting up in fiat terms. It&#8217;s [...]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/oped-nfts-spike-the-metaverse-asset-is-popular-again/">OpEd: NFTs Spike – The Metaverse Asset is Popular Again!</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In the world of blockchain technology – there will always be hype – and underlying innovation.</p>
<p>The McTrumper <a href="https://www.zerohedge.com/crypto/nfts-weekly-sales-surge-94-crypto-market-continues-bullish-run">crypto rally</a> is in full force. BTC is flirting with $100k! $1 Million USD is next!</p>
<p>The long hated NFT complex sprung back to life – with some unique digital items blasting up in fiat terms. It&#8217;s a feeding frenzy and every asset seems to be on the menu.</p>
<p>NFTs are an interesting way to store unique data. After the boom in 2021 – and then the FTX crash – NFTs kinda lost their appeal.</p>
<p>Turns out that unique digital items just aren&#8217;t that useful – at least not yet.</p>
<h2>Heading For The Metaverse</h2>
<p>Early and wrong look the same – but they are very different.</p>
<p>NFTs go back a few years. ETH&#8217;s blockchain likely brought the first NFTs to market. They look like a child&#8217;s experimentation with Corel draw.</p>
<p>Of course, in the boom times, these early ETH NFTs sold for big money.</p>
<p>Silly.</p>
<p>The lockdowns could have played a role in the market action we saw in 2020-2022. Work from home – play from home. Never leave your pod.</p>
<p>Digital became a lot more real in those times.</p>
<p>Hell – Facebook transitioned to Meta!</p>
<p>The idea of online life isn&#8217;t new, but it is becoming a lot more feasible. We think the future of NFTs is directly connected to online living.</p>
<h2>The City of The Future</h2>
<p>We like fresh air and being away from electronics. In fact, we understand why people live off the grid. But that isn&#8217;t the direction humanity is headed.</p>
<p>No, this is the techpocalypse!</p>
<p>What happens when the Metaverse meets Neuralink and Starlink – we will tell you – global mental domination. We are talking about a global metropolis of the mind.</p>
<p>In the city of the future – NFTs are how novelty exists. Money (BTC, ETH, SOL, XRP) isn&#8217;t interesting. Stack it up. Who cares. Humans crave novelty.</p>
<p>NFTs are the only way people can have decentralized novelty in the digital hellscape that is being created in the early 21st century.</p>
<h2>Back in The Pod!</h2>
<p>Cities are an abnormal state for humans. A city is unnatural. It is how humans dominate the planet on a small scale. If you have ever flown on airplanes – you understand this point. We pop from urban center to urban center, passing over the wildlands where being a human isn’t easy.</p>
<p>Consider the environment where an NFTs are useful – or have value. The level of technology needed for digital assets to have value is high by historical standards.</p>
<p>Computers are needed, but people also need access to the internet. In addition to technology, people need to have a desire to have unique digital assets – which have no real use outside of the digital world.</p>
<p>NFTs are an interesting asset class that could see more popularity as people around the world transition to an online lifestyle.</p>
<h2>Another NFT Boom?</h2>
<p>With cryptos heating up – NFTs could see more people piling in. But unlike cryptos, NFTs have already been adopted by some of the world&#8217;s largest companies.</p>
<p>McDonald&#8217;s issues NFTs for seasonal promotions – and apparently people collect them. As a promotional vehicle NFTs make a lot of sense. They cost little to create, and with an existing marketing machine, NFTs are easy to promote for a company like <a href="https://en.cryptonomist.ch/2024/11/19/the-nft-collection-doodles-collaborates-with-mcdonalds-for-physical-and-digital-holiday-themed-collectibles/">McDonald&#8217;s</a>.</p>
<p>The future of all these collectible NFTs is another matter. Its unlikely these NFTs will command value in the current market – but as the NFT space ages in the coming decades – these close-to-free tokens could rise in value.</p>
<h2>Stuck in The Matrix</h2>
<p>Smartphones could be the thin end of the technology wedge that moves people into an online lifestyle. With implantable network connections like Neuralink – a world where humans never leave digital space could become a reality.</p>
<p>When the transition to digital as reality is complete, NFTs are no longer a digital asset – they are real. In fact, all the physical assets that exist today would be worthless. Without a digital presence, an object would have no value.</p>
<p>We are looking at a world where perception is reality. The Metaverse is where pure awareness is all that matters. In this world – McDonald&#8217;s collectible holiday NFTs would be a highly desirable asset that reminds people of a world where people existed in a physical reality.</p>
<h2>The World Where Digital Lags Behind</h2>
<p>The digital world is a place where most of humanity is left behind. Smartphones aren&#8217;t enough to bring about a transition to living in the Metaverse. In today&#8217;s urban centers, connection to digital reality is simple, the same isn&#8217;t true for most of the world&#8217;s emerging nations.</p>
<p>And then there is state control over access. China&#8217;s national firewall is a perfect example of this issue.</p>
<p>A global online world isn&#8217;t going to be effective if state actors can shut down access at will. Or maybe the people won&#8217;t know. If people grow up in the digital world, they won&#8217;t understand physical space in the same way we do at the moment.</p>
<p>In fact, there could be a split in humanity – between those who are part of the Metaverse – and those who live as biological humans do now.</p>
<h2>Real Innovation Means Value Creation</h2>
<p>For the moment – we still live in physical reality.</p>
<p>The level of technology that would make NFTs “real” doesn&#8217;t exist – as Meta&#8217;s total economic failure demonstrates. In fact, we lack the platforms to allow people to live in a more digital world.</p>
<p>Cryptos have value as they can be spent into the real life economy that exists today. For NFTs, their collectibility is questionable – despite the recent knee-jerk higher for some NFT prices.</p>
<p>NFTs are still being issued by artists, companies and other creators, so they are developing as a digital asset. What that means longer term is anyone&#8217;s guess.</p>
<p>In terms of innovation – there isn&#8217;t much happening in the world of NFTs. While they can be used as tickets for events, in general, they are not. This is true for most NFT use cases – as they require users to have special apps – which just makes the whole deal a little bit of a reach.</p>
<p>For now – the NFT rally looks like an echo of the crypto pump that took BTC to a new all time high. If this rally does have staying power – some of the popular NFTs will continue higher.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/oped-nfts-spike-the-metaverse-asset-is-popular-again/">OpEd: NFTs Spike – The Metaverse Asset is Popular Again!</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">106764</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Doodles NFT Floor Price Rises 28% Following McDonald&#8217;s Campaign</title>
		<link>https://blockonomi.com/doodles-nft-floor-price-rises-28-following-mcdonalds-campaign/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Oliver Dale]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 10:24:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[NFTs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blockonomi.com/?p=106699</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>TLDR McDonald&#8217;s launches &#8220;GM Spread Joy&#8221; campaign featuring Doodles NFT art on 110 million McCafé cups across US Campaign includes digital collectibles accessible through McDonald&#8217;s app Doodles NFT floor price rose 27.97% to 2.75 ETH in 24 hours after announcement Collection currently valued at 28,990 ETH ($89.86 million) with 4,220 holders Doodle #3954 sold for [...]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/doodles-nft-floor-price-rises-28-following-mcdonalds-campaign/">Doodles NFT Floor Price Rises 28% Following McDonald&#8217;s Campaign</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>TLDR</h2>
<ul>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">McDonald&#8217;s launches &#8220;GM Spread Joy&#8221; campaign featuring Doodles NFT art on 110 million McCafé cups across US</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Campaign includes digital collectibles accessible through McDonald&#8217;s app</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Doodles NFT floor price rose 27.97% to 2.75 ETH in 24 hours after announcement</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Collection currently valued at 28,990 ETH ($89.86 million) with 4,220 holders</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Doodle #3954 sold for 42.690 ETH ($132,951) just before campaign launch</li>
</ul>
<hr />
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words"><a href="https://www.crypto-news-flash.com/mcdonalds-collaboration-sparks-doodles-nft-floor-price-surge/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=mcdonalds-collaboration-sparks-doodles-nft-floor-price-surge">McDonald&#8217;s new collaboration with Doodles NFT has launched across the United States,</a> placing colorful NFT artwork on millions of McCafé cups while causing notable market movement in the collection&#8217;s value.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The &#8220;GM Spread Joy&#8221; campaign, which began November 18, features Doodles&#8217; distinctive rainbow-themed designs across 110 million McCafé coffee cups nationwide. This represents one of the largest mainstream deployments of NFT artwork in the physical retail space.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Beyond the cup designs, McDonald&#8217;s has integrated digital elements into the promotion. Customers who purchase McCafé hot beverages can access special digital collectibles and animated content through the McDonald&#8217;s mobile application.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The partnership has sparked substantial activity in the Doodles NFT marketplace. As of November 22, the collection&#8217;s floor price stands at 2.75 ETH, with trading volume reaching 275.05 ETH across 106 sales within a 24-hour period.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Market data shows a 27.97% increase in the floor price over the previous day. The collection currently has 4,220 unique holders, with total market value reaching approximately 28,990 ETH, equivalent to $89.86 million.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The announcement period saw dramatic price movement, with the floor price more than doubling from 1.25 ETH to over 2.85 ETH by November 18.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">A notable sale occurred just before the campaign launch, with Doodle #3954 selling for 42.690 ETH, approximately $132,951 at current exchange rates.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The McDonald&#8217;s partnership extends the Doodles brand beyond the digital realm, placing the artwork in physical locations across the country&#8217;s McDonald&#8217;s restaurants.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The campaign marks McDonald&#8217;s first major integration of NFT artwork into its product packaging and retail experience.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">For customers, the promotion creates multiple touchpoints &#8211; the physical cup designs, digital collectibles, and animated content through the McDonald&#8217;s app.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The trading activity suggests strong market response to the mainstream retail partnership.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Current data shows sustained trading volume and price levels above pre-announcement figures.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The campaign represents one of the largest scale deployments of NFT-based artwork in traditional retail channels.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Market metrics indicate broad participation, with thousands of unique holders maintaining positions in the collection.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The most recent data shows continued active trading of Doodles NFTs following the partnership announcement and campaign launch.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/doodles-nft-floor-price-rises-28-following-mcdonalds-campaign/">Doodles NFT Floor Price Rises 28% Following McDonald&#8217;s Campaign</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">106699</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Pac-Man 45th Anniversary Celebration Features Tokyo NFT Scavenger Hunt</title>
		<link>https://blockonomi.com/pac-man-45th-anniversary-celebration-features-tokyo-nft-scavenger-hunt/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Oliver Dale]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 10:02:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[NFTs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blockonomi.com/?p=106447</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>TLDR: Bandai Namco and Flickplay partner for Pac-Man&#8217;s 45th anniversary NFT event in February 2025 Location-based scavenger hunt across 40+ spots in Tokyo&#8217;s Shibuya district Two NFT collection series planned &#8211; one exclusive to Shibuya, one available worldwide Experience Pass required for participation, granting in-app currency (Diamonds) Blockchain network for NFTs still undecided, future game [...]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/pac-man-45th-anniversary-celebration-features-tokyo-nft-scavenger-hunt/">Pac-Man 45th Anniversary Celebration Features Tokyo NFT Scavenger Hunt</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>TLDR:</h2>
<ul>
<li>Bandai Namco and Flickplay partner for Pac-Man&#8217;s 45th anniversary NFT event in February 2025</li>
<li>Location-based scavenger hunt across 40+ spots in Tokyo&#8217;s Shibuya district</li>
<li>Two NFT collection series planned &#8211; one exclusive to Shibuya, one available worldwide</li>
<li>Experience Pass required for participation, granting in-app currency (Diamonds)</li>
<li>Blockchain network for NFTs still undecided, future game integrations being explored</li>
</ul>
<hr />
<p>Bandai Namco Entertainment <a href="https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/business/digital/pac-man-collectibles-tokyo-shibuya-1236059703/">has announced a partnership with NFT platform Flickplay to celebrate Pac-Man&#8217;s 45th anniversary.</a> The collaboration will launch a digital scavenger hunt across Tokyo&#8217;s Shibuya district in February 2025.</p>
<p>The event will take place during the four-day DIG Shibuya Festival, running from February 8-11. Participants will hunt for digital collectibles across more than 40 locations throughout Shibuya City, the birthplace of Pac-Man in 1980.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">I’m incredibly excited to announce <a href="https://twitter.com/flickplayapp?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@flickplayapp</a>  is partnering with <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/BandaiNamcoEntertainment?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#BandaiNamcoEntertainment</a> Inc. and the City of Shibuya for what will be a groundbreaking inaugural <a href="https://twitter.com/flickplayapp?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@flickplayapp</a> activation in <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Tokyo?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Tokyo</a>, celebrating Pac-Man&#39;s 45th anniversary.</p>
<p>This is more than just an… <a href="https://t.co/uD6NkMrORJ">pic.twitter.com/uD6NkMrORJ</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Pierina Merino (@MerinoPierina) <a href="https://twitter.com/MerinoPierina/status/1858982929881591863?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">November 19, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>Two separate NFT collections will be released as part of the celebration. The first series will be exclusively available to those participating in the Shibuya scavenger hunt. The second collection will be made available worldwide through the Flickplay store at a later date.</p>
<p>To participate in the hunt, <a href="https://www.about.flickplay.co/pacman-activation">users must purchase an Experience Pass during a pre-sale event.</a> This pass will provide them with Diamonds, Flickplay&#8217;s in-app currency, which can be exchanged for Pac-Man digital collectibles when within range of designated locations.</p>
<p>The Experience Pass also comes with an immediate reward &#8211; buyers receive one Pac-Man digital collectible without having to participate in the hunt. Additionally, Flickplay has announced that event participants will receive a &#8220;Mystery Super Rare item.&#8221;</p>
<p>The hunt will function similarly to Pokémon Go, requiring players to physically visit specific locations within Shibuya City. Once within a predetermined radius of these spots, players can use their Diamonds to claim the digital collectibles.</p>
<p>Flickplay&#8217;s platform currently operates across multiple blockchain networks, including Flow, Ethereum, and Polygon. The company is in discussions with other Ethereum layer-2 networks to expand compatibility, though they haven&#8217;t yet announced which blockchain will host the Pac-Man NFTs.</p>
<p>The digital collectibles will have various uses within the Flickplay ecosystem. Users can create GIFs with their characters and interact with them through Tamagotchi-style widgets, similar to the platform&#8217;s previous Bratz Dolls collection.</p>
<p>Pierina Merino, founder and CEO of Flickplay, told Decrypt that the platform is actively seeking additional utility for the collectibles. &#8220;We are actively scouting for great games where we could pilot deeper interoperability with our characters,&#8221; Merino stated.</p>
<p>The supply of these digital collectibles will be limited, adding urgency to the scavenger hunt. Players who wish to complete the collection will need to move quickly during the four-day event window.</p>
<p>This initiative follows Flickplay&#8217;s previous success with other branded NFT collections. Earlier this year, their Bratz Dolls collection was integrated into The Sandbox, an Ethereum-based metaverse game, where the characters became playable avatars.</p>
<p>Looking ahead to 2025, Flickplay aims to improve the transferability of digital collectibles between different ecosystems. &#8220;It&#8217;s in our 2025 roadmap to make the experience of taking digital toys seamlessly from one ecosystem to another accessible to regular consumers,&#8221; Merino explained.</p>
<p>While specific details about future game integrations for the Pac-Man collectibles remain unannounced, the company continues to explore partnerships that could expand their utility within the gaming ecosystem.</p>
<p>The event represents one of the largest location-based NFT initiatives to date, combining mobile gaming mechanics with blockchain technology and a beloved gaming franchise.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/pac-man-45th-anniversary-celebration-features-tokyo-nft-scavenger-hunt/">Pac-Man 45th Anniversary Celebration Features Tokyo NFT Scavenger Hunt</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">106447</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>NFT Sales Volume Reaches $181 Million in Weekly Trading</title>
		<link>https://blockonomi.com/nft-sales-volume-reaches-181-million-in-weekly-trading/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Oliver Dale]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2024 09:30:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[NFTs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blockonomi.com/?p=106295</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>TLDR NFT weekly sales hit $181 million, up 94% from previous week&#8217;s $93 million Ethereum led with $67 million in NFT sales, followed by Bitcoin at $60 million Average NFT transaction value increased 87% to $133.08 October broke seven-month NFT sales downturn with $356 million total Rising NFT sales coincide with broader crypto market rally, [...]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/nft-sales-volume-reaches-181-million-in-weekly-trading/">NFT Sales Volume Reaches $181 Million in Weekly Trading</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>TLDR</h2>
<ul>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">NFT weekly sales hit $181 million, up 94% from previous week&#8217;s $93 million</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Ethereum led with $67 million in NFT sales, followed by Bitcoin at $60 million</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Average NFT transaction value increased 87% to $133.08</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">October broke seven-month NFT sales downturn with $356 million total</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Rising NFT sales coincide with broader crypto market rally, with Bitcoin at $91,000</li>
</ul>
<hr />
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The NFT (non-fungible token) market has recorded a remarkable recovery, with weekly sales volumes reaching $181 million, according to data from digital collectible tracker<a href="https://www.cryptoslam.io/nftglobal?headerPeriod=7d&amp;timeFrame=week&amp;tab=collection_rankings"> CryptoSlam. </a></p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words"><a href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/nft-weekly-sales-crypto-market-surge">This represents a 94% increase from the previous week&#8217;s $93 million in sales</a>, marking a clear shift in market momentum.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Ethereum maintained its position as the leading blockchain for NFT trading, generating $67 million in sales over the past week. This represents a 111% increase compared to the previous week&#8217;s figures, demonstrating strong growth in the ecosystem&#8217;s most established NFT marketplace.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Bitcoin-based NFTs closely followed Ethereum&#8217;s performance, recording $60 million in weekly sales. The Bitcoin NFT market showed similar growth patterns with a 115% week-over-week increase, suggesting growing adoption of NFTs on the Bitcoin blockchain.</p>
<figure id="attachment_106296" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-106296" style="width: 1132px" class="wp-caption aligncenter"><img decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-106296" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/Screenshot-2024-11-18-at-09-27-23-NFT-Global-Sales-Volume-Index-_-CryptoSlam.png" alt="NFT Global Sales Volume" width="1132" height="906" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/Screenshot-2024-11-18-at-09-27-23-NFT-Global-Sales-Volume-Index-_-CryptoSlam.png 1132w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/Screenshot-2024-11-18-at-09-27-23-NFT-Global-Sales-Volume-Index-_-CryptoSlam-300x240.png 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/Screenshot-2024-11-18-at-09-27-23-NFT-Global-Sales-Volume-Index-_-CryptoSlam-768x615.png 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/Screenshot-2024-11-18-at-09-27-23-NFT-Global-Sales-Volume-Index-_-CryptoSlam-50x40.png 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/Screenshot-2024-11-18-at-09-27-23-NFT-Global-Sales-Volume-Index-_-CryptoSlam-150x120.png 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/Screenshot-2024-11-18-at-09-27-23-NFT-Global-Sales-Volume-Index-_-CryptoSlam-450x360.png 450w" sizes="(max-width: 1132px) 100vw, 1132px" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-106296" class="wp-caption-text"><a href="https://www.cryptoslam.io/nftglobal?headerPeriod=7d&amp;timeFrame=week&amp;tab=collection_rankings">NFT Global Sales Volume</a></figcaption></figure>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Other major blockchain networks also contributed to the overall market recovery. Solana, Mythos Chain, Immutable, Polygon, and BNB Chain collectively achieved $45.5 million in weekly sales volume, indicating broad-based growth across the NFT ecosystem.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The average value per NFT transaction showed substantial growth during this period. Traders spent an average of $133.08 per NFT, representing an 87% increase from the previous week&#8217;s average of $71.11. This increase suggests renewed confidence among buyers in the NFT market.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">October proved to be a turning point for the NFT market, breaking a seven-month downward trend. Monthly sales reached $356 million, showing an 18% improvement from September&#8217;s record low of approximately $300 million.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Transaction activity also showed strong growth in October, with the total number of NFT transactions reaching 7.2 million. This represents a 42% increase compared to September&#8217;s figures, indicating higher market participation and trading activity.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The market recovery extends beyond just sales volumes. The increased transaction count suggests broader participation in the NFT market, with more buyers and sellers actively trading digital collectibles across various blockchain platforms.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The timing of this NFT market recovery coincides with positive movements in the broader cryptocurrency market. Bitcoin, the leading cryptocurrency, reached new price levels during this period, trading around $91,000 with a market capitalization of $1.8 trillion.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The data shows that both <a href="https://moneycheck.com/best-ethereum-casinos/">Ethereum</a> and<a href="https://moneycheck.com/best-bitcoin-casinos/"> Bitcoin</a> NFT markets are experiencing similar growth patterns, suggesting that the recovery is not limited to a single blockchain ecosystem. This parallel growth indicates increased confidence across the entire NFT space.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The rise in average transaction values points to increased willingness among collectors to invest in higher-value NFTs. This trend suggests that buyers are becoming more comfortable with larger investments in digital assets.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Transaction data reveals that the NFT market recovery is happening across multiple price points, from more affordable NFTs to high-value digital collectibles. This broad-based recovery indicates participation from various types of buyers and collectors.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The October sales figures are particularly notable as they mark the first monthly increase after seven consecutive months of declining sales. This reversal suggests a potential shift in market sentiment toward NFT collecting and trading.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The increase in total transaction count, rising from September to October, shows that more users are engaging with NFT platforms. The 42% growth in transactions indicates increased market activity across all segments of the NFT ecosystem.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The latest weekly sales data of $181 million represents the current state of the market recovery, with both Ethereum and Bitcoin NFTs showing strong performance in terms of sales volume and transaction counts.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/nft-sales-volume-reaches-181-million-in-weekly-trading/">NFT Sales Volume Reaches $181 Million in Weekly Trading</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">106295</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Doodles NFT Trading Volume Rises 500% Following McDonalds Announcement</title>
		<link>https://blockonomi.com/doodles-nft-trading-volume-rises-500-following-mcdonalds-announcement/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Oliver Dale]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 10:24:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[NFTs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blockonomi.com/?p=106022</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>TLDR Doodles NFT sales volume increased by 500% in 24 hours McDonalds is collaborating with Doodles NFT project Trading volume reached 766 ETH Floor price increased 33% to 2.71 ETH Official unveiling scheduled for November 18, 2024 McDonald&#8217;s entrance into the NFT space has created a surge in trading activity for Doodles, a popular NFT [...]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/doodles-nft-trading-volume-rises-500-following-mcdonalds-announcement/">Doodles NFT Trading Volume Rises 500% Following McDonalds Announcement</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>TLDR</h2>
<ul>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Doodles NFT sales volume increased by 500% in 24 hours</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">McDonalds is collaborating with Doodles NFT project</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Trading volume reached 766 ETH</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Floor price increased 33% to 2.71 ETH</li>
<li class="whitespace-normal break-words">Official unveiling scheduled for November 18, 2024</li>
</ul>
<hr />
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words"><a href="https://insidebitcoins.com/news/doodles-nft-sales-pump-500-in-the-past-24-hours-following-mcdonalds-collaboration">McDonald&#8217;s entrance into the NFT space</a> has created a surge in trading activity for Doodles, a popular NFT collection.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The partnership announcement led to a 500% increase in Doodles NFT sales volume within 24 hours, according to data from <a href="https://www.coingecko.com/en/nft/doodles-official">CoinGecko.com.</a></p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The collaboration came to light when Guillaume Huin, McDonald&#8217;s Senior Marketing Director, posted about an upcoming project on social media. Huin described it as &#8220;something a little different than usual&#8221; and &#8220;more niche than what we normally do.&#8221;</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Something a little different than usual is coming to McDonald’s.</p>
<p>A new kind of collab to explore new spaces. Tad more niche than what we normally do, but with a superb fan base, that will only grow when more people get to see it.</p>
<p>More to come tomorrow. <br />In the meantime, Gm.</p>
<p>&mdash; Guillaume Huin (@HuinGuillaume) <a href="https://twitter.com/HuinGuillaume/status/1856123873781330395?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">November 11, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Doodles, launched in 2021 by former Dapper Labs team members, consists of 10,000 NFTs on the Ethereum blockchain. The collection has established itself as a major player in the NFT market since its inception, working to transform from a pure NFT startup into a broader media franchise.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Following the partnership announcement, Doodles&#8217; trading metrics showed substantial growth across multiple areas.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The collection&#8217;s floor price rose 33% to reach 2.71 ETH, while trading volume hit 766 ETH in a single day. This volume nearly matched the combined trading of two other major NFT collections, Pudgy Penguins and Bored Ape Yacht Club.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The news attracted attention from several prominent figures in the crypto and NFT space. The Azuki founder Zagabond and Yuga Labs co-founder Greg Solana were among those who commented on the partnership, highlighting its potential impact on the NFT market.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">DOODLES X MCDONALDS PARTNERSHIP CONFIRMED <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/15.0.3/72x72/1f6a8.png" alt="🚨" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> <a href="https://t.co/ezSmCFvPvJ">pic.twitter.com/ezSmCFvPvJ</a></p>
<p>&mdash; wale.moca <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/15.0.3/72x72/1f433.png" alt="🐳" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> (@waleswoosh) <a href="https://twitter.com/waleswoosh/status/1856379449987739725?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">November 12, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The timing of the announcement aligns with Doodles&#8217; ongoing strategy to expand beyond its initial NFT focus. The project has been working to develop a larger presence in the media and entertainment space, making the McDonald&#8217;s partnership a natural step in this direction.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Trading data shows that the announcement&#8217;s impact was immediate and substantial. The 500% increase in sales volume demonstrates strong market interest in the collaboration, suggesting traders and collectors see value in the partnership.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">McDonald&#8217;s brings considerable brand recognition to the partnership. As one of the world&#8217;s most recognized fast-food chains, their entry into the NFT space represents a major mainstream business embracing digital collectibles.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The floor price increase to 2.71 ETH indicates growing confidence in the project&#8217;s future value. This price represents the minimum amount needed to purchase a Doodles NFT on the secondary market.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">CoinGecko.com&#8217;s data tracking showed the sharp rise in trading activity began immediately after the partnership news broke. The platform&#8217;s metrics revealed the surge in both volume and price occurred within hours of the announcement.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The 766 ETH trading volume achievement stands out particularly when compared to other major NFT collections. This level of trading activity places Doodles among the most actively traded NFT collections during this period.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The partnership marks a new direction for McDonald&#8217;s digital strategy. While the company has previously explored various digital initiatives, this represents their first major foray into the NFT space.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Public reaction on social media platforms has been notable, with thousands of community members discussing the collaboration. The announcement generated substantial engagement across various crypto and NFT-focused channels.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">Doodles&#8217; achievement of matching the combined trading volume of Pudgy Penguins and Bored Ape Yacht Club demonstrates the market&#8217;s strong response to the partnership news.</p>
<p class="whitespace-pre-wrap break-words">The official unveiling of the Doodles x McDonald&#8217;s collaboration is scheduled for November 18, 2024, when more details about the specific nature of the partnership will be revealed.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/doodles-nft-trading-volume-rises-500-following-mcdonalds-announcement/">Doodles NFT Trading Volume Rises 500% Following McDonalds Announcement</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">106022</post-id>	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
