<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	
	xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
	xmlns:geo="http://www.w3.org/2003/01/geo/wgs84_pos#"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Metaverse Archives - Blockonomi</title>
	<atom:link href="https://blockonomi.com/metaverse/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://blockonomi.com/metaverse/</link>
	<description>Cryptocurrency News &#38; Your Guide to the Blockchain Economy</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 09:04:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.7.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/fav-50x50.png</url>
	<title>Metaverse Archives - Blockonomi</title>
	<link>https://blockonomi.com/metaverse/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
<site xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">134176212</site>	<item>
		<title>The Sandbox Expands with Launch of Hellboy &#038; Terminator Interactive Gaming Experiences</title>
		<link>https://blockonomi.com/the-sandbox-expands-with-launch-of-hellboy-terminator-interactive-gaming-experiences/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Oliver Dale]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 09:04:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Gaming]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Metaverse]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blockonomi.com/?p=107489</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>TLDR: The Sandbox launches two new games featuring Hellboy (2019) and Terminator franchises Players can experience iconic scenes from the 2019 Hellboy film as BPRD agents Terminator: Dark Fate game transports players to 2042 for resistance missions The platform&#8217;s Alpha Season 4 has broken previous engagement records Over 400 partners including major brands have joined [...]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/the-sandbox-expands-with-launch-of-hellboy-terminator-interactive-gaming-experiences/">The Sandbox Expands with Launch of Hellboy &#038; Terminator Interactive Gaming Experiences</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>TLDR:</h2>
<ul>
<li>The Sandbox launches two new games featuring Hellboy (2019) and Terminator franchises</li>
<li>Players can experience iconic scenes from the 2019 Hellboy film as BPRD agents</li>
<li>Terminator: Dark Fate game transports players to 2042 for resistance missions</li>
<li>The platform&#8217;s Alpha Season 4 has broken previous engagement records</li>
<li>Over 400 partners including major brands have joined The Sandbox platform</li>
</ul>
<hr />
<p>The Sandbox, a decentralized gaming platform and subsidiary of Animoca Brands, has expanded its virtual world with two new games based on popular movie franchises. The platform has launched gaming experiences inspired by <a href="https://www.sandbox.game/en/experiences/Hellboy%202019%20by%20LIONSGATE/9a61c449-af1d-4ece-8749-34f732d26064/page/">Hellboy (2019)</a> and <a href="https://www.sandbox.game/en/experiences/-0-10-terminator-future-hub/8c69d9de-8e6d-47e4-a7ca-93743754c351/page/">Terminator: Dark Fate</a>, allowing players to immerse themselves in these iconic universes.</p>
<p>The Hellboy game, presented by Lionsgate, puts players in the role of potential agents for the Bureau of Paranormal Research and Defense (BPRD). Players travel between Tijuana and the United Kingdom, moving across different time periods as they complete their missions.</p>
<p><iframe class="youtube-player" width="814" height="458" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/HpX5-bVw_EM?version=3&#038;rel=1&#038;showsearch=0&#038;showinfo=1&#038;iv_load_policy=1&#038;fs=1&#038;hl=en-US&#038;autohide=2&#038;wmode=transparent" allowfullscreen="true" style="border:0;" sandbox="allow-scripts allow-same-origin allow-popups allow-presentation allow-popups-to-escape-sandbox"></iframe></p>
<p>During their adventures, agents encounter well-known characters from the Hellboy universe, including the mysterious Baba Yaga and the fearsome Blood Queen, Nimue. The game features combat scenarios against demons and tasks players with tracking giants while uncovering hidden secrets throughout the storyline.</p>
<p>The Terminator: Dark Fate experience takes a different approach, setting players in a post-apocalyptic world of 2042. In this timeline, killer machines known as Terminators hunt the remaining human population, forcing players to join the resistance movement.</p>
<p>Players in the Terminator game must develop survival strategies, create weapons, and work to eliminate the mechanical threats. The game includes time travel elements as players search for ways to stop the Terminator threat.</p>
<p><iframe class="youtube-player" width="814" height="458" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/y4p7j0jK9xQ?version=3&#038;rel=1&#038;showsearch=0&#038;showinfo=1&#038;iv_load_policy=1&#038;fs=1&#038;hl=en-US&#038;autohide=2&#038;wmode=transparent" allowfullscreen="true" style="border:0;" sandbox="allow-scripts allow-same-origin allow-popups allow-presentation allow-popups-to-escape-sandbox"></iframe></p>
<p>These new releases coincide with The Sandbox&#8217;s Alpha Season 4, which has already broken previous player engagement records set during Alpha Season 3 in 2022. The platform continues to attract users with its diverse range of gaming experiences.</p>
<p>The Sandbox has built partnerships with more than 400 brands and creators, bringing together various entertainment forms in its virtual space. Partners include major names such as Warner Music Group, Gucci, and Ubisoft, alongside celebrities like Paris Hilton and Snoop Dogg.</p>
<p>Popular entertainment properties such as The Walking Dead, Attack on Titan, and The Smurfs have also established their presence on the platform. The Sandbox offers experiences ranging from Gordon Ramsay&#8217;s Hell&#8217;s Kitchen to Ubisoft&#8217;s Rabbids and Captain Laserhawk.</p>
<p>The platform operates as a metaverse environment where users can both play and create their own experiences. It incorporates Web3 technologies, allowing players to own their digital assets and creations through non-fungible tokens (NFTs).</p>
<p>Players can access these new games through The Sandbox&#8217;s free desktop application, available for both Windows and Mac operating systems. The platform&#8217;s map feature helps users navigate between different experiences and discover new content.</p>
<p>The Hellboy game recreates scenes from the 2019 film, offering fans a new way to interact with the franchise&#8217;s characters and storylines. Players face challenges and missions that align with the movie&#8217;s supernatural themes.</p>
<p>In the Terminator experience, players must navigate a dangerous future world while working with other resistance members. The game combines action elements with strategic planning as players fight against the machine threat.</p>
<p>The addition of these movie-based games represents The Sandbox&#8217;s ongoing efforts to blend popular entertainment properties with interactive gaming experiences. Each game maintains core elements from its source material while adapting them to the platform&#8217;s gaming format.</p>
<p>The platform allows users to monetize their creations, establishing a creator economy within its virtual space. This system enables both players and creators to benefit from their contributions to the platform&#8217;s growing ecosystem.</p>
<p>These new releases add to The Sandbox&#8217;s existing collection of branded experiences, which span gaming, entertainment, music, and art sectors. The platform continues to expand its offerings through partnerships with established entertainment brands.</p>
<p>The games are now available for players to access through The Sandbox&#8217;s platform, joining other recent additions like Dungeon Siege and various creator-developed experiences.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/the-sandbox-expands-with-launch-of-hellboy-terminator-interactive-gaming-experiences/">The Sandbox Expands with Launch of Hellboy &#038; Terminator Interactive Gaming Experiences</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">107489</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>OpEd: NFTs Spike – The Metaverse Asset is Popular Again!</title>
		<link>https://blockonomi.com/oped-nfts-spike-the-metaverse-asset-is-popular-again/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Nicholas Say]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 10:44:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Metaverse]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NFTs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blockonomi.com/?p=106764</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In the world of blockchain technology – there will always be hype – and underlying innovation. The McTrumper crypto rally is in full force. BTC is flirting with $100k! $1 Million USD is next! The long hated NFT complex sprung back to life – with some unique digital items blasting up in fiat terms. It&#8217;s [...]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/oped-nfts-spike-the-metaverse-asset-is-popular-again/">OpEd: NFTs Spike – The Metaverse Asset is Popular Again!</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In the world of blockchain technology – there will always be hype – and underlying innovation.</p>
<p>The McTrumper <a href="https://www.zerohedge.com/crypto/nfts-weekly-sales-surge-94-crypto-market-continues-bullish-run">crypto rally</a> is in full force. BTC is flirting with $100k! $1 Million USD is next!</p>
<p>The long hated NFT complex sprung back to life – with some unique digital items blasting up in fiat terms. It&#8217;s a feeding frenzy and every asset seems to be on the menu.</p>
<p>NFTs are an interesting way to store unique data. After the boom in 2021 – and then the FTX crash – NFTs kinda lost their appeal.</p>
<p>Turns out that unique digital items just aren&#8217;t that useful – at least not yet.</p>
<h2>Heading For The Metaverse</h2>
<p>Early and wrong look the same – but they are very different.</p>
<p>NFTs go back a few years. ETH&#8217;s blockchain likely brought the first NFTs to market. They look like a child&#8217;s experimentation with Corel draw.</p>
<p>Of course, in the boom times, these early ETH NFTs sold for big money.</p>
<p>Silly.</p>
<p>The lockdowns could have played a role in the market action we saw in 2020-2022. Work from home – play from home. Never leave your pod.</p>
<p>Digital became a lot more real in those times.</p>
<p>Hell – Facebook transitioned to Meta!</p>
<p>The idea of online life isn&#8217;t new, but it is becoming a lot more feasible. We think the future of NFTs is directly connected to online living.</p>
<h2>The City of The Future</h2>
<p>We like fresh air and being away from electronics. In fact, we understand why people live off the grid. But that isn&#8217;t the direction humanity is headed.</p>
<p>No, this is the techpocalypse!</p>
<p>What happens when the Metaverse meets Neuralink and Starlink – we will tell you – global mental domination. We are talking about a global metropolis of the mind.</p>
<p>In the city of the future – NFTs are how novelty exists. Money (BTC, ETH, SOL, XRP) isn&#8217;t interesting. Stack it up. Who cares. Humans crave novelty.</p>
<p>NFTs are the only way people can have decentralized novelty in the digital hellscape that is being created in the early 21st century.</p>
<h2>Back in The Pod!</h2>
<p>Cities are an abnormal state for humans. A city is unnatural. It is how humans dominate the planet on a small scale. If you have ever flown on airplanes – you understand this point. We pop from urban center to urban center, passing over the wildlands where being a human isn’t easy.</p>
<p>Consider the environment where an NFTs are useful – or have value. The level of technology needed for digital assets to have value is high by historical standards.</p>
<p>Computers are needed, but people also need access to the internet. In addition to technology, people need to have a desire to have unique digital assets – which have no real use outside of the digital world.</p>
<p>NFTs are an interesting asset class that could see more popularity as people around the world transition to an online lifestyle.</p>
<h2>Another NFT Boom?</h2>
<p>With cryptos heating up – NFTs could see more people piling in. But unlike cryptos, NFTs have already been adopted by some of the world&#8217;s largest companies.</p>
<p>McDonald&#8217;s issues NFTs for seasonal promotions – and apparently people collect them. As a promotional vehicle NFTs make a lot of sense. They cost little to create, and with an existing marketing machine, NFTs are easy to promote for a company like <a href="https://en.cryptonomist.ch/2024/11/19/the-nft-collection-doodles-collaborates-with-mcdonalds-for-physical-and-digital-holiday-themed-collectibles/">McDonald&#8217;s</a>.</p>
<p>The future of all these collectible NFTs is another matter. Its unlikely these NFTs will command value in the current market – but as the NFT space ages in the coming decades – these close-to-free tokens could rise in value.</p>
<h2>Stuck in The Matrix</h2>
<p>Smartphones could be the thin end of the technology wedge that moves people into an online lifestyle. With implantable network connections like Neuralink – a world where humans never leave digital space could become a reality.</p>
<p>When the transition to digital as reality is complete, NFTs are no longer a digital asset – they are real. In fact, all the physical assets that exist today would be worthless. Without a digital presence, an object would have no value.</p>
<p>We are looking at a world where perception is reality. The Metaverse is where pure awareness is all that matters. In this world – McDonald&#8217;s collectible holiday NFTs would be a highly desirable asset that reminds people of a world where people existed in a physical reality.</p>
<h2>The World Where Digital Lags Behind</h2>
<p>The digital world is a place where most of humanity is left behind. Smartphones aren&#8217;t enough to bring about a transition to living in the Metaverse. In today&#8217;s urban centers, connection to digital reality is simple, the same isn&#8217;t true for most of the world&#8217;s emerging nations.</p>
<p>And then there is state control over access. China&#8217;s national firewall is a perfect example of this issue.</p>
<p>A global online world isn&#8217;t going to be effective if state actors can shut down access at will. Or maybe the people won&#8217;t know. If people grow up in the digital world, they won&#8217;t understand physical space in the same way we do at the moment.</p>
<p>In fact, there could be a split in humanity – between those who are part of the Metaverse – and those who live as biological humans do now.</p>
<h2>Real Innovation Means Value Creation</h2>
<p>For the moment – we still live in physical reality.</p>
<p>The level of technology that would make NFTs “real” doesn&#8217;t exist – as Meta&#8217;s total economic failure demonstrates. In fact, we lack the platforms to allow people to live in a more digital world.</p>
<p>Cryptos have value as they can be spent into the real life economy that exists today. For NFTs, their collectibility is questionable – despite the recent knee-jerk higher for some NFT prices.</p>
<p>NFTs are still being issued by artists, companies and other creators, so they are developing as a digital asset. What that means longer term is anyone&#8217;s guess.</p>
<p>In terms of innovation – there isn&#8217;t much happening in the world of NFTs. While they can be used as tickets for events, in general, they are not. This is true for most NFT use cases – as they require users to have special apps – which just makes the whole deal a little bit of a reach.</p>
<p>For now – the NFT rally looks like an echo of the crypto pump that took BTC to a new all time high. If this rally does have staying power – some of the popular NFTs will continue higher.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/oped-nfts-spike-the-metaverse-asset-is-popular-again/">OpEd: NFTs Spike – The Metaverse Asset is Popular Again!</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">106764</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>McDonald&#8217;s Singapore Introduces &#8216;My Happy Place&#8217; Metaverse</title>
		<link>https://blockonomi.com/mcdonalds-singapore-introduces-my-happy-place-metaverse/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Oliver Dale]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 07:29:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Metaverse]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blockonomi.com/?p=96646</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>TLDR McDonald&#8217;s Singapore launched the &#8216;My Happy Place&#8217; metaverse in collaboration with Bandwagon Labs Users can build virtual burgers, play multiplayer games, and earn rewards in the metaverse The project will run from June 6 to July 7, and its success will determine future deployments Web3 technologies are used to enhance security, functionality, and use [...]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/mcdonalds-singapore-introduces-my-happy-place-metaverse/">McDonald&#8217;s Singapore Introduces &#8216;My Happy Place&#8217; Metaverse</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>TLDR</h2>
<ul>
<li>McDonald&#8217;s Singapore launched the &#8216;My Happy Place&#8217; metaverse in collaboration with Bandwagon Labs</li>
<li>Users can build virtual burgers, play multiplayer games, and earn rewards in the metaverse</li>
<li>The project will run from June 6 to July 7, and its success will determine future deployments</li>
<li>Web3 technologies are used to enhance security, functionality, and use cases for digital collectibles</li>
<li>Bandwagon Labs aims to address issues of third-party hosting and lack of tangible rewards in current metaverse experiences</li>
</ul>
<hr />
<p>McDonald&#8217;s, the global fast-food giant, has taken a step into the world of Web3 <a href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/mcdonalds-singapore-my-happy-place-metaverse">with the launch of its &#8216;My Happy Place&#8217; metaverse</a> in Singapore.</p>
<p>The project, a collaboration between <a href="https://www.mcdonalds.com.sg/">McDonald&#8217;s Singapore</a> and <a href="https://www.bandwagonlabs.xyz/">Bandwagon Labs</a>, the metaverse division of entertainment media tech company Bandwagon, aims to provide customers with an engaging and rewarding virtual experience.</p>
<p>The &#8216;My Happy Place&#8217; metaverse allows users to build virtual burgers, participate in multiplayer games, and earn tangible rewards, such as fries, for their participation.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">???????? IT’S HERE! ????????</p>
<p>We&#39;re thrilled to launch My Happy Place, together with McDonald&#39;s Singapore! Dive into the metaverse where fun, flavor &amp; friendship collide. Join us for interactive games, exclusive wearables, &amp; endless joy. </p>
<p>????????<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/15.0.3/72x72/2728.png" alt="✨" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> Welcome to your happiest moments! <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/15.0.3/72x72/2728.png" alt="✨" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />???????? <a href="https://t.co/jXTtBRqjKN">pic.twitter.com/jXTtBRqjKN</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Bandwagon Labs (@BandwagonLabs) <a href="https://twitter.com/BandwagonLabs/status/1798555064065466622?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">June 6, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>According to Clarence Chan, the founder of Bandwagon Labs, the metaverse is designed as a creative canvas where users can express their creativity while interacting with others in real time.</p>
<p>McDonald&#8217;s maintains full control over its in-app metaverse, which will run from June 6 to July 7. The success of this trial period will determine the future of the project and potential further deployments.</p>
<p>The integration of Web3 technologies, such as wallet hosting services like MetaMask, enhances the security, functionality, and use cases for digital collectibles within the metaverse.</p>
<p>Chan, who has personally experienced the potential of the metaverse by getting married in a virtual environment, believes that this technology can significantly boost customer retention and fan engagement. However, he also acknowledges that current metaverse experiences often suffer from issues related to third-party hosting and a lack of tangible rewards for users.</p>
<p>Bandwagon Labs aims to address these challenges by providing McDonald&#8217;s with a metaverse that not only allows users to engage and play with friends but also offers tangible rewards for participation.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/mcdonalds-singapore-introduces-my-happy-place-metaverse/">McDonald&#8217;s Singapore Introduces &#8216;My Happy Place&#8217; Metaverse</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">96646</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Food Rescue World: Blending Gaming and Charity in The Sandbox Metaverse</title>
		<link>https://blockonomi.com/food-rescue-world-blending-gaming-and-charity-in-the-sandbox-metaverse/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Oliver Dale]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 10:01:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Gaming]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Metaverse]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blockonomi.com/?p=96231</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>TLDR The Sandbox and Food Angel have launched &#8216;Food Rescue World&#8217;, a gaming experience in The Sandbox metaverse to raise awareness about food conservation and help those in need. Players can complete virtual quests to understand the food rescue process and earn coupons from local partners to directly support Food Angel&#8217;s initiatives. Food Angel rescues [...]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/food-rescue-world-blending-gaming-and-charity-in-the-sandbox-metaverse/">Food Rescue World: Blending Gaming and Charity in The Sandbox Metaverse</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>TLDR</h2>
<ul>
<li>The Sandbox and Food Angel have launched &#8216;Food Rescue World&#8217;, a gaming experience in The Sandbox metaverse to raise awareness about food conservation and help those in need.</li>
<li>Players can complete virtual quests to understand the food rescue process and earn coupons from local partners to directly support Food Angel&#8217;s initiatives.</li>
<li>Food Angel rescues 45 tonnes of edible surplus food each week, producing over 20,000 nutritious meals and distributing over 11,000 meals and food packs daily.</li>
<li>The Sandbox supports various charitable causes worldwide, and Food Angel joins organizations such as UNICEF, the French Red Cross, Nori, and WeForest.</li>
<li>The partnership showcases the potential of &#8220;Metaverse for Good&#8221;, where virtual worlds are used to make a significant impact on real-world charitable causes.</li>
</ul>
<hr />
<p>The Sandbox, a prominent decentralized gaming virtual world and subsidiary of Animoca Brands, has joined forces with Food Angel, a Hong Kong-based charity,<a href="https://www.animocabrands.com/the-sandbox-and-food-angel-launch-food-rescue-world-to-blend-gaming-and-charity"> to launch the Food Rescue World gaming experience</a> within <a href="https://blockonomi.com/buy-sandbox/">The Sandbox metaverse.</a></p>
<p>This groundbreaking partnership, announced on May 31, 2024, marks Food Angel as the first social enterprise or non-governmental organization (NGO) in Hong Kong to venture into The Sandbox, highlighting the potential of using virtual worlds to make a tangible impact on real-world charitable causes through the &#8220;Metaverse for Good&#8221; initiative.</p>
<p>In celebration of World Food Rescue Week 2024, players are encouraged to explore Food Rescue World within The Sandbox and assist Food Angel&#8217;s mascot, Rice Boy, in completing a series of virtual quests.</p>
<p>These quests involve collecting surplus food from markets, processing it in a central kitchen, and distributing meals to underprivileged families.</p>
<p>Through this immersive metaverse experience, players gain a deeper understanding of the food rescue process while raising awareness about the importance of food conservation and sharing surplus food with those in need.</p>
<p><img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-large wp-image-96233" src="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/1-1400x933.png" alt="" width="814" height="542" srcset="https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/1-1400x933.png 1400w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/1-300x200.png 300w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/1-768x512.png 768w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/1-1536x1024.png 1536w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/1-2048x1365.png 2048w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/1-50x33.png 50w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/1-150x100.png 150w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/1-450x300.png 450w, https://blockonomi.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/1-1200x800.png 1200w" sizes="(max-width: 814px) 100vw, 814px" /></p>
<p>By successfully completing all quests in Food Rescue World, players can earn coupons from local partners Lalamove and Maxim&#8217;s, enabling them to directly support Food Angel&#8217;s initiatives.</p>
<p>Ms. Gigi Tung, founder of Food Angel, expressed her enthusiasm for the collaboration, stating,</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;By utilizing the power of the metaverse to expand our reach to the next generation, we hope to build a deep collaboration with The Sandbox. This innovative approach provides a new way to promote and ensure a sustainable future for our cause.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The Sandbox Hong Kong team, along with their Trusted Partners GoGoBox and Chord Hero, recently visited Food Angel&#8217;s kitchen to prepare food ingredients and meal boxes, fostering a hands-on collaboration that bridges virtual and real-world efforts.</p>
<p>Food Angel, launched in 2011 by the Bo Charity Foundation, operates a food rescue and food assistance program with the mission of &#8220;Waste Not, Hunger Not, With Love&#8221;.</p>
<p>The program rescues edible surplus food from various sectors of the food industry that would otherwise be discarded as waste.</p>
<p>Following strict safety protocols, the rescued food items are prepared as nutritious meals in central kitchens and distributed as food packs to underprivileged communities in Hong Kong. Currently, Food Angel rescues 45 tonnes of edible surplus food each week, producing over 20,000 nutritious meals and helping distribute over 11,000 other meals and food packs daily, free of charge, to those in need of food assistance.</p>
<p>The Sandbox, a subsidiary of Animoca Brands, is an immersive metaverse platform that allows users to play, create, and monetize unique experiences alongside their favorite brands, IPs, and celebrities across various aspects of culture.</p>
<p>The platform leverages Web3 technologies to enable end-user creation and creator economies, providing both players and creators with true ownership of their assets, creations, and rewards in the form of non-fungible tokens (NFTs).</p>
<p>As Sebastien Borget, co-founder and COO of The Sandbox, stated,</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;We are proud that The Sandbox team, creators, and players can get involved in Hong Kong Food Angel and make a difference in the lives of local people in need by taking part in the Food Rescue World experience.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/food-rescue-world-blending-gaming-and-charity-in-the-sandbox-metaverse/">Food Rescue World: Blending Gaming and Charity in The Sandbox Metaverse</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">96231</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Victoria VR Set to Launch First Metaverse Experience on Apple&#8217;s Vision Pro Headset</title>
		<link>https://blockonomi.com/victoria-vr-set-to-launch-first-metaverse-experience-on-apples-vision-pro-headset/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Oliver Dale]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 08:23:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Metaverse]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blockonomi.com/?p=87756</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Virtual reality developer Victoria VR has announced plans to release the first ever metaverse experience designed specifically for Apple&#8217;s newly launched Vision Pro headset. Slated for launch in Q2 2024, Victoria VR aims to usher in a new era of ultra-realistic and immersive gameplay fueled by blockchain technology. TLDR Victoria VR is releasing the first [...]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/victoria-vr-set-to-launch-first-metaverse-experience-on-apples-vision-pro-headset/">Victoria VR Set to Launch First Metaverse Experience on Apple&#8217;s Vision Pro Headset</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Virtual reality developer <a href="https://www.victoriavr.com/">Victoria VR</a> has announced plans to release <a href="https://victoriavr.com/White-Paper-victoria-vr.pdf">the first ever metaverse experience</a> designed specifically for Apple&#8217;s newly launched Vision Pro headset. Slated for launch in Q2 2024, Victoria VR aims to usher in a new era of ultra-realistic and immersive gameplay fueled by blockchain technology.</p>
<hr />
<h2>TLDR</h2>
<ul>
<li>Victoria VR is releasing the first metaverse app for Apple&#8217;s new Vision Pro headset in Q2 2024, featuring ultra-realistic graphics and immersive gameplay</li>
<li>The Victoria VR metaverse will showcase the capabilities of the Vision Pro while highlighting Web3 technology</li>
<li>Victoria VR&#8217;s metaverse is fueled by the ERC-20 based VR token, which rewards users for engagement and locks up half of in-game revenue to redistribute</li>
<li>The VR token price surged 60% in the last 24 hours to a $103 million market cap after the Vision Pro app announcement</li>
<li>Victoria VR aims to make its metaverse inclusive and accessible using a &#8220;pay-to-speed&#8221; model rather than &#8220;pay-to-win&#8221;</li>
</ul>
<hr />
<p>Crafted over two years by a 80-person development team in Prague, Victoria VR leverages the advanced display and tracking capabilities of the Vision Pro to transport users into stunning VR environments centered around the concept of Feng Shui. Players can acquire virtual land plots as NFTs and freely design lavish interiors and exteriors tied to their blockchain wallet.</p>
<p>Central to Victoria VR is its ERC-20 VR governance token, which powers participation incentives and the in-game economy. Active users and stakers will be rewarded from a pool funded by 50% of revenue from in-game NFT sales. This unique tokenomics design aims to drive engagement while preventing &#8220;pay-to-win&#8221; dynamics.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">ARE YOU READY? ????????????<a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/VictoriaVR?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#VictoriaVR</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/VR?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#VR</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%24VR&amp;src=ctag&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">$VR</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/VisionPro?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#VisionPro</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/VisionOS?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#VisionOS</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Apple?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Apple</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/AppleVisionPro?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#AppleVisionPro</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/AppleVR?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#AppleVR</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/VirtualReality?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#VirtualReality</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Metaverse?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Metaverse</a> <a href="https://t.co/6oxIwNa7dm">pic.twitter.com/6oxIwNa7dm</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Victoria VR (@VictoriaVRcom) <a href="https://twitter.com/VictoriaVRcom/status/1753416240989667481?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">February 2, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>The VR token has already attracted strong interest, seeing 24-hour trading volume over $100 million immediately after its IDO. Speculation around the Vision Pro app has now sent VR surging 60% in the past day to a market capitalization of $103 million.</p>
<p>For Apple, the Victoria VR app represents its first foray into the potentially lucrative metaverse space, positioning Vision Pro as an alternative to Meta&#8217;s established Meta Quest headset. While companies like Disney have recently scaled back their metaverse investments, Victoria VR sees strong potential in blending VR technology with blockchain rewards.</p>
<p>Indeed, Victoria VR appears uniquely poised to showcase the promise of Web3 integration with augmented reality. And with crypto adoption steadily rising, Victoria VR&#8217;s model of incentivizing participation could make its metaverse radically more engaging than existing alternatives while upholding principles of accessibility and inclusion.</p>
<p>Of course, questions remain around VR hardware adoption and Victoria VR&#8217;s ability to retain users long-term. The staggering $4.6 billion 2023 operating loss posted by Meta’s Reality Labs segment shows the challenges of profitability, even for metaverse first-movers.</p>
<p>Still, by aligning itself with Apple’s walled garden ecosystem from the outset, Victoria VR is betting it can leapfrog incumbent platforms by tapping into the world&#8217;s most valuable brand community. If this gambit pays off, Victoria VR could emerge as the first genuinely mainstream and self-sustaining metaverse underpinned by blockchain rewards.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/victoria-vr-set-to-launch-first-metaverse-experience-on-apples-vision-pro-headset/">Victoria VR Set to Launch First Metaverse Experience on Apple&#8217;s Vision Pro Headset</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">87756</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Enter the OASIS: Inside the Ambitious New Metaverse Based on &#8220;Ready Player One&#8221;</title>
		<link>https://blockonomi.com/enter-the-oasis-inside-the-ambitious-new-metaverse-based-on-ready-player-one/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Oliver Dale]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 10:34:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Metaverse]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blockonomi.com/?p=85369</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ernest Cline&#8217;s dystopian novel &#8220;Ready Player One&#8221;, about a virtual reality world called OASIS where people escape a bleak real world, is coming to life in an ambitious new metaverse project. Cline has teamed up with AI and metaverse company Futureverse to create the &#8220;Readyverse&#8221; &#8211; an interactive virtual world inspired by the one depicted [...]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/enter-the-oasis-inside-the-ambitious-new-metaverse-based-on-ready-player-one/">Enter the OASIS: Inside the Ambitious New Metaverse Based on &#8220;Ready Player One&#8221;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ernest Cline&#8217;s dystopian novel &#8220;Ready Player One&#8221;, about a virtual reality world called OASIS where people escape a bleak real world,<a href="https://www.latimes.com/entertainment-arts/business/story/2024-01-04/ready-player-one-metaverse-readyverse"> is coming to life in an ambitious new metaverse project.</a></p>
<p>Cline has teamed up with AI and metaverse company Futureverse to create the &#8220;Readyverse&#8221; &#8211; an interactive virtual world inspired by the one depicted in Cline&#8217;s bestselling book and its 2018 film adaptation by Steven Spielberg.</p>
<hr />
<h2>Keypoints</h2>
<ul>
<li>Ernest Cline, author of &#8220;Ready Player One&#8221;, is working with an AI company called Futureverse to create a metaverse based on the book/movie.</li>
<li>They have launched a new company called Readyverse Studios to develop this metaverse, called the &#8220;Readyverse&#8221;.</li>
<li>Readyverse Studios has partnered exclusively with Warner Bros. Discovery to bring the Ready Player One franchise into the metaverse.</li>
<li>The Readyverse will be an interactive virtual world where people can explore environments and characters from the story through VR headsets and other devices.</li>
<li>There will be opportunities for other studios and brands to create content and experiences in the Readyverse metaverse.</li>
</ul>
<hr />
<p>To bring the Readyverse to fruition, Cline and &#8220;Ready Player One&#8221; film producer Dan Farah have co-founded a new venture called Readyverse Studios. The company has partnered exclusively with Warner Bros. Discovery, which released the Ready Player One movie, to develop metaverse experiences based on the franchise across web3 platforms.</p>
<p>According to Futureverse&#8217;s co-founders, the Readyverse metaverse will allow people to explore environments, characters and objects from the Ready Player One universe. Users will be able to <a href="https://beanstalk.io/csgofast-review/">purchase custom &#8220;skins&#8221;</a> or looks for their avatars, as well as digital assets like vehicles and real estate that are typically out of reach in the real world.</p>
<p>The goal is to make the Readyverse an interoperable, decentralized open metaverse powered by blockchain technology for secure digital ownership.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">We couldn’t be more excited to announce that we’ve teamed up with <a href="https://twitter.com/readyplayerone?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@readyplayerone</a> creator and producer to launch Readyverse Studios to bring leading IP and brands to the  metaverse. <a href="https://t.co/6sU6FpOSdE">pic.twitter.com/6sU6FpOSdE</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Futureverse (@futureverse) <a href="https://twitter.com/futureverse/status/1742924263303348616?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">January 4, 2024</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>Bringing a major Hollywood IP like Ready Player One into a digital metaverse marks a major milestone in bridging entertainment with virtual worlds. It shows the momentum behind metaverses and the opportunity for studios to engage fans in new interactive storytelling formats. For Web3 advocates, it&#8217;s a step toward mass consumer adoption of blockchain-based metaverse experiences.</p>
<p>While the full scope of the Readyverse is still taking shape, fans can expect to visit virtually rendered versions of iconic settings from the Ready Player One book and film. They may be able to<a href="https://blockonomi.com/gamdom-review/"> play games</a>, go on quests and interact with characters like Parzival, Art3mis and IOI head Nolan Sorrento. Readyverse Studios envisions partnerships with other studios to incorporate more IPs into this open metaverse.</p>
<p>Silicon Valley has poured investment into metaverse and VR technology with the belief it&#8217;s the next evolution of the internet. However, some experts argue the vision in Ready Player One of everybody abandoning the real world for a utopian virtual simulation remains far from reality. Challenges around hardware constraints and mass adoption persist.</p>
<p>Still, the momentum behind Readyverse Studios shows major entertainment and tech players are placing their bets. For Warner Bros, the Readyverse provides more monetization of a hit franchise. For Ernest Cline, it&#8217;s a chance to fully realize the virtual world he imagined. As he put it, &#8220;The future has arrived even more quickly than I imagined.&#8221; Now fans eagerly await their golden ticket to experience this virtual OASIS.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/enter-the-oasis-inside-the-ambitious-new-metaverse-based-on-ready-player-one/">Enter the OASIS: Inside the Ambitious New Metaverse Based on &#8220;Ready Player One&#8221;</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">85369</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Pudgy Penguins Waddles into Web3 Gaming with Upcoming Metaverse Experience</title>
		<link>https://blockonomi.com/pudgy-penguins-waddles-into-web3-gaming-with-upcoming-metaverse-experience/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Oliver Dale]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 08:53:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Metaverse]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NFTs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blockonomi.com/?p=84090</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The popular NFT collection turned global entertainment brand Pudgy Penguins has unveiled plans for Pudgy World, a new metaverse gaming experience coming in early 2024. Pudgy World marks the brand&#8217;s first foray into web3 gaming by leveraging blockchain technology to create an immersive, social virtual world for fans. Keypoints Pudgy Penguins is launching an open [...]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/pudgy-penguins-waddles-into-web3-gaming-with-upcoming-metaverse-experience/">Pudgy Penguins Waddles into Web3 Gaming with Upcoming Metaverse Experience</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The popular NFT collection turned global entertainment brand <a href="https://blockonomi.com/from-turmoil-to-walmart-the-remarkable-turnaround-of-pudgy-penguins-by-luca-netz/">Pudgy Penguins</a> has unveiled plans for <a href="https://lobby.pudgyworld.com/">Pudgy World</a>, <a href="https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/pudgy-penguins-announces-pudgy-world-alpha-powered-by-zksync-at-art-basel-miami-302010721.html">a new metaverse gaming experience</a> coming in early 2024. Pudgy World marks the brand&#8217;s first foray into web3 gaming by leveraging blockchain technology to create an immersive, social virtual world for fans.</p>
<hr />
<h2>Keypoints</h2>
<ul>
<li>Pudgy Penguins is launching an open world alpha game called Pudgy World in Q1 2024 using zkSync layer-2 technology</li>
<li>Pudgy World will allow Pudgy NFT holders and Pudgy Toy owners to customize penguin characters and go on story adventures</li>
<li>The launch introduces two new &#8220;Hero Characters&#8221;, Pudgy and Peaches, to guide players</li>
<li>Pudgy World aims to be an easy introduction to web3 through a fun, immersive experience</li>
<li>zkSync was chosen for its accessibility, privacy features, and ability to scale the game</li>
</ul>
<hr />
<p>Centered around the beloved cast of Pudgy Penguin characters, Pudgy World will allow players to explore an open world, customize unique penguin avatars, and embark on story-driven adventures alongside friends. Central to these adventures will be two newly introduced “Hero Characters” named Pudgy and Peaches who act as guides in the Pudgy World narrative.</p>
<p>Access to Pudgy World will be granted not only to holders of the Pudgy Penguins NFT collection but also to owners of the brand’s recently launched toy line now available in over 2,000 Walmart stores. Each plush Pudgy Penguin toy contains a scannable QR code that enables its owner to claim a specifically traited digital penguin character to play within the game. For non-NFT and toy holders, Pudgy World will also be free-to-play with the ability to purchase customizable cosmetic traits.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Pudgy World Alpha, powered by <a href="https://twitter.com/zksync?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@zksync</a>, releasing Q1 of 2024.</p>
<p>The beginning of a new era of blockchain-backed experiences, with the goal of onboarding millions, brought to you by Pudgy Penguins. <a href="https://t.co/ZvCRRGSUSH">pic.twitter.com/ZvCRRGSUSH</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Pudgy Penguins (@pudgypenguins) <a href="https://twitter.com/pudgypenguins/status/1733672528453705819?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">December 10, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>The strategic blending of IP between physical and digital worlds aims to provide an easy onboarding to web3 concepts for mainstream audiences through recognizable characters applied to gaming experiences. As an entertainment brand with established mass market penetration, Pudgy Penguins is uniquely positioned to introduce web3 technology to the next generation of users.</p>
<p>Powering the backend technology for Pudgy World is zkSync, an Ethereum layer-2 scaling solution using zero-knowledge proofs to enable faster and more affordable transactions. zkSync offers the reliability and accessibility needed for Pudgy World to potentially scale to millions of players over time.</p>
<p>While many view web3 gaming as the inevitable future, tangible examples of hybrid physical/digital interactive worlds are still few and far between. Yet with brands like Pudgy Penguins leveraging their IP in innovative ways, the metaverse future may arrive sooner than expected. If done right, Pudgy World could provide a blueprint for others looking to transform dedicated fanbases into engaged web3 communities.</p>
<p>For Pudgy Penguin fans, Pudgy World promises to deliver on the desires for more interactive experiences with their beloved characters.</p>
<p>With the power of an established brand, cutting-edge technology, and a passionate audience at its back, Pudgy World has the makings of a breakout hit in web3 gaming’s early days.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/pudgy-penguins-waddles-into-web3-gaming-with-upcoming-metaverse-experience/">Pudgy Penguins Waddles into Web3 Gaming with Upcoming Metaverse Experience</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">84090</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Animoca Brands’ Ambitious Mocaverse Attracts $31.88 Million in Funding to Empower Web3 Gaming</title>
		<link>https://blockonomi.com/animoca-brands-ambitious-mocaverse-attracts-31-88-million-in-funding-to-empower-web3-gaming/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Oliver Dale]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 17:40:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Metaverse]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NFTs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blockonomi.com/?p=83998</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Hong Kong-based crypto gaming firm Animoca Brands has raised an impressive $31.88 million in funding over two rounds to power the growth of Mocaverse, its highly ambitious metaverse initiative. This includes a recent $11.88 million tranche from investors like Dapper Labs, Polygon Ventures, and Foresight Ventures who are betting on the transformative vision. Keypoints Animoca [...]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/animoca-brands-ambitious-mocaverse-attracts-31-88-million-in-funding-to-empower-web3-gaming/">Animoca Brands’ Ambitious Mocaverse Attracts $31.88 Million in Funding to Empower Web3 Gaming</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Hong Kong-based crypto gaming firm Animoca Brands<a href="https://www.animocabrands.com/animoca-brands-raises-additional-usd11888888-in-second-tranche-of-funding-for-mocaverse"> has raised an impressive $31.88 million in funding over two rounds</a> to power the growth of <a href="https://www.mocaverse.xyz/">Mocaverse</a>, its highly ambitious metaverse initiative. This includes a recent $11.88 million tranche from investors like Dapper Labs, Polygon Ventures, and Foresight Ventures who are betting on the transformative vision.</p>
<hr />
<h2>Keypoints</h2>
<ul>
<li>Animoca Brands has raised $31.88 million total for its Mocaverse metaverse project, including a new $11.88 million tranche</li>
<li>Mocaverse aims to be an &#8220;empowerment layer for Web3 culture and entertainment&#8221; via digital identities and loyalty points</li>
<li>The ecosystem will initially include Animoca&#8217;s portfolio of 400+ companies, with plans to expand to more Web3 projects</li>
<li>Mocaverse recently partnered with blockchain game Pixels to integrate rewards and exclusives into its platform</li>
<li>Over 41,000 Moca IDs have been minted already for access to the metaverse and loyalty program</li>
</ul>
<hr />
<p>Described by Animoca as the “cornerstone for web3 culture and entertainment,” Mocaverse aims to serve as an open and permissionless empowerment layer that supercharges engagement, growth, and rewards for users across a myriad of blockchain-based games, apps, platforms and more.</p>
<p>Central to this sprawling ecosystem is the web3 Frequent Player Program and the introduction of loyalty points known as Realm Points. By obtaining a Moca ID digital identity, users can seamlessly engage across the 400+ companies in Animoca’s portfolio and earn Realm Points for participation, which can then be exchanged for real-world rewards and exclusives.</p>
<p>The recent integration with hit blockchain game Pixels represents the expansive potential in connecting platforms via Mocaverse. Pixels users can now access special pets, avatars, boosts when linking their account to Mocaverse and partaking in collaborative quests, with much more slated to come.</p>
<p>With over 41,000 Moca IDs already claimed, users are clearly excited by the prospect of interoperable loyalty perks that transcend individual walled gardens in the blockchain gaming space. And by progressive decentralization of the loyalty and identity constructs over time, Mocaverse aims to spur adoption across hundreds of Web3 apps to bootstrap the next generation of users.</p>
<p>“We’re creating an ecosystem where users can easily onboard into Web3, establish their identities, build reputation, and be rewarded for their participation,” said Animoca co-founder and executive chairman Yat Siu. “It’s a completely new way of thinking about how we interact in virtual worlds.”</p>
<p>The additional influx of funding will spur more collaborations like Pixels while expanding the digital identity and loyalty offerings. And the investor mix provides both deep gaming expertise via outfits like Dapper Labs as well as blockchain infrastructure support from Polygon to help scale Mocaverse to its lofty goals.</p>
<p>If Animoca can rally its network of partners around this interoperable meta-layer while enticing new platforms into the ecosystem, Mocaverse has the potential to redefine community loyalty to bootstrap the open metaverse. Judging by progress so far Animoca may soon make its ambitious Mocaverse vision an empowering reality across Web3.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/animoca-brands-ambitious-mocaverse-attracts-31-88-million-in-funding-to-empower-web3-gaming/">Animoca Brands’ Ambitious Mocaverse Attracts $31.88 Million in Funding to Empower Web3 Gaming</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">83998</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Get Ready to Play in Reebok’s Mind-Bending Blockchain Sneakers</title>
		<link>https://blockonomi.com/get-ready-to-play-in-reeboks-mind-bending-blockchain-sneakers/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Oliver Dale]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 11:48:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Metaverse]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NFTs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blockonomi.com/?p=83938</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Legacy shoe brand Reebok is leaping full-force into digital worlds and virtual gaming. This week, Reebok announced an exclusive partnership with crypto tech startup Futureverse to develop a wide range of blockchain and AI-powered games and metaverse experiences. Keypoints Reebok has partnered with crypto startup Futureverse to develop AI and blockchain-based games and digital experiences [...]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/get-ready-to-play-in-reeboks-mind-bending-blockchain-sneakers/">Get Ready to Play in Reebok’s Mind-Bending Blockchain Sneakers</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Legacy shoe brand Reebok is leaping full-force into digital worlds and virtual gaming. This week,<a href="https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/futureverse--reebok-announce-exclusive-partnership-to-leverage-cutting-edge-ai-and-metaverse-technology-to-revolutionize-digital-fashion-302009135.html"> Reebok announced</a> an exclusive partnership with crypto tech startup Futureverse to develop a wide range of blockchain and AI-powered games and metaverse experiences.</p>
<hr />
<h2>Keypoints</h2>
<ul>
<li>Reebok has partnered with crypto startup Futureverse to develop AI and blockchain-based games and digital experiences</li>
<li>They will launch an on-chain gaming experience next year called &#8220;Reebok Impact&#8221; that incorporates digital wearables</li>
<li>This aims to extend Reebok&#8217;s brand presence into the metaverse and virtual worlds</li>
<li>Parent company Adidas and rival Nike have also moved into digital fashion, NFTs, and gaming</li>
<li>But Reebok seems focused on creating immersive gaming experiences for its digital shoes</li>
</ul>
<hr />
<p>The goal is to revolutionize digital fashion by transporting the Reebok brand into virtual realms. Reebok and Futureverse plan to showcase digital versions of Reebok&#8217;s shoes as on-chain wearable items paired with NFTs. This digital integration mirrors steps already taken by Reebok&#8217;s parent company Adidas along with other shoe brands such as Nike.</p>
<p>But uniquely, Reebok&#8217;s partnership appears intensely focused on building immersive gaming universes in which its coming digital kicks can live. The centerpiece of the collaboration is an ambitious on-chain game slated for 2024 dubbed &#8220;Reebok Impact.&#8221;</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr">Excited to partner with <a href="https://twitter.com/futureverse?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@futureverse</a> to launch <a href="https://twitter.com/ReebokImpact?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@ReebokImpact</a> in 2024, a mind and heart-bending digital shoe experience that will allow our community and beyond to dive into AI and digital wearables. <a href="https://t.co/uH4CgAiYQn">https://t.co/uH4CgAiYQn</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Reebok (@Reebok) <a href="https://twitter.com/Reebok/status/1732794420540449091?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">December 7, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>Described as a &#8220;mind and heart-bending digital shoe experience,” Impact will demonstrate “that life is not about your sneakers, it’s about what you do while you wear them,” according to Reebok. The game will leverage AI, digital wearables, and haptic feedback for interactive play that seems poised to take the idea of “connected shoes” to new territory.</p>
<p>For Reebok, moving aggressively into web3 gaming and metaverse branding reflects the ethos of its “life is not a spectator sport” campaign. The company wants to use technologies like augmented reality not just to sell digital products, but to create participatory adventures that estrange shoes from real-world practicality.</p>
<p>Reebok’s CEO Todd Krinsky said that through ventures like Reebok Impact, the company “transcend[s] traditional boundaries of innovation to engage our consumers in the digital evolution of our products.” The promise is to revolutionize physical fashion by sending it hurtling into virtual worlds.</p>
<p>Futureverse, Reebok&#8217;s technology partner, focuses on establishing an open, multi-platform metaverse ecosystem via major acquisitions. The startup raised $54 million in Series A funding in July 2022 to aid its buying spree of NFT games and crypto companies. While none have specifically dealt with digital wearables yet, Futureverse now seems primed to help Reebok pave new terrain.</p>
<p>For legacy fashion and footwear brands, expanding into metaverse experiences has become imperative amid shifting consumer attitudes and behaviors seen during the pandemic. Companies like Nike and Adidas have already experimented with digital apparel tied to NFTs that offer exclusive access to real products.</p>
<p>But in doubling down on metaverse gaming, Reebok is now betting that virtual worlds won&#8217;t just complement physical ones—they&#8217;ll be instrumental in redefining products and how brands engage with consumers. The promise of ventures like Reebok Impact is to make real-life shoes almost secondary to the digital experiences they unlock.</p>
<p>It&#8217;s a bold leap for a decades-old company steeped in tangible sports heritage. But by targeting new demographics through virtual entry points, Reebok hopes to inject renewed life into its business via digital means—while keeping at least one foot rooted in the physical world.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/get-ready-to-play-in-reeboks-mind-bending-blockchain-sneakers/">Get Ready to Play in Reebok’s Mind-Bending Blockchain Sneakers</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">83938</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Decentraland (MANA) Hosts Immersive Musical Metaverse Experience</title>
		<link>https://blockonomi.com/decentraland-mana-hosts-immersive-musical-metaverse-experience/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Oliver Dale]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 18:36:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Metaverse]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NFTs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blockonomi.com/?p=82585</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Decentraland, the leading virtual social world, is hosting its most ambitious music festival from November 16-18. Named Decentraland Music Festival ‘23 (#DCLMF23), the event promises three days of groundbreaking musical performances, games, and experiences accessible to everyone globally. Keypoints Decentraland is hosting its 3rd annual music festival from Nov 16-18 called Decentraland Music Festival &#8217;23 [...]</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/decentraland-mana-hosts-immersive-musical-metaverse-experience/">Decentraland (MANA) Hosts Immersive Musical Metaverse Experience</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://blockonomi.com/decentraland-virtual-world-ethereum-mainnet/">Decentraland</a>, the leading virtual social world,<a href="https://events.decentraland.org/event/?id=97aff492-b4b9-4ba1-bd08-bfa7e32be036"> is hosting its most ambitious music festival</a> from November 16-18. Named <a href="https://themetaversefestival.io/">Decentraland Music Festival ‘23</a> (#DCLMF23), the event promises three days of groundbreaking musical performances, games, and experiences accessible to everyone globally.</p>
<hr />
<h2>Keypoints</h2>
<ul>
<li>Decentraland is hosting its 3rd annual music festival from Nov 16-18 called Decentraland Music Festival &#8217;23 (#DCLMF23)</li>
<li>The festival will feature over 80 performances, games, and events across 5 stages designed by award-winning virtual creators</li>
<li>Headliners include digital music pioneers like Cora Novoa, Trick Daddy, GuccieToe, Bufalo, Glitch Rave, Steve Sai</li>
<li>Attendees can participate in interactive music experiences like a collaborative art tower, medieval music quest, and more</li>
<li>Festival showcases innovative projects fusing music, gaming, virtual worlds, and explores the future of artist-fan connections</li>
</ul>
<hr />
<p>Boasting five stages designed by award-winning virtual creators, the festival features over 80 diverse acts. Headliners include digital music pioneers like Cora Novoa, Trick Daddy, GuccieToe, Bufalo, Glitch Rave, and Steve Sai. Beyond the performances, #DCLMF23 offers numerous interactive experiences fusing music, gaming, and virtual worlds.</p>
<p>Attendees can jam with friends in an interactive music river. They can also build a collaborative pixel art tower that gets displayed as a festival landmark. One medieval village quest tasks users with restoring stolen music by battling a boss. Neo-Techno Paganist raves send explorers on virtual wearable quests.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true">
<p lang="en" dir="ltr"><a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/DCLMF23?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#DCLMF23</a> is your ticket to a Neo-TechnoPaganist extravaganza, featuring 5 stages, over 80 performances, and 15 new games &amp; experiences! </p>
<p>???? Save your spot for Nov 16-18! <a href="https://t.co/SHb8fBcaKA">https://t.co/SHb8fBcaKA</a></p>
<p>&mdash; Decentraland (@decentraland) <a href="https://twitter.com/decentraland/status/1724560655103979589?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">November 14, 2023</a></p></blockquote>
<p><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></p>
<p>These metaverse-native experiences highlight the festival&#8217;s goal of redefining musical artist-fan connections. #DCLMF23 also showcases innovative projects from Japan fusing music and gaming. Synthetic human DJs are set to perform, offering a glimpse into the music industry&#8217;s hi-tech future.</p>
<p>With values of radical creative expression, community bonding, and artistic renewal, #DCLMF23 pushes the boundaries of musical entertainment. It represents a future vision of music where virtual venues, cross-medium experiences, and new creator-fan dynamics are the norm.</p>
<p><a href="https://events.decentraland.org/event/?id=97aff492-b4b9-4ba1-bd08-bfa7e32be036">The festival schedule and lineup are available online</a>. Decentraland&#8217;s guide also assists visitors in navigating the sprawling metaverse event. Attendees are encouraged to sport virtual fashion items from the<a href="https://beanstalk.io/buy-decentraland/"> Decentraland</a> marketplace to fully immerse themselves in this digital music revolution.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://blockonomi.com/decentraland-mana-hosts-immersive-musical-metaverse-experience/">Decentraland (MANA) Hosts Immersive Musical Metaverse Experience</a> appeared first on <a href="https://blockonomi.com">Blockonomi</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">82585</post-id>	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
